<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-06-14T01:01:44.679Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Linux Crash Course with Labs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-linux-crash-course-with-labs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-linux-crash-course-with-labs/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T13:36:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Linux is important because it powers the majority of the world's servers, from web hosting to cloud infrastructure. Its open-source nature ensures that it remains versatile, secure, and continually updated by a global community of developers...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Viewing Patterns in Your Website Designs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-viewing-patterns-in-your-website-design/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-viewing-patterns-in-your-website-design/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T14:33:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While going through a website or an application, people tend to take in the information displayed differently. You may notice that sometimes a person may miss information that others wouldn't miss. This may have happened to you before, as well. This is because everyone has a particular way they process]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Three.js By Building Five Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-threejs-by-building-five-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-threejs-by-building-five-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T13:33:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three.js is a powerful JavaScript library that simplifies the process of creating 3D graphics in the browser. We just released a video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Three.js by guiding you through build...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Scent Of UX: The Unrealized Potential Of Olfactory Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/scent-ux-unrealized-potential-olfactory-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/scent-ux-unrealized-potential-olfactory-design/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kristian Mikhel covers various practical applications of scents in product experience, from immersive entertainment to healing spaces and medical appliances, and how designers can drive innovation across spheres and disciplines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kristian Mikhel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next-Gen Large Language Models: The Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/retrieval-augmented-generation-rag-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/retrieval-augmented-generation-rag-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T21:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) signifies a transformative advancement in large language models (LLMs). It combines the generative prowess of transformer architectures with dynamic information retrieval.  This integration allows LLMs to access and incorporate relevant external knowledge during text generation, resulting in outputs that are more accurate, contextual, and factually]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Hack Your Google Lighthouse Scores In 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/how-hack-google-lighthouse-scores-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/how-hack-google-lighthouse-scores-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do perfect Lighthouse scores mean the performance of your website is perfect? As it turns out, Lighthouse is influenced by a number of things that can be manipulated and bent to make sites seem more performant than they really are, as Salma Alam-Naylor demonstrates in several experiments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Salma Alam-Naylor)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn High-Level System Design by Building a YouTube Clone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-high-level-system-design-by-building-a-youtube-clone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-high-level-system-design-by-building-a-youtube-clone/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T16:33:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High-Level System Design involves creating a blueprint for complex systems, focusing on architecture, component interactions, and scalability. It addresses how different parts of a system communicate, manage data, and handle user requests efficiently...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Python for Data Science – Hands-on Projects with EDA, AB Testing & Business Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-python-for-data-science-hands-on-projects-with-eda-ab-testing-business-intelligence/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-python-for-data-science-hands-on-projects-with-eda-ab-testing-business-intelligence/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T15:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data science skills are increasingly in-demand. We just published a hands-son data science with Python course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This comprehensive, 5.5+ hour course is designed to provide aspiring data scientists with essential...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix Common Python Installation Errors on macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fix-python-installation-errors-on-mac/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fix-python-installation-errors-on-mac/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T22:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python's popularity keeps growing as more developers adopt it for data science and machine learning, although it is already among the most popular programming languages.  I recently wrote an article for freeCodeCamp titled "How to Install Python on a Mac [/news/how-to-install-python-on-a-mac/]", which provides a clear guide to installing Python]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kehoe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Unit Tests in Python – with Example Test Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/unit-testing-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/unit-testing-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T16:33:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unit testing is a software testing technique in which individual components or units of a software application are tested independently from the rest of the application.  In software development, it's beneficial to break your application into small, isolated units. This approach allows you to write independent tests to check]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damilola Oladele</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=378111</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T16:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The main idea of CSS Container Queries is to register an element as a “container” and apply styles to other elements when the container element meets certain conditions. 
CSS Container Queries originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Notice Blocks in Markdown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-notice-blocks-in-markdown/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-notice-blocks-in-markdown/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T09:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Markdown is a very popular lightweight markup language. It is used for writing documentation and even for creating a complete website. Therefore, almost all of us frequently use this markup language every once in a while. However, there are some limitations to this language. In some cases, we can not]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Outsmart AI as a Developer [Dr. Chuck Interview #127]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-outsmart-ai-as-a-developer-dr-chuck-interview-127/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-outsmart-ai-as-a-developer-dr-chuck-interview-127/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T00:54:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews Dr. Chuck. He's a software engineer and Computer Science professor at University of Michigan, which has one of the top-ranked CS programs in the world. Dr. Charles "...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use WeakMap and WeakSet in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/weakmap-and-weakset-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/weakmap-and-weakset-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T16:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript offers a number of tools for organizing and managing data. And while developers often use widely recognized tools like Maps and Sets, they may often overlook certain other valuable resources.  For example, are you familiar with WeakMap and WeakSet? They're special tools in JavaScript that help store and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful CSS Tips And Techniques]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/css-tips-and-techniques/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/css-tips-and-techniques/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The times for CSS have probably never been more exciting than today. In this quick read, we’ve got some useful CSS tips and techniques for you that you can apply to your work right away. Let’s dive deeper into self-modifying CSS variables, hanging punctuation, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Real-Time Chat App With Go, Fiber and HTMX]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/real-time-chat-with-go-fiber-htmx/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/real-time-chat-with-go-fiber-htmx/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T18:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll build a simple real-time chat app using Go, Fiber and HTMX.  You will learn how to leverage the versatility of Fiber by making use of a WebSocket. You'll also learn how to create a reactive frontend without the use of JavaScript. Prerequisites  * A]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Akinwumi Iyanuoluwa Ayomiposi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master the Azure DevOps Engineer Expert Certification (AZ-400)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-the-azure-devops-engineer-expert-certification-az-400/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-the-azure-devops-engineer-expert-certification-az-400/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T14:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Azure DevOps Engineer Expert Certification (AZ-400) is for professionals who aim to demonstrate their expertise in integrating people, processes, and technologies to continuously deliver valuable products and services. It’s ideal for those who ar...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How to Build a Decentralized File Storage System with Go]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-how-to-build-a-decentralized-file-storage-system-with-go/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-how-to-build-a-decentralized-file-storage-system-with-go/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T21:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just posted a 10-hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build a decentralized, fully distributed, content-addressable file storage system using Go. This course is perfect for those interested in system desig...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Presenting UX Research And Design To Stakeholders: The Power Of Persuasion]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/presenting-ux-research-design-stakeholders/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/presenting-ux-research-design-stakeholders/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s more to achieving good UX than research and design. We need to effectively communicate our ideas to gain buy-in from key stakeholders. Victor covers how UX practitioners can harness the power of persuasion and other tactics from the field of communication when presenting research findings and design concepts to key stakeholders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Yocco)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript this Keyword Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-this-keyword-explained-with-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-this-keyword-explained-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T14:58:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All leading web browsers support JavaScript, a popular and versatile programming language. The this keyword is a very important concept to know in JavaScript. The this keyword is a reference to an object, but the object varies based on where and how it is called. In this article, you'll learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kamaldeen Lawal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Virtual DOM in React?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-the-virtual-dom-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-the-virtual-dom-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T14:51:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As web applications become more complex, managing updates to the user interface becomes a challenging task. This is where the Virtual DOM (Document Object Model) comes into play – particularly in React, the leading JavaScript library for building user interfaces. The virtual DOM is a lightweight copy of the real]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Go in Spanish – Golang Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-go-in-spanish-golang-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-go-in-spanish-golang-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T12:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Go is a powerful programming language that is quickly growing in popularity. It's easy to learn and works great for building powerful applications. Whether you're new to coding or already know other programming languages, Go is a great choice for exp...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Guide to Linear Algebra in Data Science and AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linear-algebra-roadmap/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linear-algebra-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T20:22:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> "In God we trust; all others bring data." – W. Edwards Deming This famous quote from Edwards Deming perfectly captures the essence of modern Data Science and AI.  Data is the lifeblood of Data Science and AI fields – Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Generative AI and much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tatev Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Coding Challenges For Beginner Developers – Code and Explanations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-coding-challenges-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-coding-challenges-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T20:18:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Python can be challenging, especially if you're not actually writing enough code. As a beginner, you may go through lessons and tutorials without practicing on your own – and this makes it harder to learn the language. The truth is, you cannot truly learn programming without writing code. It]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhilekh Gautam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a YouTube Clone with Flutter, Firebase, and Riverpod]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-youtube-clone-with-flutter-firebase-and-riverpod/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-youtube-clone-with-flutter-firebase-and-riverpod/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T19:07:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just released a new course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build a full stack application. This beginner-friendly course will guide you through the process of creating a fully functional YouTube clone app, utiliz...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn to Code REST APIs using Next.js 14]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-code-rest-apis-using-nextjs-14/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-code-rest-apis-using-nextjs-14/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T19:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just posted a new course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is designed to help you master the creation of RESTful APIs using Next.js 14, a popular React framework. Umair Jameel developed this course. Next.js is a framework built on top ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applied Data Science with Python – Business Intelligence for Developers [Full Book]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/applied-data-science-with-python-book/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/applied-data-science-with-python-book/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T17:14:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the high-stakes game of modern business, data isn't just an asset – it's the power you need to outpace your competition. But as a developer, you know that turning raw data into actionable insights can be a frustrating battle. Imagine having the power to effortlessly transform raw data into]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Success: Key Insights And Practical Takeaways]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/scaling-success-key-insights-pratical-takeaways/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/scaling-success-key-insights-pratical-takeaways/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The web is still a young platform, and we’re only now beginning to recognize what “success” looks like for large projects. In his recent Smashing book, [Success at Scale](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/printed-books/success-at-scale/), Addy Osmani presents practical case studies featuring the web’s most renowned companies and their efforts to make big changes to existing apps and sites. In this article, Addy shows some of the key insights he has learned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build and Deploy a Smart Contract With Rust and the Gear Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-deploy-smart-contract-rust-gear-protocol/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-deploy-smart-contract-rust-gear-protocol/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T10:36:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart contracts are like digital agreements that run on blockchain technology, making transactions automatic and secure. While many people use Ethereum and Solidity to create these contracts, there are other options that can be just as powerful.  One great combination is using Rust with the Gear Protocol. In this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rocky Essel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Rating Component with the React Compound Component Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-rating-component-with-the-react-compound-component-pattern/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-rating-component-with-the-react-compound-component-pattern/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T22:03:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever watched a captivating movie or used a fantastic product and wanted to share your experience? In today's world, feedback is critical, and ratings are like currency.  Rating systems are everywhere, from the classic star ratings on movie review websites to the ubiquitous thumbs up/down on streaming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose the Right IaC Tool – AWS CDK, CloudFormation, and Terraform Compared]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/comparing-iac-tools-aws-cdk-cloudformation-terraform/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/comparing-iac-tools-aws-cdk-cloudformation-terraform/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:27:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infrastructure as Code (IaC) has become a cornerstone of modern cloud resource management. It enables developers and engineers to manage their cloud resources with the same level of control and precision as application code.  When you're working with AWS, among the tools at the forefront of utilizing IaC are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ifeanyi Otuonye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Quickly Add Auth to your Flutter Apps with Supabase Auth UI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/add-auth-to-flutter-apps-with-supabase-auth-ui/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/add-auth-to-flutter-apps-with-supabase-auth-ui/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T19:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to use Supabase's auth package [https://pub.dev/packages/supabase_auth_ui] to quickly and efficiently add authentication functionality to your Flutter apps. We will go through the entire process, from setting up a Flutter project to configuring Email/Password, OAuth, and Magic link flows. In the end, you'll have]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fatuma Abdullahi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Length Units]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375815</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-length-units/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T19:22:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A comprehensive guide covering nine types of lengths that CSS uses to size elements in terms of dimensions, space, time, and even sound.
CSS Length Units originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use AI to Automate Unit Testing with TestGen-LLM and Cover-Agent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automated-unit-testing-with-testgen-llm-and-cover-agent/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automated-unit-testing-with-testgen-llm-and-cover-agent/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T14:45:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's important to write clear and efficient unit tests that actually work during the software development process. Unit tests separate out individual code elements and confirm that they work as intended.  Effective unit tests not only catch errors but also help you be confident that your code can be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwadamisi Samuel Praise</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ice Cream Ahead (June 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s kick off June with some fresh inspiration! Artists and designers from across the globe once again tickled their creativity to celebrate the beginning of the new month with a collection of beautiful and unique wallpaper calendars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Suz Hinton went from Dev to White Hat Hacker [Podcast #126]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-suz-hinton-went-from-dev-to-white-hat-hacker-podcast-126/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-suz-hinton-went-from-dev-to-white-hat-hacker-podcast-126/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T15:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews Suz Hinton. She's a software engineer, security researcher, and one of the first ever people to live-stream her coding on Twitch. We talk about: How Suz started her...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Prototypal Inheritance in JavaScript? Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-prototypal-inheritance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-prototypal-inheritance/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T08:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prototypal inheritance can feel like a complex concept shrouded in technical jargon. But fear not! This guide will break it down using clear, relatable examples that go beyond the typical textbook explanations.  We'll ditch the confusing terms and focus on real-world scenarios that you can easily understand. By the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asoluka Tochukwu Austin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the Basics of Go by Building a Full Stack Web App with React and Go]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-basics-of-go-by-building-a-full-stack-web-app-with-react-and-go/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-basics-of-go-by-building-a-full-stack-web-app-with-react-and-go/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T15:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Go can work great on the backend for a React project. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org channel that will leach you how to build a full stack web app with React and Go. This comprehensive course is designed to teach you the fundamenta...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Complete C Programming Course from Dr. Chuck]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-c-programming-course-from-dr-chuck/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-c-programming-course-from-dr-chuck/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T15:21:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just released a comprehensive C course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This course, developed by Dr. Charles Severance (aka Dr. Chuck), is designed to help you understand computer architecture and low-level programming using the classic C...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Praise Of The Basics]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/in-praise-of-the-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/in-praise-of-the-basics/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What does it mean to learn the “basics”, or fundamentals, of front-end web development? Is starting with HTML and CSS still the best entry point to learn how to make websites and apps when we have a seemingly endless supply of frameworks? Geoff Graham thinks so and discusses why you might consider going “back to basics” to start or move forward in your career.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Context API Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-context-api-explained-with-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-context-api-explained-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T08:13:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing state has always been a critical aspect of making web applications with React. The most basic way to do this is prop drilling. In prop drilling, you pass props around from the parent component to other components that need it, no matter how deeply nested they are. The problem]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do Numerical Conversions Work in Computer Systems? Explained With Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-numerical-conversions-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-numerical-conversions-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T19:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computers perform complex calculations when carrying out their assigned tasks. At the very core, the calculations boil down to operations like comparisons, assignments, and addition. Have you ever wondered how they are performed under the hood and wh...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decision Trees For UI Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/decision-trees-ui-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/decision-trees-ui-components/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine finally resolving never-ending discussions about UI decisions for good. Here are some practical examples of decision trees for UI components and how to use them effectively. An upcoming part of [Smart Interface Design Patterns](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust Tutorial – Learn Advanced Iterators & Pattern Matching by Building a JSON Parser]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rust-tutorial-build-a-json-parser/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rust-tutorial-build-a-json-parser/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T10:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Iterators and match patterns are two of the most used language features in Rust. If you have written any real world application, big or small, chances are that you've already used these, whether knowingly or unknowingly. In this tutorial, I aim to help you understand how they actually work, the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshul Sanghi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linear Algebra Crash Course - Mathematics for Machine Learning and Generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linear-algebra-crash-course-mathematics-for-machine-learning-and-generative-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linear-algebra-crash-course-mathematics-for-machine-learning-and-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T20:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linear algebra is a useful skill for professionals in data science, machine learning, and AI. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you linear algebra. This crash course spans just over 6 hours and is a great...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an EKS Cluster Across AWS Local Zones using the AWS CDK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-eks-cluster-using-aws-local-zones-with-aws-cdk/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-eks-cluster-using-aws-local-zones-with-aws-cdk/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T14:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Local Zones are a new type of infrastructure that enables you to build and run applications closer to end-users, providing low latency and improved performance.  They are designed to provide the same high availability and reliability as an AWS Region, but with the added benefit of low-latency connections]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gursimar Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linear vs Logistic Regression:  How to Choose the Right Regression Model for Your Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linear-regression-vs-logistic-regression/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linear-regression-vs-logistic-regression/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T13:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regression models identify trends in a dataset and predict outcomes based on the trends they have analyzed and identified.  Linear and Logistic Regression are two types of regression models that are similar but carry out their functions in distinct ways. They're also two fundamental techniques in machine learning that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwadamisi Samuel Praise</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React 19 – New Hooks Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-19-new-hooks-explained-with-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-19-new-hooks-explained-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T12:56:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi fellow readers! Web Development is a constantly evolving landscape. The whole ecosystem consists of different libraries and technologies. React is one of the most widely used libraries in web development.  There are small releases every now and then. However, this year, the React team has made a significant]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Era Of Platform Primitives Is Finally Here]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/netlify-platform-primitives/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/netlify-platform-primitives/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Application frameworks have built whole ecosystems on top of them. Let’s take a closer look at serverless platforms such as Netlify’s [Platform Primitives](https://www.netlify.com/platform/primitives) and explore how they can increase our productivity with a serverless fullstack experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide to the Node.js Event Loop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-guide-to-the-node-js-event-loop/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-guide-to-the-node-js-event-loop/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T07:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js is an open-source JavaScript runtime environment that allows you to run JavaScript outside the browser. Although Node.js is single-threaded, it has an event loop that makes it multi-threaded. The Node.js event loop is a crucial mechanism in Node.js that makes Node.js programs run concurrently and asynchronously. Mastering the Node.js]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Musab Habeeb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manipulate Strings in JavaScript – With Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manipulate-strings-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manipulate-strings-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T21:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[String manipulation is a common task for programmers, whether it is extracting information from the string, converting letter cases, joining strings, or trimming extra white spaces. This tutorial covers various methods and techniques for manipulating strings using JavaScript, offering you a comprehensive guide on how to work with strings in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Hu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build CRUD Operations with .NET Core – A Todo API Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-crud-operations-with-dotnet-core-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-crud-operations-with-dotnet-core-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T14:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to this comprehensive guide on building CRUD operations with .NET Core. We'll use a Todo API as our practical example so you can get hands-on experience as you learn. Throughout this tutorial, you'll learn how to create, read, update, and delete Todo items, and how to leverage Entity Framework]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaiah Cliford  Opoku</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source is Changing. The Changelog Host Jerod Santo on How to Keep Up [Podcast #125]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/open-source-is-changing-the-changelog-host-jerod-santo-on-how-to-keep-up-podcast-125/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/open-source-is-changing-the-changelog-host-jerod-santo-on-how-to-keep-up-podcast-125/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T14:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Jerod Santo, host of The Changelog, a podcast about open source software development that has been going strong for 15 years. Jerod is plugged in to the world of Open Source, going to all the big con...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an MVP for Your Project – and Why You Should Do It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/minimum-viable-product-between-an-idea-and-the-product/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/minimum-viable-product-between-an-idea-and-the-product/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proof of concept, prototypes, wireframes, mockups… what actually constitutes a Minimum Viable Product (MVP)? Well, it's a product with just enough features to gather comprehensive qualitative feedback. In practice, it's as easy to understand the concept of an MVP as it is to ride a bicycle. Let's do it then.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oleg Romanyuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching It Up With HTML’s Latest Control]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/switching-it-up-html-latest-control/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/switching-it-up-html-latest-control/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of relying on checkbox hacks to create a “switch” control for forms that toggle between two states, HTML may be gaining a native way to go about it by adding a `switch` attribute to checkbox inputs. Daniel Yuschick walks us through a first impression of switch controls and discusses current and ongoing considerations that need to be explored further before it is ready for prime time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Daniel Yuschick)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose a Tech Stack for Your SaaS Product – Lessons from a Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/choose-a-tech-stack-for-your-saas-product/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/choose-a-tech-stack-for-your-saas-product/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T08:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a developer, I've seen how choosing the "right" tech stack can be a double-edged sword. I often fell into the trap of chasing shiny new technologies, thinking they were the key to building the next great product. But experience has taught me that prioritizing speed to market trends often]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Cruz Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Partition Queues for Distributed Workloads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-partition-queues-for-distributed-workloads/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-partition-queues-for-distributed-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T20:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technology, like human lives, evolves, and with this evolution comes the use of better solutions to existing problems. You might wonder: does this complicate systems or make them more efficient?  In this article, we will discuss some measures you can take to make systems much more efficient and reliable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoye Victor Chukwuebuka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pass the AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate Certification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pass-the-aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-certification/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pass-the-aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-certification/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T20:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you trying to earn the AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate certification? We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is is designed to help you pass the certification exam and showcase your expertise in AWS t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Practices For Naming Design Tokens, Components, Variables, And More]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/naming-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/naming-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can we get better at naming? This post is dedicated to naming conventions, tips, and real-world examples that help you name things in a robust and flexible way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Your Django App – Best Practices and Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-secure-your-django-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-secure-your-django-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T15:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a software developer or engineer, it's not enough to know how to build useful solutions – you must also ensure that they are secure. Prioritizing your users is crucial when developing and deploying your software because if users can't use your app, it becomes useless. In this guide, we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Iroegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern CSS Layouts: You Might Not Need A Framework For That]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/modern-css-layouts-no-framework-needed/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/modern-css-layouts-no-framework-needed/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easy to get lost in a sea of CSS frameworks and libraries, each promising easier styling and smoother layouts. Brecht De Ruyte demonstrates four CSS utility classes (plus a bonus) using techniques that allow them to be used practically anywhere you need a particular layout — be it Grid or Flexbox — with configurable options.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript Interview Prep Handbook – Essential Topics to Know + Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/js-interview-prep-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/js-interview-prep-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T09:58:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a widely used language in web development and powers interactive features of virtually every website out there. JavaScript makes it possible to create dynamic web pages and is very versatile. JavaScript remains one of the most in-demand programming languages in 2024. Many companies are looking for proficiency in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Style React Components]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-style-react-components/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-style-react-components/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T09:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can only make your React app visually appealing to users with styling. That makes styling a fundamental aspect of building captivating user interfaces. With React's component-based architecture, there are a ton of options for styling. These include traditional CSS, utility-first approach, CSS-in-JS solutions, and more. In this article, we'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[APIs with Node.js and Express – Course in Spanish for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/apis-with-nodejs-and-express-course-in-spanish-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/apis-with-nodejs-and-express-course-in-spanish-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T08:11:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An application programming interface (API) is software that acts as an intermediary, allowing two applications to communicate. This project will teach you how to develop an API step by step and connect it to a database. We just published a course on ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-Tuning LLM Models Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fine-tuning-llm-models-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fine-tuning-llm-models-course/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T16:22:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-tuning is a process in machine learning that allows you to adapt pre-trained models to specific tasks or datasets, enhancing their performance and usability. We just posted a comprehensive course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Real Time Chat App with Supabase and Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-real-time-chat-app-with-supabase-and-angular/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-real-time-chat-app-with-supabase-and-angular/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T14:32:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you improve your skills with Supabase and Angular. In this course, you will learn how to build a real-time chat application. The course is perfect for anyone lookin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Collaborate with Web Development Teams Using Productivity Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-collaborate-with-web-development-teams-using-productivity-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-collaborate-with-web-development-teams-using-productivity-tools/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T12:52:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a web developer, designer, or project manager, you're likely quite busy these days and have a lot on your plate.  This is partly because the number of websites is growing rapidly, with 71% of all businesses [https://www.forbes.com/advisor/business/software/website-statistics/] in the world having one. In fact, every three seconds]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarif Kahn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Resilient Microservice Systems – SOLID Principles for Microservices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/solid-principles-for-microservices/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/solid-principles-for-microservices/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:56:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are in the era of transformative technology with several innovations springing up to improve service delivery and enhance customers’ satisfaction. More so is the introduction of microservices and other distributed systems into the software industry to revolutionize enterprise application development. Its introduction has helped to solve problems associated with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oluwatobi Joshua</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hidden vs. Disabled In UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/hidden-vs-disabled-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/hidden-vs-disabled-ux/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Should you hide or disable a feature? You’ve probably been there before. Here are some considerations for hiding versus disabling, along with possible alternatives to improve UX. An upcoming part of [Smart Interface Design Patterns](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript Class Handbook – Complete Guide to Class Fields and the Super Keyword]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-class-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-class-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T20:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Classes let you privatize your data while providing users indirect access to it. It is an excellent way to prevent direct access to your constructor’s data. This handbook aims to show you exactly how classes work in JavaScript. We will also discuss class fields and the super keyword. Table of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi Sofela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become an Open Source Project Maintainer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-an-open-source-maintainer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-an-open-source-maintainer/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T17:21:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might be wondering why you would want to become an open source maintainer.  Well, I can tell you from my own experience that you'll learn a lot, grow your network, and meet and collaborate with people you wouldn’t have the opportunity to otherwise.  It also helps you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BekahHW</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Online Safety – A Guide to Protecting Yourself]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/online-safety-a-guide-to-protecting-yourself/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/online-safety-a-guide-to-protecting-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T15:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating digital accounts safely is a concern for many in the modern age.  Digital accounts have become an integral part of our daily lives. From email and online banking to accounts on ride-sharing platforms like Uber and e-commerce platforms like Amazon, protecting our digital lives online is becoming imperative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohit Jacob Mathew</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a REST API Without a Server]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-rest-api-without-a-server/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-rest-api-without-a-server/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T10:13:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a Front-End developer and want to showcase your skills, it may be a problem if you use GitHub pages or Netlify to show your apps.  Instead, you can create a REST API directly in the browser without the need of any server. With this, you can showcase]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakub T. Jankiewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Your Flutter Package Privacy Manifest Compatible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-your-flutter-package-privacy-manifest-compatible/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-your-flutter-package-privacy-manifest-compatible/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T08:10:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beginning May 1st, Apple will enforce all new applications or updated versions of applications that will be uploaded to the Apple Store, to include a Privacy Manifest file.  If you are unfamiliar with what a Privacy Manifest is, I suggest reading my  other article [/news/what-the-ios-privacy-manifest-means-for-developers/]. There has been]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Ben Rachel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI is Overrated – Why ThePrimeagen Ripped Out GitHub Copilot From His Code Editor [Podcast #124]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-is-overrated-why-theprimeagen-ripped-out-github-copilot-from-his-code-editor-podcast-124/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-is-overrated-why-theprimeagen-ripped-out-github-copilot-from-his-code-editor-podcast-124/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T23:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp I interview The Primeagean. He's a software engineer who streams himself programming. He recently left his job at Netflix to stream full-time. We talk about: Prime's journey from his teacher tellin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn College Precalculus with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-college-precalculus-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-college-precalculus-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T19:07:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Precalculus is an important mathematical course that lays the groundwork for calculus and other higher-level math subjects. We just released a college precalculus course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This course is unique in that you will ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A User Segmentation Matrix To Foster Cross-Org Alignment]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/building-user-segmentation-matrix-foster-cross-org-alignment/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/building-user-segmentation-matrix-foster-cross-org-alignment/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there such a thing as harmony between designers and developers in the workplace, and if so, how can it be achieved? In this article, Chris Day explores the challenges of effective collaboration, outlines the key factors at play, and (hopefully!) empowers you to find the right solutions to help you and your team deliver to their full potential.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Talke Hoppmann-Walton)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deal with Traffic Surges in Distributed Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deal-with-traffic-surges-in-distributed-systems/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deal-with-traffic-surges-in-distributed-systems/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web and Distributed Systems can often get overwhelmed with traffic.  What leads to systems being overwhelmed, why does it happen, and what are some common strategies we can use to deal with this? We'll answer these questions in this article. Table of Contents  1. What is traffic in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anant Chowdhary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why am I not getting Quincy Larson's email anymore?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-am-i-not-getting-quincy-larsons-email-anymore/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-am-i-not-getting-quincy-larsons-email-anymore/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T23:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're not getting Quincy Larson's email each week, and you want to get them again, do the following: Fill out this form. It takes less than a minute. Search your spam folder for "Quincy Larson" and if you find any of my emails in there, mark th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Join the freeCodeCamp Discord Server and Chat with Fellow Campers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-join-the-freecodecamp-discord-server-and-chat-with-fellow-campers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-join-the-freecodecamp-discord-server-and-chat-with-fellow-campers/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T21:13:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp runs a popular Discord community where we hang out and chat about technology. You can join in the fun and learn from fellow campers who are going through freeCodeCamp's core curriculum. You can use this link: https://discord.com/invite/f...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond CSS Media Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/beyond-css-media-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/beyond-css-media-queries/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Juan Diego Rodriguez explains why media queries still occupy a vital role in responsive layouts; only they are now one tool in a larger toolbox with modern techniques that are best when used together.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Pop-up Image in Your Spreadsheet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-image-lightbox/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-image-lightbox/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T10:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll show you two ways to create a lightbox effect in a spreadsheet. The first will trigger the image to be displayed in a large area in the sheet. The second will be an actual HTML popup on top of the sheet. If you want to follow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the Algorithms Behind Quantum Computing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-algorithms-behind-quantum-computing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-algorithms-behind-quantum-computing/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T15:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum computing leverages the principles of quantum mechanics to process information at incredible speeds. We just posted a Quantum Computing course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This course, created by Michael from Quantum Soar, is desi...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>