<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-09-17T01:42:52.465Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Alt Text? Image Alt Text HTML Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-alt-text-image-alt-text-html-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-alt-text-image-alt-text-html-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T20:39:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images play a significant role on our web pages. They help explain concepts better, make our web pages visually attractive, and lots more. In HTML, you use the  tag to embed an image into your web page. This  tag has two required attributes: src to specify the path]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Accept Payments with React and Stripe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-stripe-payments/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-stripe-payments/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T18:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Payments are an essential part of any online business. But the process of setting up those payments can be incredibly complex at times.  To accept payments, developers were traditionally required to set up code both on the client and server. This was in addition to learning complex third-party APIs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dictionary Comprehension in Python – Dict Comprehensions Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dictionary-comprehension-in-python-dict-comprehensions-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dictionary-comprehension-in-python-dict-comprehensions-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T18:47:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use Dictionaries [/news/python-add-to-dictionary-adding-an-item-to-a-dict/]in Python to store data in key and value pairs.  And you can use dictionary comprehension to create a new dictionary from an already existing one.  When creating a new dictionary using dictionary comprehension, you can perform various operations using expressions to determine the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Python to Scrape App Store Reviews]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-python-to-scrape-app-store-reviews/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-python-to-scrape-app-store-reviews/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T18:04:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data scraping, commonly referred to as web scraping, is a technique for getting data and content from the internet.  You usually keep this information in a local file so that you can change and inspect it as needed.  Web scraping is basically just copying and pasting content from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edge Cloud Microservices – How to Build High Performance & Secure Apps with WasmEdge and Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/edge-cloud-microservices-with-wasmedge-and-rust/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/edge-cloud-microservices-with-wasmedge-and-rust/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T17:43:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The edge cloud allows developers to deploy microservices (that is, fine-grained web services) close to their users. This gives them a better user experience (and very fast response times), security, and high availability.  It also leverages local or even private data centers, CDN networks, and telecomm data centers (for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Yuan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are White Hat, Black Hat, and Red Hat Hackers? Different Types of Hacking Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/white-hat-black-hat-red-hat-hackers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/white-hat-black-hat-red-hat-hackers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T17:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the movies, everyone! 🍿 Have you ever heard the term white hat or black hat hacker, and wondered what it means? Well, in this article, you will learn how hackers are classified by comparing them to a Marvel or DC hero that more or less represents them and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Iwugo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work with Numbers and Dates in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/numbers-and-dates-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/numbers-and-dates-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T15:42:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Numbers, dates, and timers are important parts of JavaScript. And you'll need to know how to work with them when writing your code. We often ignore these topics as many articles don't discuss them. So here, we'll dive deep into the techniques you can use and learn some interesting things]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Jenkins by Building a CI/CD Pipeline]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-jenkins-by-building-a-ci-cd-pipeline/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-jenkins-by-building-a-ci-cd-pipeline/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T14:10:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jenkins is an open source automation server which makes it easier to build, test, and deploy software. We just published a video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you about Jenkins by showing you how to build a CI/CD pipeline for a web application.  Gwendolyn Faraday]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rethinking Star Ratings For Readers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/rethinking-star-ratings-readers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/rethinking-star-ratings-readers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can companies change their rating and review systems to better benefit users? Matt Athanasiou shares some steps to improve the experience of reviewing literature and other products — while also building stronger connections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matt Athanasiou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comparing Arrays in JavaScript – How to Compare 2 Arrays in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-compare-arrays-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-compare-arrays-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T00:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When handling logic with JavaScript, you might need to compare two arrays to see if they are equal or not. Really, this shouldn't be difficult, as you'd think we could easily use either the loose equality (double equals - ==) or the strict equality (triple equals -  ===). But]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Data Science? What a Data Scientist Actually Does]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-data-science-what-a-data-scientist-actually-does/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-data-science-what-a-data-scientist-actually-does/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T20:11:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data Science is one of the most in-demand and desirable careers of the 21st century. Even though the term was introduced in the early 1960s, its meaning has changed considerably over time. And despite its rise in popularity in recent years, many people outside the field still find the term]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Animate Your React Apps with 1 Line of Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/animate-react-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/animate-react-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T19:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animations have the powerful ability to turn a boring, static application into a more dynamic, memorable experience for your users.  In general, animations can be quite difficult to set up, especially if you intend to animate multiple components in your app.  In this tutorial, we will see how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Kali Linux on Your Computer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-kali-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-kali-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T19:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kali Linux (formerly known as BackTrack) is an open-source Linux distro developed and funded by Offensive Security.  It’s basically an ethical hacker's dream operating system, because it has most of the tools you'll ever need built-in. From Metasploit to JohntheRipper to the one and only Aircrack-ng, this OS has]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Iwugo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Details on `details`]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373372</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/more-details-on-details/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T13:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of chatter around the ol’ <details> and <summary> elements lately! I saw Lea Verou recently tweet an observation about the element’s display behavior and that sorta splintered into more observations and usage notes from folks, including a revived …
More Details on `details` originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility In Times Of Headless]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/accessibility-times-headless/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/accessibility-times-headless/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to make your new website as accessible as possible? Amazing, that’s a great mindset! Let’s have a closer look at the factors you should take into consideration when choosing a content management system (CMS) in terms of web accessibility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Josefine Schaefer)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Pivot Table in Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-pivot-table-in-excel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-pivot-table-in-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T22:35:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Excel, pivot tables let you analyze and visualize your data in an easy way. With pivot tables, you can make comparisons and create calculations more quickly. You can even create charts to visualize your data. Creating pivot tables might be intimidating if you're doing it for the first time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Evaluate Machine Learning Models using TensorBoard with TensorFlow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-evaluate-machine-learning-models-using-tensorboard/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-evaluate-machine-learning-models-using-tensorboard/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T18:31:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improving a Machine Learning model is an iterative process. No machine learning model is ever perfect on the first attempt at training it. It usually takes a few iterations.  But a common mistake you might make as a Machine Learning practitioner is failing to realize that you need to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salim Oyinlola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn HTML and CSS from the CEO of Scrimba]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-html-and-css-from-the-ceo-of-scrimba/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-html-and-css-from-the-ceo-of-scrimba/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T18:15:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost every website in the world uses HTML and CSS. So you should definitely learn them if you want to create websites. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build websites with HTML and CSS. Per Borgan created this course. Per]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Practices for Scaling Your Node.js REST APIs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nodejs-api-best-practices-for-scaling/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nodejs-api-best-practices-for-scaling/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T16:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is more to scalability than using cluster mode. In this tutorial, we'll explore 10 ways you can make your Node.js API ready to scale. When working on a project, we often get a few real nuggets here and there on how to do something in a better way. We]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rishabh Rawat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel Security Check Failure – How to Restart the Kernel in Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kernel-security-check-failure-how-to-restart-the-kernel-in-windows-10/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kernel-security-check-failure-how-to-restart-the-kernel-in-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T15:41:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been a professional software engineer for many years, and I can testify that there are few things worse than getting the dreaded BSOD (Blue Screen of Death). Especially when you are about to write a piece of mind bending code at 2am to meet a looming deadline.  That’s]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gavin Lon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I Learned Teaching 20 High School Girls How to Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-i-learned-teaching-20-hs-girls-to-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-i-learned-teaching-20-hs-girls-to-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T14:46:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On day 1, they barely knew what a float was. On day 14, they had programmed a game of minesweeper, a cipher decoder, or a zombie apocalypse simulation. And I helped teach them how to do it. Each summer, MIT hosts a program called WTP, or Women's Technology Program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kylie Ying</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When is it OK to Disable Text Selection?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373100</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/when-is-it-ok-to-disable-text-selection/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T13:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using CSS, it’s possible to prevent users from selecting text within an element using user-select: none. Now, it’s understandable why doing so might be considered “controversial”. I mean, should we be disabling standard user behaviors? Generally speaking, no, we …
When is it OK to Disable Text Selection? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript APIs You Don’t Know About]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/javascript-api-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/javascript-api-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Juan Diego covers the least known yet extremely useful APIs, such as the Page Visibility API, Web Sharing API, Broadcast Channel API and Internationalization API. Together we will see what they are, where we should use them, and how to use them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL vs NoSQL: When to Use Which]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-vs-nosql-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-vs-nosql-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T03:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When should you use a SQL database and when should you use a NoSQL database? We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you the differences between NoSQL and SQL databases as well as when and why to use each kind of database. Ania Kubow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Static Markdown Blog with Deno and Deploy It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-blog-with-deno/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-blog-with-deno/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T16:46:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deno is a runtime for JavaScript and TypeScript. The creator of Node.js built it, and while Node is built with C and C++, Deno is built with the Rust language. You might be wondering what some of the main differences between Node and Deno are. Well, Rust is a low-level]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebKit Features in Safari 16.0]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373367</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/webkit-features-in-safari-16-0/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T16:14:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whew boy, Safari 16 is officially out in the wild and it packs in a bunch of features, some new and exciting (Subgrid! Container Queries! Font Palettes!) and others we’ve been waiting on for better cross-browser support (Motion Path! Overscroll …
WebKit Features in Safari 16.0 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sort Dictionary by Value in Python – How to Sort a Dict]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sort-dictionary-by-value-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sort-dictionary-by-value-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T15:16:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, a dictionary is a fat structure that is unordered by default. So, sometimes, you'll want to sort dictionaries by key or value to make queries easier. The problem is that sorting a dictionary by value is never a straightforward thing to do. That’s because Python doesn’t have an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Basics of Remix]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373081</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-basics-of-remix/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T12:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably heard a lot of hype around one of the newest kids on the framework block, Remix. It may be surprising that it got its start back in 2019, but it was originally only available as a subscription-based premium …
The Basics of Remix originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brittney Postma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Sense Of WAI-ARIA: A Comprehensive Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/wai-aria-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/wai-aria-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Kate Kalcevich explains when to use ARIA and how to use it properly so that you can use ARIA in a way that’s helpful to the many disabled people who use [assistive technology](https://makeitfable.com/glossary/?utm_source=Smashing+Magazine&utm_medium=sponsored+content&utm_campaign=Upskill&utm_term=Fable&utm_content=Sept2022) to navigate the Internet. Let’s dive in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change Text Color in HTML – Font Style Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-change-text-color-in-html/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-change-text-color-in-html/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T20:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Text plays a significant role on our web pages. This is because it helps users learn what the web page is all about and what they can do there. When you add text to your web pages, this text defaults to a black color. But sometimes you will want to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the JavaScript DOM Works – A Practical Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-dom-a-practical-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-dom-a-practical-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T20:19:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you were listening to music on an app and you wanted to pause or skip a song, you'd have to do that through the app. This process is similar to how the Document Object Model or DOM works. Here, the music app represents the DOM because it serves as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ophy Boamah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Read and Write Data using Azure Databricks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-read-and-write-data-using-azure-databricks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-read-and-write-data-using-azure-databricks/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T18:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Databricks is a Microsoft Azure cloud service that provides a scalable platform for data analytics using Apache Spark. It is a fully managed, cloud-based data analytics platform that allows developers to create enterprise-grade data apps more quickly, which accelerates AI and innovation.  In this tutorial, you will cover]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salim Oyinlola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add the Chart.js Zoom Plugin to an Angular App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chart-js-zooom-plugin/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chart-js-zooom-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T18:38:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial you will learn how to the Add Chart.js Zoom plugin to an Angular application. When you have a lot of data in a chart, you may want to zoom in and see the details. Line charts are a good way to visualise large amounts of data. You]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Swatej Patil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 30 React Interview Questions and Concepts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/top-30-react-interview-questions-and-concepts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/top-30-react-interview-questions-and-concepts/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T17:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you have a React interview coming up? Or do you just want to test your React skills? We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you to prepare for a React interview by teaching you about 30 common React interview questions and concepts. Nishant]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Background Color – Change BG Color Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-background-color-change-bg-color-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-background-color-change-bg-color-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T17:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building web pages, you always want to create unique layouts. You want your web page to be appealing to your users and not jarring to the eye. And to help do that, you can choose background and text colors that blend well and complement each other. By default,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Tailwind CSS? A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-tailwind-css-a-beginners-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-tailwind-css-a-beginners-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T15:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing CSS can be really difficult. Period. And I get it – it can be frustrating to nail down your own ideas or the designs you get from your design team. I'm sure many of you have gone through the same pain at least a few times in your development]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soham De Roy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Container Orchestration? How to Manage your Containers with MicroK8s]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/container-orchestration-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/container-orchestration-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T14:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Container orchestration has been called the next big thing in the world of technology. And it’s easy to see why. Container orchestration helps IT professionals and programmers maximize their applications’ performance. It helps them ensure that multiple containers can work together to handle more tasks at the same time than]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ModuleNotFoundError: no module named Python Error [Fixed]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/module-not-found-error-in-python-solved/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/module-not-found-error-in-python-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T14:17:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you try to import a module in a Python file, Python tries to resolve this module in several ways. Sometimes, Python throws the ModuleNotFoundError  afterward. What does this error mean in Python? As the name implies, this error occurs when you're trying to access or use a module]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Interactive Figma Widgets]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372991</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/building-interactive-figma-widgets/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T13:05:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Figma has always encouraged collaboration between developers and designers. It strives on an endless treasury of community-made plugins. Need 3D elements? There’s a plugin for that. Need abstract SVGs? There’s a plugin for that, too.
That said, the design part of Figma has …
Building Interactive Figma Widgets originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eluda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Smart Interface Design Patterns Checklists” (Deck With 166 Cards)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/smart-interface-design-checklist-cards-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/smart-interface-design-checklist-cards-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Smart Interface Design Patterns Checklists”, a deck of 166 checklist cards to help you design and build better interfaces, faster. With accordions, mega-drop-downs, data tables, carousels, and everything in-between.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[200 Universities Just Launched 850+ Free Online Courses. Here’s the Full List.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/new-online-courses/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/new-online-courses/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-10T10:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you haven’t heard, universities around the world are offering their courses online for free (or at least, partially free). These courses are collectively called MOOCs or Massive Open Online Courses. [https://www.classcentral.com/help/moocs] In the past ten years, ~1000 universities have created around tens of thousands of MOOCs. I’ve been keeping]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhawal Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intro to Deno – Guide for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/intro-to-deno/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/intro-to-deno/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T22:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Deno? Deno is a new JavaScript runtime. It was built by Ryan Dahl, the creator of Node.js.  Dahl had a few things that he regretted doing with Node and wanted to build a runtime that could solve those issues. Deno, like Node, is built on the V8]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Barrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Push Local Branch to Remote – How to Publish a New Branch in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-push-local-branch-to-remote-how-to-publish-a-new-branch-in-git/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-push-local-branch-to-remote-how-to-publish-a-new-branch-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T20:36:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git branches let you add new features without tampering with the live version of your projects. And if you work in a team, different developers might have unique branches they work on. In the long run, you'll have to push those independent branches to a remote server. For example, GitHub,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node Version Manager – nvm Install Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/node-version-manager-nvm-install-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/node-version-manager-nvm-install-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T18:23:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll explain how you can install NVM, or Node Version Manager, on Windows, Linux, and Mac. What is NVM? Node Version Manager (NVM), as the name implies, is a tool for managing Node versions on your device. Different projects on your device may be using different versions]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Made a Pure CSS Puzzle Game]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372952</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-i-made-a-pure-css-puzzle-game/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T13:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently discovered the joy of creating CSS-only games. It’s always fascinating how HTML and CSS are capable of handling the logic of an entire online game, so I had to try it! Such games usually rely on the ol’ …
How I Made a Pure CSS Puzzle Game originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Formula To Rule Them All: The ROI Of A Design System]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/formula-roi-design-system/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/formula-roi-design-system/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design systems are a crucial success factor for digital businesses, and virtually every major player works with one. Still, they can sometimes be hard to sell to management. Here’s a ready-to-use formula to calculate the ROI of any design system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maximilian Speicher &amp; Guido Baena Wehrmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Line Charts Tutorial – How to Create a Line Graph in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-line-charts-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-line-charts-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T19:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data visualization is a vast field with so many different types of charts [https://datavizcatalogue.com/] to learn and create.  But there are several basic, evergreen graphs that every data designer and web developer dealing with analytics should know how to build.  One of them is a Line Chart (or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shachee Swadia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python .split() – Splitting a String in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-split-a-string-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-split-a-string-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T17:22:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to split a string in Python. Firstly, I'll introduce you to the syntax of the .split() method. After that, you will see how to use the .split() method with and without arguments, using code examples along the way. Here is what we will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve Machine Learning Code Quality with Scikit-learn Pipeline and ColumnTransformer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-pipeline/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-pipeline/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T16:31:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working on a machine learning project, the most tedious steps are often data cleaning and preprocessing. Especially when you're working in a Jupyter Notebook, running code in many cells can be confusing. The Scikit-learn library has tools called Pipeline and ColumnTransformer that can really make your life easier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yannawut Kimnaruk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use IndexedDB – Database Guide for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-indexeddb-works-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-indexeddb-works-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T16:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The modern browser has given us a number of options when it comes to storing data on the client-side. Aside from storing data, browser databases allow us to retrieve that data.  Based on your application's needs, you can choose from the different browser storage options out there to enhance]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Yakubu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Debug Dockerized .NET Core Apps in VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-debug-dockerized-net-core-apps-in-vs-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-debug-dockerized-net-core-apps-in-vs-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T15:34:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently switched to VS Code for development of a dockerized .NET core app. But I then realized that there weren't many up-to-date articles about debugging dockerized .NET core applications in VS Code. Source: GIPHYSo, here I am, writing this article. I hope that it'll help others like myself in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haseeb Ahmed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Excel Tutorial – How to Create Formulas and Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-microsoft-excel-formulas-and-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-microsoft-excel-formulas-and-functions/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T15:17:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spreadsheets aren't merely for arranging data into rows and columns. Most of the time, you use them for data analysis as well.  Microsoft Excel is one of the most widely used spreadsheet applications, especially in finance and accounting. This is partly because of its easy UI and unmatched depth]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benny Ifeanyi Iheagwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New With Forms in 2022?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372979</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/whats-new-with-forms-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T13:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Browsers are constantly adding new HTML, JavaScript and CSS features. Here are some useful additions to working with forms that you might have missed…
requestSubmit()
Safari 16 will be the final browser to add support for requestSubmit.
Before we …
What’s New With Forms in 2022? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UX Checklists For Interface Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/ux-checklists-for-interface-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/ux-checklists-for-interface-designers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UX checklists with best design practices, accessibility guidelines, design system checklist, tables UX checklist, UX research methods, form design UX and flowcharts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Prepare for React Interviews – Front-End Technical Interview Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-for-react-technical-interviews/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-for-react-technical-interviews/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T00:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A front-end technical interview is an opportunity for a potential employer to assess your skills and knowledge in web development. The interviewer will ask you questions about your experience and skills in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. They'll also likely ask you some framework specific questions about React, Angular, Vue, or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manu Arora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Geolocation API Tutorial – How to Get a User's Location in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-user-location-with-javascript-geolocation-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-user-location-with-javascript-geolocation-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T18:29:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some applications require you to know your user's location, like food delivery or eCommerce apps. So you'll need an efficient way to get this info. The Geolocation API, which we will look at today, is a simple solution. You can use it to determine your users' location, local currency, language,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Mitolu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is deb-get? How to Install the Debian Package with the deb-get Command]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-deb-get-debian-package-manager/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-deb-get-debian-package-manager/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T18:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[deb-get is a new command line utility built by Martin Wimpress [https://twitter.com/m_wimpress], an active contributor to the Linux community.  You can use this utility to install third-party packages on your Debian machine. It only works with Debian or Debian-based distros like Ubuntu, Linux mint, Kali Linux, and so on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Renaming a Git Branch – How to Rename the Current Branch in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/renaming-a-git-branch-how-to-rename-the-current-branch-in-git/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/renaming-a-git-branch-how-to-rename-the-current-branch-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T18:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are using Git for version control, it’s likely you’ve created branches for various reasons. Since you have those branches in place, you might want to rename any of them if you find a typo, for example, or change the code's purpose. In this article, I will show you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remove a Directory in Linux – How to Remove folders from the Command Line]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/remove-directory-in-linux-from-the-command-line/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/remove-directory-in-linux-from-the-command-line/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T18:18:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux is a powerful OS with various command line utilities to help you achieve your day-to-day tasks. Removing folders is a very common operation that allows you to either remove a single folder or remove them recursively (folders within folders).  In this tutorial, we will see how we can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Java Handbook – Learn Java Programming for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-java-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-java-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T18:05:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Java has been around since the 90s. And despite its massive success in many areas, this cross-platform, object-oriented programming language is often maligned. Regardless of how people feel about Java, I can tell you from experience is that it is an excellent programming language. After its first appearance back in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farhan Hasin Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular for Beginners Course + TypeScript [Full Front-End Tutorial]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/angular-for-beginners-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/angular-for-beginners-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T16:45:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular is a popular TypeScript-based open-source web application framework created by Google. We just published a comprehensive 18-hour Angular course for beginners on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. In this course you will first you will learn the basics of TypeScript. Then you will learn about important Angular concepts such as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overlapping Bar Charts]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372968</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/overlapping-bar-charts/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T13:46:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the name suggests, overlapping charts visualize two different sets of data in a single diagram. The idea is that the overlapping bars allow us to compare data, say, year-over-year. They are also useful for things like tracking progress for …
Overlapping Bar Charts originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saleh Mubashar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Responsive Web Design Can Help Your Business – A Beginner's Guide to RWD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-responsive-web-design-helps-businesses/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-responsive-web-design-helps-businesses/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T20:18:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the world of technology continues to advance, so does the way people interact with businesses and organizations.  With the growing popularity of mobile devices, responsive website design has become a must-have. It helps you provide the best user experience to customers regardless of which device they are using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Reverse List – Reversing an Array in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-reverse-list-reversing-an-array-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-reverse-list-reversing-an-array-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T19:36:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to reverse a list in Python. Firstly, I'll introduce you to lists in Python and you'll learn how to write them. After that, you will see three different ways you can reverse the list items inside any list you create. Here is what]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Realities And Myths Of Contrast And Color]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/realities-myths-contrast-color/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/realities-myths-contrast-color/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Andrew Somers, a 35-year veteran of the Hollywood film and television industry, shares his experience about the hard-fought battles and lessons learned designing for illuminated presentations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andrew Somers)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacking CSS Animation State and Playback Time]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372850</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/hacking-css-animation-state-and-playback-time/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T18:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS-only Wolfenstein is a little project that I made a few weeks ago. It was an experiment with CSS 3D transformations and animations.
Inspired by the FPS demo and another Wolfenstein CodePen, I decided to build my own version. …
Hacking CSS Animation State and Playback Time originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lu Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Framework? Software Frameworks Definition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-framework-software-frameworks-definition/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-framework-software-frameworks-definition/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T17:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're learning to code, you'll frequently hear the term "framework". And it can be difficult for new developers to grasp. You'll commonly come across frameworks in roadmap resources, when speaking with other developers, when learning about a new coding tool, and many other places. In this article, you will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Machine Learning? ML Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-machine-learning-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-machine-learning-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T17:25:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “Machine Learning” was coined by a computer gamer named Arthur Samuel in 1959. He defined it like this: > "[Machine learning is a] Field of study that gives computers the ability to learn and make predictions without being explicitly programmed." ML is a sub-field of Artificial Intelligence. It's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwafunmilola Obisesan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OOP Meaning – What is Object-Oriented Programming?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-object-oriented-programming/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-object-oriented-programming/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T17:15:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's technology driven society, computer programming knowledge is in high demand. And as a developer, you'll need to know various programming languages. Over the past few decades, many programming languages have risen in popularity. You can see how popular languages are ranked in this real time ranking chart]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hillary Nyakundi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the Eleventy Static Site Generator by Building and Deploying a Portfolio Website]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-eleventy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-eleventy/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T16:26:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Eleventy? Eleventy (also called 11ty) is a simple yet powerful static site generator. It uses JavaScript to transform data and templates into HTML pages. It’s beginner-friendly, has fast build times, and generates fast sites by default. It also has a very active and friendly community. Eleventy excels at]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gerard Hynes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Translation Month is Back – How to Help Translate freeCodeCamp into Your Native Language]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/world-translation-month-is-back-how-can-you-contribute-to-translate-freecodecamp-into-your-language/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/world-translation-month-is-back-how-can-you-contribute-to-translate-freecodecamp-into-your-language/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T14:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One year has passed since freeCodeCamp held our first World Translation Month in September 2021.  Well, it’s September again – and here we are for the second installment of this month-long event. freeCodeCamp is holding our World Translation Month for the second year in a row, taking place September]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Rosa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 52 With Yiying Lu: How Do You Become An NFT Artist?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/smashing-podcast-episode-52/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/smashing-podcast-episode-52/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we ask how do you go from running a creative studio to designing NFTs. Vitaly talks to artist Yiying Lu to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter For Front-End Web Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372853</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/flutter-for-front-end-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T20:10:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I started as a front-end web developer and then became a Flutter developer. I think there were some concepts that helped me adopt Flutter easier. There were also some new concepts that were different.
In this article, I want to …
Flutter For Front-End Web Developers originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Obumuneme Nwabude</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Understanding Privacy, A New Smashing Book By Heather Burns]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/understanding-privacy-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/understanding-privacy-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Understanding Privacy”, our upcoming book on what data privacy is really about beyond scary headlines. Approx. 350 pages. eBook available in October, print shipping in November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source for Developers – A Beginner's Handbook to Help You Start Contributing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-practical-guide-to-start-opensource-contributions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-practical-guide-to-start-opensource-contributions/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T16:34:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What comes to mind when you hear the term Open Source? In the programming world, open source is a generic term for Open Source Software (OSS). Open-source software is built on source code that's open to everyone to view, change, extend, and distribute. In this article, we will get into]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript DOM Tutorial – How to Build a Calculator App in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-dom-build-a-calculator-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-dom-build-a-calculator-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You're going to spend a lot of time working on webpages when using JavaScript. In fact, while you're using JavaScript, the webpage is where all the exciting and important stuff takes place.  A webpage is one big document for a JavaScript developer since every element on the page is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spruce Emmanuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Monitor Python APIs using Pyctuator and SpringBootAdmin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-monitor-python-apis-using-pyctuator-and-springbootadmin/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-monitor-python-apis-using-pyctuator-and-springbootadmin/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T15:02:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Actuator endpoints help us monitor our services. By using actuators, we can gain a lot of information about what’s going on.  SpringBoot has a number of in-built actuators, and it also allows us to create our own Actuator Endpoint.  For frameworks written in Python like Flask or FastAPI,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sameer Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Accessibility And Usability Journey Of Drupal’s Primary Navigation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/accessibility-usability-drupal-primary-navigation/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/accessibility-usability-drupal-primary-navigation/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Mike Herchel covers Drupal’s new default theme, Olivero, which is usable, accessible, robust, and beautiful and will help you improve websites’ navigation systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mike Herchel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python String.replace() – How to Replace a Character in a String]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-string-replace-how-to-replace-a-character-in-a-string/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-string-replace-how-to-replace-a-character-in-a-string/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T21:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python has numerous string modifying methods, and one of them is the replace  method. In this article, I'll show you how this method can be used to replace a character in a string. How the replace Method Works in Python The replace string method returns a new string with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the CSScenes, September 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373126</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/behind-the-csscenes-sept2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T20:06:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Those of you who have been reading CSS-Tricks for a while may remember that we used to publish a little thing we called CSS-Tricks Chronicles. Our friend Chris Coyier would write up a reflection from the past couple of …
Behind the CSScenes, September 2022 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haley Mills</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is an IDE? IDE Meaning in Coding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-an-ide-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-an-ide-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T18:48:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're first learning to code, there are a few tools you'll typically want to decide on before getting started. You'll pick a tech stack and a programming language to learn and use, and you'll also choose an IDE, or integrated development environment, where you'll write your code. Many different]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comparing JAWS, NVDA, and VoiceOver]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372855</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/comparing-jaws-nvda-and-voiceover/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T17:47:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A screen reader is an important accessibility tool for people with no or limited vision. People who are blind or those with low vision can use a screen reader to navigate the computer. Screen readers will read contents on the …
Comparing JAWS, NVDA, and VoiceOver originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilknur Eren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Your Node.js Application for Free with Render]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-nodejs-application-with-render/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-nodejs-application-with-render/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T16:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, Heroku has been an excellent platform to host your Full Stack applications. freeCodeCamp made heavy use of Heroku early on – as have countless open source projects.  But that may change, as Heroku is bringing its generous free tier to an end. You may have received email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yogesh Chavan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Aggregate Functions – How to Group By in MySQL and PostgreSQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-aggregate-functions-how-to-group-by-in-mysql-and-postgresql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-aggregate-functions-how-to-group-by-in-mysql-and-postgresql/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T15:57:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In SQL, aggregate functions let you perform a calculation on multiple data and return a single value. That’s why they are called “aggregate” functions. Those aggregate functions are AVG(), COUNT(), SUM(), MIN(), and MAX(). While making queries with the aggregate functions, you can also use them in combination with the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Blueprints to Organize Your Flask Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-blueprints-to-organize-flask-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-blueprints-to-organize-flask-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T15:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flask is a simple, easy-to-use microframework for Python that can help you build scalable and secure web applications.  Sometimes you'll find developers dumping all of their logic into a single file called app.py. You will find a lot of tutorials that follow the same pattern. But it's not a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iShadeed’s Container Queries Lab]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373087</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/ishadeeds-container-queries-lab/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T14:29:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahmad Shadeed got an early jump on container queries and has a growing collection of examples based on everyday patterns.
And, if you missed it, his latest post on container queries does a wonderful job covering how they work since …
iShadeed’s Container Queries Lab originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Databases For Front-End Developers: The Concepts Under The Hood (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/databases-frontend-developers-concepts-under-hood/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/databases-frontend-developers-concepts-under-hood/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the second part of “Databases For Front-End Developers” series, Atila Fassina explores concepts to equip you to have your own opinions about which kinds of databases suit your specific needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful JavaScript Data Grid Libraries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/useful-javascript-data-grid-libraries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/useful-javascript-data-grid-libraries/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Zara Cooper provides a rundown of some popular data grid libraries that would be a great addition to any data-heavy application and shares recommendations on what factors to consider when choosing a suitable data grid library.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Lazy Load Images in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-lazy-load-images-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-lazy-load-images-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T22:24:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing the assets you use on your websites – like lazy loading images – is one of the most effective ways to improve web performance. Doing this helps you make sure that your websites are fast, they have great SEO [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Search_engine_optimization], and it helps enhance the user experience. In this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Eke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful HTML5 Tags You Might Not Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html5-tags-you-might-not-know/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html5-tags-you-might-not-know/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T21:47:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the key factors that differentiates HTML 5 from its predecessors is the introduction of semantic tags.  Semantic tags add real meaning to the webpage and make it easy for humans, and search engines, to differentiate between different parts of the website.  To a certain extent, it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bhavesh Rawat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Coding Interview Practice – Sample Interview Questions and Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-coding-interview-practice/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-coding-interview-practice/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T17:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Goggins is an ultramarathon runner, a public speaker, a retired navy SEAL, and the author of the book 'Can't Hurt Me: Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds [https://www.amazon.com/Cant-Hurt-Me-Master-Your/dp/1544512287]'. He's one of my role models because of his physical strength and mental resilience.  You might say: "Wait a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damla Erkiner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove an Element from a JavaScript Array – Removing a Specific Item in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-an-element-from-a-javascript-array-removing-a-specific-item-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-an-element-from-a-javascript-array-removing-a-specific-item-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T17:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You will often need to remove an element from an array in JavaScript, whether it's for a queue data structure, or maybe from your React State. In the first half of this article you will learn all the methods that allow you to remove an element from an array without]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilenia Magoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn React from Three All-Star Instructors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-react-from-three-all-star-instructors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-react-from-three-all-star-instructors/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T14:46:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is one of the most popular frontend JavaScript frameworks. If you want to be a frontend developer, you will likely need to know something about React. We just published a full React course for beginners on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This course is unlike most of the other React]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding The Balance (September 2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-september-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-september-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T08:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s welcome September with some fresh desktop wallpapers. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for the month. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From WordPress to Hugo – How I Migrated a 250+ Page Site and the Scripts I Used]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/wordpress-to-hugo-scripts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/wordpress-to-hugo-scripts/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T23:25:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently decided to switch Boot.dev's [https://boot.dev] blog from WordPress to a static site generator. I decided on Hugo [https://gohugo.io/], partly because I’m a huge fan of the Go programming language, but also because it just seemed like the best option from a dev-experience perspective.  Here’s why I decided]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Wagner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use JavaScript's Map() Method to Solve Breadth-First and Depth-First Search Problems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-javascript-map-method-to-make-a-breath-first-and-depth-first-search/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-javascript-map-method-to-make-a-breath-first-and-depth-first-search/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T17:17:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript map() method [/news/array-map-tutorial/] is an object [https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/JavaScript/Reference/Global_Objects/Object]  with a key and value pair. An object's key and value are connected using a colon (:) while the key and value of a map are connected using an arrow (=>). Here's an example of an object in JavaScript: {]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Njoku Samson Ebere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Personal Digital Security – How to Protect Yourself Online for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/personal-digital-security-an-intro/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/personal-digital-security-an-intro/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T16:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you protect yourself online without having to remember a million impossible passwords?  This is an (actually) easy to implement guide, which is the digital equivalent of locking your house when you leave.  Taking these steps won’t make you hack-proof (just as locking your house won’t make]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Kaczanowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[String to Number in JavaScript – Convert a String to an Int in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/string-to-number-in-javascript-convert-a-string-to-an-int-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/string-to-number-in-javascript-convert-a-string-to-an-int-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T16:38:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're programming, you'll often need to switch between data types. For example, you may need to convert a string into a number. The ability to convert one data type to another gives you great flexibility when working with information. JavaScript has different built-in methods to convert or cast a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL HAVING – How to Group and Count with a Having Statement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-having-how-to-group-and-count-with-a-having-statement/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-having-how-to-group-and-count-with-a-having-statement/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T15:59:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In SQL, you use the HAVING keyword right after GROUP BY to query the database based on a specified condition. Like other keywords, it returns the data that meet the condition and filters out the rest. The HAVING keyword was introduced because the WHERE clause fails when used with aggregate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SSH Keygen Tutorial – How to Generate an SSH Public Key for RSA Login]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ssh-keygen-how-to-generate-an-ssh-public-key-for-rsa-login/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ssh-keygen-how-to-generate-an-ssh-public-key-for-rsa-login/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T15:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptography uses encryption and decryption to conceal messages. This introduces secrecy in information security.  The purpose of cryptography is to ensure secure communication between two people or devices who are connecting through insecure channels. The sender often employs an encryption key to lock the message, while the recipient uses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bolaji Ayodeji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use GitHub Super Linter in Your Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/github-super-linter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/github-super-linter/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T15:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're starting a new project, you might have to add multiple linting tools to beautify your code and prevent simple errors.  You will often use multiple linters – one of them might support an npm installation and other one might have a PyPI installation and so on. You]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rishit Dagli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS in 11 Hours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-in-11-hours/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-in-11-hours/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T13:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is essential for frontend web developers to understand how to use CSS. This is what is used to style a website. We just published a comprehensive CSS course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. In this in-depth course, you will learn about all the key features of CSS. This is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interpolating Numeric CSS Variables]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372839</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/interpolating-numeric-css-variables/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T13:17:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can make variables in CSS pretty easily:
:root {
  --scale: 1;
}
And we can declare them on any element:
.thing {
  transform: scale(--scale);
}
Even better for an example like this is applying the variable on a user …
Interpolating Numeric CSS Variables originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Improve And Measure Your Progress Learning Web Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/improve-measure-progress-learning-web-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/improve-measure-progress-learning-web-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever felt overwhelmed by the number of things you need to learn? Today, we look at how [Uxcel](https://uxcel.com/) eases this transition and approaches actively learning new skills to take our careers to the next level.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shane Hudson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Common Attacks on SSL/TLS – and How to Protect Your System]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/attacks-on-ssl-tls-and-how-to-protect-your-system/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/attacks-on-ssl-tls-and-how-to-protect-your-system/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T21:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SSL and TLS protocols are frequently attacked. And understanding past attacks can inform your knowledge as a defender and help you secure current systems. It can also help you predict the direction of future attacks. So here's a summary of some of the most famous attacks targeting these protocols:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Kaczanowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Makes A Great Toggle Button? (Case Study, Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/toggle-button-case-study-part-2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/toggle-button-case-study-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The problem of how to design an effective toggle button that shows the selected option clearly is a long-term open question among UI/UX designers. In this second part, Eduard Kuric explains a complex list of visual cues used by toggle buttons to communicate which of their options is active.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eduard Kuric)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Linear Models and Decision Trees in Julia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linear-models-vs-decision-trees-in-julia/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linear-models-vs-decision-trees-in-julia/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T13:46:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a machine learning engineer or data scientist, one of the most critical decisions you can make is what type of model to use to solve a specific problem. Do you really need to use Deep Learning to model this specific problem? Will something like a Random Forest model or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Logan Kilpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code 20 Beginner Python Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/20-beginner-python-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/20-beginner-python-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T12:44:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking to improve your Python skills? Try coding these 20 Python projects! We just posted a video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create 20 fun Python projects. Tomi Tokko created this course. Tomi has created a bunch of really popular tutorials]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java scanner.nextLine() Method Call Gets Skipped Error [SOLVED]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-scanner-nextline-call-gets-skipped-solved/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-scanner-nextline-call-gets-skipped-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T21:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a common error that tends to stump new Java programmers. It happens when you group together a bunch of input prompts and one of the scanner.nextLine()  method calls gets skipped – without any signs of failure or error. Take a look at the following code snippet, for example:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farhan Hasin Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python to Lowercase a String – str.lower() Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-to-lowercase-a-string-str-lower-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-to-lowercase-a-string-str-lower-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T20:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strings can be in different formats such as lowercase, capitalized, and uppercase. In this article, I'll show you how to convert a string to lowercase in Python. A lowercase string has all its characters in small letters. An example is python . A capitalized string has the first letter of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML TextArea – How to Add a Text Box Input Type Tag to Your Website]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-textarea-how-to-add-text-box-to-your-website/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-textarea-how-to-add-text-box-to-your-website/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T16:21:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A text box is a section of your website where users can enter text. A blinking cursor appears when you click or tap on or inside the text box, indicating that you are ready to begin typing. And an on-screen keyboard will appear if you're using a tablet or smartphone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perform Integration Testing using JUnit 5 and TestContainers with SpringBoot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/integration-testing-using-junit-5-testcontainers-with-springboot-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/integration-testing-using-junit-5-testcontainers-with-springboot-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T15:46:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TestContainers is a library that helps you run module-specific Docker containers to simplify Integration Testing.  These Docker containers are lightweight, and once the tests are finished the containers get destroyed. In the article we are going to understand what the TestContainers is and how it helps you write more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sameer Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[File Handling in Python – How to Create, Read, and Write to a File]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/file-handling-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/file-handling-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T15:42:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn how to open a file, write to the file, and close it. You will also learn how to read from the file using Python.  By the end of this tutorial, you should know the basics of how to use files in Python. File]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Fagbuyiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn Serverless AWS by Building 7 Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-serverless-aws-by-building-7-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-serverless-aws-by-building-7-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T15:34:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following tutorials when you start learning serverless is a good first step. But to really get better, you need to build your own projects.  The problem is that coming up with ideas that are realistic but help you grow is hard. To help you out, I’ve come up with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Grid Named Areas to Visualize (and Reference) Your Layout]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372634</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-grid-named-areas-to-visualize-and-reference-your-layout/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T13:44:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whenever we build simple or complex layouts using CSS Grid, we’re usually positioning items with line numbers. Grid layouts contain grid lines that are automatically indexed with positive and negative line numbers (that is unless we explicitly name them). …
Using Grid Named Areas to Visualize (and Reference) Your Layout originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi Selvam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Relational Database? RDBMS Definition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-relational-database-rdbms-definition/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-relational-database-rdbms-definition/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T22:51:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A relational database is a type of database that stores data in tables made up of rows and columns. Each table represents a specific object in the database like users, products, orders, and so on.  The term "relational" is the main characteristic feature that makes relational databases unique. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Better Error Messages UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/error-messages-ux-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/error-messages-ux-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Error messages need to be easy to spot, but they also need to be helpful. Let’s explore when error messages should live above input fields and why toast error messages are usually not a very good idea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Sure How to WordPress Anymore?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372616</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/not-sure-how-to-wordpress-anymore/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T14:34:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neither do I! And that’s probably because there’s a lot happening in WordPress-land. The evolution towards full-site editing (FSE) introduces frequent changes to the way we build themes and plugins, and at such break-neck speed that the documentation itself is …
Not Sure How to WordPress Anymore? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Games with LÖVE 2D and Lua]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-games-with-love-2d-and-lua/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-games-with-love-2d-and-lua/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T13:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Lua programming language is becoming increasingly popular for game development. And the LÖVE 2D game engine makes it simpler to create games using Lua.  We just published a full 11-hour game development course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create games using LÖVE]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Video Streaming With imgix]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/better-video-streaming-with-imgix/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/better-video-streaming-with-imgix/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you need to deliver a large number of images and videos, a solution like [imgix](https://imgix.com/?utm_medium=banner&utm_source=smashingmag&utm_campaign=video-api-smashingmag-article-2022-08) can optimize and process both types of assets without you having to build it from the ground up or cobble together different solutions. Let’s take a closer look at how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Doug Sillars)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Dual Boot Windows 10 and Ubuntu – Linux Dual Booting Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-dual-boot-windows-10-and-ubuntu-linux-dual-booting-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-dual-boot-windows-10-and-ubuntu-linux-dual-booting-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T20:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You don’t have to have two different computers to use Linux and Windows 10. It's possible to have a Linux distro installed on a computer with Windows 10 preinstalled. In this article, I will show you how to dual boot Windows 10 and the popular Ubuntu Linux distro. But before]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Python Concepts to Know Before Learning Data Science]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/top-python-concepts-for-data-science/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/top-python-concepts-for-data-science/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T17:53:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're interested in learning data science, you've likely heard the buzzword  "Python,". It's a popular programming language often used in data science.  But Python is a general-purpose programming language. This means that it's not limited to data science alone. You can use it to develop web and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ibrahim Abayomi Ogunbiyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend Web Developer 21-Hour Bootcamp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/frontend-web-developer-bootcamp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/frontend-web-developer-bootcamp/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T17:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a lot of jobs available for frontend web developers. And you can learn all the skills you need to know without paying anything. You probably already know about freeCodeCamp's free interactive curriculum [https://freecodecamp.org] that will teach you the skills you need to become a fullstack web developer. But]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Date Format – How to Format a Date in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-date-format-how-to-format-a-date-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-date-format-how-to-format-a-date-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T15:25:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is one of the three fundamental web technologies you'll use when developing websites or web applications. When creating these web pages, you will, at some point, likely need to use dates for some reason – such as displaying when something was uploaded, stored, and so on. In this article,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an OTP Input in Vue 3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-otp-input-vue-3/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-otp-input-vue-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T15:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OTP inputs are one of the most fun components you can use in your app. They make the dry process of filling in yet another form a little more engaging. In this article, you’ll learn how to build an OTP input from scratch in Vue 3. By the end of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Akinyemi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using CSS Cascade Layers to Manage Custom Styles in a Tailwind Project]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372576</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-css-cascade-layers-to-manage-custom-styles-in-a-tailwind-project/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T13:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If a utility class only does one thing, chances are you don’t want it to be overridden by any styles coming from elsewhere. One approach is to use !important to be 100% certain the style will be applied, regardless of …
Using CSS Cascade Layers to Manage Custom Styles in a Tailwind Project originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Linux Utilities to Improve Your Programming Workflow in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/5-linux-utilities-for-better-programming-workflow/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/5-linux-utilities-for-better-programming-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T11:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working as a Software Developer, there are always new tools and frameworks coming out that can completely change your workflows – for the better (or worse?).  Either way, there is always the possibility to optimize how you do things day-to-day. This article contains some Linux utilities that have recently]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rishabh Rawat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.gitignore File – How to Ignore Files and Folders in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gitignore-file-how-to-ignore-files-and-folders-in-git/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gitignore-file-how-to-ignore-files-and-folders-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T16:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a popular version control system. It is how developers can collaborate and work together on projects. Git allows you to track the changes you make to your project over time. On top of that, it lets you revert to a previous version if you want to undo a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Python in Power BI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-in-powerbi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-in-powerbi/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T16:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Power BI is a business analytics tool which allows users to gain insight from their data.  You can easily create an interactive dashboard by just dragging and dropping data columns into the visualization plane. In this article, I'll show you how to use Python to help you leverage]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yannawut Kimnaruk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chart.js Tutorial – How to Make Bar and Line Charts in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-bar-and-line-charts-using-chartjs-in-angular/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-bar-and-line-charts-using-chartjs-in-angular/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T15:35:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial we will learn how to create simple bar and line charts using the Chart.js library in an Angular application. But first of all, what is Chart.js and what does it do? What is Chart.js? Chart.js is a JavaScript library for building charts. It's designed to be intuitive]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Swatej Patil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Arrays.binarySearch() in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-arrays-binarysearch-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-arrays-binarysearch-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T15:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'm going to show you how to use the Arrays.binarySearch()  method in Java. What is Arrays.binarySearch() in Java?  According to the official docs [https://docs.oracle.com/javase/7/docs/api/java/util/Arrays.html#binarySearch(byte[],%20byte)]  on the Arrays.binarySearch() method: > (It) Searches the specified array of bytes for the specified value using the binary search]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farhan Hasin Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Override Root Font Size to Create a Better User Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/override-root-font-size-for-a-better-user-experience/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/override-root-font-size-for-a-better-user-experience/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T15:14:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in the day, web developers, front-end engineers, and UI designers had a bit of an easier job. This is because they weren't expected to rearrange their code and designs to fit so many different screen sizes.  But in today's world, if you make a decision that doesn't take]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damla Erkiner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Removing jQuery from GOV.UK]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372485</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/removing-jquery-from-gov-uk/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T13:04:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GOV.UK team recently published “How and why we removed jQuery from GOV.UK“. This was an insightful look at how an organization can assess its tooling and whether something is still the best tool for the job. This …
Removing jQuery from GOV.UK originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Kouchi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 51 With Ben Callahan: What’s The Value Of A Design System?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/smashing-podcast-episode-51/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/smashing-podcast-episode-51/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we ask how you can prove the value of a Design System and how you can pitch it effectively to stakeholders. Vitaly talks to Ben Callahan to find out more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Markdown Cheat Sheet – How to Write Articles in Markdown Language]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/markdown-cheatsheet/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/markdown-cheatsheet/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T22:16:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a developer, you have likely heard of HTML [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTML], which stands for HyperText Markup L anguage. And you may know that HTML is a language used to create websites – but what does  markup mean? Markup languages [https://techterms.com/definition/markup_language] are languages that use tags to define different elements within]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kealan Parr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Generate WordPress Posts Automatically with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-generate-wordpress-posts-automatically/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-generate-wordpress-posts-automatically/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T20:55:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you run a website, you are aware of the importance of content. It's important for your web presence, to help you be recognized as a leader in your field, to improve your SEO ranking, to increase your audience, and more. WordPress is one of the most popular and widely-used]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Venturi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Round to 2 Decimal Places in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-round-to-2-decimal-places-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-round-to-2-decimal-places-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T17:17:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python provides many math methods for mathematical operations such as square roots, exponents, and so on. In this article, I will show you how to round up a number to a specified decimal place. What is a Decimal Place? Look at this number: 324.89. Each number here has a position]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize Your Node.js API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-optimize-nodejs-apis/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-optimize-nodejs-apis/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T17:16:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will walk you through some of the best methods to optimize APIs written in Node.js. Prerequisites To get the most out of this article, you will need an understanding of the following concepts:  * Node.js setup and installation  * How to build APIs with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kayode Adeniyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming Naming Conventions – Camel, Snake, Kebab, and Pascal Case Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/programming-naming-conventions-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/programming-naming-conventions-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T15:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've been programming for a while, you may have heard the words "camel case" or "pascal case". And maybe you're wondering what those terms mean. Well, let me explain. What are Naming Conventions in Programming? Apart from the hard and fast rules that we get with every programming language,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farhan Hasin Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Developer Certification (AZ-204) – Pass the Exam With This Free 13.5-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/azure-developer-certification-az-204-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-13-5-hour-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/azure-developer-certification-az-204-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-13-5-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T14:51:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can learn everything you need to know to earn the Azure Developer Certification by completing this free 13-hour course. What is Microsoft Azure Developer Associate? The Microsoft Azure Developer Associate (commonly known as the AZ-204) is a Microsoft Azure certification focused on building web-applications on-top of Azure cloud services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Brown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Grid and Custom Shapes, Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372396</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-grid-and-custom-shapes-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T14:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alright, so the last time we checked in, we were using CSS Grid and combining them with CSS clip-path and mask techniques to create grids with fancy shapes.
Here’s just one of the fantastic grids we made together:
CodePen…
CSS Grid and Custom Shapes, Part 2 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Makes A Great Toggle Button? (Case Study, Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/toggle-button-case-study-part-1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/toggle-button-case-study-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this first part of a two-part article, Eduard Kuric analyzes the characteristics of effective toggle buttons that make it error-proof and prevent confusion and frustration of users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eduard Kuric)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement a GameKit Leaderboard in SwiftUI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-a-leaderboard-in-swiftui/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-a-leaderboard-in-swiftui/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T21:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article we will talk about why and how to implement the GameCenter's Leaderboard [https://developer.apple.com/design/human-interface-guidelines/technologies/game-center/leaderboards/]  within your app.  Why GameCenter is Making a Huge Revival You can make iPhone games without a scoreboard, but leaderboards can help make the game feel more competitive, like people are competing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saamer Mansoor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Graph Theory to Build a More Sustainable World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-value-of-graph-theory-within-sustainability/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-value-of-graph-theory-within-sustainability/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T20:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discrete mathematics is an area of mathematical knowledge based on the study of formal structures whose nature is fundamentally separate and distinct.  This means it focuses on integers and natural sets of numbers, shapes, and other objects that can be counted finitely or distinguished from one another. It models]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel García Solla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Refactor to Configurable Dependency in 5 Steps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/refactoring-to-configurable-dependency-in-5-steps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/refactoring-to-configurable-dependency-in-5-steps/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T20:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Configurable Dependency, also known as Dependency Injection, is a pattern that enables you to switch dependencies of your application. The term [https://web.archive.org/web/20170624023207/http://alistair.cockburn.us/Configurable+Dependency]  was coined by Alistair Cockburn. Say your application has a GUI. But your administrator wants to use certain functions via the console. Or your production code calls]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bertil Muth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Timestamp – How to Use getTime() to Generate Timestamps in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-timestamp-how-to-use-gettime-to-generate-timestamps-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-timestamp-how-to-use-gettime-to-generate-timestamps-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T17:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, timestamps are usually associated with Unix time [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Unix_time]. And there are different methods for generating such timestamps. When we make use of the different JavaScript methods for generating timestamps, they return the number of milliseconds that has passed since 1 January 1970 UTC (the Unix time).  In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing A Reset Password Feature With Next.js Dynamic Routes]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/implementing-reset-password-feature-nextjs-dynamic-routes/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/implementing-reset-password-feature-nextjs-dynamic-routes/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most users tend to forget their passwords, so create experiences that will always be valuable for people when they use your products. In this article, we’ll discuss how to implement a password-reset feature with Next.js dynamic routes while prioritizing the UX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Caleb Olojo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I Learned Speaking at VueConf US 2022 – Tech Conference Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-i-learned-speaking-at-vueconf-us/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-i-learned-speaking-at-vueconf-us/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T19:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year I had the honor of speaking at VueConf US 2022 [https://us.vuejs.org/]  and I thought I would share my experience.  Part of this article will cover my personal process, part will look at VueConf specifically, and the rest will be about the conference at large. I hope]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Austin Gil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Calculate Percentage in Excel – Formula for Percentages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-calculate-percentage-in-excel-formula-for-percentages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-calculate-percentage-in-excel-formula-for-percentages/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T17:44:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A percentage is a kind of fraction saying how many parts over 100 something is. In this article you will see in detail what a percentage is, and how to calculate a percentage in Excel. First, before diving into how it works in Excel, let's take a look at the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilenia Magoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Revert File – Reverting a File to a Previous Commit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-revert-file-reverting-a-file-to-a-previous-commit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-revert-file-reverting-a-file-to-a-previous-commit/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T15:39:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a version control system that helps teams and individuals track and record changes made to a file or an entire project. When working with Git, you often commit your changes and then push them to a remote repository. Suppose you have made a lot of commits and later]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discord Update Failed – How to Fix the Error on a Windows 10 PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/discord-update-failed-how-to-fix-the-error-on-a-windows-10-pc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/discord-update-failed-how-to-fix-the-error-on-a-windows-10-pc/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T15:31:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discord is a popular chat app for gamers and anyone else who wants to create an online community. Despite its popularity, one major problem users report about Discord is the update failed loop. Discord has to update often because the Discord team implements new features and bug fixes regularly. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Structural Directive Patterns – What They Are and How to Use Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/angular-structural-directive-patterns-what-they-are-and-how-to-use-them/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/angular-structural-directive-patterns-what-they-are-and-how-to-use-them/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T15:21:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two types of  directives in Angular. Attribute directives modify the appearance or behavior of DOM elements. Structural directives add or remove elements from the DOM. Structural directives are one of the most powerful features of Angular, and yet they’re frequently misunderstood.  If you’re interested in learning more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code Refactoring Best Practices – with Python Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-practices-for-refactoring-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-practices-for-refactoring-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T15:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will discuss what code refactoring is. We'll go over why you need to refactor your code, the advantages of code refactoring, and some best practices for code refactoring. What is Code Refactoring? Refactoring means organizing your code without modifying its original functionality. Refactoring is the process]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Fagbuyiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Flatten an Array in JavaScript Using Recursion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flatten-array-recursion/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flatten-array-recursion/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T15:11:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we'll go through a common coding problem that interviewers love to ask candidates. Hopefully this will help you understand how to think through it and solve it. Let's begin by understanding the problem. You are given an array which contains numbers and nested arrays of numbers. Your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adwaith KS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn C Programming Using the Classic Book by Kernighan and Ritchie]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-c-programming-classic-book-dr-chuck/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-c-programming-classic-book-dr-chuck/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T14:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dennis Ritchie created the C programming language. He also co-authored the authoritative reference book on C programming with Brian Kernighan. If you want to truly understand C programming, it is a good idea to go straight to the source. We just published a C programming course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>