<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-04-02T01:06:44.565Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin VS Java – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kotlin-vs-java-whats-the-difference/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kotlin-vs-java-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T20:21:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Java is a widely popular programming language that has been used for years in various domains, including web development, mobile app development, desktop applications, and game development.  On the other hand, Kotlin is a relatively new programming language that has been gaining popularity in recent years. Both languages are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insertion Sort Algorithm - Most Asked Questions About Insertion Sort]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/most-asked-questions-about-insertion-sort-algorithm/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/most-asked-questions-about-insertion-sort-algorithm/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T19:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sorting algorithms are an essential part of computer science. There are many sorting algorithms used to sort data. The insertion sort algorithm is one of the most basic and simple sorting algorithms. It is an efficient algorithm for small input sizes or for partially sorted data. The algorithm works by]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Paraphrasing Tool with ReactJs & ChatGPT Turbo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-paraphrasing-tool-with-reactjs-chatgpt-turbo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-paraphrasing-tool-with-reactjs-chatgpt-turbo/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T17:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a world where online content is growing exponentially, it's more important than ever to produce unique content that stands out. Paraphrasing tools can offer a quick solution to help you develop unique ideas and create original content. With the help of ReactJs and ChatGPT Turbo, developers can build a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Idris Olubisi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JS Sum of an Array – How to Add the Numbers in a JavaScript Array]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-numbers-in-javascript-arrays/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-numbers-in-javascript-arrays/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T17:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An array in JavaScript is an object that allows you to store an ordered collection of multiple values under a single variable name and manipulate those values in numerous ways. In this article, you will learn how to calculate the sum of all the numbers in a given array using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comments Inside JSON – Commenting in a JSON File]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/comments-in-json/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/comments-in-json/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T15:10:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JSON (JavaScript Object Notation) is a popular data interchange format used in web development and mobile applications due to its simplicity and flexibility. But JSON files do not officially support comments. This makes providing additional context or explanation for the data challenging. This article will show you how to include]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Include an Empty String in RegEx]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-include-empty-string-in-regex/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-include-empty-string-in-regex/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T11:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regular expressions (RegEx or RegExp for short) are a sequence of characters that define a search pattern. You can use them to search, replace, and validate the strings of a text in a wide variety of applications, such as text editors, developer tools, and command line tools. RegEx is also]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swing Into April (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With April just around the corner, we have a new collection of desktop and mobile wallpapers waiting for you to celebrate the beginning of the new month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, the wallpapers come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use an Email Validation Service for Flask User Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-email-validation-api-for-flask-user-authentication/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-email-validation-api-for-flask-user-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T22:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital world, online security is really important, and user authentication is a key aspect of it.  Email-based authentication [https://ashutoshkrris.hashnode.dev/how-to-set-up-email-verification-in-a-flask-app]  is one of the most popular and widely used methods for user registration and login. But it's not always reliable, as users can enter fake or invalid]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Integrate Chart.js in Angular Using Data from a REST API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-integrate-chart-js-in-angular-using-data-from-a-rest-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-integrate-chart-js-in-angular-using-data-from-a-rest-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T15:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Charts are a great way of visually displaying large sets of data in formats that are easy to understand and analyze. They are a great way of showing the relationship that exists between two or more data sets.  Different types of charts exist, some of which includes bar chart,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deji Adesoga</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Bubble Sort Algorithm With JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-bubble-sort-algorithm-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-bubble-sort-algorithm-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T15:34:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sorting is an essential task in programming, and the bubble sort algorithm is one of the simplest and most commonly used methods. As a beginner in solving algorithm questions or preparing for an interview, you might wonder how to implement this algorithm effectively. Don't worry; in this article, I will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use ChatGPT to Build a Low Code RegEx Generator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-chatgpt-to-build-a-regex-generator/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-chatgpt-to-build-a-regex-generator/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T13:33:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you tired of spending hours writing complex Regular Expressions (RegEx) to manipulate strings? Do you want to learn how to build a RegEx generator quickly and easily? Then this course is for you! We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you build a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Regular Expressions in CTRL F]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-you-use-regular-expression-in-ctrl-f/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-you-use-regular-expression-in-ctrl-f/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T13:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The conventional CTRL + F does not support Regex in many software tools we use in our day-to-day lives. But almost nothing is impossible in the tech world. Many of these software tools, such as VS Code, Chrome browser, Dreamweaver, Jetbrains, and others, have a built-in mechanism that supports RegEx]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Organizing Design Workshops: A Detailed Checklist]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/organizing-design-workshops-checklist/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/organizing-design-workshops-checklist/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workshops are all about people: they involve people, are conducted by people, and aim to close the gaps in people’s communication. Slava Shestopalov shares a checklist with everything you need to keep in mind when running a workshop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Slava Shestopalov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does :: Mean in Python? Operator Meaning for Double Colon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-mean-in-python-operator-meaning-for-double-colon/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-mean-in-python-operator-meaning-for-double-colon/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T07:21:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use the double colon (::) in Python to slice or extract elements in a collection such as a list or string. In this article, you'll learn the syntax and how to use :: to slice a list in Python. You'll also learn how to use the parameters associated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code a Simple Game and Host it on Your Website]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-a-simple-game/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-a-simple-game/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T23:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wanted to create your own game to share with others on your website? In this article, we'll be learning how to code a simple game using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, and then host it on your website.  The game we'll be coding is a classic word-guessing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Duggan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build and Push Dockerized Applications to the Azure Registry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-and-push-dockerized-applications-to-azure-registry/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-and-push-dockerized-applications-to-azure-registry/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T21:53:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A common issue on development teams is that an application might work on one developer’s computer but not on the others. Luckily, there's Docker, a popular containerization technology. It works by packing up all the components needed to run the application and then executing the application in an isolated environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Destiny Erhabor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the React Context API in Your Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/context-api-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/context-api-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T20:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing state is an essential part of developing applications in React. A common way to manage state is by passing props. Passing props means sending data from one component to another. It's a good way to make sure that data gets to the right place in a React application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dickson Boateng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Google Apps Script Code to Clear Data Ranges in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-apps-script-to-clear-data-in-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-apps-script-to-clear-data-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T19:55:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Apps Script allows you to write code in your spreadsheet. It functions like Visual Basic for Applications (VBA) does in Excel. They're both incredibly useful for executing more complicated actions or for automating repetitive tasks. In this article, I'll give you a brief overview of Google Apps Script by]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is the Second Argument in JSON.stringify() usually null?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-is-the-second-argument-in-json-stringify-usually-undefined/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-is-the-second-argument-in-json-stringify-usually-undefined/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T17:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Usually, when developers use the JSON.stringify() method, the second argument is usually skipped, or with a value null. But this argument has its relevance. Here's a common example usage of JSON.stringify(): const obj = {   name: "Dillion",   language: "JavaScript",   age: 100,   isEngineer:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software Engineering Job Interview – Full Mock Interview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/real-world-coding-interview-for-software-engineering/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/real-world-coding-interview-for-software-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T14:28:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you preparing for a technical programming interview for a software engineering role? If so, you might want to check out this new informative video, which features a mock full-length, real-world coding technical interview. This is a full-length interview between Keith Gali and Kylie Ying. Keith, who is an experienced]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slicing and Indexing in Python – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/slicing-and-indexing-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/slicing-and-indexing-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T14:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slicing and indexing are two fundamental concepts in Python. They help you access specific elements in a sequence, such as a list, tuple or string.  By using these techniques, you can extract substrings from strings, filter lists, and extract columns from 2D lists, among other things.  Understanding how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-Grained Access Handling And Data Management With Row-Level Security]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/access-handling-data-management-row-level-security/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/access-handling-data-management-row-level-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with sensitive data is an important topic for any app. In this article, you will find out how to handle sensitive or confidential information in your apps and what Row-Level Security means.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter App Development – Create a Twitter Clone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flutter-app-development-create-a-twitter-clone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flutter-app-development-create-a-twitter-clone/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T20:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking to improve your Flutter skills and build a fully-functional Twitter clone? We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Flutter, Appwrite, and Riverpod to create a Twitter clone. Rivaan Ranawat created this course. He is an expereinced course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a 3D Element in Your React Site]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/3d-react-webgi-threejs-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/3d-react-webgi-threejs-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T20:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you interested in learning how to build a 3D animation using React? We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to add 3D elements into your React websites. Slobodan Gajic created this course. He is a senior fullstack developer and popular]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix Merge Conflicts in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fix-merge-conflicts-in-git/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fix-merge-conflicts-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T20:25:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever worked on a team that's working on a large codebase, you’ve likely experienced merge conflicts while creating a pull request or merging two branches. Even if you’ve never worked with a team or on a large codebase, it is still possible to have merge conflicts as long]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Iterate Over Rows with Pandas – Loop Through a Dataframe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-iterate-over-rows-with-pandas-loop-through-a-dataframe/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-iterate-over-rows-with-pandas-loop-through-a-dataframe/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T18:35:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article provides a comprehensive guide on how to loop through a Pandas DataFrame in Python.  I'll start by introducing the Pandas library and DataFrame data structure. I'll explain the essential characteristics of Pandas, how to loop through rows in a dataframe, and finally how to loop through columns]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Website Encryption Works]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-website-encryption/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-website-encryption/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T17:35:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's one thing to protect your data when it's sitting quietly on your own local machine and not bothering anyone. But moving data between locations – as you do whenever you open a website on a remote server or send an email attachment across the internet – introduces a whole]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Get Current Directory – Print Working Directory PWD Equivalent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-get-current-directory/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-get-current-directory/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T16:27:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to get the current working directory (another name for folder) in Python, which is the equivalent of using the pwd  command. There are a couple of ways to get the current working directory in Python:  * By using the os module]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use GitHub Actions to  Automate Open-Source Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-open-source-projects-with-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-open-source-projects-with-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T15:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, developers use automation tools all the time to manage tasks effectively and streamline their daily activities. And one of these popular tools is GitHub Actions. When talking about software, including the open-source variety, you'll likely agree with me that efficiency is in high demand. And with the help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hillary Nyakundi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is R Squared? R2 Value Meaning and Definition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-r-squared-r2-value-meaning-and-definition/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-r-squared-r2-value-meaning-and-definition/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T14:51:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regression analysis is a statistical method used to study the relationship between a dependent variable and one or more independent variables.  One of the most commonly used methods for linear regression analysis is R-Squared.  In this article, you'll get to know what R-Squared is and the meaning of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to replace links in a text with Anchor Tags using JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-replace-links-in-a-text-with-anchor-tags-using-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-replace-links-in-a-text-with-anchor-tags-using-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T10:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you make a post on social media, and that post contains links, you would see the links styled differently from other text. How can you achieve this? For example, here's a tweet I made on Twitter The text for my tweet is: > hi good morning my website is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn React by Building a Mortgage Calculator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-mortgage-calculator-tutorial-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-mortgage-calculator-tutorial-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T22:56:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we will learn and practice ReactJs by building a mortgage calculator step by step. This is the project that we will build today 👇  * Heres a live demo of the project    [https://mortgage-calculator-tutorial.vercel.app/]  * And here's the Github Repo Link    [https://github.com/JoyShaheb/mortgage-calculator-tutorial]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joy Shaheb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Setup a CI/CD Pipeline for a Next.js App using AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ci-cd-pipeline-for-nextjs-app-with-aws/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ci-cd-pipeline-for-nextjs-app-with-aws/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T21:53:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Everyone! Deploying a web application is a challenging task (at least for me), especially when it comes to keeping it updated. It can take up a lot of time and energy if it has to be deployed manually every time you make a change.  But I recently discovered]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Array Tutorial – Array Methods in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-array-tutorial-array-methods-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-array-tutorial-array-methods-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T19:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arrays are data structures that are extremely useful and versatile. They're present in many programming languages, and they allow you to store multiple values in a single variable. In this tutorial, we will explore how arrays work in JavaScript, their characteristics, and how to manipulate them using the most common]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dario Di Cillo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dataframe Drop Column in Pandas – How to Remove Columns from Dataframes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dataframe-drop-column-in-pandas-how-to-remove-columns-from-dataframes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dataframe-drop-column-in-pandas-how-to-remove-columns-from-dataframes/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T18:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Pandas, sometimes you'll need to remove columns from a DataFrame for various reasons, such as cleaning data, reducing memory usage, or simplifying analysis. And in this article, I'll show you how to do it. I'll start by introducing the .drop() method, which is the primary method for removing columns]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create and Sync Git and GitHub Repositories]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-and-sync-git-and-github-repositories/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-and-sync-git-and-github-repositories/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T17:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working with Git and GitHub is often an essential part of your daily programming tasks. In many cases, you'll want both a local Git repository and a remote GitHub repository for a project.  * With the local repository, you work on your own copy of the project. You make]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Kurata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Instal ChatGPT in VSCode]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/install-chatgpt-in-vscode/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/install-chatgpt-in-vscode/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T17:50:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT – or Chat Generative Pre-Training Transformer – has been making waves in the tech industry recently.  It was first launched in November 2022 and upgraded to ChatGPT-4 in March 2023. In this tutorial, I will explain how you can use ChatGPT to become more productive. Then I'll walk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Measure and Improve the Performance of a React App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/measure-and-improve-performance-of-react-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/measure-and-improve-performance-of-react-apps/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T17:18:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! React is a popular JavaScript library for building user interfaces. As applications built with React become more complex, their performance can start to degrade.  Poor performance can lead to a frustrating user experience and a negative impact on user engagement. So in this article, we will discuss]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up AWS Simple Email Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-aws-simple-email-service/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-aws-simple-email-service/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T15:44:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're looking for a reliable and cost-effective way to send emails, AWS Simple Email Service (SES) is a great option. It's a cloud-based email platform that helps you send and receive emails quickly and easily.  With SES, you don't have to worry about managing your mail server, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Iroegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Handoff Is No Handoff]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/best-handoff-is-no-handoff/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/best-handoff-is-no-handoff/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design handoffs are inefficient and painful. They cause frustration, friction and a lot of back and forth. Can we avoid them altogether? Of course we can! Let’s see how to do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn Different Tech Stacks IRL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-learn-different-tech-stacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-learn-different-tech-stacks/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-25T17:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last couple years, I've learned that being a consultant means you have to be able to learn new things quickly. At first, this was really scary to me. Now, as someone who has had to learn several new tech stacks over the last year, it’s still a little]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dataframe to CSV – How to Save Pandas Dataframes by Exporting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dataframe-to-csv-how-to-save-pandas-dataframes-by-exporting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dataframe-to-csv-how-to-save-pandas-dataframes-by-exporting/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T18:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pandas is a widely used open-source library in Python for data manipulation and analysis. It provides a range of data structures and functions for working with data, one of which is the DataFrame.  DataFrames are a powerful tool for storing and analyzing large sets of data, but they can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Scroll Animations to a Page with JavaScript's Intersection Observer API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/scroll-animations-with-javascript-intersection-observer-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/scroll-animations-with-javascript-intersection-observer-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T17:42:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, when you visit a website, you'll notice that certain elements or a particular section gets revealed dynamically as you scroll.  It's like the contents of that particular section weren't available to view until you scrolled into the section – but now, because you're there, the website decides to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mwendwa Bundi Emma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Where Contains String – Substring Query Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-where-contains-string-substring-query-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-where-contains-string-substring-query-example/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T22:36:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re working with a database, whether large or small, there might be occasions when you need to search for some entries containing strings. In this article, I’ll show you how to locate strings and substrings in MySQL and SQL Server. I‘ll be using a table I call products_data in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Reveal on Scroll in React using the Intersection Observer API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/reveal-on-scroll-in-react-using-the-intersection-observer-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/reveal-on-scroll-in-react-using-the-intersection-observer-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T22:20:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking for an elegant way to reveal content on your React website as users scroll down the page? Look no further than the Intersection Observer API. In this article, you’ll learn how to implement the reveal on scroll effect in React using Intersection Observer. This will allow you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Remove from List – How to Remove an Item from a List in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-remove-from-list-how-to-remove-an-item-from-a-list-in-python-2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-remove-from-list-how-to-remove-an-item-from-a-list-in-python-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T18:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A list in Python is a collection of items that are ordered and changeable. It is one of the most versatile and frequently used data structures in Python.  A list can contain any type of data, such as integers, strings, floats, and even other lists. In Python, lists are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Undo Git Add – How to Remove Added Files in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/undo-git-add-how-to-remove-added-files-in-git/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/undo-git-add-how-to-remove-added-files-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T18:27:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a powerful version control and collaboration tool. It allows developers to work together seamlessly on projects. But even the most experienced developers can make mistakes while using Git, such as accidentally adding files that were not meant to be committed. This can be a problem, especially if the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overcoming The Challenges Of Content Creation For Informational Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/overcoming-challenges-content-creation-informational-websites/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/overcoming-challenges-content-creation-informational-websites/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content matters! Unfortunately, when it comes to informational websites, content quality is often poor. There is no magic answer to fix that. However, there are practical techniques you can use to improve the copy on your websites and ensure your users find the content they are looking for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a Directory in Python – How to Create a Folder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/creating-a-directory-in-python-how-to-create-a-folder/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/creating-a-directory-in-python-how-to-create-a-folder/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T13:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to create new directories (which is another name for folders) in Python. You will also learn how to create a nested directory structure. To work with directories in Python, you first need to include the os module in your project, which allows you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Vite to Speed Up Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-vite-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-vite-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T13:20:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vite is a powerful build tool and development server designed to speed up modern web development. We just published a full Vite course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Vite effectively and efficiently to streamline your web development workflow. Arsalan Khattak developed this course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started in Data Analytics – A Roadmap for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-analytics-roadmap/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-analytics-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T00:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello and welcome to the world of data analysis! If you're considering a career in this field, you're in good company. Data analysis is a growing and exciting field that's becoming increasingly important in today's data-driven world. Let's face it, we're all drowning in data these days. From social media]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Squash Commits – Squashing the Last N Commits into One Commit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-squash-commits/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-squash-commits/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T23:16:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are working on a project and trying to implement a new feature, you might commit your code a few times to test things out. This lets you see how the code works or looks. While doing this, things might get messy because you now have several commits, even]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Cross-Browser DevTools Features You Might Not Know]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377264</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-cross-browser-devtools-features-you-might-not-know/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T20:22:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I spend a lot of time in DevTools, and I’m sure you do too. Sometimes I even bounce between them, especially when I’m debugging cross-browser issues. DevTools is a lot like browsers themselves — not all of the features in …
Some Cross-Browser DevTools Features You Might Not Know originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pankaj Parashar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CRM App Development with Django, Python, and MySQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crm-app-development-with-django-python-and-mysql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crm-app-development-with-django-python-and-mysql/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T19:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you interested in learning how to build a customer relationship management (CRM) app with Django, Python, and MySQL? We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will guide you step-by-step on how to build a fully-functional CRM application using Django, Python, and MySQL. John Elder developed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Print Newline in Python – Printing a New Line]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/print-newline-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/print-newline-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T19:17:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working with strings or text data in programming frequently involves printing a newline. The end of a line is indicated by a newline character, which also advances the cursor to the start of the following line. Using the escape character "\n," we can print a newline in Python. Other programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Variables – The Complete Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-variables/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-variables/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T18:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Variables are an essential part of Python. They allow us to easily store, manipulate, and reference data throughout our projects. This article will give you all the understanding of Python variables you need to use them effectively in your projects. If you want the most convenient way to review all]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Prevent Account Loss When using Two-Factor Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-prevent-account-loss-when-using-two-factor-authentication/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-prevent-account-loss-when-using-two-factor-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T16:28:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If someone gains unauthorized access to your passwords, two-factor authentication (2FA) can prevent them from accessing your account.  But if you ever lose access to all your 2FA methods, you have lost your account. How do you prevent such loss? In this article, we will look at two-factor authentication]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Obumuneme Nwabude</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Incorporate Cybersecurity Audits into Your Workflow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/incorporate-cybersecurity-audits-into-your-workflow/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/incorporate-cybersecurity-audits-into-your-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T16:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The word "audit" describes any process designed to review and assess a system's current state, capacity, and integrity.  An internal audit is a review process initiated and carried out by an organization itself. External audits are often performed by or on behalf of banking entities or government regulatory bodies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The freeCodeCamp Mobile App – Learn to Code Right On Your Phone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-mobile-app-curriculum-update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-mobile-app-curriculum-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T12:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am happy to announce that the freeCodeCamp mobile app is finally ready for you to download. 🎊 The mobile development team just pushed a big update with many helpful improvements, including the much-awaited /learn user experience. You can now code your way through the Responsive Web Design curriculum and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sem Bauke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What does => Mean in JavaScript? The Equals Greater Than Symbol aka Hashrocket Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-the-hashrocket-symbol-mean-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-the-hashrocket-symbol-mean-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T22:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prior to the introduction of arrow functions, function expressions in JavaScript had a verbose syntax that often made code harder to read and understand.  As a more concise way of writing function expressions in JavaScript, arrow functions were introduced in ECMAScript 6 (ES6). They quickly gained popularity among developers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Social Engineering Explained – 10 Types of Social Engineering Cyberattacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/modern-social-engineering-cyberattacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/modern-social-engineering-cyberattacks/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T22:03:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever received a suspicious email or phone call from an unknown number asking for information? Or clicked on that link promising discount deals but ended up entering sensitive information? Chances are you were a victim of a social engineering attack. Social engineering is a manipulation technique used by]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript if Statements, Equality and Truthy/Falsy – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-if-statement-equality-and-truthy-falsy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-if-statement-equality-and-truthy-falsy/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T21:06:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decisions, decisions, decisions. Go left? Or go right? In programming, we use an  if statement when we want our code to make a decision. In this tutorial, we'll deep dive into the JavaScript if statement. Along the way, we'll examine the difference between single equals, double equals, and triple]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Kurata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chart.js Tutorial – How to Make Marimekko Charts in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chart-js-tutorial-how-to-make-marimekko-charts-in-angular/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chart-js-tutorial-how-to-make-marimekko-charts-in-angular/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T17:51:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data visualization is an essential part of data analysis. And charts are one of the most effective ways to present data in a clear and concise manner.  Marimekko charts are an excellent choice for displaying complex data sets in a compact and visually appealing format.  A Marimekko chart,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Swatej Patil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced SQL Techniques for Complex Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-sql-techniques/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-sql-techniques/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T17:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Structured Query Language or SQL is an effective tool for managing and modifying data that is stored in databases.  The SELECT, INSERT, UPDATE, and DELETE SQL commands are suitable for many common use cases. But sometimes, more sophisticated techniques can help you perform out more complex queries and analyses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use OpenAI Gymnasium for Reinforcement Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-openai-gymnasium-for-reinforcement-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-openai-gymnasium-for-reinforcement-learning/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T14:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Embark on an exciting journey to learn the fundamentals of reinforcement learning and its implementation using Gymnasium, the open-source Python library previously known as OpenAI Gym. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you the basics of reinforcement learning using Gymnasium. Mustafa Esoofally]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 58 With Debbie Levitt: What Is CX Design?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/smashing-podcast-episode-58/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/smashing-podcast-episode-58/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we ask what is Customer Experience design, and how does it differ from User Experience design? Vitaly Friedman talks to expert Debbie Levitt to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Developers Can Prevent Fraud and Stop Scammers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-developers-can-prevent-fraud-and-stop-scammers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-developers-can-prevent-fraud-and-stop-scammers/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T22:32:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Online frauds and scams have shot past projections in the last decade, and no one seems to be immune to them—including developers.  The shift to serverless cloud management has opened doors for hackers to try new attack surfaces and the impact is right in front of us. 90% of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dmitry Dragilev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js SEO for Developers – How to Build Highly Performant Apps with Next]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nextjs-seo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nextjs-seo/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T21:17:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js is a popular React-based web framework that has gained popularity and a growing community in recent years. It's a powerful tool for building fast and SEO-friendly web applications with dynamic pages that work great on mobile devices.  Due to the complex nature of isomorphic system design, Next.js SEO]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Operators and Operator Precedence – Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-operators-and-operator-precedence/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-operators-and-operator-precedence/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T21:15:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few months ago, I attempted to solve a math problem in my head before writing it in JavaScript. It was then that I received the most stunning revelation of my career, which was both shocking and eye-opening.  So what did I attempt to do? I made the following]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Franklin Okolie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Basics – How to Work with Strings, Arrays, and Objects in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-basics-strings-arrays-objects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-basics-strings-arrays-objects/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T20:12:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a popular programming language that 78% of developers use. You can build almost anything with JavaScript. The problem is that many developers learn JavaScript in a very short period of time, without understanding some of the most essential features of the language. In this article, we will cover]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Houssein Badra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a platformer game with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-platformer-game-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-platformer-game-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T19:47:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to build a classic platformer game in Python from start to finish? If so, you're in the right place! We just published a video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create a platformer game in Python using the Pygame library. We'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bash Scripting Tutorial – Linux Shell Script and Command Line for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/bash-scripting-tutorial-linux-shell-script-and-command-line-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/bash-scripting-tutorial-linux-shell-script-and-command-line-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T17:35:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Linux, process automation relies heavily on shell scripting. This involves creating a file containing a series of commands that can be executed together. In this article, we'll start with the basics of bash scripting which includes variables, commands, inputs/ outputs, and debugging. We'll also see examples of each along]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[List Flatten in Python – Flattening Nested Lists]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/list-flatten-in-python-flattening-nested-lists/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/list-flatten-in-python-flattening-nested-lists/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T17:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lists are one of the core data structures of Python. Due to their flexibility, there are a lot of things you can do with lists. And one of those things is turning a list of lists into a single list. It is also possible to turn a list of dictionaries,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build React Forms with Formik]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-react-forms-with-formik-library/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-react-forms-with-formik-library/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T16:56:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Form building in React [https://reactjs.org/] can be complex and time-consuming, requiring state management, validation, and error handling.  To simplify this process, the Formik [https://formik.org/] library provides an intuitive solution for building forms in React. Formik has a straightforward API and built-in validation, making collecting and manipulating input data in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Popoola Temitope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Serverless ChatGPT App in 10 Minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-serverless-chatgpt-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-serverless-chatgpt-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T16:52:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since OpenAI released an official API for ChatGPT [https://openai.com/blog/introducing-chatgpt-and-whisper-apis] in March 2023, many developers and entrepreneurs are interested in integrating it into their own business operations.  But some significant barriers remain that make it difficult for them to do this:  * OpenAI provides a simple stateless API]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Yuan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Define Relationships Between Django Models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/django-model-relationships/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/django-model-relationships/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T16:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Django [https://www.djangoproject.com/] is a free and open-source web framework written in Python. It helps with rapid web development and provides out-of-the-box web security. Websites must be able to store and retrieve data from databases. Django makes provisions for this. By default, Django operates a Relational Database Management System.  >]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damilola Oladele</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Fonts For Interface Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/free-fonts-interface-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/free-fonts-interface-designers/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just a few beautiful, well-crafted fonts for headings and body text that you probably haven’t spotted before. Free for personal and commercial use. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Method Overloading vs Method Overriding in Java – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/method-overloading-and-overriding-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/method-overloading-and-overriding-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-17T17:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Java, method overloading and method overriding both refer to creating different methods that share the same name.  While the two concepts share some similarities, they are distinct notions with markedly different use cases. Having a firm grasp of them is important in building strong foundational Java skills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mikael Lassa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Program Examples – Simple Code Examples for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-program-examples-simple-code-examples-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-program-examples-simple-code-examples-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-17T17:09:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Twain said that the secret of getting ahead is getting started. Programming can seem daunting for beginners, but the best way to get started is to dive right in and start writing code.  Simple code examples are a great way for beginners to get their feet wet and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binary Search in C++ – Algorithm Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/binary-search-in-c-algorithm-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/binary-search-in-c-algorithm-example/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-17T16:52:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The binary search algorithm is a divide and conquer algorithm that you can use to search for and find elements in a sorted array.  The algorithm is fast in searching for elements because it removes half of the array every time the search iteration happens.  So instead of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python range() Function Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-range-function-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-range-function-example/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-17T11:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to use the range() function in Python with some code examples along the way. What is the range() Function in Python? range() Function Syntax Breakdown Python's built-in range() function is mainly used when working with for loops – you can use it to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python RegEx Tutorial – How to use RegEx inside lambda Expression]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-regex-tutorial-how-to-use-regex-inside-lambda-expression/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-regex-tutorial-how-to-use-regex-inside-lambda-expression/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-17T09:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s possible to use RegEx inside a lambda function in Python. You can apply this to any Python method or function that takes a function as a parameter. Such functions and methods include filter(), map(), any(), sort(), and more. Keep reading as I show you how to use regular expressions]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Generate Automated Reports from a SQL Database Using Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automating-report-generation-from-sql-databases-using-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automating-report-generation-from-sql-databases-using-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T22:09:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generating reports from SQL databases is a common task in many organizations. But the process can be time-consuming and error-prone, especially if it involves manual data extraction, transformation, and formatting.  In this article, we will explore how to use Python to automate the process of generating reports from SQL]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Visualization in Google Sheets for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-visualization-in-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-visualization-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T20:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spreadsheets are the OG resource for visualizing data with charts and graphs...unless you count chalkboards, I suppose.  Spreadsheets are built to churn through tons of data. And by using a few simple built-in tools, you can glean valuable insights from large chunks of data. gif of "OG" graphicWhen dealing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internationalization In Next.js 13 With React Server Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/internationalization-nextjs-13-react-server-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/internationalization-nextjs-13-react-server-components/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Jan Amann, based on an example of a multilingual app that displays street photography images from Unsplash, explores next-intl to implement all internationalization needs in React Server Components.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jan Amann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an Array in Java – Array Declaration Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-array-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-array-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T19:48:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating and manipulating arrays is an essential skill for any Java programmer. Arrays provide a way to store and organize multiple values of the same type, making it easier to work with large sets of data. In this article, we will provide a step-by-step guide on how to create an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lambda Sorted in Python – How to Lambda Sort a List]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/lambda-sort-list-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/lambda-sort-list-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T19:37:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sort() method and the sorted() function let you sort iterable data like lists and tuples in ascending or descending order. They take parameters with which you can modify how they perform the sorting. And one of those parameters could be a function or even a lambda function. In this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Grid Handbook – Complete Guide to Grid Containers and Grid Items]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-guide-to-css-grid/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-guide-to-css-grid/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T18:19:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Grid gives you the tools to create basic and advanced website layouts in responsive ways that look great on mobile, tablet, and desktop devices. This tutorial discusses everything you need to know to use CSS Grid like a pro. Table of Contents  1.  What Is CSS Grid?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi Sofela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GSoC 2023 Guide – How to Prepare for Google Summer of Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-summer-of-code-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-summer-of-code-guide/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T17:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Summer of Code [https://summerofcode.withgoogle.com/] is an open source program that is managed by Google's Open Source team.  They invite developers to spend their summer contributing to the source code for various different organisations taking part in the program.  There are many organisations that list their project ideas]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhisman Sarkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automate SQL Database Backups Using Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-sql-database-backups-using-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-sql-database-backups-using-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T14:49:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You should back up your SQL database on a regular basis. It's a critical task that helps ensure that your data is always protected.  But manually backing up a database can be time-consuming and error-prone, especially if you have multiple databases to back up.  In this article, we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a SQL Database App with a Windows GUI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-database-app-with-windows-gui/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-database-app-with-windows-gui/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T14:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you interested in learning how to design and use databases for Windows applications? We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create a SQL database application with a Windows graphical interface. Led by Shad Sluiter, a Professor Of Computer Science]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Stack GraphQL With Next.js, Neo4j AuraDB And Vercel]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/full-stack-graphql-nextjs-neo4j-auradb-vercel/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/full-stack-graphql-nextjs-neo4j-auradb-vercel/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, William Lyon explores how to build a full stack GraphQL application that takes advantage of the API Routes feature of Next.js API to combine your GraphQL server and front-end React applications into a single framework.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (William Lyon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Print Exception – How to Try-Except-Print an Error]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-print-exception-how-to-try-except-print-an-error/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-print-exception-how-to-try-except-print-an-error/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T21:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every programming language has its way of handling exceptions and errors, and Python is no exception. Python comes with a built-in try…except syntax with which you can handle errors and stop them from interrupting the running of your program. In this article, you’ll learn how to use that try…except syntax]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternatives to Prettier – Popular Code Linting and Formatting Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/alternatives-to-prettier/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/alternatives-to-prettier/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T17:43:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many programmers hate code formatting because it is tedious and time-consuming. You can spend hours making sure everything is perfect and well-indented.  This is why code formatters are so useful. A code formatter is a tool that formats code according to certain standards. It makes it so you don't]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kamaldeen Lawal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn React 18 with Redux Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-react-18-with-redux-toolkit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-react-18-with-redux-toolkit/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T15:44:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is a popular JavaScript library that is widely used for building dynamic user interfaces. It has gained a lot of popularity over the years due to its flexibility, scalability, and ease of use. If you're a beginner looking to learn React 18 with Redux Toolkit, you're in luck. We]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I uncovered 1700 Coursera Courses that Are Still Completely Free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/coursera-free-online-courses-6d84cdb30da/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/coursera-free-online-courses-6d84cdb30da/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is Coursera Free? At Class Central [https://www.classcentral.com/], we get that question so often that I wrote a guide to answer it [https://www.classcentral.com/report/coursera-signup-for-free/]. Nowadays, most Coursera courses are free to audit. But if you want to complete graded assignments or get a course certificate, you have to pay. Coursera’s entire catalog]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhawal Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Write Quick Sort Algorithm With JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-quick-sort-algorithm-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-quick-sort-algorithm-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T09:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick sort is a widely used sorting algorithm that efficiently sorts an array of elements by dividing it into smaller subarrays based on a chosen pivot element. In this article, we will walk through how to write a quick sort algorithm using JavaScript and explore the key concepts behind the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pip Upgrade – And How to Update Pip and Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pip-upgrade-and-how-to-update-pip-and-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pip-upgrade-and-how-to-update-pip-and-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T21:04:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python is a widely used and powerful programming language that's relatively simple to learn. Python releases patch updates every few months and major updates around once in a year. Because of this, it is always a good idea to update the version of Python you have on your computer. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Vulnerabilities – How Attackers Can Get Your Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cybersecurity-vulnerabilities/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cybersecurity-vulnerabilities/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T18:47:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In order to understand potential threats hanging over your organization, you'll need to understand two things: what dangerous stuff is out there on the internet right now, and what impact it could have were it to actually hit you.  Once you have that information, you'll be in a position]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Functional Programming in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/functional-programming-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/functional-programming-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T17:34:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Functional programming (FP) is a programming paradigm. It emphasizes the use of pure functions that don't have side effects and always return the same output for a given input.  This article explores how to implement FP concepts in Java, including viewing functions as first-class citizens, chaining, and composing them]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sameer Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Simple Login App with Flutter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-simple-login-app-with-flutter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-simple-login-app-with-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T16:39:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter is one of the most popular frameworks for building mobile and desktop applications. And many companies are using it today. This is in part because of its outstanding performance, having a benchmark of 60 Frames Per Second (FPS). This helps it outperform other cross-platform technologies, and it performs better]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joining Lists in Python – How to Concat Lists]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/joining-lists-in-python-how-to-concat-lists/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/joining-lists-in-python-how-to-concat-lists/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T16:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The process of combining two or more strings, lists, or other data structures into a single entity is known as concatenation in programming.  Concatenation produces a new object with all the components of the original objects, arranged in the concatenation order. Concatenation in the context of strings refers to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create and Manipulate Tables in a SQL Database Using Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-and-manipulate-tables-in-a-sql-database-using-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-and-manipulate-tables-in-a-sql-database-using-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T16:28:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python is a powerful programming language that you can use to interact with SQL databases. With the help of Python, you can create, manipulate, and interact with the tables in the SQL database.  In this tutorial, we will be discussing how to create and manipulate tables in a SQL]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Leonardo Da Vinci Can Teach Us About Web Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/leonardo-da-vinci-teach-web-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/leonardo-da-vinci-teach-web-design/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perhaps more than any other person in history, Leonardo da Vinci showed the kind of magic that can happen in the overlap between art and science, where much of web development lives. His methods and outlooks are just as applicable to the web today as they were in Renaissance Italy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Sort Array - How to Sort an Array Accurately]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-sort-javascript-array-accurately/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-sort-javascript-array-accurately/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T15:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In programming, situations that need you to sort data will always arise. When you sort data, you will always want accurate results because failure to get an accurate result can result in malfunctions or bugs within your code. In this article, you will learn how to sort an array in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matplotlib Marker - How To Create a Marker in Matplotlib]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-marker-in-matplotlib/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-marker-in-matplotlib/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T15:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll learn how to use markers in Matplotlib to indicate specific points in a plot.  The marker parameter can be used to create "markers" in a plot. You can specify the shape of the marker by passing a value to the parameter.  Here's what a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Change Legend Font Size in Matplotlib]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-change-legend-fontsize-in-matplotlib/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-change-legend-fontsize-in-matplotlib/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T15:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can modify different properties of a plot — color, size, label, title and so on — when working with Matplotlib.  In this article, you'll learn what a legend is in Matplotlib, and how to use some of its parameters to make your plots more relatable.  You'll then]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hack Summit 2023 – Developer Conference Focused on Blockchain Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hack-summit-2023-developer-conference-focused-on-blockchain-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hack-summit-2023-developer-conference-focused-on-blockchain-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T08:03:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hack Summit is one of the largest online developer conferences in history. Across its 5 events over the past decade, more than 130,000 developers have attended. And this year's event should be no different – filled with opportunities to learn from speakers and expand your professional network. This year, the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Calendars With Accessibility and Internationalization in Mind]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376950</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/making-calendars-with-accessibility-and-internationalization-in-mind/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T13:23:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doing a quick search here on CSS-Tricks shows just how many different ways there are to approach calendars. Some show how CSS Grid can create the layout efficiently. Some attempt to bring actual data into the mix. Some …
Making Calendars With Accessibility and Internationalization in Mind originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mads Stoumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove Duplicate Data 
in SQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-duplicate-data-in-sql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-duplicate-data-in-sql/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T21:22:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Duplicates can be a big problem in SQL databases as they can slow down query performance and waste valuable storage space.  Fortunately, there are several ways to remove duplicate data in SQL.  In this article, we will explore some of the most effective methods for removing duplicate data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript One-Liners to Use in Every Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-one-liners-to-use-in-every-project/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-one-liners-to-use-in-every-project/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T21:18:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a powerful language that can do a lot with very little code. In some cases, the amount of code you need to write doesn't exceed more than a single line, which is why they are known as one-liners. Let's go through 10 essential one liners worth using in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Iterate Over Dictionary – How to Loop Through a Dict]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-iterate-over-dictionary-how-to-loop-through-a-dict/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-iterate-over-dictionary-how-to-loop-through-a-dict/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T21:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will talk about dictionaries, and also learn how to loop through a dictionary in python. Python Dictionaries In Python, a dictionary is a built-in data structure used to store and organize data in key-value pairs.  A dictionary has two parts for each entry: a key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript String Tutorial – String Methods in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-tutorial-string-methods-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-tutorial-string-methods-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T19:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A string is a sequence of characters intended to represent text. Strings can contain any kind of character, like letters, numbers, or special characters.  They are a very useful data type and you will be probably working with them frequently. So it's important to know how to manipulate them]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dario Di Cillo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Simpler JavaScript Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/simplify-javascript-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/simplify-javascript-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T18:57:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As developers, writing clean and maintainable code is the goal. But sometimes, this is hard to achieve when we have a large and bulky codebase that can become complex and difficult to manage. One way to avoid this is to simplify your code. This can help improve its readability, efficiency,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oyedele Temitope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Forms in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-forms-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-forms-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T17:43:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forms play an essential role in modern web applications. They enable users to share information, complete tasks and provide feedback.  Without forms, many of the tasks that we take for granted on the web, such as logging in, signing up, or making purchases, would not be possible. As such,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dickson Boateng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Mistakes I Made When Starting My First React Project]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377098</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/5-mistakes-starting-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T16:41:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know what it’s like to pick up a new language or framework. Sometimes there’s great documentation to help you find your way through it. But even the best documentation doesn’t cover absolutely everything. And when you work with something …
5 Mistakes I Made When Starting My First React Project originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Oliver Bray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Pragmatist’s Guide To Lean User Research]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/pragmatists-guide-lean-user-research/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/pragmatists-guide-lean-user-research/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instead of telling you once again what the best practice is and adding to your imposter syndrome, let’s concentrate on some practical approaches to user research that we might be able to fit into our existing projects without being left disillusioned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a Clickable SVG Map With HTML and CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-clickable-svg-map-html-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-clickable-svg-map-html-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T19:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tour Afrique]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rufai Mustapha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perform Machine Learning Tasks with Python and SQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-with-python-and-sql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-with-python-and-sql/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T17:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning has become a popular field in recent years, with various applications in data analysis, computer vision, natural language processing, and more.  Python is one of the most widely used programming languages for machine learning, thanks to its rich ecosystem of libraries, frameworks, and tools.  But to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting CORS – How to Pentest Cross-Origin Resource Sharing Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/exploiting-cors-guide-to-pentesting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/exploiting-cors-guide-to-pentesting/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T16:25:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All web browsers implement a security model known as the Same-Origin Policy (SOP). It restricts domains from accessing and retrieving data from other domains’ resources.  The SOP policy helps protect users from malicious scripts that could access their sensitive data or perform unauthorized actions on their behalf. For example,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nairuz Abulhul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Web Development from Harvard University (CS50 Web)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-web-development-from-harvard-university-cs50/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-web-development-from-harvard-university-cs50/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T12:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking to expand your knowledge and skills in web programming? Look no further than CS50's Web Programming with Python and JavaScript course from Harvard University. This full course is designed to provide a comprehensive understanding of web programming, from the basics of HTML and CSS to more advanced]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn LaTeX for Creating Scientific Documents]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-latex-full-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-latex-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T12:27:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking to create professional-looking documents with ease? Look no further than the world of LaTeX. LaTeX is a typesetting system that enables users to produce high-quality documents, such as academic papers, scientific publications, and even books. We just published a beginner's course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do I Make RegEx Optional? Specify Optional Pattern in Regular Expressions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-i-make-regex-optional-specify-optional-pattern-in-regular-expressions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-i-make-regex-optional-specify-optional-pattern-in-regular-expressions/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T11:34:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regular expressions are greedy by default, meaning they try to match as many strings as possible. One of the ways to write accurate regular expressions is to make them as lazy as possible. The metacharacter that helps achieve laziness is the question mark ?. It helps you make any RegEx]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Complex Forms In Vue]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/building-complex-forms-vue/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/building-complex-forms-vue/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that creating a complex form can be progressively enhanced using some Vue features like the v-for and the v-model? In this article, Olufunke shares some basic Vue core features that are super useful when building out the complex form in your day-to-day Vue usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Olufunke Moronfolu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to React to User and Browser Actions with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/reacting-to-actions-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/reacting-to-actions-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T00:47:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When a user clicks a button on a webpage, the user expects the page to respond to their action and do something: play the game, buy the product, display a message, and so on. In this tutorial, we walk through how to use JavaScript to react to user or browser]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Kurata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binary Search in Java – Algorithm Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/binary-search-in-java-algorithm-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/binary-search-in-java-algorithm-example/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-08T22:26:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Algorithms provide step by step instructions on solving specific problems. They help you solve problems using efficient, standard, and reusable steps.  The binary search algorithm is one of the commonly used algorithms in programming. It is used to search and find an element in a sorted array.  The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Convert Arabic Numbers to Roman Numerals with SolidJS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-arabic-numbers-to-roman-numerals-with-solidjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-arabic-numbers-to-roman-numerals-with-solidjs/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-08T20:52:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you heard about the Romans? Who hasn’t, right 🙂 They used their own numeric system, which was a bit of a mouthful, especially when it came to writing. It looks like this: I, II, III, IV, V, VI and so on. Maybe that’s one of the reasons that people]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mihail Gaberov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Read and Write Data to a SQL Database Using Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-read-and-write-data-to-a-sql-database-using-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-read-and-write-data-to-a-sql-database-using-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-08T19:27:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Databases are a crucial component of modern-day software systems. And SQL databases are one of the most widely used types of databases.  They are ideal for managing data in a structured and organized way, and they are widely used in various applications, including e-commerce, healthcare, finance, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MERN App Development – How to Build a CI/CD Pipeline with Jenkins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-mern-app-deployment-with-jenkins-and-aws/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-mern-app-deployment-with-jenkins-and-aws/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-08T17:42:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you continue to develop your software, you must also continue to integrate it with previous code and deploy it to servers.  Manually doing this is a time-consuming process that can occasionally result in errors. So we need to do this in a continuous and automated manner – which]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rakesh Potnuru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C Operator – Logic Operators in C Programming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/c-operator-logic-operators-in-c-programming/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/c-operator-logic-operators-in-c-programming/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-08T15:25:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn about the three logical operators in C. I will first explain what operators are in programming and list the different types of operators available in C. Then, you will learn the role logical operators have and how to use them with the help of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does B in RegEx Mean? Word Boundary and Non-word Boundary Metacharacters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-b-in-regex-mean-word-boundary-and-non-word-boundary-metacharacters/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-b-in-regex-mean-word-boundary-and-non-word-boundary-metacharacters/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-08T14:10:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In regular expressions, “B” is a metacharacter for specifying word boundary. It could be in two forms – the capital letter “B” and the small letter “b”. Since B (and b) is a metacharacter, you need to escape it to make it work (\b  and \B). Otherwise, b or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a Clock with the New CSS sin() and cos() Trigonometry Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377074</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-a-clock-with-the-new-css-sin-and-cos-trigonometry-functions/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-08T14:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS trigonometry functions are here! Well, they are if you’re using the latest versions of Firefox and Safari, that is. Having this sort of mathematical power in CSS opens up a whole bunch of possibilities. In this tutorial, I thought …
Creating a Clock with the New CSS sin() and cos() Trigonometry Functions originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mads Stoumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Different Types of APIs – SOAP vs REST vs GraphQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rest-vs-graphql-apis/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rest-vs-graphql-apis/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T23:24:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we're going to take a good look at APIs, a core concept in modern software development. We're going to talk about the main kinds of APIs used nowadays (SOAP, REST and GraphQL), their characteristics, pros and cons, and situations in which each of them might]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Generate Colors in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/generate-colors-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/generate-colors-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T22:11:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll use build a random color generator in JavaScript. Along the way, we will explore general topics in programming like functions and randomization.  We will build a project called Change The Background Color to illustrate these concepts. You can see the demo here [http://rufai.github.io/buildingx/random_bg_color.html].  In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rufai Mustapha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circular Reference Error in JavaScript – Meaning and How to Fix It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/circular-reference-in-javascript-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/circular-reference-in-javascript-explained/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T21:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever encountered a "circular reference" error when working with JSON? In this tutorial, I'll explain what this error means as well as how to fix it. This error, in my experience, occurs when you try to convert an object with circular references to JSON. You may have experienced]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Loops in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-loops-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-loops-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T21:36:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Loops are an essential concept in programming. They allow you to execute a block of code repeatedly based on certain conditions.  Python offers two types of loops: for and while loops. In this article, we will explore both of these loop types and provide examples of how to use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep Learning with Julia – How to Build and Train a Model using a Neural Network]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deep-learning-with-julia/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deep-learning-with-julia/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T21:34:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Julia [https://julialang.org/] is a general purpose programming language well suited for numerical analysis and computational science. Some consider it the future of machine learning and the most natural replacement for Python in this field. In the previous post "Machine learning with Julia – How to Build and Deploy a Trained]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrey Germanov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Business of Technology Research – Who Funds It, And What's Being Done]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-business-of-technology-research-5-10/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-business-of-technology-research-5-10/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T17:07:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting a new technology out to consumers will usually require good people and boat loads of resources – including money. Generally, lots of money.  A lot of that money will be spent on research. And, more often than not, the hard research needed to translate a great idea into]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Variable Data Types Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/variable-data-types-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/variable-data-types-explained/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T16:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Walking into a hardware store, it's not enough to say: "I need a tool". You need to be specific about the type of tool you need.  Each tool type has its particular purpose: A hammer to drive a nail into wood, a paint brush to paint, and a wrench]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Kurata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Conditional Statements in Python – Examples of if, else, and elif]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-conditional-statements-if-else-elif-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-conditional-statements-if-else-elif-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T16:03:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conditional statements are an essential part of programming in Python. They allow you to make decisions based on the values of variables or the result of comparisons.  In this article, we'll explore how to use if, else, and elif statements in Python, along with some examples of how to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Static Variables in Java – Why and How to Use Static Methods]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/static-variables-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/static-variables-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T15:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Static variables and static methods are two important concepts in Java.  Whenever a variable is declared as static, this means there is only one copy of it for the entire class, rather than each instance having its own copy. A static method means it can be called without creating]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create Dynamic Donut Charts With TailwindCSS And React]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/dynamic-donut-charts-tailwind-css-react/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/dynamic-donut-charts-tailwind-css-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Paul Scanlon shares a super lightweight approach to creating a Donut chart using conic-gradient(). There are no additional libraries to install or maintain, and there’s no heavy JavaScript that needs to be downloaded by the browser in order for them to work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What does \S in Regex Mean? Space and Negated Space Metacharacters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-s-in-regex-mean-space-and-negated-space-metacharacters/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-s-in-regex-mean-space-and-negated-space-metacharacters/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T14:09:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In regular expressions, “S” is a metacharacter that represents space. The small letter “s” metacharacter stands for space, and the capital letter “S” stands for non-space. That's how the pattern for most metacharacters works. For instance, the small letter “d” is the metacharacter for a digit, and the capital letter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Consider Graphs For Your Next GraphQL Project]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/consider-graphs-graphql-project/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/consider-graphs-graphql-project/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adam Cowley examines the Graph behind GraphQL and demonstrates why Neo4j could be the best fit for your next project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adam Cowley)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Test and Debug SQL Queries with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/testing-and-debugging-sql-queries-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/testing-and-debugging-sql-queries-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T22:20:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SQL is a powerful language that allows you to extract, manipulate and analyze data from relational databases. But writing and debugging SQL queries can be a challenging task.  Testing and debugging SQL queries is crucial to ensure that they produce accurate and efficient results. And you can use Python]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use scanf( ) in C to Read and Store User Input]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/using-scanf-in-c/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/using-scanf-in-c/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T21:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The scanf() function is a commonly used input function in the C programming language. It allows you to read input from the user or from a file and store that input in variables of different data types.  Input is an essential part of most programs, and the scanf() function]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rendering Patterns for Web Apps – Server-Side, Client-Side, and SSG Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rendering-patterns/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rendering-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T18:22:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we're going to take a look at the different rendering pattern options available nowadays for web applications. I'll start by explaining what a rendering pattern is, then go through each of the main options available. Finally we'll compare them, explaining the pros and cons and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Extract Data from PDF Files with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/extract-data-from-pdf-files-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/extract-data-from-pdf-files-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T17:51:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data is present in all areas of the modern digital world, and it takes many different forms.  One of the most common formats for data is PDF. Invoices, reports, and other forms are frequently stored in Portable Document Format (PDF) files by businesses and institutions.  It can be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Excel – How to Use Data Validation and Conditional Formatting to Prevent Errors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/excel-use-data-validation-and-conditional-formatting-to-prevent-errors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/excel-use-data-validation-and-conditional-formatting-to-prevent-errors/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T16:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been using Microsoft Excel and Google Sheets in my business for over a decade. And as I've learned better ways to clean and validate data, it's increased productivity, decreased human errors, and generally caused a lot of joy! 🥳 In this article, we'll look at two ways to validate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inspiring Web Design And UX Showcases]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/inspiring-web-design-ux-showcases/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/inspiring-web-design-ux-showcases/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you sometimes feel that all websites look the same? In this post, we compiled web design showcases that prove differently. They highlight some of the finest web designs, well-crafted experiences, and delightful interactions from across the web. Inspiration is guaranteed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Fonts in WordPress Block Themes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377123</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/managing-fonts-in-wordpress-block-themes/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T15:26:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fonts are a defining characteristic of the design of any site. That includes WordPress themes, where it’s common for theme developers to integrate a service like Google Fonts into the WordPress Customizer settings for a “classic” PHP-based theme. That hasn’t …
Managing Fonts in WordPress Block Themes originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Dahal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Search Files Effectively in the Linux Terminal – Advanced Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-search-files-effectively-in-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-search-files-effectively-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T14:58:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! Thanks for your great feedback on my tutorial about the basics of the find command [/news/how-to-search-files-in-the-linux-terminal/]. After reading it, many people requested that I write a more advanced version about the  find command.  Well, here it is! Now, it's time to take your skills to the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can ChatGPT Ensure Secure Coding Practices?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chat-gpt-and-secure-coding/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chat-gpt-and-secure-coding/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T14:56:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT has been in the news a lot recently. The hype around it continues, and many are concerned that this AI service might put many out of work.  Developers in particular feel threatened by this AI bot’s ability to write code on the fly. The general consensus is, however,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrej Kovacevic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Define And Call Functions in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-define-and-call-functions-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-define-and-call-functions-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-03T21:18:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python is a powerful and versatile programming language that offers a wide range of functionalities for developers.  One of the most essential features of Python is the ability to define and call functions.  A function is a block of code that performs a specific task. In Python, defining]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Market a New Project –Incorporate Design, Create a Landing Page, and Get Users]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-market-your-new-project-incorporate-design-create-a-landing-page-and-get-your-users-97812fd9dd4d/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-market-your-new-project-incorporate-design-create-a-landing-page-and-get-your-users-97812fd9dd4d/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-03T18:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only a few of us come naturally to self-marketing. Most of us prefer making the thing and enjoy showing it off (at least a little!), but hope it’ll be appreciated on its own merits – or that someone else will champion it.  Deliberate marketing and sales makes people uncomfortable,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jane Sorensen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trim a String in Python – How to Strip Trailing Whitespace]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-strip-trailing-whitespace-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-strip-trailing-whitespace-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-03T17:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python has three built-in methods for trimming leading and trailing whitespace and characters from strings: strip(), lstrip(), and rstrip(). In this article, I will explain how to remove trailing whitespace in Python using the rstrip() method. Let's get into it! How To Trim Whitespace From A String in Python To]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Table of Contents Component for Your Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-table-of-contents-component/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-table-of-contents-component/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-03T14:54:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you visit documentation sites, you'll notice that many of them have a common component: the  component. The idea behind it is to give the reader a "heads-up" about the information they're trying to consume. This feature, in turn, helps the reader go directly to the section that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caleb Olojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Tips to Help You Save Time and Write Simpler Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-tips-save-time-write-simpler-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-tips-save-time-write-simpler-queries/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-03T14:28:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a data analyst, you'll want to be as efficient and and effective as possible when working with databases.  SQL is one of the most widely used languages for managing and manipulating data stored in a relational database. In this article, we'll cover some SQL cheat codes that can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>