<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-01-28T00:58:23.767Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Python Decorator Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-python-decorator-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-python-decorator-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T17:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python decorators provide an easy yet powerful syntax for modifying and extending the behavior of functions in your code.  A decorator is essentially a function that takes another function, augments its functionality, and returns a new function – without permanently modifying the original function itself. This tutorial will walk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atharva Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Simple Guide To Retrieval Augmented Generation Language Models]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/guide-retrieval-augmented-generation-language-models/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/guide-retrieval-augmented-generation-language-models/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Language models have shown impressive capabilities. But that doesn’t mean they’re without faults, as anyone who has witnessed a ChatGPT “hallucination” can attest. In this article, Joas Pambou diagnoses the symptoms that cause hallucinations and explains not only what RAG is but also different approaches for using it to solve language model limitations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a React App in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-react-app-in-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-react-app-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T13:44:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2024, there are more ways than ever to get your React projects started. But which one should you choose? In this article, I'm going to break down all of the major ways you can use to create a React app and which one you should pick based off of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Simple Sentiment Analyzer Using Hugging Face Transformer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-simple-sentiment-analyzer-using-hugging-face-transformer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-simple-sentiment-analyzer-using-hugging-face-transformer/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T00:32:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will look at writing a sentiment analyzer using Hugging Face Transformer, a powerful tool in the world of NLP.  Imagine you’re running a business and you want to know what your customers think about your product. Or maybe you’re a movie director wanting to gauge]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React.js with Laravel to Build a Draggable Tasklist App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-react-with-laravel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-react-with-laravel/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T00:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have seen tutorials that help you build a simple React.js app that use some third-party API or a Node.js server as a backend. You could also use Laravel for this purpose and integrate it with React. As a backend framework, Laravel actually offers a tool to help you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>San B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize Your CSS Code for Faster Web Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-optimize-your-css-code-for-faster-web-pages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-optimize-your-css-code-for-faster-web-pages/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T00:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS is more than just a tool for styling. It also determines how web pages render in a browser. Well-optimized CSS means faster loading times and a smoother user experience. In today's digital landscape, the performance of a website is a key factor in its success. Writing efficient CSS code]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ophy Boamah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Running the Biggest Programming Channel on YouTube with freeCodeCamp's Beau Carnes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-biggest-youtube-programming-channel-beau-carnes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-biggest-youtube-programming-channel-beau-carnes/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T19:50:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beau Carnes has run the freeCodeCamp community YouTube channel for the past 5 years, taking it from 75,000 subscribers all the way up to 9 million. Beau started out working as a Special Education teacher at a Michigan high school. He taught himself how to code before working as a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Hash Map? Time Complexity and Two Sum Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-hash-map/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-hash-map/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T17:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hash table or hash map, is a data structure that helps with mapping keys to values for highly efficient operations like the lookup, insertion and deletion operations. In this tutorial, you'll learn the following:  * Constant and linear time complexity.  * Why use a hash map?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sule-Balogun Olanrewaju Ganiu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Natural Language Processing Techniques for Topic Identification – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/topic-identification-using-natural-language-processing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/topic-identification-using-natural-language-processing/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T16:16:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a lot of textual information available these days. It ranges from articles to social media posts and research papers. So our ability to distill meaningful insights is key. This helps us make informed decisions in a wide array of contexts.  For example, you can analyze a large volume]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ibrahim Abayomi Ogunbiyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn LangChain and Gen AI by Building 6 Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-langchain-and-gen-ai-by-building-6-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-langchain-and-gen-ai-by-building-6-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T16:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning LangChain empowers you to seamlessly integrate advanced language models like GPT-4 into diverse applications, unlocking capabilities in natural language processing and AI-driven applications. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build six end-to-end projects using LangChain and a variety]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Blurry Shimmer Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/css-blurry-shimmer-effect/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/css-blurry-shimmer-effect/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taking inspiration from shadows, author Yair Even Or creates the same sort of thing, only with a blurring effect in place of the shadow. Read along for a step-by-step explanation of how it comes together using a combination of masks, gradients, and the good ol’ `backdrop-filter` property.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yair Even Or)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Units – When to Use rem, em, px, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-units-when-to-use-each-one/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-units-when-to-use-each-one/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T00:58:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS units allow you to measure and specify different property values. You use them to modify CSS properties such as margins, padding, height, and width to make them compatible with devices of all screen sizes. CSS units have two basic types:  * Absolute units  * Relative units Absolute]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esther Christopher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get the First Line of a Multiline String in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-the-first-line-of-a-multiline-string-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-the-first-line-of-a-multiline-string-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T23:33:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, getting the first element of an array or string is pretty easy. But when it comes to getting the first line of a multiline string, some approaches can hurt your app's performance in certain cases. In this article, we will look at the three best ways you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Furkan Emin Can</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Next.js Apps to Github Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-next-js-app-to-github-pages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-next-js-app-to-github-pages/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T22:46:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will walk you through the process of publishing a Next.js application on GitHub Pages.  What makes this guide particularly helpful is that I'll teach you how to integrate with GitHub Actions, too. This means your application will be automatically deployed every time you push code]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code Extensions to Boost Your Productivity in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-vscode-extensions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-vscode-extensions/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T22:42:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the 2023 Stack Overflow Developer Survey [https://survey.stackoverflow.co/2023/#section-most-popular-technologies-integrated-development-environment] , Visual Studio Code (also known as VSCode) ranked as the most preferred integrated developer environment (IDE) tool.  Visual Studio Code has many great features out-of-the-box, and supports a large community of extensions to add enhanced functionality.  Stack Overflow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie Pina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Back Up and Restore Azure SQL Databases]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-back-up-and-restore-sql-azure-database/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-back-up-and-restore-sql-azure-database/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T22:34:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's Azure’s provides many services via a single cloud, which lets them offer one solution for multiple corporate infrastructures. Teams use Azure because they value the opportunity to run SQL databases in the cloud and complete simple operations via the Azure portal.  But you'll need to have a way]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Tray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyGame Tutorial – How to Build a Bouncing Ball Game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pygame-tutorial-build-a-bouncing-game/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pygame-tutorial-build-a-bouncing-game/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T22:46:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn how to create a simple yet funny bouncing ball game using the PyGame library.  Whether you're a beginner seeking to grasp the fundamentals of game development or an enthusiast eager to explore PyGame's capabilities, this article is your guide to crafting a simple yet]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan P. Romano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build AI Apps – A Frontend Developer's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/frontend-ai-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/frontend-ai-guide/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T22:05:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence: The New Frontier for Frontend Developers The demand for AI-powered applications is growing at a fast pace. As a front-end developer, you can take advantage of this trend and advance your career by integrating your skills in frontend development with AI technologies. This integration allows you to build]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahmud Adeleye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring with Event-Driven Architecture on AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deep-dive-into-event-driven-architecture-on-aws/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deep-dive-into-event-driven-architecture-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T15:03:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Event-driven architecture is a software design pattern where components or services perform actions in response to events, often asynchronously. This post serves as a companion to our video course, "Deep Dive into Event-Driven Architecture on AWS." In the course, we delve into some of the core fundamentals of event-driven architecture]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Dilemma In Graphic Design: Steering Towards Excellence In Typography And Beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/ai-dilemma-graphic-design-typography/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/ai-dilemma-graphic-design-typography/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI promises a major upheaval in typography, with designers finding themselves navigating both opportunities and challenges. How will it impact quality, design roles, and our use of type in the future? As we explore this new frontier, we realise that we are at a juncture as significant as Gutenberg’s press, set to redefine how we interact with text and visual communication.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Filip Paldia &amp; Jamie Clarke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage State in React Apps with APIs – Redux, Context API, and Recoil Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manage-state-in-react-apps-with-apis/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manage-state-in-react-apps-with-apis/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T00:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State management is a crucial aspect of building robust and scalable React applications, especially when dealing with APIs.  As your application grows in complexity, efficiently managing the state becomes essential for a smooth user experience.  In the React ecosystem, there are several options for state management, each with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a CRUD REST API with NestJS, Docker, Swagger, and Prisma]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-crud-rest-api-with-nestjs-docker-swagger-prisma/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-crud-rest-api-with-nestjs-docker-swagger-prisma/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T00:17:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to this in-depth guide on crafting a RESTful API with NestJS, Docker, Swagger, and Prisma. My goal here is to teach you how to build robust and efficient backends, regardless of whether you're a seasoned developer or a beginner just dipping your toes into the world of coding. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaiah Clifford Opoku</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Command Line Tricks You Can Learn Faster than Drinking Your Morning Coffee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/command-line-tricks-you-can-learn-quickly/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/command-line-tricks-you-can-learn-quickly/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T23:15:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this short tutorial, I want to share with you a few tricks and tips to help you deal with some common situations when you're working in the Linux command line. We will cover the following:  * find  * xargs and nproc  * taskset  * numactl]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Tools You Can Use in Visual Studio Code Besides GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-tools-to-use-in-vs-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-tools-to-use-in-vs-code/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T19:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI tools have become quite popular recently. Developers use these tools to help generate ideas, create simple code examples, and so on.  In 2023, ChatGPT and other Large Language Models found their way into many of our toolkits. And we can use them to be more productive and save]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create AI Assistants with OpenAI's Assistants API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-ai-assistants-with-openais-assistants-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-ai-assistants-with-openais-assistants-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T17:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI's Assistants API is a powerful tool that allows developers to build AI assistants within their apps efficiently. It simplifies managing conversation history and provides access to advanced features like Code Interpreter and Retrieval. The API also improves function-calling for third-party tools. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Data Analysis and Visualization with Python Using Astronomical Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-data-analysis-and-visualization-with-python-using-astrongomical-data/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-data-analysis-and-visualization-with-python-using-astrongomical-data/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T19:48:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you fascinated by both Python and the night sky? We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Python to analyze and visualize astronomical Data. This course was created by Spartificial, whose mission is to provide engineering education in the most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Your Web Server with Continuous Integration Using NGINX and CircleCI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/secure-web-server-with-continuous-integration-using-nginx-and-circleci/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/secure-web-server-with-continuous-integration-using-nginx-and-circleci/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T16:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web servers are responsible for delivering web pages and various resources to clients through the internet. They can exist either as software or hardware components. But unfortunately, they often become targets for hackers and malicious individuals seeking to exploit any vulnerabilities to compromise data and disrupt functionality. As a result,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abraham Dahunsi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with FPM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/getting-started-with-fpm/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/getting-started-with-fpm/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T16:42:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FPM [https://fpm.readthedocs.io/en/latest/getting-started.html] is a powerful wrapper that allows you to create packages for multiple programs in multiple operating systems.  In this tutorial I will show you how you can replace some of the tedious packaging of third party applications. What You Need to Complete this Tutorial  * A]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use SonarLint to Write Cleaner Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-sonarlint-to-write-cleaner-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-sonarlint-to-write-cleaner-code/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T23:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building a coding project, the better it is, the more fun it'll be to use. And the prouder you'll be of your hard work, right?  Also, writing quality and performant code helps your program or website work as expected – which should be every developer's goal. SonarLint]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okosa Leonard Onyekachukwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get a Developer Job]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-a-developer-job/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-a-developer-job/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T17:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The demand for skilled software developers continues to grow. However, for many self-taught developers, the path to securing a job in this competitive field can seem daunting. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is designed to guide aspiring software engineers through the job-hunting process. Lane]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perform CRUD Operations with Django Models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/models-in-django/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/models-in-django/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T16:10:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Django is a super useful tool for building web applications with Python. It follows the Model-View-Template (MVT) architecture, which is a popular design pattern for building web apps. In the MVT architecture, the Model refers to the internal representation of information stored, the View is responsible for processing user requests]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chepkirui dorothy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a High-Performance Tab Component in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-high-performance-tab-component/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-high-performance-tab-component/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T16:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tabs are more than mere UI elements – they're the backbone of user navigation and content organization in many applications. In React, crafting a tabbed component that's both efficient and responsive is not just an improvement, it's a necessity. This article takes a deep dive into constructing a React tab]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Progressive Web Apps? PWA Guide for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-progressive-web-apps-pwa-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-progressive-web-apps-pwa-guide/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T15:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Progressive Web Apps (PWAs) are simply installable web applications – websites that you can install on your device, much like you would install an app from an app store.  They bring together the best parts of using a website (easy to access, no need to install anything) with the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ophy Boamah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Design and Build Sustainable Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/design-and-build-sustainable-software/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/design-and-build-sustainable-software/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T01:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Electronic devices that run software are all around us. Your mobile phone, your car, your microwave, and virtually anything around you – there’s a very good chance that they have electronic components running some form of software. These devices inevitably use power and have batteries and circuits, which degrade over]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jayant Chowdhary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Validate Forms with Zod and React-Hook-Form]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-form-validation-zod-react-hook-form/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-form-validation-zod-react-hook-form/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T21:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forms allow you to collect user data on your websites and apps. And validation is essential to guarantee type safety and the proper format for collected data. You can perform validation on both the client and server side of the application.  This is where Zod and React-Hook-Form come in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gift Uhiene</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to create Python User Interfaces with PyQt5]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-python-user-interfaces-with-pyqt5/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-python-user-interfaces-with-pyqt5/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T21:21:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python can be used for everything from scripting, machine learning, web development, and graphical user interfaces. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that teaches them how to create visually appealing and functional user interfaces (UIs) using Python, with a specific focus on developing a Modern Music]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ACID Databases – Atomicity, Consistency, Isolation & Durability Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/acid-databases-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/acid-databases-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T17:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ACID stands for Atomicity, Consistency, Isolation and Durability. These are four key properties that most database management systems (DBMS) offer as guarantees when handling transactions. Most popular DBMS like MySQL [https://dev.mysql.com/doc/refman/8.0/en/mysql-acid.html], PostgresSQL [https://www.postgresql.org/about/] and Oracle [https://docs.oracle.com/cd/F51125_01/docs.85/SDS%20PI/acid-compliant-transactions.html#GUID-ECB79D66-46DE-4F48-93DC-8677E7BB44EF]  have ACID guarantees out of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TUI Applications with Click and Trogon – Linux Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tui-applications-with-click-and-trogon/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tui-applications-with-click-and-trogon/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T17:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux and terminal applications are almost synonymous. If you have used applications like grep, cat, sed, and AWK, those are command line interfaces ( CLI [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Command-line_interface]). And when they work together, they allow you to unleash the power of your computer by mixing and matching a few commands. Sometimes the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Custom Buttons to a Date Picker in Flatpickr]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-custom-buttons-to-flatpickr/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-custom-buttons-to-flatpickr/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T02:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever had to use a date picker in a web frontend project, chances are that you've used flatpickr. For the unacquainted, flatpickr [https://flatpickr.js.org/] is one of the most popular date picker libraries in the open source-verse. It's framework-agnostic, highly customizable, and lightweight. I recently had to use it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Idris Abdul-Lateef</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atomics and Concurrency in C++]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/atomics-and-concurrency-in-cpp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/atomics-and-concurrency-in-cpp/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T23:50:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concurrency is a programming term you'll need to be familiar with if you code in C++. It's especially relevant if you want to get more out of your available compute resources.  But concurrency comes with certain problems. Some of them can be solved using  mutexes [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mutual_exclusion], although mutexes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaid Humayun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Object-Oriented Programming in Java – Full Book]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-oriented-programming-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-oriented-programming-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T23:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Java is a go-to language for many programmers, and it's a critical skill for any software engineer. After learning Java, picking up other programming languages and advanced concepts becomes much easier.  In this book, I'll cover the practical knowledge you need to move from writing basic Java code to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Arrow Functions vs Regular Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/regular-vs-arrow-functions-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/regular-vs-arrow-functions-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T22:19:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, there are two main ways of writing functions. You can create functions using the regular function syntax. Or you can use the arrow function syntax.  In this article, you will learn how to use both options. You'll also learn about the differences between the two and when]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the Essentials of Data Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-essentials-of-data-engineering/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-essentials-of-data-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T21:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to freeCodeCamp's Data Engineering Video Course Data Engineering is a vital field in the tech industry focused on designing, building, and maintaining systems that collect, process, and analyze large volumes of data. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel all about data engineering, designed to cater]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize AWS Simple Storage Service for Better Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-optimize-aws-s3-for-performance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-optimize-aws-s3-for-performance/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T21:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[S3 is an Amazon Web Service that provides data storage and retrieval in the cloud. ‌‌ This article will discuss the common S3 performance bottlenecks and how they impact the service's overall performance. It will also share some best practices to serve as guidelines for optimising the performance of your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Feyijimi Erinle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How File Ownership and Permissions Work in RHEL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/file-ownership-permissions-rhel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/file-ownership-permissions-rhel/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T20:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux commands give you precise control over file ownership and permissions, ensuring data security and access control.  This guide will delve into several essential commands: chown, chgrp, chmod, and  umask. The examples will showcase their functionality, variations, and practical applications. Table Of Contents Here's what we'll cover in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Engine and Runtime Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-engine-and-runtime-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-engine-and-runtime-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T19:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A JavaScript engine is simply a computer program that executes JavaScript code. It's responsible for translating human-readable JavaScript code into machine-readable instructions that the computer's hardware can execute. When you write JavaScript code and run it in a browser, the code doesn't directly interact with your computer's hardware. Instead, it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Complex But Awesome CSS border-image Property]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/css-border-image-property/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/css-border-image-property/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS `border-image` property is one of those properties you undoubtedly know exists but may not have ever reached for. In this article, Temani Afif demonstrates different approaches for using `border-image` to create clever decorative accents and shapes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 React Projects to Build in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-projects-to-build-in-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-projects-to-build-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T12:07:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To be confident with using React, you need to build real-world projects. But what projects are worth building in 2024? I have put together a list of seven projects that I think are ideal for becoming a confident React developer, from simple to complex applications. This will give you some]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Immutability in JavaScript – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/immutability-in-javascript-with-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/immutability-in-javascript-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T23:21:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often hear the terms: immutable and immutability. But what do they mean, and, as developers, why should we care? Immutable basically means something that cannot be changed. In programming, immutable is used to describe a value that cannot be changed after it's been set. But, most programs require creating,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Kurata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Callbacks and Higher Order Functions in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/callbacks-higher-order-functions-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/callbacks-higher-order-functions-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T18:07:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way functions are treated and used in JavaScript is quite interesting. They are very flexible – we can assign a function as a value to a variable, return them as a value from another function, and pass them as an argument to another function. We can do all this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Franklin Okolie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Markdown in VSCode – Syntax and Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-markdown-in-vscode/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-markdown-in-vscode/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T17:46:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Markdown is a lightweight markup language for creating formatted text using a plain-text editor. It is widely used for creating README files, documentation, and other forms of text. Visual Studio Code (VSCode) is a popular source code editor that provides excellent support for Markdown, making it easy for developers, writers,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Poromon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Storage API – How to Store Data on the Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-storage-api-how-to-store-data-on-the-browser/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-storage-api-how-to-store-data-on-the-browser/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T17:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Web Storage API is a set of APIs exposed by the browser so that you can store data in the browser. The data stored in the Web Storage use the key/value pair format, and both data will be stored as strings. There are two types of storage introduced in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JS DOM Manipulation Best Practices – with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dom-manipulation-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dom-manipulation-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T17:41:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, you can manipulate the content of a web page using the Document Object Model (DOM). But how do you write code that is readable, easy to maintain, and not prone to performance issues?  That's what we'll cover in this article. I'll discuss some important best practices so]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Prepare for Data Analyst Job Interviews]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-for-data-analyst-job-interview/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-for-data-analyst-job-interview/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T17:31:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s digital world, every business and organization collects and uses data to build better products, target the right customers, improve efficiency, and even forecast future demand.  They say that data is the new oil – and now is the perfect time to enter the data analytics job market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jess Wilk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NGINX for Backend Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nginx/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nginx/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T16:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NGINX is a versatile and powerful open-source software used for web serving, reverse proxying, caching, load balancing, media streaming, and more. It's important to understand for backend developers. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you what you need to know about NGINX. Laith]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Magic Link Authentication with React, Flask, and Authsignal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-magic-link-authentication-with-react-flask-and-authsignal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-magic-link-authentication-with-react-flask-and-authsignal/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T18:40:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authentication is the process of verifying the identity of a user or system. It ensures that only authorized individuals or systems can access certain resources or perform specific actions. Magic Link Authentication offers a simple yet secure way for users to log in without passwords. This tutorial will walk you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Front-End Tools Of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/top-frontend-tools-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/top-frontend-tools-2023/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Useful front-end tools for CSS and JavaScript developers that were most popular last year and will help you speed up your development workflow. Let’s dive in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Sliding Window Technique – Algorithm Example and Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sliding-window-technique/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sliding-window-technique/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T15:11:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I was practicing coding problems that focused on Data Structures and Algorithms in preparation for a job change.  During this process, I came across the Sliding Window technique. I found this algorithm to be very interesting, so I wanted to share my learnings with the community.  This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize Search Queries in MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/optimize-search-queries-in-mongodb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/optimize-search-queries-in-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T21:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Searching through a database to extract relevant data can be quite cumbersome if you don't have – or know how to use – the right tools. MongoDB is a non-relational, no-SQL database that differs from relational SQL-based databases such as PostgresSQL, MySQL. These SQL-based databases use conventional rows and columns]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oluwatobi Joshua</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with Hugging Face – Open Source AI Models and Datasets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-started-with-hugging-face/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-started-with-hugging-face/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T21:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Hugging Face 🤗? If you are interested in Artificial Intelligence and Natural Language Processing, you have probably heard of Hugging Face – the company named after a cute emoji.  Hugging Face is not only a company, but also a platform that is transforming the fields of AI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ambreen Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding DOM Events and JavaScript Event Listeners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dom-events-and-javascript-event-listeners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dom-events-and-javascript-event-listeners/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T20:38:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript code in the browser uses an event-driven programming pattern. What this means is that when a specific DOM event happens in the browser, a piece of code will be executed as a response to that action. In this article, I will help you see and understand how to listen]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyTorch vs TensorFlow – Which is Better for Deep Learning Projects?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pytorch-vs-tensorflow-for-deep-learning-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pytorch-vs-tensorflow-for-deep-learning-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:46:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll look at two popular deep learning libraries — PyTorch and TensorFlow – and see how they compare. If you are getting started with deep learning, the available tools and frameworks will be overwhelming. Industry experts may recommend TensorFlow while hardcore ML engineers may prefer PyTorch. Both]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Stepper Component in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-stepper-component-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-stepper-component-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T15:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was working on a React project recently, and I realized that there were so many UI components that I had to build to get things done quickly. So I began to explore a lot of UI libraries like Material UI [https://mui.com] or Chakra UI [https://chakra-ui.com/]. Then I started wondering]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olabisi Olaoye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work with Third-Party APIs in React by Building a Crypto Exchange Rate Web App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/work-with-third-party-libraries-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/work-with-third-party-libraries-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T15:24:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working with APIs is crucial to any web application. And as a frontend developer, knowing how to connect your apps with third-party APIs is an important skill to have. In this article, you'll learn how to connect your app and fetch data from a third-party API by building a crypto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidera Humphrey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Document Object Model? DOM for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-the-dom/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-the-dom/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T15:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'm going to explain to you how the DOM works so that you have a clear picture of why JavaScript is needed to develop a web application. First, let's recap what we know about HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. How HTML, CSS, and JavaScript work When you want]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript DOM Manipulation Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-dom-manipulation-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-dom-manipulation-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T15:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOM Manipulation is one of the most exciting topics to learn about in JavaScript. This is because one of JavaScript's main uses is to make web pages interactive – and the Document Object Model (DOM) plays a major role in this.  The DOM is a powerful tool that allows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Custom CSS Animations with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-custom-css-animations/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-custom-css-animations/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T21:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animations are a crucial component of modern web design. They enable you to create dynamic and engaging web elements that attract more customers and drive more sales. In this article, we will discuss how to create cool custom animations using CSS. Prerequisites Before going forward with this article, make sure]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Hu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do Zsh Configuration Files Work?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-zsh-configuration-files-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-zsh-configuration-files-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T20:37:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beginners often get confused when configuring Zsh shell on a Mac. Zsh shell offers four configuration files with no discernible differences. Particularly, ~/.zshrc and ~/.zprofile appear to be identical, leaving us wondering which one to use.  In this article, you'll learn the difference and a simple guideline for your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kehoe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Work with RESTful APIs in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-work-with-restful-apis-in-react-simplified-steps-and-practical-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-work-with-restful-apis-in-react-simplified-steps-and-practical-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T19:09:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RESTful APIs are a crucial component in modern web development. They allow communication between different applications over the internet.  REST (which stands for Representational State Transfer) APIs operate on a stateless client-server architecture, providing a standardized way to create, read, update, and delete resources. Integrating RESTful APIs with React]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The React Roadmap for 2024 – How to Learn React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-react-roadmap-learn-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-react-roadmap-learn-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T18:57:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, I'll break down a complete roadmap that will cover all the concepts, libraries, and tools to help you become a React developer in 2024. My goal is to show you the happy path in React, navigating you away from pitfalls so you can spend your time on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a GitHub Template Repository for Scaffolding with React, Vite, and TailwindCSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-github-template-repository-with-react-vite-and-tailwindcss/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-github-template-repository-with-react-vite-and-tailwindcss/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T18:04:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers love productivity. When it comes to coding, we want to do things fast and we look out for opportunities to re-use things as much as possible. Say, you are getting started with a ReactJS project and want to use TailwindCSS  for the same. The first time, it would]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use New CSS Features to Build a Progress Indicator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-new-css-features-to-build-a-progress-indicator/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-new-css-features-to-build-a-progress-indicator/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T15:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the last 7 months, I’ve had my head down building Component Odyssey [https://component-odyssey.com/]. It’s been a richly fulfilling project and I’m eager for people to take the course and learn heaps about building component libraries using web components. I’ve seen some incredible demos over the past year, and wanted]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrico Karoulla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Data Analysis with Comprehensive 19-Hour Bootcamp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-data-analysis-with-comprehensive-19-hour-bootcamp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-data-analysis-with-comprehensive-19-hour-bootcamp/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T15:39:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of data analysis is vast and continually evolving, and staying ahead in this field requires a solid foundation in its core technologies and methodologies. We just published a 19-hour data analysis bootcamp on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This bootcamp, developed by Alex Freberg, provides an immersive learning experience]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use pnpm – Installation and Common Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-pnpm/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-pnpm/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T15:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[pnpm is like npm, but it's way faster and more efficient. After all, the starting p stands for performant. According to its creator, Zoltan Kochan, pnpm "allows you to save gigabytes of disk space." Many popular projects including Next.js, Vite, Svelte, and even freeCodeCamp use pnpm. So now is a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Biswas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make React Apps SEO-Friendly – A Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-seo-friendly-react-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-seo-friendly-react-apps/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T15:25:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing your web applications, you should always consider search engine optimization (SEO) techniques. Many things come into play when you're making sure your web application operates as intended and has an online presence. Search engines such as Google, Bing, and Yahoo serve as the primary medium for users seeking]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okosa Leonard Onyekachukwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless Architecture Patterns and Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serverless-architecture-patterns-and-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serverless-architecture-patterns-and-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T01:07:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless architecture has become a hot topic in the developer world, and for good reason.  It promises a paradigm shift – one where we leave behind the burdens of server management and focus solely on building and deploying code. No more provisioning VMs, patching software, or scaling infrastructure manually.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Faith Oyama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collect.js Tutorial – How to Work with JavaScript Arrays and Objects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/work-with-javascript-arrays-objects-with-collect-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/work-with-javascript-arrays-objects-with-collect-js/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T22:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript arrays are one of the most important data structures in the language, since everything is already an object in JavaScript. They're useful in so many applications, and many other data structures build on top of JavaScript arrays and objects. While the language provides a lot of helpful array and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zubair Idris Aweda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use CSS Flexbox to Break Elements Out of Their Containers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/break-out-elements-from-containers-using-flexbox/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/break-out-elements-from-containers-using-flexbox/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:15:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building a webpage, sometimes you might want images or other elements to go beyond the boundaries of a container. So in this tutorial, I'll show you a couple ways you can accomplish this. To illustrate a situation when you might find this useful, let's say we are given]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kheoh Yee Wei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-code-without-being-a-coder/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-code-without-being-a-coder/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:08:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever dreamt of building your own apps but felt intimidated by the complex world of programming? Or maybe you just want to quickly enhance your coding output? We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to write code using AI. Guil Hernandez teaches]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memcached Crash Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/memcached-crash-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/memcached-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Memcached is an important technology for back end developers to understand. It is a distributed memory caching system, primarily used to speed up web applications by reducing database load. It stores data in memory, allowing quicker access compared to traditional database-driven methods. We just published a Memcached crash course on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage Users and Groups in Red Hat Enterprise Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manage-users-and-groups-in-rhel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manage-users-and-groups-in-rhel/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T17:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To effectively safeguard your system and regulate access when working in Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL), you'll need to understand user and group management.  This is a critical component that's significant for both individual and complex network environments, as it's key to adeptly handle user accounts and groups. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gitting Things Done – A Visual and Practical Guide to Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gitting-things-done-book/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gitting-things-done-book/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T17:12:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Git is awesome. Most software developers use Git on a daily basis. But how many truly understand Git? Do you feel like you know what's going on under the hood as you use Git to perform various tasks? For example, what happens when you use git commit? What is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SolidStart: A Different Breed Of Meta-Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/solidstart-different-breed-meta-framework/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/solidstart-different-breed-meta-framework/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready for a little exercise of pulling a framework apart and putting the pieces back together? In this article, Atila Fassina explains how meta-frameworks have evolved around core libraries in their own unique ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn React – A Guide to the Key Concepts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-react-key-concepts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-react-key-concepts/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T01:52:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to this comprehensive guide to learning React. If you're looking for an efficient and well-thought-out approach to understanding React fundamentals, you've just hit the jackpot. This guide follows the 80/20 rule – we'll focus on a few key React concepts that you'll use in the majority of your work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankur Tyagi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React Context in Your Project – Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-context/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-context/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T20:06:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As beginners, managing state in React applications can be challenging, especially when passing and utilizing props in deeply nested components.  The usual way of passing information from a main component to its smaller parts — like a parent passing data to a child, then to a grandchild — can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benedicta Onyebuchi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Template Literals in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/template-literals-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/template-literals-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T18:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Template literals are a feature in JavaScript that were introduced with ES6. They gives you a more flexible and maintainable way of working with strings in JavaScript. By the end of this article, you will know how to use template literals. You will learn the syntax, the benefits, and some]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fine-Tune EasyOCR with a Synthetic Dataset]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fine-tune-easyocr-with-a-synthetic-dataset/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fine-tune-easyocr-with-a-synthetic-dataset/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T17:48:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OCR is a valuable tool that you can use to extract text from images. But the OCR you are using may not work as intended for your specific needs. In such situations, fine-tuning your OCR engine is the way to go.  In this tutorial, I will show you how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eivind Kjosbakken</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Analyze and Visualize Large Datasets with Microsoft Excel Using Pivot Tables and Charts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/analyze-and-visualize-large-datasets-with-excel-pivot-tables-charts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/analyze-and-visualize-large-datasets-with-excel-pivot-tables-charts/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T17:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Excel is a very powerful tool that you can use to analyze and visualize data.  In this tutorial, you will learn how to build a simple Excel Dashboard that visualizes important data from a large dataset.  The dataset we'll be working with is the transaction records of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel A. Olubiyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Defend Against Server-Side Request Forgery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/defending-against-ssrf-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/defending-against-ssrf-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T17:21:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) has been a consistent issue in application security and is among the OWASP Top 10 vulnerabilities.  In this walkthrough, you'll first learn what Server-Side Request Forgery is and how it differs from Client-Side Request Forgery. We will create a sample application to gain a better]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamdaan Ali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript String Handbook – How to Work with Strings in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T17:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strings, in the context of JavaScript, are essential data types that represent sequences of characters. They are integral to web development, forming the foundation for handling and presenting textual information on websites. Whether it's displaying user names, handling form input, or generating dynamic content, strings are omnipresent in JavaScript programming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Machine Learning Models with Reliable Validation Scores]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-machine-learning-models-with-reliable-validation-scores/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-machine-learning-models-with-reliable-validation-scores/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T17:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine that you took a test in school, and you expected to score 80-90% based on how you thought you performed. But when the results came out, you learned that you scored 50-60% in the test. You'd be shocked, right?  Well sometimes these same scenarios play out in machine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saheed Azeez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Concurrency in Kotlin Server-Side Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/concurrency-in-kotlin-server-side-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/concurrency-in-kotlin-server-side-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T23:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you're running a bustling restaurant. Orders fly in, dishes need cooking, tables require clearing, and happy customers demand attention. How can you handle all this chaos without everything turning into a total disaster? This is where concurrency comes in. In the world of server-side development, things can get just]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Faith Oyama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[K-Means Clustering – How to Unveil Hidden Patterns in Your Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/k-means-clustering-unveil-hidden-patterns-in-data/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/k-means-clustering-unveil-hidden-patterns-in-data/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T22:52:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[K-means clustering is a powerful technique that can help you discover hidden patterns and groupings in your datasets. Let’s look at how it works. K-means clustering is a basic but powerful tool in data science. It has changed the way we look at and understand large datasets. In this article,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Kotlin Server Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/securing-kotlin-server-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/securing-kotlin-server-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T22:33:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In server-side application development using Kotlin, taking robust security measures is important. Developers encounter various threats and vulnerabilities that can compromise applications. This article delves into comprehensive security strategies tailored for Kotlin server applications, aiming to equip developers with the knowledge to fortify their systems against potential risks. Security in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Faith Oyama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn React in 2024 – A Step-by-Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-learn-react-step-by-step/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-learn-react-step-by-step/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T21:48:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's never been a better time to learn React than in 2024. In this comprehensive guide, I'll show you how I would go from knowing nothing about React to becoming a job-ready, junior React developer in 3 to 6 months. Keep in mind that becoming a skilled developer is not]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Accessible Custom Dropdown Select Element]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-accessible-custom-dropdown-select-element/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-accessible-custom-dropdown-select-element/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T17:06:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you might want to use a different select element to match your style based on the theme of your design. Or perhaps the default design is different on separate browsers and you want uniformity.  But when designing this new element, you might forget to consider the accessibility of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth  Meshioye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new() vs make() Functions in Go – When to Use Each One]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/new-vs-make-functions-in-go/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/new-vs-make-functions-in-go/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T15:44:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Go, also known as Golang, is a statically-typed, compiled programming language designed for simplicity and efficiency.  When it comes to working with data structures like slices, maps, and channels, you'll likely encounter the new() and make() functions. While both are used for memory allocation, they serve distinct purposes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Destiny Erhabor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced JavaScript Operators – Nullish Coalescing, Optional Chaining, and Destructuring Assignment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-advanced-operators/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-advanced-operators/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T15:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi Everyone! In this article, I'm going to teach you how to use three advanced JavaScript operators: the Nullish Coalescing, Optional Chaining, and Destructuring Assignment operators. These three operators will help you write clearer and less error-prone code.  The Nullish Coalescing Operator When you’re inspecting JavaScript code, you may]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Lazy Loading Works in Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-lazy-loading-works-in-web-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-lazy-loading-works-in-web-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T01:08:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving landscape of web development, performance optimization remains a top priority.  Among the plethora of strategies you can use to enhance web performance, lazy loading stands out for its efficiency and impact.  But what exactly is lazy loading, and how does it revolutionize the way we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SUDHEER KUMAR REDDY GOWRIGARI</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MERN Stack Roadmap – How to Learn MERN and Become a Full-Stack Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mern-stack-roadmap-what-you-need-to-know-to-build-full-stack-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mern-stack-roadmap-what-you-need-to-know-to-build-full-stack-apps/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T00:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how modern web applications are built? How you can learn and master the technologies that you can use to build your own full stack projects from scratch? In this handbook, I'm going to introduce you to the MERN stack, a widely-used technology stack embraced by many]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Blakely</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Cloud Computing? Introduction to the Cloud for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-cloud-computing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-cloud-computing/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T21:40:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the digital landscape continues to evolve and technology marches forward, cloud computing has remained an important topic for developers to learn. You've probably encountered cloud requirements in job listings, heard people talk about it in conversations, or seen ads by companies offering cloud services – and now you're interested]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zubair Idris Aweda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Git Cherry Pick and Avoid Duplicate Commits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-cherry-pick-avoid-duplicate-commits/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-cherry-pick-avoid-duplicate-commits/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T21:33:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine a beautiful cherry tree full of sweet, red, round fruit hanging on lush, glistening branches. But imagine if those cherries grew so quickly that the branches started bending, overlapping, and breaking...sounds chaotic right?  This is what can happen if you don't use Git's cherry-pick command properly in open]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CHRISTINE T. BELZIE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Enterprise Linux – Essential RHEL Concepts and Commands to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/red-hat-enterprise-linux-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/red-hat-enterprise-linux-guide/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T15:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the fundamental world of Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL)! In order to be an effective Linux user, you'll need to learn and truly understand some essential concepts and commands. Let's dive into the core aspects of RHEL administration to help you understand these key topics that form the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comprehensive Full Stack React with Appwrite – Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/comprehensive-full-stack-react-with-appwrite-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/comprehensive-full-stack-react-with-appwrite-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T14:19:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React and Appwrite make a great combination for creating full stack apps.  We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use React and Appwrite to create full stack applications. This course is designed and delivered by Hitesh Choudhary, a excellent instructor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyGame Tutorial – How to Build an Alien Abduction game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pygame-tutorial-alien-abduction-game/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pygame-tutorial-alien-abduction-game/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T23:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever since I was a kid, I've been hooked on video games. My first experience with coding involved kind of a wild project – a Tron races simulator in Quick Basic on an ancient IBM computer (I was like 6 years old, so I didn't really understand what I was]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan P. Romano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android Proto DataStore – Should You Use It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/android-proto-datastore-should-you-use-it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/android-proto-datastore-should-you-use-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T19:52:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few years back, Google announced the DataStore, which is a replacement for the tried and true SharedPreferences.  If you use or have used SharedPreferences in your applications, you might be thinking of making the switch. But as with everything, the main question here is: what is going to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Ben Rachel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free WebDev and JS Bootcamps for 2024 – Learn HTML, CSS, and JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-webdev-and-js-bootcamps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-webdev-and-js-bootcamps/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T16:56:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New year's resolutions are hard. But if your goal for 2024 is to learn some Web Development or JavaScript, we want to help.  The Bad Website Club [http://badwebsite.club/] will be running a free, online, part time bootcamp based on the freeCodeCamp Web Development and JavaScript curricula back to back]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Rose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API And Delightful UI Animations (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part2/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API is a new — but game-changing — feature that allows us to do the types of reactive state-based UI and page transitions that have traditionally been exclusive to JavaScript frameworks. In the second half of this mini two-part series, Adrian Bece expands on the demos from the first article to demonstrate how the View Transitions API can be used to transition not just elements between two states but the transition between full views and pages in single-page and multi-page applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Magic Of New Beginnings (January 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s start into the new year with a little inspiration boost: wallpapers created with love by the community for the community. Happy 2024!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Memory of Robert Yannaccone, freeCodeCamp camper,  Telecom Analyst, and philanthropist]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/in-memory-of-robert-yannaccone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/in-memory-of-robert-yannaccone/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T18:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year we lost Robert Yannacconne, a freeCodeCamp camper who supported our mission to the end. Robert was born in Detroit in 1949. After graduating high school, he joined the United States Air Force, learned Mandarin Chinese, and served as a translator in the Philippines. After 3 years of service,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>