<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-02-26T01:18:03.496Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Lambda Functions – How to Use Anonymous Functions with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-lambda-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-lambda-functions/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-24T17:25:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lambda functions, also known as anonymous functions, are small, one-time-use functions in Python.  You can define them using the lambda keyword followed by the function's inputs, a colon, and the function's expression. The output of a lambda function is returned as the result of the expression, rather than a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Sorted List – And How to Sort or Reverse an Array in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-sort-lists-and-reverse-arrays/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-sort-lists-and-reverse-arrays/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-24T17:24:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arrays and lists in Python are very interesting data structures.  Both lists and arrays consist of ordered, mutable items – but arrays contain items of the same type, while lists can store multiple types of items.  In this article, we will learn how to reverse an array using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Convert a String to an Integer in C# – with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-a-string-to-an-integer-in-c-sharp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-a-string-to-an-integer-in-c-sharp/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-23T23:22:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are various situations where you need to convert a string to a number. Whether you are working with user input or data from an external source, converting a string to a number is a common task for developers. This article will explore some of the most common methods to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Unhide a Row or Column in Excel – Or Unhide All Rows and Columns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-unhide-a-row-or-column-in-excel-or-unhide-all-rows-and-columns/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-unhide-a-row-or-column-in-excel-or-unhide-all-rows-and-columns/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-23T22:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re working with a spreadsheet that contains sensitive or private data, then some rows and columns might be hidden. You might also need to hide unimportant information or data you don’t want others to see in your own spreadsheet. In these cases, you might need to unhide those hidden]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Company Should Be Using Log Management Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-you-should-use-log-management-software/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-you-should-use-log-management-software/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-23T21:24:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Logging, safeguarding, and utilizing data is a massive part of any software development operation. And chronological records of events have become an invaluable tool for determining future decisions. Today, we're fortunate enough to have the concept of system logs, which represents a collection of files. These files have data crucial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrej Kovacevic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Virtual Inheritance?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-virtual-inheritance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-virtual-inheritance/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-23T21:09:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C++ supports the concept of inheritance – that is, a class can inherit properties from other classes.  But sometimes you might need to use what is commonly referred as virtual inheritance.  In this article we will discuss when you might need to use virtual inheritance and how to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhilekh Gautam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bad Website Club (and more free Bootcamps)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-bad-website-club-and-more-free-bootcamps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-bad-website-club-and-more-free-bootcamps/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-23T15:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past 24 months Ramón Huidobro [https://twitter.com/hola_soy_milk] and I have been running free programming bootcamps teaching web development and JavaScript skills.  We've been stunned by the demand for these courses, which averaged 8,000 learners per cohort and let us reach 35,000 unique learners in total.  We've also]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Rose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Tokenization using JWT and Django Rest Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-jwt-and-django-rest-framework-to-get-tokens/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-jwt-and-django-rest-framework-to-get-tokens/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-23T15:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I was a young girl, we used to have sports competitions like running a hundred meters, relays, swimming, and basketball games.  My strengths were swimming and basketball. I went home with many gifts or, as my school's game master said, a token of appreciation. A token is a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Velda Kiara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Linux, Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-linux-part-2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-linux-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-23T13:49:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this comprehensive course, you'll learn many of the tools used every day by both Linux SysAdmins and the millions of people running Linux distributions like Ubuntu on their PCs. This course will teach you how to navigate Linux's Graphical User Interfaces and powerful command line tool ecosystem. This is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-linux/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-23T13:49:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're new to Linux, this course is for you. In this comprehensive course, you'll learn many of the tools used every day by both Linux SysAdmins and the millions of people running Linux distributions like Ubuntu on their PCs. This course will teach you how to navigate Linux's Graphical]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Nested Functions in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nested-functions-in-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nested-functions-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-23T01:49:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data analysis is an extremely valuable skill to have. But to make the most of your analysis, it's invaluable to get your data neat and orderly.  In this article, I'll show you how to combine several functions together to better organize your data. gif of toys talking to each]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Future-Proof High-Performance Websites With Astro Islands And Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/building-future-proof-high-performance-websites-astro-islands-headless-cms-storyblok/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/building-future-proof-high-performance-websites-astro-islands-headless-cms-storyblok/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-22T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s see how to achieve phenomenal web performance and great developer experience with Astro and a headless CMS, resulting in the best possible experience for users, developers and content creators alike.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Manuel Schröder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a 3D Tilting Card Effect in React Native]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-3d-tilting-card-in-react-native/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-3d-tilting-card-in-react-native/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-22T16:35:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I came across a tutorial about how to create a 3D tilting card effect (with mouse tracking functionality) on Kevin Powell's YouTube channel [https://www.youtube.com/@KevinPowell]. Kevin used HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to create the markup, style the card, and implement the mouse tracking functionality, respectively. In this tutorial, we'll take]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kingsley Ubah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Remote Branch in Git? How to Check out Remote Branches from GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/remote-branches-in-git/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/remote-branches-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-22T16:22:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a free and open-source tool. Specifically, it is the most popular version control system used in software development today. Git allows you to keep track of and maintain different versions of a coding project. With Git, developers and technical teams can collaborate and work together on a project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ValueError: math domain error [Solved Python Error]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/valueerror-python-math-domain-error-solved/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/valueerror-python-math-domain-error-solved/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-22T16:11:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In mathematics, there are certain operations that are considered to be mathematically undefined operations.  Some examples of these undefined operations are:  * The square root of a negative number (√-2).   * A divisor with a value of zero (20/0).  The "ValueError: math domain error" error]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open-Closed Principle – SOLID Architecture Concept Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/open-closed-principle-solid-architecture-concept-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/open-closed-principle-solid-architecture-concept-explained/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-22T15:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Open-Closed principle (OCP) is one the 5 SOLID design principles. It was popularized by the American computer scientist and instructor, Robert C. Martin (aka Uncle Bob) in a paper he published in 2000. The other 4 SOLID design principles are:  * Single Responsibility Principle (SRP)  * Liskov]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Build Your Own Open-Source Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-build-your-own-open-source-project/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-build-your-own-open-source-project/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-22T15:41:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After starting to learn about Open Source and making some good contributions during my first Hacktoberfest, I was moving ahead in my OSS journey.  I wanted to have a big project of my own to which others could contribute. Fortunately, I had an idea for a project, and decided]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prakhar Tiwari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Remove Key from Dictionary – How to Delete Keys from a Dict]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-remove-key-from-dictionary/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-remove-key-from-dictionary/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-22T15:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dictionaries are a useful data type in Python for storing data in a key-value format. And there are times when you might need to remove a particular key-value pair from a dictionary.  You'll learn some dictionary basics, as well as how to delete keys, in this tutorial. How to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chocolate, Waffles And Fries: Meet SmashingConf Antwerp 2023 🇧🇪]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/meet-smashingconf-antwerp/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/meet-smashingconf-antwerp/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-22T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brand new conference on design & UX, for designers and UI engineers who love the web. On design systems, usability, product design and complex UIs. That’s SmashingConf Antwerp, taking place in magical Bourla on October 9–11, 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data-Driven Reality – Exploring the Power of AI, ML, Virtual and Augmented Reality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-driven-reality/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-driven-reality/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-21T22:57:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now it's no secret that digital data is generated by the truckload and that it can be worth its weight in gold.  But that knowledge isn't half as important as understanding how you can tame the data beast and then wring out every drop of its value. Naturally,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Difference Between Data Science and Data Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-science-vs-data-engineering/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-science-vs-data-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-21T22:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently became very interested in Data Science and Data Engineering, especially how they compare and complement each other.  I initially assumed Data Engineering was a subset of Data Science. But after extensive research I found out just how much the two fields differ. In this article, I'll discuss]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Gold</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Diff and Patch – Full Tutorial for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-diff-and-patch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-diff-and-patch/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-21T21:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many of the interesting processes in Git like merging, rebasing, or even committing are based on diffs and patches. Developers work with diffs all the time, whether using Git directly or relying on the IDE's diff view. In this post, you will learn what Git diffs and patches are, their]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use SQLite with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sqlite-python-beginners-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sqlite-python-beginners-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-21T21:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Databases are a crucial component in software development. After all, we need to collect data in a location where we can digitally access it for reading, writing, updating, and deleting. In this tutorial, you'll learn how to use SQLite with Python. Learning SQLite is a great way to learn how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eesa Zahed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use SQL Triggers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-triggers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-triggers/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-21T20:13:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MySQL Triggers are like JavaScript event listeners. They are not executed until an action that they have been told to listen for happens.  Here's a helpful description of them from the MySQL docs: > A trigger is a named database object that is associated with a table, and that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zubair Idris Aweda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Topic Modeling Tutorial – How to Use SVD and NMF in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-topic-modeling-how-to-use-svd-nmf-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-topic-modeling-how-to-use-svd-nmf-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-21T18:32:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the context of Natural Language Processing (NLP), topic modeling is an unsupervised learning problem whose goal is to find abstract topics in a collection of documents.  Topic Modeling answers the question: "Given a text corpus of many documents, can we find the abstract topics that the text is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bala Priya C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML & Coding Introduction – Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-coding-introduction-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-coding-introduction-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-21T16:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you interested in coding but have never tried it before? Are you curious about how to create your own website or app? If so, then this video course is for you! We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you the basics of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Internationalization (i18n) Right With Remix And Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/internationalization-i18n-right-remix-headless-cms-storyblok/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/internationalization-i18n-right-remix-headless-cms-storyblok/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-21T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article will show you the impact of internationalization, its fundamental logic, how to approach it with Remix, and optionally, how to manage it more conveniently using a headless CMS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani &amp; Arisa Fukuzaki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 57 With Marcin Wichary: What’s The Key To A Great Keyboard?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/smashing-podcast-episode-57/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/smashing-podcast-episode-57/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we ask what’s the key to a great keyboard? Is this essential part of our daily toolkit easily overlooked? Vitaly Friedman talks to expert Marcin Wichary to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code Pong in Python – a Step-By-Step Tutorial with Turtle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-pong-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-pong-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-20T21:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pong is a classic video game that has stood the test of time. It's a crowd favorite that many among you might recognise.  For the programmers out there, coding Pong in Python is a fun and challenging way to learn the language and basic concepts of game development. But]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Duggan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with MongoDB in Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mongodb-in-rust/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mongodb-in-rust/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-20T20:41:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MongoDB is a popular NoSQL database that has been gaining increasing popularity in recent years. It offers developers a flexible, scalable, and high-performance database solution, which can be used for a wide range of applications.  For Rust programmers, MongoDB provides an excellent option for storing and retrieving data in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chigozie Oduah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Test User Interactions Using the React Testing Library]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-test-user-interactions-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-test-user-interactions-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-20T19:12:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're testing different components in React, you’ll need to simulate user interactions with various parts of each component. In this tutorial, I am going to show you some methods to simulate user interactions with different interactive elements. Before getting started, make sure you know how to structure a test]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keys To An Accessibility Mindset]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/keys-accessibility-mindset/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/keys-accessibility-mindset/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An accessible product can be daunting to build as there’s so much nuance and technical depth to consider. In this article, Daniel Yuschick demonstrates three keys for approaching and developing accessible content without leaving you lost in the weeds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Daniel Yuschick)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Your Own Commands in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-your-own-command-in-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-your-own-command-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-17T23:04:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, let's learn about creating your own commands in Linux. Yes – we're going to talk about creating an alias command.  Before we begin, I want to tell you how the idea for this tutorial came about.  One of the followers of my blog asked me,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Identity – Build a Profile with Next.js, Ethereum & Ceramic Network]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/decentralized-identity-build-a-profile-with-ethereum-ceramic-and-reactjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/decentralized-identity-build-a-profile-with-ethereum-ceramic-and-reactjs/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-17T22:44:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Long-standing centralized intermediaries, like the government or big companies, are the ones who make and keep your ID information in traditional systems that manage who you are.  But this implies that you have no control over the information relating to your identification, who has access to personally identifiable information]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Idris Olubisi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning with Julia – How to Build and Deploy a Trained AI Model as a Web Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-using-julia/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-using-julia/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-17T22:33:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Julia [https://julialang.org/] is a general purpose programming language well suited for numerical analysis and computational science. Some consider it the future of machine learning and the most natural replacement for Python in this field. This article introduces the Julia language and its ecosystem. You'll learn how to use it to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrey Germanov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Asynchronous JavaScript Works]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/asynchronous-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/asynchronous-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-17T18:37:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn all about Asynchronous JavaScript.  But before we dive into that, we need to make sure you understand what Synchronous code is and how it works. What is Synchronous Code? When we write a program in JavaScript, it executes line by line. When a line]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Full Stack App with Next.js 13 and Firebase]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-full-stack-app-with-nextjs13-and-firebase/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-full-stack-app-with-nextjs13-and-firebase/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-17T17:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js is a React framework that makes building powerful full stack (front end + back end) applications a lot easier.  The team behind Next.js recently released Next.js 13 [https://nextjs.org/blog/next-13] which has a whole lot of futures like a new  app Directory, server and client components, and more. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spruce Emmanuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dot Notation vs Bracket Notation for Object Properties – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dot-notation-vs-square-brackets-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dot-notation-vs-square-brackets-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-17T16:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are multiple ways to access object properties in JavaScript. But two common ones are dot notation and bracket notation. I'll explain the difference between these two approaches in this article. With dot and bracket notation, you can:  * access the value of a property by its key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Dynamic Object Properties using Computed Property Names]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-dynamic-object-properties-using-computed-property-names/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-dynamic-object-properties-using-computed-property-names/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-17T16:53:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When declaring objects before ES6, you had to use static keys for properties. But since the release of ES6, you can use dynamic keys. I'll show you how they work in this article. What are Static and Dynamic Keys? What do I mean by static keys? Take a look at]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Step-By-Step Guide To Building Accessible Carousels]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/guide-building-accessible-carousels/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/guide-building-accessible-carousels/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-17T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most carousels come along with usability and accessibility issues. To avoid these issues, this article addresses step-by-step design considerations as well as semantic requirements for carousels to be accessible. It is intended to create an in-depth understanding of the implementation and its impact on users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sonja Weckenmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Filter an Array in JavaScript – JS Filtering for Arrays and Objects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/filter-arrays-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/filter-arrays-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-17T01:13:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When building a dynamic and interactive program, you may need to add some interactive features. For example, where a user clicks a button to filter through a long list of items. You may also need to manipulate a large array of data to return only items that match your specified]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhanced For Loops in Java – How to Use ForEach Loops on Arrays]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/enhanced-for-loops-in-java-how-to-use-foreach-loops-on-arrays/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/enhanced-for-loops-in-java-how-to-use-foreach-loops-on-arrays/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-17T00:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use enhanced loops in Java to achieve the same results as a for loop [/news/java-for-loop-example/]. An enhanced loop is also known as a for-each  loop in Java.  Enhanced loops simplify the way you create for loops. They are mostly used to iterate through an array or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Print Array Elements in a Given Order with or without a Function]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-print-array-elements-in-given-order-with-and-without-function/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-print-array-elements-in-given-order-with-and-without-function/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T21:58:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are learning to solve problems using a programming language, you've likely faced the problem of printing array elements in a given order or in reverse order. You might have also needed to do this by either using a user-defined function or not using any function at all. If]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Force Pull in GitHub – How to Overwrite on Local Changes with Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/force-pull-in-github-how-to-overwrite-on-local-changes-with-git/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/force-pull-in-github-how-to-overwrite-on-local-changes-with-git/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T17:32:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While working on a project as part of a team, you may get an error message telling you that you can't execute git pull on your repository because you have local changes. Why does this happen? This error usually occurs when several people are introducing updates to the same file.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[List Within a List in Python – How to Initialize a Nested List]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/list-within-a-list-in-python-initialize-a-nested-list/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/list-within-a-list-in-python-initialize-a-nested-list/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T17:24:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lists are a built-in data type in Python. And you can use them to store a collection of elements.  Lists are ordered, mutable, and contain elements of different data types, such as strings, integers, and other lists.  In Python, lists are a fundamental type of data structure that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOLID Design Principles in Software Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/solid-design-principles-in-software-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/solid-design-principles-in-software-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T17:11:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOLID is a set of five design principles. These principles help software developers design robust, testable, extensible, and maintainable object-oriented software systems. Each of these five design principles solves a particular problem that might arise while developing the software systems. In this article, I’ll show you what the SOLID principles]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Grainy CSS Backgrounds Using SVG Filters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/grainy-css-backgrounds-using-svg-filters/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/grainy-css-backgrounds-using-svg-filters/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T16:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article we're going to create more interesting website backgrounds by using grainy effects.  There's a full video walkthrough at the bottom of the article 👇, as well as a 15 second video in the middle for those of you who just want a quick soundbite. We'll cover]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Message Queues Work in Distributed Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/message-queues-in-distributed-systesms/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/message-queues-in-distributed-systesms/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T15:54:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From town criers to written letters and now real-time chat applications, humanity has always been on the lookout for innovative ways to communicate. And we can say the same about computers. There's an even greater need to allow computers to communicate with the increasing adoption of distributed architecture. This also]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nyior Clement</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Develop Database-Driven Web Apps with Python, Flask, and MySQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/develop-database-driven-web-apps-with-python-flask-and-mysql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/develop-database-driven-web-apps-with-python-flask-and-mysql/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to take your web development skills to the next level? Do you want to learn how to build dynamic database-driven web applications with Python, Flask, and MySQL?  We just published a comprehensive video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is designed to teach you how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Putting Gears In Motion: Animating Cars With HTML And SVG]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/putting-gears-motion-animating-cars-with-html-svg/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/putting-gears-motion-animating-cars-with-html-svg/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SVG `` provides a way to define how an element moves along a motion path. In this article, Paul Scanlon shares an idea of how to use it by animating race cars in an infinite loop as easy as one-two-three!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn JavaScript Effectively – Tips and Learning Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-learn-javascript-effectively/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-learn-javascript-effectively/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T17:21:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a widely used programming language that has ruled the software development technology stack for over a decade.  You can find JavaScript in web applications, mobile applications, or apps for your desktop. According to a survey done by Statista in 2022, JavaScript developer communities worldwide have about 17.4]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Anonymous Function – How to Use Lambda Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-lambda-functions-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-lambda-functions-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T17:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use functions in programming to store a piece of code that can be invoked when needed. This prevents you from retyping the same logic every time you need that code. In this article, you'll learn how to create and use anonymous functions in Python. They are also called]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Type Error vs Reference Error in JavaScript – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/type-error-vs-reference-error-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/type-error-vs-reference-error-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T17:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a JavaScript developer, you've likely encountered different types of errors while coding. Most of the time these will be type errors or reference errors. But have you ever wondered what they mean? Have you ever tried reading about the error type specified by the interpreter before solving these errors?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tejan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five Steps To Sell Your Product With Powerful Storytelling]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/sell-product-powerful-storytelling/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/sell-product-powerful-storytelling/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to apply powerful storytelling to design a compelling and memorable digital experience on a landing page. A case study of the [Smart Interface Design Patterns landing page](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Chiara Aliotta)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TensorFlow for Deep Learning – Basics for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tensorflow-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tensorflow-basics/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-14T23:46:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TensorFlow is a library that helps engineers build and train deep learning models. It provides all the tools we need to create neural networks. We can use TensorFlow to train simple to complex neural networks using large sets of data. TensorFlow is used in a variety of applications, from image]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prim's Algorithm – Explained with a Pseudocode Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prims-algorithm-explained-with-pseudocode/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prims-algorithm-explained-with-pseudocode/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-14T22:12:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Computer Science, Prim’s algorithm helps you find the minimum spanning tree of a graph. It is a greedy algorithm – meaning it selects the option available at the moment. In this article, I’ll show you the pseudocode representation of Prim’s algorithm. But before that, let’s take a deeper look]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Vim Is More than Just an Editor – Vim Language, Motions, and Modes Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vim-language-and-motions-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vim-language-and-motions-explained/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-14T19:52:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout my time as a developer, I've used VS Code, Sublime, Notepad++, TextMate, and others. But shortcuts like cmd(+shift)+end and jumping with  option+arrow-keys from word to word needed to be faster at some point.  I was hitting my limits. Everything I was doing I did decently fast, but]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simon Späti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Scrape Multiple Web Pages Using Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-scrape-multiple-web-pages-using-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-scrape-multiple-web-pages-using-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-14T19:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data is all around us. Every website you visit includes data in a readable format that you can utilize for a project.  And although you can easily copy and paste the data, the best approach for big amounts of data is to perform web scraping. Learning web scraping can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage Data Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manage-data-storage/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manage-data-storage/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-14T19:44:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've all been at this 21st Century thing for a while. And by now it's pretty clear that data is the big driver of, well, of everything.  Governments build their policies around economic and population data. Scientists build their theories around environmental, physical, and biological data. Businesses build their]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create an Animated Physics Game with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-an-animated-physics-game-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-an-animated-physics-game-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-14T18:54:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you interested in game development but don't know where to start? Do you want to create a unique and engaging game with interesting physics and artificial intelligence mechanics? If so, then our new video course is just what you need! We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How is == Different from === in JavaScript? Strict vs Loose Equality Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/loose-vs-strict-equality-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/loose-vs-strict-equality-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-14T18:09:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are reading this blog, you're probably learning JavaScript – and that's awesome. Double equals (==) and triple equals (===) in JavaScript often make beginners scratch their heads. This doesn't mean that you should fear JavaScript, in fact jargon like this makes JavaScript even more beautiful once you know]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sobit Prasad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exponent in Python – Power Function and Exponents Using a Loop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-bytes-to-string-how-to-convert-a-str-to-bytes-and-back-again/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-bytes-to-string-how-to-convert-a-str-to-bytes-and-back-again/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-14T17:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exponent of a number refers to the power to which that number should be raised. In this article, I'll show you how to find exponents using two ways: the power function and a loop. Exponents are usually written like this: Baseexponent Take an example like 103. This means, "10,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Configure a Laravel Project with a Custom Domain Name on Windows with XAMPP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/configure-a-laravel-project-with-custom-domain-name/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/configure-a-laravel-project-with-custom-domain-name/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-14T02:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Laravel's simplicity and MVC architecture make it an ideal PHP framework for building web applications.  In this article, I will show you how to set up Laravel on your Windows machine and configure it to run on a custom domain name. This guide is best suited for a beginner]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdulwahab Ashimi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP Networking in JavaScript –Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/http-full-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/http-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-14T00:42:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP is the backbone of the modern internet. In this text-based course, you'll learn how the HTTP protocol works and how it's used in real-world web development. All the code samples for this course are in JavaScript, but the networking concepts you'll learn here apply generally to all coding languages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Wagner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OWASP Top 10 Vulnerabilities – A Guide for Pen-Testers & Bug Bounty Hunters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/owasp-top-10-vulnerabilities/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/owasp-top-10-vulnerabilities/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-13T23:44:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will look at OWASP and the top 10 web application vulnerabilities they've identified. This is a useful topic for both web app pen-testers and bug bounty hunters. What do web app pen-testers and bug bounty hunters have in common? They are both hunting for bugs, but]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Cognito for Web Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-cognito-for-web-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-cognito-for-web-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-13T22:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Cognito [https://aws.amazon.com/cognito/] is a cloud-based, serverless solution for identity and access management. It provides capabilities similar to  Auth0 [https://aws.amazon.com/cognito/] and Okta [https://aws.amazon.com/cognito/].  Cognito is part of the AWS suite of services so you can easily incorporate it if you are already using AWS in other parts of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Rohde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asynchronous Programming in JavaScript for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/asynchronism-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/asynchronism-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-13T16:15:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we're going to take a look at a key topic when it comes to programming: managing asynchronism. We'll start by giving a theoretical foundation about what asynchronism is, and how it relates to key components of JavasScript: The execution thread, the call stack and the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Approach to Lazy Loading Custom Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376991</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/an-approach-to-lazy-loading-custom-elements/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-13T15:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re fans of Custom Elements around here. Their design makes them particularly amenable to lazy loading, which can be a boon for performance.
Inspired by a colleague’s experiments, I recently set about writing a simple auto-loader: Whenever a custom …
An Approach to Lazy Loading Custom Elements originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frederik Dohr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use MySQL Transactions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-mysql-transactions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-mysql-transactions/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-10T21:35:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Database Transaction and Why is it Important? A database transaction is a single area of the database where multiple data operations are carried out and written as a whole.  These operations can be create, read, update, or delete operations.  During the process of a transaction,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aisha Bukar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Modulo Operator – How to Use the Modulus in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-modulo-operator-how-to-use-the-modulus-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-modulo-operator-how-to-use-the-modulus-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-10T19:35:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, you may need to perform mathematical calculations such as determining if a number is even or odd, wrapping values within a range, and converting between degrees and radians in trigonometry. To help you perform all these mathematical calculations, the modulo operator can be extremely useful. This article will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get GitHub Pro and Replit Hacker for Free as a Student]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-github-pro-and-replit-hacker-for-free-as-a-student/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-github-pro-and-replit-hacker-for-free-as-a-student/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-10T17:47:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are in high school or college/university and are interested in coding, you should consider signing up for GitHub Education.  This allows you to use GitHub Pro, as well as having many other benefits.  In this quick guide, I'll show you the steps to sign up for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eesa Zahed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a REST API? API Endpoint Request Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-rest-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-rest-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-10T16:39:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An API (short for Application Programming Interface) allows for two or more applications to communicate with one another and send data back and forth. APIs operated based on a standardized set of rules and they're an integral component of modern-day software development. There are different API styles, and each one]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Set and Map in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-and-map-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-and-map-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-10T15:29:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are three major iterables available in JavaScript: Arrays, Maps, and Sets.  In this article, we will cover the following topics:   * What is an Array?  * What is a Set?  * What is a Map?  * How to Create a Set]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kamaldeen Lawal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Different Ways to Get CSS Gradient Shadows]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376764</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/different-ways-to-get-css-gradient-shadows/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-10T15:13:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a question I hear asked quite often: Is it possible to create shadows from gradients instead of solid colors? There is no specific CSS property that does this (believe me, I’ve looked) and any blog post you find about …
Different Ways to Get CSS Gradient Shadows originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discovering Primitive Objects In JavaScript (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/discovering-primitive-objects-javascript-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/discovering-primitive-objects-javascript-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-10T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first part of the series, Kirill Myshkin covers some aspects of JavaScript that help bring objects closer to primitive values, which allow benefiting from common language features that aren’t usually associated with an object, like comparisons and arithmetic operators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kirill Myshkin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Z-index Property Works – Stacking Order of Elements in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/z-index-property-and-stacking-order-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/z-index-property-and-stacking-order-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T22:48:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend engineers can testify that they sometimes face weird z-index bugs and end up spending hours trying to fix them.  Change one property here and you have your header flying away from where it was meant to be.  Well, we can attribute this to the fact that debugging]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Franklin Okolie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Search Files Effectively in the Linux Terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-search-files-in-the-linux-terminal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-search-files-in-the-linux-terminal/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T22:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever felt frustrated searching for files manually on your computer? If you’re a developer or DevOps engineer working on GUI-less Linux servers, it'll be hard navigating back and forth to find files. Many people are unaware of the power of Linux terminals. Linux has an incredibly powerful command]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Use Java for Backend Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-for-backend-web-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-for-backend-web-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T21:54:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Java is a well-established and widely-used programming language. You can use it to create desktop and mobile applications, for massive data processing, for backend development, to program embedded devices, and more.  Oracle, the company that owns Java, claims that Java is used on 3 billion devices worldwide, making it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Fagbuyiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Window Functions in SQL – with Example Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/window-functions-in-sql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/window-functions-in-sql/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T21:47:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Window functions are an advanced type of function in SQL. They let you work with observations more easily.  Window functions give you access to features like advanced analytics and data manipulation without the need to write complex queries. In this lesson you will learn about what window functions are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ibrahim Abayomi Ogunbiyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work with Branches in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-branches-in-git/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-branches-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T21:42:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the things we fell in love with when we saw our future backyard was the tree. The valley oak is the largest North American oak. It can grow to be 600 years old and 100 feet tall. It's known for its irregular, spreading branches. Speaking of branches...a key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Kurata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Healthcare, Selling Lemons, and the Price of Developer Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377169</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/healthcare-selling-lemons-and-the-price-of-developer-experience/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T19:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every now and then, a one blog post is published and it spurs a reaction or response in others that are, in turn, published as blogs posts, and a theme starts to emerge. That’s what happened this past week and …
Healthcare, Selling Lemons, and the Price of Developer Experience originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Git and GitHub in Spanish – Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-git-and-github-in-spanish-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-git-and-github-in-spanish-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T15:25:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi! If you speak Spanish and you want to learn Git and GitHub, you are in the right place. In this article, you will find a brief introduction to Git and GitHub. You will learn why they are very powerful tools and why you should learn them if your goal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moving Backgrounds]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376723</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/moving-backgrounds/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T15:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often think of background images as texture or something that provides contrast for legible content — in other words, not really content. If it was content, you’d probably reach for an <img> anyway, accessibility and whatnot.
But there are …
Moving Backgrounds originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saleh Mubashar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Picture Perfect: Meet Pixo, A Photo Editor For Your End Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/pixo-photo-editor/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/pixo-photo-editor/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With so many image editing services available nowadays, it’s good to have one good solution that is applicable for all websites and web apps that need to provide image editing as a feature. Hristo Chakarov explains how Pixo Editor’s easy integration (just a few JavaScript lines) and rich API can save your time and improve your end users’ workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Hristo Chakarov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Object-Oriented Programming in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-oriented-programming-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-oriented-programming-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T02:04:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Object-Oriented Programming is a programming style based on classes and objects. These group data (properties) and methods (actions) inside a box.  OOP was developed to make code more flexible and easier to maintain. JavaScript is prototype-based procedural language, which means it supports both functional and object-oriented programming. What are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python list.pop() – How to Pop an Element from a Array]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-pop-how-to-pop-an-element-from-a-array/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-pop-how-to-pop-an-element-from-a-array/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T01:31:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python has various built-in methods you can use to interact with elements stored in a list [/news/how-to-make-a-list-in-python-declare-lists-in-python-example/]. These methods let you add, access, modify, and remove elements.  In this article, you'll learn how to remove elements in a Python list using:  * The pop() method.  * The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Objects in JavaScript?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/objects-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/objects-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T19:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Objects are important data structures in JavaScript. This is partly because arrays are objects in JavaScript, and you'll use them all the time. Objects are super important for grouping data and functionalities, so you can do a lot with an object in JavaScript. The DOM node, and any DOM node]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kamaldeen Lawal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Encode and Decode HTML Base64 using JavaScript – JS Encoding Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/encode-decode-html-base64-using-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/encode-decode-html-base64-using-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T19:20:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When building an application or writing a program, you may need to encode or decode with HTML Base64 in JavaScript. This is possible thanks to two Base64 helper functions that are part of the HTML specification and are supported by all modern browsers. In this article, you will learn about]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn to Code a BuzzFeed Clone in Three Ways (JavaScript, React, TypeScript)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-how-to-code-a-buzzfeed-clone-in-three-ways/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-how-to-code-a-buzzfeed-clone-in-three-ways/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T17:06:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking to level up your web development skills? Do you want to know how to build a BuzzFeed clone in three different technologies? Look no further!  We just published a 4-hour video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to code a BuzzFeed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Designers Should Ask For (And Receive) High-Quality Feedback]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/designers-ask-receive-high-quality-feedback/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/designers-ask-receive-high-quality-feedback/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Andy Budd shares his way of requesting feedback: rather than sharing a linear case study that explains every design revision, the first thing to do would be to better frame the problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andy Budd)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Secure APIs with Flask and Auth0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-secure-apis-with-flask-and-auth0/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-secure-apis-with-flask-and-auth0/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T00:32:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[APIs are at the heart of modern development. They support all kinds of systems, from mobile, web, and desktop applications, to IoT devices and self-driving cars. They are a bridge between your clients and your application logic and storage.  This central access point to your application’s data raises the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Cruz Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Hide API Keys in Frontend Apps using Netlify Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hide-api-keys-in-frontend-apps-using-netlify-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hide-api-keys-in-frontend-apps-using-netlify-functions/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T23:46:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netlify is a popular web development platform that makes it easier to build, deploy, and manage websites.  You can use Netlify to host websites, and it helps you update and release new changes. It also provides additional features such as security, user authentication and authorization services, and more. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Franklin Ohaegbulam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOOKUP Functions in Google Sheets and Excel – VLOOKUP, XLOOKUP, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/lookup-functions-in-excel-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/lookup-functions-in-excel-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T20:47:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are several ways to lookup data in a spreadsheet. If you're building a dashboard, you'll find this very useful.  The =XLOOKUP() function is my new favorite way to lookup data. It's discussed in the last section 👇. We'll look at four of the built in lookup functions in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Modern Compute Platforms Work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/modern-compute-platforms/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/modern-compute-platforms/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T20:22:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way things sit now, if you were somehow allergic to computers, you'd be hard pressed to really banish them from your life, no matter where you found yourself.  Taking a quiet walk in the woods? What about the smartphone in your pocket. Left the phone in the car?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java For Loop Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-for-loop-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-for-loop-example/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T17:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use loops in programming to carry out a set of instructions repeatedly until a certain condition is met. There are three types of loops in Java:   * for loop.  * while loop.   * do...while loop. In this article, we'll focus on the for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The truth about CSS selector performance]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376659</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-truth-about-css-selector-performance/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T15:59:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Geez, leave it to Patrick Brosset to talk CSS performance in the most approachable and practical way possible. Not that CSS is always what’s gunking up the speed, or even the lowest hanging fruit when it comes to improving …
The truth about CSS selector performance originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 56 With Veerle Pieters: How Has The Design Industry Changed?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/smashing-podcast-episode-56/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/smashing-podcast-episode-56/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast we ask how has the design industry changed? Is technology making our work easier? Vitaly Friedman talks to veteran designer Veerle Pieters to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[APIs for Beginners Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/apis-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/apis-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T17:57:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[APIs, or Application Programming Interfaces, are a critical component of web development and programming. They provide a way for different applications and systems to communicate with each other, exchanging data and enabling functionalities. We just published an API basics course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This is an updated version]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a CRUD Command Line Application With Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-command-line-application-with-nodejs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-command-line-application-with-nodejs/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T15:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're looking for a tutorial to teach you the basics of Nodejs [https://nodejs.org/en/] and the command line, you're in the right place. You can use JavaScript to build almost any software (web, mobile, bots, and so on). The reason is that computers no longer depend on browsers only to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Njoku Samson Ebere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Double Emphasis Thing]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376548</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-double-emphasis-thing/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T15:06:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to have this boss who loved, loved, loved, loved to emphasize words. This was way back before we used a WYSIWYG editors and I’d have to handcode that crap.
<pI used to have this 
…
The Double Emphasis Thing originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Magazine Layout With CSS Grid Areas]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/build-magazine-layout-css-grid-areas/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/build-magazine-layout-css-grid-areas/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web development, especially what you can do with CSS, has become increasingly complex. With the added capabilities of CSS Grid, it is now possible to achieve layouts that look like they were laid out by hand. Let’s tackle a practical example of how to do something like that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jennifer Brehm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Apache Kafka Handbook – How to Get Started Using Kafka]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/apache-kafka-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/apache-kafka-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T23:48:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Kafka is an open-source event streaming platform that can transport huge volumes of data at very low latency.  Companies like LinkedIn, Uber, and Netflix use Kafka to process trillions of events and petabtyes of data each day. Kafka was originally developed at LinkedIn [https://engineering.linkedin.com/27/project-kafka-distributed-publish-subscribe-messaging-system-reaches-v06] , to help handle]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gerard Hynes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a React Admin Panel with Refine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-react-admin-panel-with-refine/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-react-admin-panel-with-refine/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T23:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is a popular front-end framework for building interactive user interfaces. It has helped revolutionize the development of data-intensive front-end applications. React's declarative nature makes building user interfaces intuitive. And reusable React components increase development speed and reduce time to production. To further improve the development experience when building user]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Mawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a String in JS? The JavaScript String Variable Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-string-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-string-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T19:26:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When learning JaveScript or any programming language, you'll encounter the keyword or term string. A string represents textual data, which is a fundamental part of many applications. You can also use strings to interact with users through prompts, alerts, and other forms of user input and output. In this article,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Automation Scripts You Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-automation-scripts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-automation-scripts/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T18:36:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all have those same old boring tasks that we do over and over again. Fortunately, we can automate some of these processes so that we can focus on doing other things that really need our energy and attention. In this article, we will talk about some Python automation scripts]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Fancy Hover Effect For Your Avatar]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376676</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-fancy-hover-effect-for-your-avatar/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T15:11:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you know that kind of effect where someone’s head is poking through a circle or hole? The famous Porky Pig animation where he waves goodbye while popping out of a series of red rings is the perfect example, and …
A Fancy Hover Effect For Your Avatar originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage Linux Processes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manage-linux-processes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manage-linux-processes/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T00:07:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all follow certain processes to achieve our goals. Similarly, every system has its own processes to accomplish tasks.  Every program or command that executes in a Linux system is called a process. In this tutorial, let's explore processes and how we can manage them in Linux. What is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Data Structures and Algorithms – Introduction and Learning Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-data-structures-and-algorithms/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-data-structures-and-algorithms/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T23:51:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data structures and algorithms (DSA) are an important aspect of any programming language. Every language has its own data structures and its way of handling different types of algorithms. So, as a programmer, no matter what programming language you are working with, data structures and algorithms have to be an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Native Tutorial – How to Create a Simple Responsive Layout for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/responsive-layout-react-native/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/responsive-layout-react-native/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T23:50:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having a responsive layout is an important component of user interface (UI) design. It enables a website or application to automatically adjust its size and layout based on the size of the user's device and screen. This provides an optimal viewing experience.  Responsive layouts also give the user a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kingsley Ubah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Calculator App Using React Native – A Step-by-Step Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-calculator-app-using-react-native-a-step-by-step-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-calculator-app-using-react-native-a-step-by-step-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T19:29:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A calculator application is a simple application that is always available on every Android, iOS, and desktop device.  In this article, we will build a calculator application using React Native and Expo. So why are we using these tools?  React Native is a JavaScript-based framework you can use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muhammad Adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Django by Building a Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-django-by-building-a-marketplace/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-django-by-building-a-marketplace/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T19:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Django is a powerful and popular web framework for Python. It is used to build robust and scalable web applications with ease. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you learn Django through building your own online marketplace. Stein from Code with Stein teaches]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computer Basics for Absolute Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/computer-basics-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/computer-basics-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T19:21:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You have to start somewhere when learning about computers. We just published a comprehensive video course on the freeCodeCamp.org channel designed to help you develop a solid foundation in computer and technology skills. This course is for anyone who is brand new to working with computers or for those who]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Escape a String in JavaScript – JS Escaping Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-escape-strings-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-escape-strings-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T19:05:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, a string is a data type representing a sequence of characters that may consist of letters, numbers, symbols, words, or sentences. Strings are used to represent text-based data and are mostly defined using either single quotes (') or double quotes ("). let name1 = 'John Doe'; let name2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fall-Through in JavaScript Switch Statements – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fall-through-in-javascript-switch-statements/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fall-through-in-javascript-switch-statements/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T17:42:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Switch statements in JavaScript have a behavior called fall-through which can cause unexpected results. I will explain what this behavior is, how to avoid it, and use cases for it. Switch statements allow you to create conditional statements in JavaScript. You have a conditional expression, and depending on the returned]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python String to Datetime – How to Convert an Str to a Date Time with Strptime]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-string-to-datetime-how-to-convert-an-str-to-a-date-time-with-strptime/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-string-to-datetime-how-to-convert-an-str-to-a-date-time-with-strptime/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T15:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python offers a variety of built-in modules that you can include in your program. A module is a Python file containing the necessary code to execute an individual functionality. This file is imported into your application to help you perform a specific task. One of those modules is the datetime]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcasts For UX Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/podcasts-ux-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/podcasts-ux-designers/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Podcasts are a fantastic opportunity to get up close with the people who know their craft. In this post, we compiled podcasts that are bound to provide valuable insights into UX and new perspectives on the field. Perfect for a short coffee break or a long commute.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Host A WordPress Site On Amazon Lightsail]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/host-wordpress-site-amazon-lightsail/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/host-wordpress-site-amazon-lightsail/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lightsail provides all the power we need to host our websites, as we are used to from AWS, but making it way easier than ever before. In this article, Leonardo Losoviz explores how to launch a WordPress site in Lightsail in a quick and easy way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Apache Airflow on Windows without Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/install-apache-airflow-on-windows-without-docker/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/install-apache-airflow-on-windows-without-docker/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T00:18:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Airflow is a tool that helps you manage and schedule data pipelines. According to the documentation [https://airflow.apache.org/], it lets you "programmatically author, schedule, and monitor workflows."  Airflow is a crucial tool for data engineers and scientists. In this article, I'll show you how to install it on Windows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aviator Ifeanyichukwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Al Assistants That Help Your Productivity (Besides ChatGPT)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-assistants-for-productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-assistants-for-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T22:10:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT may be the talk of the town these days, but there are other AI assistants that can help you increase your productivity.  AI assistants are specialized artificial intelligence software programs designed to imitate human behavior and thinking. They are able to recognize objects, solve problems, and perform tasks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create and Publish an NPM Package – a Step-by-Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-and-publish-your-first-npm-package/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-and-publish-your-first-npm-package/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T21:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NPM is the largest software registry on the internet. There are over a million packages in the NPM Library.  Developers publish packages on NPM to share their code with others. And organisations also use NPM to share code internally. In this article, you will learn how to create a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Serialize Your Data in Kotlin and Jetpack Compose]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serializing-your-data-in-kotlin/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serializing-your-data-in-kotlin/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T21:19:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serialization is the process of transforming data that's in one format into another format that can be stored.  If you have ever worked with a database or fetching data from a server, this should all be familiar to you. If not, you have come to the right place.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Ben Rachel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caching Data in SvelteKit]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376634</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/caching-data-in-sveltekit/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T15:04:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My previous post was a broad overview of SvelteKit where we saw what a great tool it is for web development. This post will fork off what we did there and dive into every developer’s favorite topic: caching. So, …
Caching Data in SvelteKit originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding App Directory Architecture In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/understanding-app-directory-architecture-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/understanding-app-directory-architecture-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new App Directory architecture has been the main character of the recent Next.js release, which keeps bringing up many questions. In this article, Atila Fassina explores the advantages and pitfalls of this new strategy and reflects on whether you should use it in production now or not.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React.js vs React Native – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-js-vs-react-native-whats-the-difference/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-js-vs-react-native-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T00:41:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are React.js and React Native the same? If you're new to the world of web and mobile development, you might be wondering the same thing.  As a newbie, it's easy to assume that React.js are React Native are the same. After all, they both have "React" as part of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kingsley Ubah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the "this" Keyword in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-this-keyword-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-this-keyword-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T23:40:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone! In this article we're going to talk about the THIS keyword in Javascript.  This used to be a concept that confused me a little bit, so I'll try to break it down for you so you can understand its uses and in what situations can it be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asynchronous Programming in JavaScript – Guide for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/asynchronous-programming-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/asynchronous-programming-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T23:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To understand what asynchronous programming means, think about multiple people working on a project simultaneously, each on a different task. In traditional (synchronous) programming, each person would have to wait for the person before them to finish their task before starting their own.  But with asynchronous programming, everyone can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dickson Boateng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio vs Visual Studio Code – What's The Difference Between These IDE Code Editors?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/visual-studio-vs-visual-studio-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/visual-studio-vs-visual-studio-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T19:17:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first time I heard about “Visual Studio”, I thought it was the same as “Visual Studio Code”. I don’t know why Microsoft decided to confuse everyone with the names of those two development tools. But that’s a story for another day. “Visual Studio” and “Visual Studio Code” are not]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chart.js Tutorial – How to Make Pie and Doughnut Charts in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-pie-and-doughnut-charts-using-chartjs-in-angular/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-pie-and-doughnut-charts-using-chartjs-in-angular/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T17:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial we will learn how to create a simple pie and doughnut chart using the Chart.js library in an Angular application. What is Chart.js? Chart.js is a JavaScript library for building charts. It's designed to be intuitive and simple, but it's powerful enough to build complex visualizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Swatej Patil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Length of List – How to Find the Size of a List]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-length-of-list-how-to-find-the-size-of-a-list/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-length-of-list-how-to-find-the-size-of-a-list/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T16:56:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A list is a data structure in Python that contains multiple elements in a particular order. And sometimes you might need to get the size of a list. I'll show you how to do that in this article. How to Create a List in Python You can create lists in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Magic Of February (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-february-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-february-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new batch of desktop wallpapers is for you. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for February 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Scraping in JavaScript – How to Use Puppeteer to Scrape Web Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-scraping-in-javascript-with-puppeteer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-scraping-in-javascript-with-puppeteer/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T15:26:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the world of web scraping! Have you ever needed data from a website but found it hard to access it in a structured format? This is where web scraping comes in. Using scripts, we can extract the data we need from a website for various purposes, such as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaël Thomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How B2B Sales Help Us Understand Our Role As UX Designers Better]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/b2b-sales-understand-role-ux-designers-better/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/b2b-sales-understand-role-ux-designers-better/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout a customer journey (particularly in B2B), there will be interactions that are primarily between two people rather than a human and an interface. In this article, Paul Boag explains why you cannot improve the user experience without considering the entirety of the UX journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Unit Tests for Instance Methods in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-unit-tests-for-instance-methods-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-unit-tests-for-instance-methods-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T00:13:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tutorial will teach you how to write unit tests for instance methods in Python. In a previous tutorial [/news/how-to-write-unit-tests-for-python-functions/], we covered how to write unit tests for Python functions. While unit testing for instance methods works similarly, you may have some challenges creating and managing objects (instances of a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bala Priya C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Require – How to Use the require() Function in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-javascript-require-function/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-javascript-require-function/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T00:07:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, modules refer to a file that holds JavaScript code which performs a specific purpose. Modules are self-contained, making it easy to add, remove, and update functionalities without affecting your entire code because they are decoupled from other pieces of code. When you have these modules in separate JavaScript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Dockerize an AdonisJS Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-dockerize-an-adonisjs-application/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-dockerize-an-adonisjs-application/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T00:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating software is hard. So you want to build it once and run it everywhere without adjusting configurations for different operating systems and machines every time. Well, this is one problem that dockerizing your application can help solve. Here's what we'll cover in this tutorial:  * What is Docker?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Solomon Eseme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Hooks Tutorial – How to Use the useReducer Hook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/usereducer-hook-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/usereducer-hook-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T23:15:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State is an important part of a React application. Most functionalities involve making state updates in your component.  But as your application grows, state updates become more and more complex. These complex state updates might get overwhelming when you revisit your code. There is a different way of handling]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find a Remote Developer Job in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-a-remote-developer-job/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-a-remote-developer-job/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T22:09:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the world continues to adapt to the new normal of remote work, the demand for remote developers has never been higher.  Companies are now realizing the benefits of hiring remote workers, including cost savings and access to a wider pool of talent.  If you're looking for a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Field</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java List – Example Lists in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-lists-work-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-lists-work-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T18:09:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use the Java List interface to store objects/elements in a an ordered collection. It extends the Collection interface.  TheList interface provides us with various methods for inserting, accessing, and deleting elements in a collection. In this article, you'll learn how to extend and implement the List interface]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Sheets Tutorial – How to Enable Multiple Selection Data Validation Using Apps Script]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-sheets-multiple-data-validation-selections/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-sheets-multiple-data-validation-selections/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T17:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I will show you how to allow for multiple items to be selected using the drop-down data validation feature in Google Sheets. Here's the Google Sheet [https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1yxc4k1x5idcS_moQ1Bq8LnHGZF2nm9dpARglY7Rv0UI/edit#gid=390071620]  we'll use for the example. You can make a copy of this to edit yourself by clicking File ->]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where Hot Trends Go to Die – What We Can Learn from Failed Tech Products]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/where-hot-tech-trends-go-to-die/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/where-hot-tech-trends-go-to-die/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T17:17:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're interested in technology, you may also have an active interest in learning about hot technology trends.  But you don't want to take every last one of these gadgets and business fads too seriously: some are bound to disappoint.  (Although don't think you can hold me personally]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TypeScript in React Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/using-typescript-in-react-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/using-typescript-in-react-apps/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T16:59:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! A while ago I wrote an article about TypeScript [/news/an-introduction-to-typescript/], explaining its main features and why it's a good idea to use it in large projects.  Today we're going to take a quick look at how we can use TypeScript in a React app, so you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master the HTTP Networking Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/http-networking-protocol-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/http-networking-protocol-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T16:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP (Hypertext Transfer Protocol) is the foundation of data communication on the World Wide Web. It is used to transfer data from the client (web browser) to the server (web host) and vice versa. Understanding the basics of HTTP networking is crucial for anyone who wants to pursue a career]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Vim – Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vim-beginners-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vim-beginners-guide/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T16:08:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vim is one of the most popular text editors among Linux users. Linux System Administrators especially often prefer it to other editors.  In this article, you'll learn a lot about Vim and see how you can quickly start using Vim as a developer. What is Vim?  Vim is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easy SVG Customization And Animation: A Practical Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/svg-customization-animation-practical-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/svg-customization-animation-practical-guide/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers often feel discouraged from editing SVG markup and experimenting with SVG animations, thinking it’s a significant time investment or they need to use a complex animation library to do so. In this article, Adrian showcases his favorite tricks, which make the process streamlined and fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AR, VR, and a Model for 3D in HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376674</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/ar-vr-and-a-model-for-3d-in-html/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-27T14:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tucked down somewhere in the Safari Technology Preview 161 release notes is a seemingly innocous line about support for a new HTML element and attribute:
Added support for <model src> and honor <source type> attributes (257518@main)
Anytime I …
AR, VR, and a Model for 3D in HTML originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>