<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-03-25T01:00:06.760Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to SSH into a Docker Container – Secure Shell vs Docker Attach]]></title>
        <id>6234b763cdcd57069ddfb192</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-ssh-into-a-docker-container-secure-shell-vs-docker-attach/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T19:47:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers are the bread and butter for running applications today. And the most popular container technology is called Docker [https://www.docker.com/].  Knowing how to SSH into a container is essential to using, debugging, and operating containers on your local operating system or remote setup.  This article will describe different]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sigl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Int Object is Not Iterable – Python Error [Solved]]]></title>
        <id>623c45ea138a19064b064195</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/int-object-is-not-iterable-python-error-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T16:46:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are running your Python code and you see the error “TypeError: 'int' object is not iterable”, it means you are trying to loop through an integer or other data type that loops cannot work on. In Python, iterable data are lists, tuples, sets, dictionaries, and so on. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Microservices with FastAPI]]></title>
        <id>623c9dd5138a19064b06449b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-microservices-with-fastapi/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T16:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FastAPI is a Web framework for developing RESTful APIs in Python. It is a great choice when you want to build an app based on microservices. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to develop microservices app using FastAPI. In this course,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[indexOf in Java – How to Find the Index of a String in Java]]></title>
        <id>62389b37cdcd57069ddfc5a0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/indexof-in-java-how-to-find-the-index-of-a-string-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T16:11:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A string is a collection of characters nested in double quotes. The indexOf  method returns the index position of a specified character or substring in a string. In this article, we'll see the syntax for the different indexOf methods. We'll also look at some examples to help you understand]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use UISearchController in iOS Apps]]></title>
        <id>62388dc7cdcd57069ddfc4d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-use-uisearchcontroller-in-ios-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T15:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! In this article we are going to learn how to use UISearchController in iOS Apps. What are we going to build? We are going to build a movie search application which uses the TMDB [https://www.themoviedb.org/] API to fetch movie info and display it using a UICollectionView based on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sai Balaji K</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a List in Python – Lists in Python Syntax]]></title>
        <id>623af0d3cdcd57069ddfd5bb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-list-in-python-lists-in-python-syntax/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T20:32:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lists are one of the core data structures in Python. We use them for storing any data type, whether it's an integer, string, boolean, or even an object. Because one list can store multiple types of data, lists are one of the most powerful and widely used tools for storing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Security – Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures for K8s Programs]]></title>
        <id>6230d789c3e3d106805db72a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kubernetes-security-common-vulnerabilities-and-exposures/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T19:06:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes has become the go-to tool for orchestration, scaling, automated deployment, and management of containerized applications.  Simply put, Kubernetes is a system that maintains coordination between diverse applications across a group of machines. It is important to note that this system mostly deals with containerized applications, like Docker images.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prajwal Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use *args and **kwargs in Python]]></title>
        <id>623a9306cdcd57069ddfd494</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/args-and-kwargs-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T18:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll discuss *args and **kwargs in Python along with their uses and some examples. When writing a function, we often need to pass values to the function. These values are called function arguments.  Problem with Function Arguments Let's define a function to add two numbers in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add a MetaMask Login to Your Laravel Web Application]]></title>
        <id>6238bd3dcdcd57069ddfc5ad</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/add-a-metamask-login-to-your-laravel-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T18:38:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Logging into a website via third parties is ubiquitous online. Almost every other member-based website allows you to log in with accounts like Facebook, Twitter, and Google. If you’ve ever visited NFT marketplaces like OpenSea or Rarible, you would have noticed they allow you to sign in with a crypto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darren Chowles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Those HTML Attributes You Never Use]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/html-attributes-you-never-use/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/html-attributes-you-never-use/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Louis Lazaris describes and demonstrates some interesting HTML attributes that you may or may not have heard of and perhaps find useful enough to personally use in one of your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taxes for Freelance Developers – How Much Tax You Should Pay as a Freelancer]]></title>
        <id>6238d5a4cdcd57069ddfc7db</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/taxes-for-freelance-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T13:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disclaimer: This article should not be construed as advice for tax management or investment decisions.  Neither the author of this article, nor freeCodeCamp, are professionals in these areas. The discussion below is a matter of personal opinion only and you should discuss such matters with a licensed professional. If]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Ciciliano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is WordPress a Code or No-code Tool?]]></title>
        <id>6236e318cdcd57069ddfbc09</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/is-wordpress-a-code-or-no-code-tool/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T01:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress is an open-source content management system (CMS) for building any kind of website – an eCommerce site, a portfolio, a forum, and many more. WordPress started out as a simple platform for creating blogs, but today WordPress powers over 43% of the total websites on earth, and that number]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Else-If in Python – Python If Statement Example Syntax]]></title>
        <id>623848d7cdcd57069ddfc40d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/else-if-in-python-python-if-statement-example-syntax/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T20:41:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're coding, you need to be able to check certain conditions and change the control of the program execution accordingly.  Python provides many conditional statements for decision making, and if-else is one of them. In this blog post, we will learn:  1. The default order of execution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Go Programming by Building 11 Projects]]></title>
        <id>623a17b2cdcd57069ddfd0b3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-go-by-building-11-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T18:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Go programming language is an open-source and compiled language designed by Google. Go is popular for cloud-based or server-side applications. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you improve your Go skills by teaching you how to create eleven projects. Akhil Sharma developed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove the Start Text from PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>62358f0ccdcd57069ddfb8b4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-starting-text-from-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T17:18:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are using a Windows operating system, you have likely used the latest Windows PowerShell at least once.  Whenever you open the PowerShell, you get a text message inside the terminal which shows the terminal version, the link to download the latest PowerShell, and so on.  Sometimes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Design Is All About Good Timing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/design-is-all-about-good-timing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/design-is-all-about-good-timing/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this shorter series of articles, we highlight design patterns, techniques, and strategies to design better digital interfaces. You can also learn much more in [“Smart Interface Design Patterns”](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com/), a 6h-video course with 100s of hand-picked examples, curated by Vitaly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Operator – Logical Operators in Python]]></title>
        <id>62346eeacdcd57069ddfae72</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/operators-in-python-how-to-use-logical-operators-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T00:21:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Operators in any programming language are the basic building blocks using which we can construct powerful, complex statements for problem solving.  Python offers different types of operators, like arithmetic operators, logical operators, relational operators and so on. In this post, let's dive into logical operators in Python and learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suchandra Datta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage State in a React App – With Hooks, Redux, and More]]></title>
        <id>62376c2ecdcd57069ddfbf7f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manage-state-in-a-react-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T23:31:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi! In this article we'll take a look at the many ways you can manage state in a React app. We'll start by talking about what state is, and then go through the many tools you can use to manage it. We'll look at the simple useState hook and also]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code Extensions to Increase Developer Productivity]]></title>
        <id>6238da58cdcd57069ddfc85e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vs-code-extensions-to-increase-developer-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T20:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code is one of the most popular code editors used by software developers. While it has many great features built-in, there are a lot of extensions you can install to increase your productivity.  We just published a video on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write HTML, the HTML Way (Not the XHTML Way)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363745</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/write-html-the-html-way-not-the-xhtml-way/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T20:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may not use XHTML (anymore), but when you write HTML, you may be more influenced by XHTML than you think. You are very likely writing HTML, the XHTML way.
What is the XHTML way of writing HTML, and what …
Write HTML, the HTML Way (Not the XHTML Way) originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jens Oliver Meiert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Solve freeCodeCamp's Record Collection Challenge]]></title>
        <id>6236cc8acdcd57069ddfba7a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-solve-the-record-collection-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T18:14:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp's JavaScript certification [https://www.freecodecamp.org/learn/javascript-algorithms-and-data-structures/]  is filled with hundreds of interactive challenges. But one of the hardest ones to tackle for most beginners is the Record Collection [https://www.freecodecamp.org/learn/javascript-algorithms-and-data-structures/basic-javascript/record-collection] . In this article, I will walk you through Record Collection [https://www.freecodecamp.org/learn/javascript-algorithms-and-data-str]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chmod Command – How to Change File Permissions in Linux]]></title>
        <id>62375a8dcdcd57069ddfbec1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-change-file-permissions-with-the-chmod-command-on-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T15:33:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the first commands I learned on Linux was the touch command that creates a file using the command line.  If you ever try to create, for instance, a text file, all you have to do is type  touch filename.txt, press Enter, and the file is created]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Rosa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get the Current Time in Python with Datetime]]></title>
        <id>6236e160cdcd57069ddfbbbf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-the-current-time-in-python-with-datetime/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T13:52:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In your Python applications, you might want to work with time to add functionalities like timestamps, check the time of a user’s activity, and more. One of the modules that helps you work with date and time in Python is datetime. With the datetime module, you can get the current]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SyntaxError Unexpected EOF While Parsing Python Error [Solved]]]></title>
        <id>6237b189cdcd57069ddfc248</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/syntaxerror-unexpected-eof-while-parsing-python-error-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T13:47:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Error messages help us solve/fix problems in our code. But some error messages, when you first see them, may confuse you because they seem unclear.  One of these errors is the "SyntaxError: unexpected EOF while parsing" error you might get in Python. In this article, we'll see why this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows High Contrast Mode, Forced Colors Mode And CSS Custom Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/windows-high-contrast-colors-mode-css-custom-properties/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/windows-high-contrast-colors-mode-css-custom-properties/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Custom Properties can be used for far more than just color, and their values update in realtime, both via display mode updates and JavaScript logic. This is powerful stuff. Eric explains how modern CSS is a powerful piece of assistive technology that can thread into it to create flexible, maintainable and adaptive digital experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing SVG Patterns to Their Smallest Size]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364090</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/optimizing-svg-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-18T22:31:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently created a brick wall pattern as part of my #PetitePatterns series, a challenge where I create organic-looking patterns or textures in SVG within 560 bytes (or approximately the size of two tweets). To fit this constraint, I have …
Optimizing SVG Patterns to Their Smallest Size originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bence Szabó</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Compare Strings – How to Check for String Equality]]></title>
        <id>6233b95bcdcd57069ddfadb1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-compare-strings-how-to-check-for-string-equality/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-18T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When crafting the logic in your code, you may want to execute different commands depending on the similarities or differences between two or more strings.  In this article, we'll see various operators that can help us check if strings are equal or not. If two strings are equal, the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend VS Backend – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>6228643563ded806bb9e6f77</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/frontend-vs-backend-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-18T20:48:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the start of your web development journey, you will often hear about the frontend and the backend parts of an application. But what do these terms mean exactly? In this article, you will learn about the differences between the two by examining the frontend and backend separately. Here is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Make A Drag-and-Drop File Uploader With Vue.js 3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/drag-drop-file-uploader-vuejs-3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/drag-drop-file-uploader-vuejs-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-18T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building on a previous article on How to Build a Drag-and-Drop File Uploader, we’ll be adding some new features, but more importantly (maybe), we’ll be learning how to build it in Vue 3 and learn some best practices for Vue along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joseph Zimmerman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python String to Int – Convert a String Example]]></title>
        <id>62333a16cdcd57069ddfa7f3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-string-to-int-convert-a-string-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T23:53:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When creating a program, you may need to get numerical input from users and perform various mathematical operations on the value.  Similarly, there are cases where you might want to perform mathematical operations on string values.  In both cases, the values returned are strings so we cannot perform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn WebGPU – A next-generation graphics API for the web]]></title>
        <id>62322496cdcd57069ddfa225</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-webgpu-a-next-generation-graphics-api-for-the-web/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T21:33:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebGPU is the next-generation graphics API and future web standard for graphics and compute, aiming to provide modern 3D graphics and computation capabilities with the GPU acceleration. We just published a WebGPU course on the freeCodeCmap.org YouTube channel.  Dr. Jack Xu developed this course. Dr. Xu has over 25]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Search for Files from the Linux Command Line]]></title>
        <id>62331abccdcd57069ddfa72f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-search-for-files-from-the-linux-command-line/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T19:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Searching for files is relatively easy when you are using a GUI. But in certain environments like GUI-less servers, you need to search for files using the command line.  There is a powerful command in Linux that helps you search for files and folders called find. In this article,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS REM – What is REM in CSS?]]></title>
        <id>621d17ecc4d0d306772f1b2f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-rem-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T19:47:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I'm going to discuss some use cases of REM (Root EM) in CSS.  I will begin with some background knowledge about CSS properties and values, which I think is necessary. Then I'll discuss the differences between absolute length values and relative ones. REM is a relative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slimane Aguersif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Sleep – time.sleep() in Python]]></title>
        <id>623308b9cdcd57069ddfa696</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-sleep-time-sleep-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T17:22:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While running a Python program, there might be times when you'd like to delay the execution of the program for some seconds. The Python time module has a built-in function called time.sleep() with which you can delay the execution of a program. With the sleep() function, you can get more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Portfolio Website Using HTML, CSS, & JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>6233481fcdcd57069ddfa86c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-portfolio-website-using-html-css-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T14:49:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are looking for a web developer job it can be helpful to have a portfolio website. It can also be helpful to have projects you've created to show to potential employers. You can accomplish both tasks at once by creating your own portfolio website with HTML, CSS, &]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Contact Book Application in Python using Rich, Typer, and TinyDB]]></title>
        <id>6231a5b3c3e3d106805db9fc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-contact-book-application-in-python-using-rich-typer-and-tinydb/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T00:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Python tutorial, we'll learn how to build a terminal application (CLI app) to manage our contact book.  We'll use Typer for building the CLI app, Rich for a colorized terminal output, and TinyDB for the database. Get your tools ready We'll be using a few external libraries]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Debugging? How to Debug Your Code for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>62321616cdcd57069ddfa114</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-debugging-how-to-debug-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T21:31:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article we'll talk about what debugging is, how to debug your code, and how you can get better at it. Table of contents  * How Debugging Started  * Why Should You Learn About Debugging?  * How to Debug Your Code  * How to Get]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Functions – How to Define and Call a Function]]></title>
        <id>6231fec0cdcd57069ddfa05d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-functions-define-and-call-a-function/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T17:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In programming, a function is a reusable block of code that executes a certain functionality when it is called. Functions are integral parts of every programming language because they help make your code more modular and reusable. In this article, I will show you how to define a function in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Python Crash Course]]></title>
        <id>623204d4cdcd57069ddfa080</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-python-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T15:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python is one of the most popular programming languages in the word. It is used everywhere from web development, to simple scripts, to machine learning and AI. We just published a Python tutorial on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you the basics of Python. Bobby Stearman developed this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claymorphism: Will It Stick Around?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/claymorphism-css-ui-design-trend/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/claymorphism-css-ui-design-trend/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This fresh new design trend has been picking up steam with the rising popularity of colorful inflated 3D graphics in web illustrations and with the latest Virtual Reality projects like “Horizon Worlds”. Let’s see if there is room for Claymorphism on the UI, and how we can create this effect with CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Get Last Element in List – How to Select the Last Item]]></title>
        <id>62310fbac3e3d106805db8d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-get-last-element-in-list-how-to-select-the-last-item/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T23:26:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lists are one of the built-in data types in Python. You use them to store multiple elements in one variable.  Lists enable us group similar data together, and we can also perform operations on these grouped elements at the same time. In this article, we will talk about how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Hooks Fundamentals for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>62245d2ac4d0d306772f4e3a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-hooks-fundamentals/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T19:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React.js is an open-source JavaScript-based user interface library. It is hugely popular for web and mobile app development.  React follows the principle of component-based architecture. A component in React is an isolated and reusable piece of code. The components can be of two types – class components and functional]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn React in Spanish – Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>6213cb7d21bfb3068cf2c271</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-react-in-spanish-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T15:41:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi! If you speak Spanish and you want you learn React, you're in the right place. In this article, you will find a brief introduction to React. You will learn why it is so important for web development and why you should learn it.  Then, you will find a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced OpenGL Animation Technique – Skeletal Animations with Assimp]]></title>
        <id>6230acbbc3e3d106805db524</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-opengl-animation-technique-skeletal-animations/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T15:37:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want your 3D animated characters to move in realistic-looking ways, you need to have a good understanding of skeletal animations. We just posted a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel well teach you how to do skeletal animations with OpenGL and the Assimp library. Etay Meiri created]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS-Tricks is joining DigitalOcean!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365042</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-tricks-is-joining-digitalocean/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T12:18:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey hey!
I’ve got a big announcement to make here. (Where’s my gong? I feel like this really needs a good gong hit.)
CSS-Tricks, this very website you’re looking at, has been acquired by DigitalOcean!
You can hear …
CSS-Tricks is joining DigitalOcean! originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Add to Dictionary – Adding an Item to a Dict]]></title>
        <id>622b887163ded806bb9e8566</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-add-to-dictionary-adding-an-item-to-a-dict/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T00:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data structures help us organize and store collections of data. Python has built-in data structures like Lists, Sets, Tuples and Dictionaries.  Each of these structures have their own syntax and methods for interacting with the data stored.  In this article, we'll talk about Dictionaries, their features, and how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose a Topic for Your Technical Article]]></title>
        <id>622ce4df63ded806bb9e8dae</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/choose-a-topic-for-your-next-article/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T23:52:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After you write your first couple of articles, a problem most technical writers face is: "So, what do I write about next?" It can be a frustrating question, so I wrote this article to help. In it, I will give you tips that will save you the headache the next]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Akinyemi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Plugins in Figma]]></title>
        <id>622acecd63ded806bb9e8101</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/plugins-in-figma/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T20:42:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll learn how to install plugins in Figma. You'll also get to know some really cool Figma plugins that every designer and developer should use.  Plugins help make your design process easier and smoother. From image assets to embedding maps into your designs, plugins are easy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove All Docker Images – A Docker Cleanup Guide]]></title>
        <id>622cecd663ded806bb9e8dfd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-all-docker-images-a-docker-cleanup-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T20:25:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers are everywhere in today’s tech world. The most popular technology for container management is Docker [https://www.docker.com/]. It makes using containers easy and helps you easily get applications up and running.  Unfortunately, this can take a lot of disk space, and you will eventually end up with a full]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sigl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perform CRUD Operations using Angular 13]]></title>
        <id>622c9d4363ded806bb9e8a9f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-perform-crud-operations-using-angular-13/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T19:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a full-stack application can be tough. And the base of building such an application is learning how to perform CRUD operations – Create, Read, Update, and Delete.  It's by using these operations that we manage the data flow between the client application and the server. So, in this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nishant Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Music for Programming – Coding Music Playlists, Radio Stations, Videos, and Lives]]></title>
        <id>622c7bf563ded806bb9e8a20</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/music-for-programming-youtube-channels-twitchtv-web-radios-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T19:16:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you like listening to music while you code? If so, you're in luck. This blog post is all about music for programming.  In this reference guide, I'll be sharing a variety of different playlists, radio stations, and videos that you can listen to while coding. Whether you're a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaël Thomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Compiler? Compilers in C Explained for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>62239491c4d0d306772f4a00</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-compiler-in-c/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T18:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that it is thanks to compilers that software exists? Exactly – compilers are very important, and some form of a compiler exists in all programming languages. But, what is a compiler? What do they do exactly? This article will teach you:  1. What a compiler is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Securely Erase a Disk and File using the Linux shred Command]]></title>
        <id>622b53f963ded806bb9e8436</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/securely-erasing-a-disk-and-file-using-linux-command-shred/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T14:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Removing files and formatting disks is a common task for users. And Linux provides a number of utilities to delete files and folders from the command line.  The most common command to delete files and folders is rm and rmdir, respectively. You can read in detail about the rm]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Dictionary in Python – Python Dict Methods]]></title>
        <id>6221c8d2c4d0d306772f3f43</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-dictionary-in-python-python-dict-methods/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T14:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn the basics of dictionaries in Python. You will learn how to create dictionaries, access the elements inside them, and how to modify them depending on your needs. You will also learn some of the most common built-in methods used on dictionaries. Here is what]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Break and Python Continue – How to Skip to the Next Function]]></title>
        <id>62134fa821bfb3068cf2bf43</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-break-and-python-continue-how-to-skip-to-the-next-function/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T13:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you ever need to skip part of the current loop you are in or break out of the loop completely, then you can use the break and continue statements. In this article, I will cover how to use the break and continue statements in your Python code. How to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The CI/CD Flow For Your Application]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/improving-ci-cd-flow-application/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/improving-ci-cd-flow-application/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for ways to create a smooth CI/CD flow for your software? In this article, Tom Hastjarjanto shares some useful concepts that can be combined with GitHub Actions and NPM packages. With this setup, you will be able to release multiple times per hour with a fully documented trace managed by Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tom Hastjarjanto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Comment Block – How to Comment Out Code in Python]]></title>
        <id>622ae68d63ded806bb9e81de</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-comment-block-how-to-comment-out-code-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-11T20:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll talk about comments in Python, why they are important, and how to use them effectively in your code.  When to Use Comments In this section, we'll talk about some of the general use cases for comments. These aren't only applicable to Python, but to most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a New Stacking Context with the Isolation Property in CSS]]></title>
        <id>61e5c35ab837d507ba0a4b06</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-css-isolation-property/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-11T20:03:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is the CSS Isolation Property? In CSS, you can use the isolation property to create a new stacking context. Here's what that looks like: .container-for-new-stacking-context {   isolation: isolate; } The default value for isolation is auto, which is a bit more nuanced as a stacking context can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie Pina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Concatenate Strings – How to Combine and Append Strings in Python]]></title>
        <id>622a2a6663ded806bb9e7d22</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-concatenate-strings-how-to-combine-and-append-strings-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-11T17:19:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're learning a programming language, you're likely to come across a data type called a string. A string usually contains a series of characters nested in quotation marks that can be represented as a text.  In this article, we will talk about string concatenation in Python. This is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Mobile App Marketing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/guide-mobile-app-marketing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/guide-mobile-app-marketing/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Standing out among the millions of mobile apps can be challenging, but proper marketing can give you that crucial edge. This piece shares how to start your mobile app marketing strategy and improve it as you go while keeping up with the latest trends in the market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sona Dabaghyan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CNCF Kubernetes and Cloud-Native Associate Study Course – Pass the Exam With This Free 13-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>6220e4a7c4d0d306772f366e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cncf-kubernetes-cloud-native-associate-exam-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T20:19:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This exam mostly deals with cloud-native concepts. Even if you are new to cloud-native, you should be able to prepare for this exam and earn the CNCF certification. This entire free course is now live on YouTube, and linked below. Before you dive into it, read this guide to help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Brown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CNCF Kubernetes and Cloud-Native Associate Study Course – Pass the Exam With This Free 13-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>6220e4a7c4d0d306772f366e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cncf-kubernetes-and-cloud-native-associate-study-course-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-13-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T20:19:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This exam mostly deals with cloud-native  concepts. Even if you are new to cloud-native, you should be able to prepare for this exam and earn the CNCF certification. This entire free course is now live on YouTube, and linked below. Before you dive into it, read this guide to help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Brown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Execute and Run Java Code from the Terminal]]></title>
        <id>6226651763ded806bb9e60eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-execute-and-run-java-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T19:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you work with Java, you've probably used one of the well known text editors like Sublime Text, VS Code, Brackets, Atom, and Notepad++ as well as IDEs like Apache NetBeans and IntelliJ IDEA.  Running code in your IDE is straightforward, but you don't often get to see how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Rename a Local or Remote Branch in Git]]></title>
        <id>622a09b763ded806bb9e7c6f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-rename-a-local-or-remote-branch-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T19:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a version control system that software developers use to keep track of changes in their applications and collaborate with others. One helpful feature of Git is branches. Different people working on a software project can work in different branches before merging their changes with the original code. You]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Print Without New Line – Print on the Same Line]]></title>
        <id>6228676363ded806bb9e6fa7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-print-without-new-line-print-on-the-same-line/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T18:11:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The print function is an important function in Python, as it is used to redirect output to the terminal. The output can also be redirected to a file.  The print function, by default, prints on a new line every time. This is due to the definition of print() in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/introduction-aws-cloud-development-kit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/introduction-aws-cloud-development-kit/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Vivek Maskara introduces Amazon Web Services’ (AWS) Cloud Development Kit (CDK) which is increasingly becoming a popular tool for managing AWS-based infrastructure. We’ll take a closer look into CDK concepts, and then how to use the AWS CDK toolkit to deploy a sample application to an AWS account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vivek Maskara)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Developed My First Adventure Game]]></title>
        <id>60c5b9d1d3126007592d75b4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-i-developed-my-first-game/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T20:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's hard to tell exactly when my journey creating Occulto, a point and click adventure game, started. But I have a significant date in mind: 3 May 2018. Here's one thing that got the ball rolling: > Luigi: Hello Andrea. Sorry to bother you. I would like to learn how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrea Koutifaris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[git config – How to Configure Git Settings to Improve Your Development Workflow]]></title>
        <id>6222908cc4d0d306772f4477</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-config-how-to-configure-git-settings/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T19:14:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[git config is a powerful command in Git. You can use the Git configuration file to customize how Git works. This file exists in the project level where Git is initialized ( /project/.git/config) or at the root level (~/.gitcongig). If no configurations are specified, Git uses its default settings. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React State for Absolute Beginners]]></title>
        <id>6216b67dc4d0d306772ef0ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-state/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T16:48:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most essential concepts that any modern JavaScript developer needs to understand is state.  If you don't understand state, you're not going to be able to fully use and take advantage of powerful libraries such as React to build your applications.  Let's see exactly what state]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Vim – Beginner's Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>6228c8f663ded806bb9e72e2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-vim-beginners-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T16:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vim is a highly configurable text editor that you can use for software development or any kind of text editing.  We just published a full Vim course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Vim. Florian Dedov from NeuralNine developed this course. When someone]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Audio Visualization With JavaScript And GSAP (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/audio-visualization-javascript-gsap-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/audio-visualization-javascript-gsap-part2/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What started as a case study turned into a guide to visualizing audio with JavaScript. Although the output demos are in React, Jhey Tompkins isn’t going to dwell on the React side of things too much. The underlying techniques work with or without React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Test PHP Code With PHPUnit]]></title>
        <id>62271f4863ded806bb9e65d2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/test-php-code-with-phpunit/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T01:15:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many different ways to test your software application, and unit testing is an important one. So what is unit testing and how can you do it? You'll learn that and more in this article. What is Unit Testing? > Unit testing is a software development process in which]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zubair Idris Aweda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Project Ideas to Improve Your Résumé]]></title>
        <id>6217b1bcc4d0d306772ef348</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-project-ideas-to-improve-your-resume/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T23:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every project is an opportunity to learn – to figure out problems and challenges, and to invent and reinvent. And as a developer, working on projects can improve not only your skills but also your résumé – which can increase your chances of getting that dream job. Have you ever]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hillary Nyakundi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coding Meaning – What does Coding Mean and What is it Used For?]]></title>
        <id>62273a7f63ded806bb9e6778</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/coding-meaning-what-does-coding-mean/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T21:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might have heard the term "coding" for a while now. It has changed the way we live and work, from automating tasks to helping people get well-paying jobs to support their families. If you want to learn about what coding means and what it is used for, you’ve come]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn HTML – Beginner's Course]]></title>
        <id>6227bf3463ded806bb9e6b72</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-html-beginners-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T20:56:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML is the backbone of every website on the internet. If you want to get into web development, learning HTML is the place to start. We just published a beginner's HTML video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. (And we still offer our free interactive HTML course [https://www.freecodecamp.org/learn/responsive-web-design/].) Dave Gray]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Live Streaming App for iOS and Android]]></title>
        <id>6227bd9e63ded806bb9e6b4a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-live-streaming-app-for-ios-and-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T20:38:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's easier than you may think to create a custom live steaming app. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Flutter and Agora.io to build a live streaming app that works on Android and iOS. Tadas Petra created this course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merge Sort Algorithm – Python and Java Examples with Time Complexity]]></title>
        <id>6225e82ec4d0d306772f5680</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/merge-sort-algorithm-python-and-java-examples-with-time-complexity/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T18:55:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we we talk about the merge sort algorithm. We will see some visual examples to help understand the algorithm and then implement it using Java and Python code. What Is a Merge Sort Algorithm? A merge sort algorithm is an efficient sorting algorithm based on the divide]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Pass the Certified Kubernetes Security Specialist Exam – Cheat sheet and Study Guide]]></title>
        <id>61ebda7f011f893303470580</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-pass-the-certified-kubernetes-security-specialist-exam/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T17:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is based on my experience studying for and passing the Certified Kubernetes Security Specialist exam. I passed the exam on my first attempt in Sep 2021. I passed the Certified Kubernetes Application Developer exam back in Feb 2020, followed by Certified Kubernetes Administrator in March 2020. The Certified]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Faizan Bashir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python .sort() – How to Sort a List in Python]]></title>
        <id>6221c8c0c4d0d306772f3f3f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-sort-how-to-sort-a-list-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T17:38:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to use Python's sort() list method. You will also learn a different way of performing sorting in Python by using the  sorted() function so you can see how it differs from sort(). By the end, you will know the basics of sorting]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Page Scroll to Top – How to Scroll to a Particular Section with React]]></title>
        <id>6223ced7c4d0d306772f4bf0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/scroll-to-top-bottom-and-particular-section-with-react/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T17:14:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're developing websites and applications using React and any React framework, you'll want to add certain features to help your users navigate your site. These features include scroll to top and scroll to bottom buttons, as well as the ability to scroll anywhere on the page. These functionalities are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Best Computer Science Courses to Take in 2022]]></title>
        <id>6224c1bbc4d0d306772f52f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-computer-science-courses/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T15:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking for the best introductions to computer science? I’ve ranked the top courses available online, following a robust methodology. And they're all free to audit. You can read about it below. But if you’re in a hurry, here are my top picks. Click on one to skip to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elham Nazif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeError String Indices Must be Integers Python Error [Solved]]]></title>
        <id>62134fb321bfb3068cf2bf47</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typeerror-string-indices-must-be-integers-javascript-error-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T23:28:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you try to access values from a dictionary or iterable object using the string value instead of the integer value then you will receive the following error message: TypeError: string indices must be integers In this article, I will show you examples of why you might receive this error]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software Testing – Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>620be72b21bfb3068cf28e55</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/software-testing-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T23:14:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Software Testing? Let's say you're working on a coding project. You have been writing a bunch of code and staying up late at night to fix bugs. All this is part of the process before you release that software product.  Then you'll check your code to verify]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maybell Obadoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Remove Character from a String – How to Delete Characters from Strings]]></title>
        <id>62134fbd21bfb3068cf2bf4b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-remove-character-from-a-string-how-to-delete-characters-from-strings/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T18:08:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python you can use the replace() and translate() methods to specify which characters you want to remove from a string and return a new modified string result.  It is important to remember that the original string will not be altered because strings are immutable.  In this article,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy a TensorFlow Model as a RESTful API Service]]></title>
        <id>62118afc21bfb3068cf2b63c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-an-ml-model-using-fastapi-and-docker/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T14:58:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're like I am, then you've probably watched and read a number of tutorials on creating machine learning models with TensorFlow, PyTorch, Scikit-Learn or any other framework out there.  But there is one thing that these tutorials tend to miss out on, and that's model deployment. In this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neil Ruaro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Signals For Customizing Website User Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/signals-customizing-website-user-experience/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/signals-customizing-website-user-experience/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using signals to deliver less, or different, content is a form of progressive enhancement (or graceful degradation depending on how you look at it), whereby extraneous content is only loaded when necessary, but the core functionality of the website still works. In this article, we’ll look at some of the signals that can be used for this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fullstack Development Project - Create a Blog with HTML & CSS]]></title>
        <id>62227173c4d0d306772f4441</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fullstack-development-project-create-a-blog-with-html-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-04T20:11:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's time for you to improve your HTML and CSS skills by creating a blog. We just posted a fullstack development course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build a blog with HTML and CSS. Julio Codes created this course. He has a popular YouTube]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Haskell Programming Language – How to Install and Use Haskell Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>6221b192c4d0d306772f3ed5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/haskell-programming-language-introduction/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-04T19:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Haskell? What is it used for? Why are there relatively few Haskell programmers? How can I get started with Haskell? If you're asking yourself these questions, then this article is for you. In it, I'll answer your questions about the Haskell programming language and demystify it for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MacBobby Chibuzor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Python 3 on Mac and Update the Version with Pyenv – MacOS Homebrew Command Guide]]></title>
        <id>607da1ecdd38b9088c2bc6c9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-python-3-on-mac-and-update-the-python-version-macos-homebrew-command-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-04T18:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When using Python, you may install different version variations for different projects. But sometimes this can affect how your code executes, as it may not use the correct version. In this article, we'll learn how to install new Python versions (Python 3 in our case) and how to set this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We All Are Ukraine 🇺🇦]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/we-all-are-ukraine/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/we-all-are-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-04T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a design community, we all can’t be silent in these times. We need to be united in our fight against the war, for democracy, for those dreams that children are entitled to have when they are growing up. It’s our obligation to help as much as we can. **We are donating all proceeds** from "Interface Design Checklists" PDF to support Ukraine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Six Years in the Open Community]]></title>
        <id>62189cadc4d0d306772ef999</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/my-six-years-in-open-community/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-04T16:35:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original article: 在开放社区中的六年，我做着喜欢且擅长的事情，利他而自利 [https://chinese.freecodecamp.org/news/my-six-years-in-open-community/] by Miya Liu [https://chinese.freecodecamp.org/news/author/miyaliu/] Translated by: Alan Luo [/news/alan-luo] Hello, I'm Yuyu Liu (Miya) from the freeCodeCamp [http://freecodecamp.org/]  community. freeCodeCamp.org is the world's largest open-source non-profit programming education community. It is also an open-source project that has long been ranked number one on GitHub. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miya Liu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create An Information Architecture That Is Easy To Use]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/easy-information-architecture/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/easy-information-architecture/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-04T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If users cannot find the answers to their questions or are not exposed to critical messaging, they will not act, and your website will fail. To prevent that from happening, you need an effective information architecture. In this article, Paul Boag provides you with a process to ensure you have precisely that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Queue Data Structure – Definition and Java Example Code]]></title>
        <id>6220a4a5c4d0d306772f338d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/queue-data-structure-definition-and-java-example-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-04T00:36:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will talk about the queue data structure, its operations, and how to implement these operations using an array in Java.  What Is a Queue? A queue is linear data structure that consists of a collection is of items that follow a first-in-first-out sequence. This implies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build and Deploy a Backend App with Express, Postgres, Github, and Heroku]]></title>
        <id>62208eb2c4d0d306772f3282</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-backend-application/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T20:46:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we will be learning how to build and deploy an image management application backend.  It will be able to store a record of an image in the database, get the image's record back from the database, update the record, and even delete the record completely as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Njoku Samson Ebere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redux Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>62210a36c4d0d306772f3898</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/redux-tutorial-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T18:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redux is a popular open-source JavaScript library for managing and centralizing application state. It is commonly used with React. We just published a complete course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Redux. Nikhil Thadani developed this course. Nikhil has created many technical courses on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python List Length – How to Get the Size of a List in Python]]></title>
        <id>6220c90cc4d0d306772f359a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-length-how-to-get-the-size-of-a-list-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T18:21:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, you use a list to store various types of data such as strings and numbers. A list is identifiable by the square brackets that surround it, and individual values are separated by a comma. To get the length of a list in Python, you can use the built-in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[pip Command Not Found – Mac and Linux Error Solved]]></title>
        <id>62208d02c4d0d306772f324e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pip-command-not-found-mac-and-linux-error-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T18:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When using Python, you might need to install and use certain packages. And there is a command available for that known as 'pip'.  With pip, you can install, upgrade, and uninstall various Python packages. You'll learn how to use it, and how to handle pip errors, in this article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Java on Windows]]></title>
        <id>621fce2dc4d0d306772f2fbf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-java-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T18:07:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to run any Java program on your Windows PC, you won't be able to do it without installing the Java Development Kit (JDK for short).  The JDK also contains the Java Runtime Environment (or JRE) which is the core of a Java program.  If you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Location Information of an IP Address Using Python]]></title>
        <id>6220562bc4d0d306772f31f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-location-information-of-ip-address-using-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T17:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you'll need to know the location of an IP address, whether it's your own or that of a site you're using.  One use-case for this is when you want to send login information to users for your website.  In this article, we're going to see how you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Solve Project Euler Problems in Rust]]></title>
        <id>62168995c4d0d306772ef0d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/project-euler-problems-in-rust/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T17:09:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now solve the classic Project Euler programming problems using the Rust language. Each of these problems comes with a user-friendly test suite. Here's the full Project Euler Rust GitHub repository [https://github.com/freeCodeCamp/euler-rust]. If you do not know Rust, and want to learn it, you can start with  freeCodeCamp's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaun Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Say Hello to selectmenu, a Fully Style-able select Element]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363972</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-selectmenu-element/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T15:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to introduce you to a new, experimental form control called <selectmenu>. We’ll get deep into it, including how much easier it is to style than a traditional <select> element. But first, let’s fill in some context …
Say Hello to selectmenu, a Fully Style-able select Element originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Brosset</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Membership Businesses with Memberful]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364001</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/build-membership-businesses-with-memberful/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T15:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
What would your business be like if you sold memberships? It might be more than fun to think about, in fact, it might just be transformative. With membership, would you include little add-ons or …
Build Membership Businesses with Memberful originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Web Layouts For Dual-Screen And Foldable Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/building-web-layouts-dual-screen-foldable-devices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/building-web-layouts-dual-screen-foldable-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dual-screen devices are just the next evolution in responsive design. If you have a PWA or website, the APIs available make integrating into your existing code base seamless. This article explains why it’s an exciting time for layout on the web, and how dual screens provide an opportunity to get even more creative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Stimac)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Fresh Links on Performance For March 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364350</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/performance-links-february-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T21:26:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a handful of good links to articles about performance that are burning a hole in my bookmarks folder, and wanna drop them here to share.
The new WebPageTest website design
From fonts to SVG: an icon migration strategy
…
7 Fresh Links on Performance For March 2022 originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python List .remove() - How to Remove an Item from a List in Python]]></title>
        <id>621e55eac4d0d306772f23d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-remove-how-to-remove-an-item-from-a-list-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T19:49:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll learn how to use Python's built-in remove() list method. By the end, you'll know how to use remove() to remove an item from a list in Python. Here is what we will cover:  1. Syntax of the remove() method  2. Remove an element from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Your Home Wireless Infrastructure with Kismet and Python]]></title>
        <id>621d7632c4d0d306772f1f61</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/wireless-security-using-raspberry-pi-4-kismet-and-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T16:22:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything is connected to wireless these days. In my case I found that I have LOTS of devices after running a simple nmap command on my home network [/news/enhance-nmap-with-python/#nmap-101-identify-all-the-public-services-in-our-network] : [josevnz@dmaf5 ~]$ sudo nmap -v -n -p- -sT -sV -O --osscan-limit --max-os-tries 1 -oX $HOME/home_scan.xml 192.168.1.0/24 So I started to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a “Raise the Curtains” Effect in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363882</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-raise-the-curtains-effect/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T15:57:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Raise the curtains” is what I call an effect where the background goes from dark to light on scroll, and the content on top also goes from light to dark while in a sticky position.
Here’s an example where I …
How to Make a “Raise the Curtains” Effect in CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silvestar Bistrović</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an eCommerce Website Using WooCommerce]]></title>
        <id>621f888ec4d0d306772f2d40</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-ecommere-website-using-woocomerce/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T15:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating your own eCommerce website is easier than you may think. You don't even need to know how to code. I just created and published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build an online store with WooCommerce and WordPress. In this video course,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps with GitLab CI Course]]></title>
        <id>621f860dc4d0d306772f2cf9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/devops-with-gitlab-ci-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T15:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitLab CI/CD can automatically build, test, deploy, and monitor your applications. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use GitLab CI. Valentin Despa developed this course. Vaentin is an experienced developer and course creator. In this course, you will learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Audio Visualization With JavaScript And GSAP (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/audio-visualization-javascript-gsap-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/audio-visualization-javascript-gsap-part1/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What started as a case study turned into a guide to visualizing audio with JavaScript. Although the output demos are in React, Jhey Tompkins isn’t going to dwell on the React side of things too much. The underlying techniques work with or without React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Node.js and npm on Windows]]></title>
        <id>621e97a4c4d0d306772f290b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-node-js-and-npm-on-windows-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T00:18:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll learn how to work with JavaScript in the backend using Node on Windows. When you start working with JavaScript and discover that you can not only work with it in the frontend but also in the backend, a new world of possibilities seems to open up]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Rosa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Wordle Clone in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>621903c6c4d0d306772efc76</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-wordle-clone-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T23:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will be recreating the guessing game Wordle [https://www.nytimes.com/games/wordle/index.html]. This article covers the core game logic but does not implement sharing your results. The article also doesn't cover the functionality that generates game statistics.  This tutorial is intended for beginner front-end developers that want to build]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Akinyemi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT Deployment – How to Secure and Deploy Internet of Things Devices]]></title>
        <id>621d6316c4d0d306772f1f16</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/internet-of-things-deployments-getting-it-right/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T21:06:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Internet of Things (IoT) is a term that has been floating around for a few years now, but what does it actually mean?  The best way to describe the IoT is to think of it as the network of physical objects that are interconnected and can communicate with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[npm Uninstall – How to Remove a Package]]></title>
        <id>621dfc8cc4d0d306772f220f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/npm-uninstall-how-to-remove-a-package/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T20:46:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Node Package Manager (NPM) provides various commands that let you work with packages. And just as you can install a package from the npm library, you can uninstall it. To uninstall a package, you can use the command provided by npm for the purpose – npm uninstall. The way]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The React useEffect Hook for Absolute Beginners]]></title>
        <id>621e4f3ec4d0d306772f239d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-useeffect-absolute-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T20:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have trouble understanding the useEffect hook, you're not alone. Beginners and experienced developers alike find it to be one of the trickiest hooks to understand, because it requires understanding a few unfamiliar programming concepts. In this quick guide, we're going to cover why this hook exists, how to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python .pop() – How to Pop from a List or an Array in Python]]></title>
        <id>621c8bcfc4d0d306772f1263</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-pop-how-to-pop-from-a-list-or-an-array-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T20:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll learn how to use Python's built-in pop() list method. By the end, you'll know how to use pop() to remove an item from a list in Python. Here is what we will cover:  1. An overview of lists in Python  2.  How to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Custom Highlight API: The Future of Highlighting Text Ranges on the Web]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363724</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-custom-highlight-api-early-loo/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T17:41:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Styling ranges of text in software is a very useful thing to be able to do. Thankfully, we have the CSS Custom Highlight API to look forward to because it represents the future of styling text ranges on the web.…
CSS Custom Highlight API: The Future of Highlighting Text Ranges on the Web originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Brosset</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ahmad Shadeed: Use Cases For CSS fit-content]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364351</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/ahmad-shadeed-use-cases-for-css-fit-content/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T15:41:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahmad Shadeed covers the CSS fit-content sizing keyword. It’s useful! It just doesn’t come up super often. I find myself using min-content a lot more, like when setting up the height of a grid-template-row.
The fit-content keyword is actually …
Ahmad Shadeed: Use Cases For CSS fit-content originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New CSS Features In 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/new-css-features-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/new-css-features-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2022 is shaping up to be a pretty great year for CSS, with a plethora of new features on the horizon. Some are already starting to land in browsers, others are likely to gain widespread browser support in 2022, while for one or two the process may be a little longer. In this article we’ll take a look at a few of them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insertion Sort – Algorithm Example in Java and C++]]></title>
        <id>620fae4a21bfb3068cf2a8f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/insertion-sort-algorithm-example-in-java-and-c/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T23:44:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Insertion sort is a sorting algorithm that creates a sorted array of items from an unsorted array, one item at a time.  In this article, we will see how the algorithm works and how to apply it in our code. How to Use Insertion Sort Consider an array of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comment out HTML – Code Example]]></title>
        <id>620ac06a21bfb3068cf288c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/comment-out-html-code-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T23:26:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding comments in your code is a good practice, as it makes your code more readable and understandable. Comments don’t run because they are ignored by compilers and interpreters. In this article, I will show you how you can comment out your HTML code, so you can help yourself and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Recoil for State Management in Your React Projects]]></title>
        <id>621bd6d1c4d0d306772f0c6e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-recoil-for-state-management-in-your-react-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T23:19:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a React developer, you've probably used a library for managing state in your React applications. And you've likely heard of Redux "the state management" library for React.  For a long time, Redux was the only reliable and most widely-adopted solution for state management in React applications. And]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdullah Adeel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IE Down, Edge Up… Global Browser Usage Stats Are for Cocktail Parties and Conference Slides]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364346</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/ie-down-edge-up-global-browser-usage-stats-are-for-cocktail-parties-and-conference-slides/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T23:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I enjoy articles like Hartley Charlton’s “Microsoft Edge Looks Set to Overtake Safari as World’s Second Most Popular Desktop Browser.” It’s juicy! We know these massive players in the browser market care very much about their market share, so when …
IE Down, Edge Up… Global Browser Usage Stats Are for Cocktail Parties and Conference Slides originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Podcast Player with Transcriptions using Vue and Supabase]]></title>
        <id>620fb63121bfb3068cf2a926</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-podcast-player-with-transcriptions-using-vue-supabase/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T23:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post we will walk through setting up a Podcast Player app using Supabase and Vue 3, including getting transcriptions for the podcasts.  This is a continuation of my previous post on setting up Authentication using Supabase [/news/add-supabase-authentication-to-vue/]. If you aren't familiar with getting Supabase set up in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Barrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Best Python Courses to Take in 2022]]></title>
        <id>62160a08c4d0d306772eecd2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-python-courses/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T19:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to learn Python, there are a lot of great resources out there. But if you're specifically looking for the best online course to learn Python, then you've come to the right place. In this article, I present a list of awesome Python courses ranked according to a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elham Nazif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Uppercase – How to Capitalize a String in JS with .toUpperCase]]></title>
        <id>620c9b9621bfb3068cf2939d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-uppercase-how-to-capitalize-a-string-in-js-with-touppercase/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T19:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While working with strings in JavaScript, you can perform different operations on them. The operations you might perform on strings include capitalization, conversion to lowercase, adding symbols within words, and many more. In this article, I will show you how to convert a string to uppercase letters with the .toUpperCase()]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Went from Classical Musician to Software Developer using freeCodeCamp]]></title>
        <id>6213501a21bfb3068cf2bf5b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-i-went-from-a-classical-musician-to-software-developer-and-techinal-writer/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T19:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before the pandemic, I spent my whole life performing, teaching, and composing music. But in June of 2020, I made the decision to learn how to code and successfully landed a job as a software developer. Here is the story of how I learned how to code using freeCodeCamp [https://www.freecodecamp.org/learn/]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Animation Performance Fundamentals – How to Make Your Pages Look Smooth]]></title>
        <id>61faafa3f2ed6b06db5ab1ab</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-animation-performance-fundamentals/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T18:49:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if I told you that web pages were interactive animations played back by your web browser? We watch various motions every time we're on a web page.  And it's not only JavaScript or CSS animations that I'm talking about. Scrolling, pinch zooming, text selection, and even hovering over]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Lavarian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Multiline Comment – How to Comment Out Multiple Lines in Python]]></title>
        <id>620abfab21bfb3068cf288b5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-multiline-comment-how-to-comment-out-multiple-lines-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T17:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Commenting is an integral part of every programming language. With comments, you get a better understanding of your own code, make it more readable, and can help team members understand how it works. Comments are ignored by compilers and interpreters, so they don’t run. Apart from making your code more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get the ASCII Value of Any Character with One Line of Code]]></title>
        <id>6213533d21bfb3068cf2bf8c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-the-ascii-value-of-any-character-with-one-line-of-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T16:20:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working on a project or computer program, you might need to use the ASCII value of a certain character.  This is a common phenomenon in competitive programming, as well – we typically need to use the ASCII value of characters when solving some of the problems on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Component Pseudo-Classes and Pseudo-Elements are Easier Than You Think]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363929</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/web-component-pseudo-classes-and-pseudo-elements/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T15:37:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve discussed a lot about the internals of using CSS in this ongoing series on web components, but there are a few special pseudo-elements and pseudo-classes that, like good friends, willingly smell your possibly halitotic breath before you go …
Web Component Pseudo-Classes and Pseudo-Elements are Easier Than You Think originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Rhea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We All Are Ukraine 🇺🇦]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/we-all-are-ukraine/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/we-all-are-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a design community, we all can’t be silent in these times. We need to be united in our fight against the war, for democracy, for those dreams that children are entitled to have when they are growing up. It’s our obligation to help as much as we can. **We are donating all proceeds** from "Interface Design Checklists" PDF to support Ukraine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March For Equality (2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following our monthly tradition, artists and designers from across the globe challenged their creative skills and designed desktop wallpapers to welcome March. They come in versions with and without a calendar and can be downloaded for free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Recipe For A Good Design System]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/recipe-good-design-system/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/recipe-good-design-system/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maintaining a design system is a lot of work. In this article, Atila Fassina shares his lessons learned and how a platform such as Backlight can help put together a series of tools to speed up your architecture setup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Section Divider Using CSS]]></title>
        <id>6217ea59c4d0d306772ef522</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/section-divider-using-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T21:46:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's always cool to have a fancy section divider on your website. And it's even better if we can make them responsive and easy to adjust. This is what you will learn in this article. We will explore different section dividers made using only CSS and some optimized code that's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trailing Slashes on URLs: Contentious or Settled?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364070</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/trailing-slashes-on-urls-contentious-or-settled/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T21:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fun deep dive from Zach. Do you have an opinion on which you should use?
1) https://website.com/foo/
2) https://websites.com/foo
The first option has a “trailing slash.” The second does not.
I’ve always preferred this thinking: you use a trailing …
Trailing Slashes on URLs: Contentious or Settled? originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When to Avoid the text-decoration Shorthand Property]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363619</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/when-to-avoid-css-text-decoration-shorthand/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T15:28:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my recent article about CSS underline bugs in Chrome, I discussed text-decoration-thickness and text-underline-offset, two relatively new and widely-supported CSS properties that give us more control over the styling of underlines.
Let me demonstrate the usefulness of …
When to Avoid the text-decoration Shorthand Property originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Šime Vidas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manuel Matuzovic’s CSS Specificity Demo]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364152</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/manuel-matuzovics-css-specificity-demo/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T15:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking for a primer on CSS specificity, we’ve got that. And if you’re trying to get ahead of the game, you should be aware of CSS Cascade Layers as well.
One of the ways to help get …
Manuel Matuzovic’s CSS Specificity Demo originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My white whale: A use case for will-change]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364138</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/my-white-whale-a-use-case-for-will-change/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T20:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nic Chan:
[…] the will-change property landed in major browsers in August 2015, and I’ve been on the lookout for when to use it ever since. It might seem self-evident to apply it to commonly animated properties such 
…
My white whale: A use case for will-change originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Find in List – How to Find the Index of an Item or Element in a List]]></title>
        <id>6213c94921bfb3068cf2c268</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-find-in-list-how-to-find-the-index-of-an-item-or-element-in-a-list/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T20:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article you will learn how to find the index of an element contained in a list in the Python programming language. There are a few ways to achieve this, and in this article you will learn three of the different techniques used to find the index of a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is len() in Python? How to Use the len() Function to Find the Length of a String]]></title>
        <id>620c980321bfb3068cf29395</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-len-in-python-how-to-use-the-len-function-to-find-the-length-of-a-string/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T18:35:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In programming languages, getting the length of a particular data type is a common practice. Python is no different because you can use the built-in len() function to get the length of a string, tuple, list, dictionary, or any other data type. In this article, I'm going to show you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explain the First 10 Lines of Twitter’s Source Code to Me]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363553</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/explain-the-first-10-lines-of-twitter-source-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T15:31:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the past few weeks, I’ve been hiring for a senior full-stack JavaScript engineer at my rental furniture company, Pabio. Since we’re a remote team, we conduct our interviews on Zoom, and I’ve observed that some developers are not …
Explain the First 10 Lines of Twitter’s Source Code to Me originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anand Chowdhary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Superior Image Optimization: An Ideal Solution Using Gatsby & ImageEngine]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363526</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/superior-image-optimization-an-ideal-solution-using-gatsby-imageengine/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T15:31:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
In recent years, the Jamstack methodology for building websites has become increasingly popular. Performance, scalable, and secure, it’s easy to see why it’s becoming an attractive way to build websites for developers.
GatsbyJS is …
Superior Image Optimization: An Ideal Solution Using Gatsby & ImageEngine originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ImageEngine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter Course for Beginners – 37-hour Android App Development Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>62179b03c4d0d306772ef2f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-flutter-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T14:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter is an open-source UI software development kit used to create cross-platform applications for iOS, Android, Windows, Mac, and more. We just published a 37-hour Flutter course for beginners on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Vandad Nahavandipoor developed this course. Vlandad is a Google Developer Expert and Lead iOS Developer. Flutter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the Basics of the Linux Operating System]]></title>
        <id>62164addc4d0d306772eef3e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-basics-of-the-linux-operating-system/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T13:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux is an open source, free operating system which is used by computers all over the world. It is especially popular for use in servers. We just published a Linux crash course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you the basics of this open source operating system. Josh]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Benchmark And Improve Web Vitals With Real User Metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/benchmark-improve-web-vitals-real-user-metrics/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/benchmark-improve-web-vitals-real-user-metrics/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web Vitals are the new gold standard in performance due to their direct correlation with the user’s experience. In this article, you’ll learn what monitoring can do and how RayGun can help you sustain performance maintenance while scaling your app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Database Queries? Sure We Can!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363937</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-database-queries/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T20:04:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kinda silly sounding, isn’t it? CSS database queries. But, hey, CSS is capable of talking to other languages in the sense that it can set the values of things that they can read. Plus, CSS can request other files, and …
CSS Database Queries? Sure We Can! originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Accessibility Quick Wins You Can Implement Today]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363532</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/5-accessibility-quick-wins-you-can-implement-today/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T15:15:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s face it: building an AA or AAA-accessible product can be quite daunting. Luckily, having an accessible product isn’t all-or-nothing. Even seemingly small improvements can have nice quality of life benefits for many people.
In that spirit, here are five …
5 Accessibility Quick Wins You Can Implement Today originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Yuschick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn NestJS by Building a CRUD API]]></title>
        <id>621648e1c4d0d306772eeefc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-nestjs-by-building-a-crud-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T14:53:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NestJS is a framework for building efficient, scalable Node.js web applications. It is a complete development kit for building scalable server-side apps. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use NestJS by building a CRUD API. Vladimir Agaev developed this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>