<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-05-20T01:01:53.696Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React Server Components – A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-server-components-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-server-components-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T20:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React Server Components have been generating significant buzz and excitement lately. They've recently been adopted as the default option in Next.js 13, so now more and more developers are using them. React Server Components seamlessly blend server-side rendering with the interactivity of client-side JavaScript. And in this tutorial, you'll learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adwaith KS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pandas Count Rows – How to Get the Number of Rows in a Dataframe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pandas-count-rows-how-to-get-the-number-of-rows-in-a-dataframe/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pandas-count-rows-how-to-get-the-number-of-rows-in-a-dataframe/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T15:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pandas is a library built on the Python programming language. You can use it to analyze and manipulate data. A dataframe is two-dimensional data structure in Pandas that organizes data in a tabular format with rows and columns.  In this article, you'll learn how to get the number of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State Management in React –Props vs the Context API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/state-management-in-react-props-vs-context-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/state-management-in-react-props-vs-context-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T14:31:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Figuring out state management in React applications can feel like trying to find your way through a labyrinth. You'll constantly be searching for the most efficient, scalable, and maintainable solution.  The journey often leads to two primary paths: Using Props or the Context API. As you embark on this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EC2 – Understanding and Addressing the Security Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/amazon-ec2-understanding-the-security-problem/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/amazon-ec2-understanding-the-security-problem/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T19:07:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi there. Great to have you here. But I'm afraid I'm going to have to start off with some bad news.  Before you can really improve the security of your Amazon EC2 instances, you'll need to get a handle on all the stuff that can go wrong. And I'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Component-Based Architecture in Medusa – How to Build Robust User Interfaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/exploring-component-based-architecture-in-medusa-building-robust-user-interfaces/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/exploring-component-based-architecture-in-medusa-building-robust-user-interfaces/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T18:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Medusa is a modern JavaScript framework that makes it easy to build robust user interfaces.  It is built around a component-based architecture, which is a design pattern that breaks down a UI into smaller, reusable components. This makes it easier to maintain and update the UI, as well as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Full Stack Application Using ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-full-stack-application-using-chatgpt/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-full-stack-application-using-chatgpt/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T15:52:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT can be used to supercharge software development. You even create complete applications with ChatGPT. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will show you how you can create a full stack app with ChatGPT. This course, authored by Judy from webdecoded, leverages the power of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RegEx for Date Formats – Regular Expressions for Matching Dates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/regex-for-date-formats-what-is-the-regular-expression-for-matching-dates/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/regex-for-date-formats-what-is-the-regular-expression-for-matching-dates/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T12:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regular expressions let you match any string, be it in the form of various user inputs such as username, password, URL, and even different date formats. In this article, I’ll show you several ways you can match a date with regular expressions. In the programming world, there are always multiple]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Upgrades That Will Improve Your Developer Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/angular-upgrades-to-improve-developer-experience/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/angular-upgrades-to-improve-developer-experience/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T23:40:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we talk about the Developer Experience [https://microsoft.github.io/code-with-engineering-playbook/developer-experience/] , we're referring to the level of difficulty a developer faces when completing essential tasks.  Factors like the complexity of a development framework or the absence of  syntactic sugar [https://www.techopedia.com/definition/10212/syntactic-sugar] in a programming language can negatively impact it. A robust]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brenda Chepkorir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Regular Expressions in YAML File – RegEx in YAML Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-regular-expressions-in-yaml-file/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-regular-expressions-in-yaml-file/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T14:48:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YAML does not have built-in support for regular expressions. But you can still include regex patterns as part of a YAML file's contents, access those patterns, and create a regex out of them. You can do this, for example, with the JavaScript RegExp constructor. So, in YAML, regular expressions are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Deal With Big Tooling Upgrades In Large Organizations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/big-tooling-upgrades-large-organizations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/big-tooling-upgrades-large-organizations/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The process of upgrading large third-party packages in equally large organizations is rarely, if ever, as easy as running an npm update and calling it a day in this context. Joran Quinten shares valuable lessons from his team’s experiences in upgrading third-party code that affects codebases across the entire organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joran Quinten)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an Interactive Heatmap Using JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/interactive-heatmap-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/interactive-heatmap-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T23:26:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data visualization is a powerful tool that helps us make sense of complex data. With it, we can spot patterns and trends that might take much more time to become obvious just by looking at raw numbers.  One particularly useful chart type is the heatmap, and I’m excited to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shachee Swadia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How JavaScript’s Asynchronous Operations Work in the Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-asynchronous-operations-in-the-browser/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-asynchronous-operations-in-the-browser/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T21:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a popular programming language used for developing interactive front-end web applications, among other things.  It's widely known for its major features: it is single-threaded, non-blocking, and asynchronous. But what do these three things mean? What Does "Single-Threaded" Mean? When a programming language is referred to as single-threaded,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amazing Enyichi Agu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Native Apps with Ionic and Capacitor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-native-apps-with-ionic-and-capacitor/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-native-apps-with-ionic-and-capacitor/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T21:14:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ionic and Capacitor are two powerful tools that can be used to build native mobile applications. Ionic is a UI framework that provides a wide range of components and features for building mobile apps, while Capacitor is a runtime that allows Ionic apps to be deployed to both iOS and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Sort() – How to Use the Sort Function in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-does-the-javascript-sort-function-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-does-the-javascript-sort-function-work/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T20:29:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I will explain how to use, and maximize the full potential of the sort() function. What is the sort() Function? The sort() function allows you to sort an array object by either the default sorting order, or by a custom sorting function. By default, it sorts the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Weatherston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can you find the bug? JavaScript security vulnerabilities course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/can-you-find-the-bug-javascript-security-vulnerabilities-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/can-you-find-the-bug-javascript-security-vulnerabilities-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T17:43:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a world where cybersecurity threats are more prevalent than ever, understanding how to safeguard your web applications is of paramount importance. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you learn common JavaScript security vulnerabilities and how to prevent them. Brandon teaches this course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Google Apps Script Basics by Building a Tic Tac Toe Game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-google-apps-script-basics-by-building-tic-tac-toe/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-google-apps-script-basics-by-building-tic-tac-toe/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T16:58:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Sheets are powerful, and Apps Script makes them even more versatile and useful. Yes, you can use them for finance dashboards, personal budgets, and project management (and we'll cover these as future topics). But in this article, I'll go through the basics of Apps Script by building a simple]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python End Program – How to Exit a Python Program in the Terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-end-program-how-to-exit-a-python-program-in-terminal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-end-program-how-to-exit-a-python-program-in-terminal/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T16:48:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can execute Python code in a terminal just like you would in an IDE like VS Code, Atom, and so on. You can do this in both Windows and Unix operating systems like Linux and macOS.  In this article, you'll learn how to exit a Python program in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Best Practices – A Guide to Version Control for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-git-best-practices-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-git-best-practices-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T16:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a software developer, you may be familiar with the concept of version control. Version control is the practice of managing changes to your codebase over time. It's an essential tool for any development project.  One of the most popular version control systems is Git, which is widely]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adekola Olawale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Computing Abstractions – IaaS, PaaS, FaaS, and SaaS Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cloud-computing-abstractions-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cloud-computing-abstractions-explained/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T16:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstracting is the process of reducing something to its most basic form. It is the hiding away of the inessential.  For a drawing, this could be reducing it to its basic lines and shapes. Naturally, there are many levels of an abstraction, since what is inessential is subjective.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design Patterns Are A Better Way To Collaborate On Your Design System]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/design-patterns-collaborate-design-system/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/design-patterns-collaborate-design-system/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every company and team has to have deep collaboration between engineering and design to get the value out of a design system (and not go nuts). Building design patterns first unblock people to work in parallel, keeps people synced up, and results in reusable modules that speed up your next project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Clemens)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Networking in Flutter By Building a Simple App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-networking-in-flutter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-networking-in-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T18:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost all apps you use today run by accessing the internet. You can hardly find an app that runs without connecting to the internet.  The internet has become an integral part of our lives, as it solves one of the most critical problems we have to handle: data transfer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caching in React – How to Use the useMemo and useCallback Hooks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/caching-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/caching-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T18:39:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As React developers become more proficient with the library, the topic of performance becomes a major focal point in their development process.  As with any tool or programming methodology, caching plays a huge role when it comes to optimizing React applications. Caching in React typically goes by the term]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the 60-30-10 Rule in Design? And How to Use it in Your Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-60-30-10-rule-in-design/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-60-30-10-rule-in-design/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T17:20:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As designers, colour is a huge component of our work. But many of us struggle with the usage of colours in our designs.  In this article, you will learn about the 60-30-10 colour rule, how it's used, and see a practical example of it. What is the 60-30-10 rule?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Your MERN Stack App with JWT-Based User Authentication and Authorization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-secure-your-mern-stack-application/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-secure-your-mern-stack-application/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T17:15:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MongoDB [https://www.mongodb.com/docs/], Express [https://expressjs.com/en/starter/installing.html], React [https://react.dev/learn], and Node.js [https://nodejs.org/en/docs] are the components of the MERN stack, one of the most widely used web development stacks out there today. The MERN stack enables programmers to create dependable web applications with strong capabilities. Yet, security should be a key concern with any]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FADAHUNSI SEYI SAMUEL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Method Overloading Works in PHP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/method-overloading-in-php/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/method-overloading-in-php/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T17:11:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As software engineers, we sometimes have to perform certain tasks that can be achieved with a variable number of inputs.  To solve this problem, you can create multiple functions to solve for the different possible number of inputs. Or we can write a large function to solve this problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zubair Idris Aweda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Clean Code – Tips and Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-clean-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-clean-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T14:43:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we're going to talk about writing "clean" code. It's a topic that used to confuse me a bit when I was starting out as a programmer, and I find that it has many nuances and possible interpretations. So in this article we'll talk about what]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solving Media Object Float Issues With CSS Block Formatting Contexts]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/media-object-float-issues-css-block-formatting-contexts/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/media-object-float-issues-css-block-formatting-contexts/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article covers common problems using CSS floats and how to solve them using a block formatting context (BFC). Whether you are a beginner or an experienced web developer, you will learn valuable insights and practical solutions for dealing with CSS float issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Gabriel Shoyombo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[URL RegEx Pattern – How to Write a Regular Expression for a URL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-a-regular-expression-for-a-url/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-a-regular-expression-for-a-url/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T12:22:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regular expressions provide a powerful and flexible way to define patterns and match specific strings, be it usernames, passwords, phone numbers, or even URLs. In this article, I'll show you the fundamentals of crafting a regular expression for URLs. Whether you need to validate user input, extract components from URLs,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Indexing Strategies in PostgreSQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/postgresql-indexing-strategies/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/postgresql-indexing-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T20:46:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indexing in PostgreSQL is a process that involves creating data structures that are optimized to efficiently search and retrieve data from tables.  An index is a copy of a portion of a table, arranged in a way that enables PostgreSQL to quickly locate and retrieve rows that match a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Faith Oyama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Greedy Algorithm? Examples of Greedy Algorithms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/greedy-algorithms/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/greedy-algorithms/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T17:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the Oxford English Dictionary, "greedy" means having excessive desire for something without considering the effect or damage done.  In computer science, a greedy algorithm is an algorithm that finds a solution to problems in the shortest time possible. It picks the path that seems optimal at the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tantoluwa Heritage Alabi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does a Linked List Work? A Beginner's Guide to Linked Lists]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-linked-lists-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-linked-lists-work/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T17:45:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Linked List is a linear data structure used for storing a collection of elements. Unlike arrays, linked lists use nodes to store elements which are not stored in contiguous memory locations.  In this article, you will learn what linked lists are, how they work, and how to build]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Palistha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Sticky Menus: UX Guidelines]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/sticky-menus-ux-guidelines/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/sticky-menus-ux-guidelines/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are sticky headers always a good idea? Best practices for designing sticky headers, with examples, UX guidelines and usability considerations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Number Systems Work in Java – Decimal, Binary, Octal, and Hexadecimal Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/number-systems-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/number-systems-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T21:54:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Knowing how to work with numbers is essential in programming. Java supports four number systems that are used for various purposes – the decimal, binary, octal, and hexadecimal systems.  Understanding what these number systems are and when to use them is an important skill for any Java programmer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mikael Lassa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Merge Dictionaries – Merging Two Dicts in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-merge-dictionaries-merging-two-dicts-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-merge-dictionaries-merging-two-dicts-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T21:51:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dictionaries are one of the built-in data structures in Python. You can use them to store data in key-value pairs.  You can read about the different methods you can use to access, modify, add, and remove elements in a dictionary here [/news/python-dictionary-methods-dictionaries-in-python/].  In this article, you'll learn how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work with Files in Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-files-in-node-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-files-in-node-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T21:16:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a popular programming language among web developers. But when it was first released, only front end developers enjoyed all of the fun it had to offer, since you couldn't run JavaScript outside the browser. But then in 2009, the first version of Node.js was released. Node is a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatise Okuwobi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Boost Your Design Workflow With Setapp]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/boost-design-workflow-setapp/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/boost-design-workflow-setapp/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll explore efficient tools to save time and speed up your workflow. Focus on what you do best — designing high-quality work, and let these tools handle the rest!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Rachel How)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ultimate Go Programming Video Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/go-programming-video-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/go-programming-video-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T13:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce a new comprehensive Go programming video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Our mission is to provide easy access to the most sought-after tech skills, and this course is our latest endeavor to fulfill that mission. Go: The Language of the Future Go, or Golang,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Difference Between AI and Machine Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/artificial-intelligence-vs-machine-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/artificial-intelligence-vs-machine-learning/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T22:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning are two terms that are commonly used interchangeably. But they are not the same thing. Artificial Intelligence is a field which contains a lot of sub-fields, including Machine Learning. In this article I hope to comprehensively differentiate between AI and Machine Learning. I'll explain how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Gold</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PostgreSQL and JSON – How to Use JSON Data in PostgreSQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/postgresql-and-json-use-json-data-in-postgresql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/postgresql-and-json-use-json-data-in-postgresql/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T20:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PostgreSQL is a powerful open-source relational database management system (RDBMS). It was initially created as a successor to the Ingres database system and was later named "PostgreSQL" (short for "Post-Ingres SQL"). PostgreSQL is known for its robustness, reliability, and scalability, making it a popular choice for large and complex database]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Faith Oyama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Accurate Cybersecurity Risk Assessment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-accurate-cybersecurity-risk-assessment/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-accurate-cybersecurity-risk-assessment/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T19:39:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you responsible for the safety and reliability of IT infrastructure and applications? You'll absolutely need regular and accurate assessments.  Effective risk assessments are about establishing how far your organization's IT stack can be stretched before it breaks.  From a big-picture perspective, you'll need to think about how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Stack Engineer – Career Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-engineer-career-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-engineer-career-guide/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T17:27:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Full-stack engineering roles have been growing in popularity over the last decade and are among the most sought-after positions in the tech job market. But what exactly are full-stack engineers? What do they do on a day-to-day basis? And how can you become a full-stack engineer yourself? In this article,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the Power of Functional Programming with Elixir]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/functional-programming-with-elixir/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/functional-programming-with-elixir/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T15:59:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transform your development approach and embrace the power of Elixir and functional programming with our new beginner's course. It is designed to help you build scalable, maintainable applications like never before. We just published a new course on the freeCodeCamp channel that will teach you how to build your own]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn SQL for Efficient Data Storage and Retrieval]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-sql-full-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-sql-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T15:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock the power of data with SQL! Master one of the most in-demand skill in the data-driven world and supercharge your career with our new video course. We just released a comprehensive video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will take you on a journey from understanding the basics]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart Quotes – Single Quote and Double Quotation Mark for Copy + Paste]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/smart-quotes-single-quote-and-double-quotation-mark-for-copy-paste/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/smart-quotes-single-quote-and-double-quotation-mark-for-copy-paste/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T14:31:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart quotes are commonly used punctuation marks in HTML and in writing. Knowing how to use them correctly can make a significant difference in the clarity and professionalism of your writing. So in this article, you will get access to the commonly used quotation marks out there that you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Redux Toolkit With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/guide-redux-toolkit-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/guide-redux-toolkit-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Redux Toolkit documentation calls the library a better way to write Redux logic for React apps and a simple and efficient toolkit for Redux development. In this article, you will learn about the Redux toolkit by building an app that tracks project issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Deepak Kumar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Wireframing? How to Go from Paper Sketches to High Fidelity Wireframes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-wireframing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-wireframing/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T22:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are Wireframes? Wireframes are visual representations of the structure, layout, and functionality of a website, application, or other digital product.  You typically create them during the early stages of the design process, and they provide a simplified and focused view of the user interface and user experience. You]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Elastic Beanstalk to Deploy a Node.js App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-elastic-beanstalk-to-deploy-node-js-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-elastic-beanstalk-to-deploy-node-js-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T21:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building and managing applications on the cloud can be a daunting task. This is especially true when it comes to handling different environments, scaling, and deploying updates.  But there's a service in AWS that can simplify this. AWS Elastic Beanstalk is here to make your life easier. It provides]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Beginner-Friendly JavaScript Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-beginner-friendly-javascript-application/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-beginner-friendly-javascript-application/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T16:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a popular programming language for building web, mobile, and desktop applications.  There are many frameworks and libraries that have been built around JavaScript, with more likely being developed even as you are reading this article. If you plan to start learning JavaScript, some of them are worth]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[900 Free Computer Science Courses from the World’s Top Universities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-courses-top-cs-universities/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-courses-top-cs-universities/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T13:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I compiled 900 online courses offered by the 60 best universities in the world for studying computer science in 2023. I built the list using a data-driven approach. You can find my methodology below. But if you’d rather go straight to the course list, click here. Methodology]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manoel Cortes Mendez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use AI Tools To Skyrocket Your Programming Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/ai-tools-skyrocket-programming-productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/ai-tools-skyrocket-programming-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise of Artificial Intelligence (AI) in recent times has incited fear in many over losing their jobs. However, that shouldn’t be the case. On the contrary, AI is an opportunity to take your programming to the next level when used tactfully with the right knowledge, as we’ll cover today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shane Duggan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Ethical Hacking? A Cybersecurity Definition of Ethical Hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-ethical-hacking/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-ethical-hacking/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T00:06:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As technology continues to advance, cyber-threats are becoming the norm. Cyber-criminals are constantly trying to find ways to exploit systems and networks, all with the purpose of stealing sensitive information or causing damage. These challenges in the tech space have led to the emergence of the term ethical hacking. The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hillary Nyakundi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google's New Cybersecurity Professional Certificate Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cybersecurity-professional-certificate-by-google/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cybersecurity-professional-certificate-by-google/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T21:38:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has released a new professional certificate in Cybersecurity. The  announcement [https://blog.google/outreach-initiatives/grow-with-google/google-cybersecurity-career-certificate/]  came on May 4th, 2023 and marks the 6th topical branch in their continually expanding certificate program. It follows five other successful entry-level certificate programs in IT Support, Data Analytics, Digital Marketing & E-commerce, Project Management]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Euclidean Algorithm Works – with Code Examples in Go]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/euclidean-algorithm-in-golang/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/euclidean-algorithm-in-golang/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T20:18:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Euclidean Algorithm is a well-known and efficient method for finding the greatest common divisor (GCD) of two integers. The GCD is the largest number that can divide both integers without leaving a remainder.  The algorithm is named after the ancient Greek mathematician Euclid, who presented it in his]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Otavio Ehrenberger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Joining a Tech Community Can Help Grow Your Career]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tech-communities/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tech-communities/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T20:09:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the tech industry, joining a community is one of the best ways to stay informed about the latest trends, connect with like-minded professionals, and stay up-to-date on the latest career opportunities.  Tech communities are groups of professionals with a common interest in technology and a shared passion for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pulkit Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[xor.py – How the Python XOR Operator Works]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/xor-py-how-the-python-xor-operator-works/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/xor-py-how-the-python-xor-operator-works/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T16:35:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use bitwise operators in Python to perform different operations on the individual bits of an integer.  There are different bitwise operators like the bitwise AND (&), bitwise OR (|), bitwise XOR (^), and so on.  In this article, we'll focus on the bitwise XOR (^) operator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Brain-Inspired Approach to AI – Explained for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-brain-inspired-approach-to-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-brain-inspired-approach-to-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T15:43:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Our intelligence is what makes us human, and AI is an extension of that quality" – Yan LeCun Since the advent of Neural Networks (also known as artificial neural networks), the AI industry has enjoyed unparalleled success. Neural Networks are the driving force behind modern AI systems and they]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Gold</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the useState() Hook in React – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/usestate-hook-3-different-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/usestate-hook-3-different-examples/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T14:11:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most well-known React hooks is the useState() hook. It lets you add a state variable to your component. The useState() hook can conveniently hold strings, arrays, numbers, objects and much more. In this article, we are going to learn about the useState() hook and demonstrate its use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mwendwa Bundi Emma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin VS Java – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kotlin-vs-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kotlin-vs-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technology advances very quickly these days, and there's always a new programming language or tool to learn.  You may have heard developers discussing the merits of and differences between two popular programming languages – Java and Kotlin.  So what's the difference between them? Which one should you learn?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Safest Way To Hide Your API Keys When Using React]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/safest-way-hide-api-keys-react/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/safest-way-hide-api-keys-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to make sure your API keys are safe and sound when working with React? Jessica Joseph’s got you covered! She will show you the best ways to hide your API keys, from using environment variables to building your own back-end proxy server.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jessica Joseph)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design Patterns for Modern Backend Development – with Example Use Cases]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/design-pattern-for-modern-backend-development-and-use-cases/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/design-pattern-for-modern-backend-development-and-use-cases/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-06T12:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In software development, design patterns are reusable solutions to common problems that developers encounter. These patterns provide a structure for organizing code that makes it more maintainable, modular, and scalable.  In modern backend development, design patterns are crucial for building robust and flexible systems that can adapt to changing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pacifique LINJANJA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an AI-Powered ChatBot with OpenAI, ChatGPT, Node.js, and React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-chatbot-with-openai-chatgpt-nodejs-and-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-chatbot-with-openai-chatgpt-nodejs-and-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T22:08:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI) has been making waves lately, with ChatGPT [https://platform.openai.com/] revolutionizing the internet with the chat completion [https://platform.openai.com/docs/guides/chat] functionality.  You can do a lot with it: drafting an email or other piece of writing, answering questions about a set of documents, creating conversational agents, giving your software a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Njoku Samson Ebere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Provision a Nexus Sonatype OSS on an Orange PI 5 with Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/provision-nexus-sonatype-oss-on-an-orange-pi-5-with-ansible/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/provision-nexus-sonatype-oss-on-an-orange-pi-5-with-ansible/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T21:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nexus 3 OSS is an Open Source [https://github.com/sonatype/nexus-public]  artifact repository manager [https://www.sonatype.com/products/repository-oss]  that can handle multiple formats like container images, Python PIP, Java jar, and many others. Why have an on-premise artifact manager? There are many reasons for it:  * Use your private infrastructure: You may have]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source Projects Every Developer Should Know About]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/open-source-projects-every-dev-should-know/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/open-source-projects-every-dev-should-know/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T21:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many companies use code from open source projects in the modern world of software development. This approach not only benefits those organizations but also different developers working on different projects. And it has created an environment where developers are able to work in a collaborative manner while also learning from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hillary Nyakundi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mutability vs Immutability in JavaScript – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mutability-vs-immutability-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mutability-vs-immutability-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T18:20:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, different data types have different behaviors and locations in memory. So to reduce the chances of having bugs in your code, you need to understand the concept of mutability and immutability in JavaScript. Mutability refers to data types that can be accessed and changed after they've been created]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chukwunonso Nwankwo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Iterator Hashmap – How to Iterate Through a Hashmap With a Loop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-iterator-hashmap-how-to-iterate-through-a-hashmap-with-a-loop/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-iterator-hashmap-how-to-iterate-through-a-hashmap-with-a-loop/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T18:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hashmap is a data structure used in programming to store data in key-value pairs. It is widely used in many programming languages, including Java, Python, and JavaScript.  Iterating through a hashmap is a regular operation that developers perform frequently. In this article, we will walk through a detailed outline]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docker Extensions to Help You Improve Your Workflow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/docker-extensions-to-improve-workflow/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/docker-extensions-to-improve-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T16:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker is becoming increasingly popular, and many organizations have started incorporating it into their development lifecycle.  Because of this, it's an important tool to learn and can help you automate many of your tasks and workflows.  If you are new to Docker, please read my previous tutorial [/news/what-is-docker-compose-how-to-use-it/]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Find and Replace in Notepad++ – How to Find String with Regular Expression in Notepad++]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-find-string-with-regular-expression-in-notepad-find-and-replace-in-notepad/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-find-string-with-regular-expression-in-notepad-find-and-replace-in-notepad/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T13:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notepad++ has a Find feature with which you can search for any text in a file. But it doesn’t end there. You can also use Notepad++'s Find and Replace feature to search for a text and replace it with a specified replacement. The Find and Find and Replace features accept]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning JavaScript With Imagination]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/learning-javascript-with-imagination/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/learning-javascript-with-imagination/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the story of how one little octopus, explaining one beginner’s concept, carried such weight and power for Kylo that it drove his work and led him to research something that is really quite silly. And yet, it transformed how he learned to write — and finally understand — JavaScript.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kylo Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Nullish Coalescing Operator in JavaScript, and how is it useful]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-the-nullish-coalescing-operator-in-javascript-and-how-is-it-useful/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-the-nullish-coalescing-operator-in-javascript-and-how-is-it-useful/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T06:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Nullish Coalescing Operator is a new logical operator in JavaScript introduced in ES 2020. In this article, we'll understand how this operator works. There are over four logical operators in JavaScript: the AND &&, OR ||, NOT !, and the Nullish Coalescing Operator ??. Sometimes called the Nullish Operator,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Parse a String in Python – Parsing Strings Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-parse-a-string-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-parse-a-string-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T21:04:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Parsing a string can mean different things in Python. You can parse a string by splitting or extracting the substrings.  You can also parse a string by converting it to an integer or float variable. Although this should be categorized as a type conversion operation, you'll come across resources]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Detect Objects in Images Using the YOLOv8 Neural Network]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-detect-objects-in-images-using-yolov8/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-detect-objects-in-images-using-yolov8/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T18:17:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Object detection is a computer vision task that involves identifying and locating objects in images or videos. It is an important part of many applications, such as self-driving cars, robotics, and video surveillance. Over the years, many methods and algorithms have been developed to find objects in images and their]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrey Germanov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You're offline. Check your Connection. [How to Fix YouTube Error]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/youre-offline-check-your-connection-how-to-fix-youtube-error/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/youre-offline-check-your-connection-how-to-fix-youtube-error/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T17:44:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever logged on to YouTube to watch videos only to see the error, "You're offline. Check your Connection"? This error can occur on both the YouTube website and the mobile apps for Android and iPhone. In the case of the mobile apps, you might get the error "You're]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Beginner's Guide to the Strategy Design Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-beginners-guide-to-the-strategy-design-pattern/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-beginners-guide-to-the-strategy-design-pattern/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T17:43:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Strategy Design Pattern is a behavioral design pattern [https://shrinke.me/XNNXyxVS]. It allows you to dynamically change the behavior of an object by encapsulating it into different strategies.  This pattern enables an object to choose from multiple algorithms and behaviors at runtime, rather than statically choosing a single one. It]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Delete a File or Directory in Linux – Command to Remove a Folder and its Contents]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-delete-a-file-or-directory-in-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-delete-a-file-or-directory-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T15:15:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Linux, deleting files or directories is a fundamental operation that every user must know. Although it may seem like a straightforward task, there are different methods to delete files or directories, each with its specific use case.  This tutorial will provide a step-by-step guide on how to delete]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn .NET MAUI for cross-platform apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-net-maui-for-cross-platform-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-net-maui-for-cross-platform-apps/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T15:09:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking to develop cross-platform desktop and mobile applications? If so, we have just the course for you! We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you the essential skills you need to build your own mobile applications using .NET MAUI. Frank Liu]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Pull Remote Branch – How To Fetch Remote Branches in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-pull-remote-branch-how-to-fetch-remote-branches-in-git/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-pull-remote-branch-how-to-fetch-remote-branches-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T14:27:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a popular version control system that's used by millions of developers to manage their codebases. One of the most powerful features of Git is its ability to work with remote repositories. When working on a project with multiple collaborators, you must be able to fetch changes from the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Redux and Redux Toolkit – Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/redux-and-redux-toolkit-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/redux-and-redux-toolkit-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T14:20:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I started learning Redux, I found it challenging to wrap my head around the concepts. Despite reading many online resources, I struggled to grasp the core ideas.  While the online tutorials and guides provided helpful information, I needed more clarity to really understand Redux. But with persistence and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dickson Boateng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Styled Components in Your React Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/styled-components-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/styled-components-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T14:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Styled-components is a library that allows you to write CSS in JS while building custom components in Reactjs. There are multiple options you can go with to style a React application. But the  CSS in JS technique is good approach, where you write the CSS code right in the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Growing Need For Effective Password Management]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/effective-password-management/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/effective-password-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Highlighting the advantages of self-hosted solutions over cloud-based alternatives and exploring collaborative password management and more, P demonstrates how to organize convenient and secure password management in a company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iliya Garakh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Redis in Your PHP Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-redis-with-php/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-redis-with-php/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T19:51:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redis is a data store that stores data primarily in memory. It's faster than traditional databases, and has grown quite popular. In this tutorial, you'll learn the basics of how Redis works, when to use it, how to install it on your device, and how to use it as a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zubair Idris Aweda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Pointers in C Programming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pointers-in-c-programming/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pointers-in-c-programming/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T19:46:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are learning C programming, you have probably heard the term "pointer" before.  Pointers are one of the most important and powerful features of the C programming language. They allow us to manipulate memory directly, which can be very useful in many programming scenarios. In C, a pointer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write More Efficient JavaScript Conditions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-more-efficient-javascript-conditions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-more-efficient-javascript-conditions/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T17:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're coding in JavaScript, conditions are important for developing a functional application.  Conditional statements are important because you use them as "validators" which can either return truth or false. You can then use them to trigger further actions within the program. But with many long, messy if statements]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eesa Zahed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Check if a String is Empty or Null in JavaScript – JS Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/check-if-string-is-empty-or-null-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/check-if-string-is-empty-or-null-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T17:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, it's important to check whether a string is empty or null before performing any operation. Trying to operate on an empty or null string can lead to errors, bugs, and unexpected results. In this tutorial, we'll explore the different ways of checking whether a string is empty or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is SOLID? Principles for Better Software Design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/solid-principles-for-better-software-design/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/solid-principles-for-better-software-design/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T14:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SOLID principles are a set of guidelines for writing high-quality, maintainable, and scalable software.  They were introduced by Robert C. Martin in his 2000 paper “Design Principles and Design Patterns” [https://fi.ort.edu.uy/innovaportal/file/2032/1/design_principles.pdf] to help developers write software that is easy to understand, modify, and extend.  These concepts were]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Regression Analysis for Machine Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-regression-analysis-for-machine-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-regression-analysis-for-machine-learning/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T13:58:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to embark on a fascinating journey into the world of machine learning? Look no further!  We just posted a machine learning course for beginners on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. The course focusses on regression analysis. Ayush Singh is a data scientist and popular course creator. He]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Copy a Directory in Linux – Use the cp Command to Copy a Folder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-copy-a-directory-in-linux-use-the-cp-command-to-copy-a-folder/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-copy-a-directory-in-linux-use-the-cp-command-to-copy-a-folder/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T13:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Often times you'll want to copy a folder in Linux to perform specific tasks – maybe for backup, sharing, editing, an so on. This is a frequent task that you can perform using the cp command.  The cp command is a simple yet powerful command you can use to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XML Formatting in Notepad++ – How to Format XML Files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/xml-formatting-in-notepad-how-to-format-xml-files/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/xml-formatting-in-notepad-how-to-format-xml-files/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T12:41:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're working with XML files in Notepad++, formatting them manually could be a cumbersome task especially if the XML files are large. In this article, I will show you how to format your XML files in a few clicks. I will also show you how to check that the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Cloud Practitioner Salary – 2023 Amazon Certification Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/aws-cloud-practitioner-salary-2023-amazon-certification-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/aws-cloud-practitioner-salary-2023-amazon-certification-guide/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T06:51:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More and more companies are making a shift towards cloud services and cloud-based systems these days, resulting in cloud computing being one of the most in-demand tech skills for 2023. AWS is currently the most popular cloud service provider, as it owns around 33% of the cloud market. Companies and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with NodeJS – a Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-started-with-nodejs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-started-with-nodejs/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T18:25:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello folks! 👋 Over the past couple weeks, I have been learning about Node.js. So I decided to share my learnings with you here. 👨‍💻 In this tutorial, we'll take a high-level look at Node.js [https://twitter.com/nodejs] – what it is, and what can you do with it.  We will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krish Jaiswal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding VPC Architecture – How to Secure AWS EC2 Instances]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-vpc-architecture-securing-aws-ec2-instances/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-vpc-architecture-securing-aws-ec2-instances/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T13:33:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Virtual Private Clouds (VPCs) are the organizing structure of most AWS network operations. Without a clear understanding of how they work, it'll be hard to get security and efficiency quite right.  But before talking about VPCs directly, I'm going to take a minute or two to refresh your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is SSH? SSH Meaning in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ssh-meaning-in-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ssh-meaning-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T13:29:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secure Shell (SSH) is a widely used network protocol that provides a secure way to access remote servers and computers.  In Linux, SSH is an essential tool for remote administration and file transfer. In this article, we will go over the meaning of SSH in Linux, its history, features,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The GraphQL API Handbook – How to Build, Test, Consume and Document GraphQL APIs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/building-consuming-and-documenting-a-graphql-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/building-consuming-and-documenting-a-graphql-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T13:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this tutorial we're going to take a deep dive into GraphQL APIs. I recently wrote this article [/news/rest-vs-graphql-apis/] where I explained the main differences between common API types nowadays. And this tutorial aims to show you an example of how you can fully implement a GraphQL API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 60 With Mei Zhang: What Is Design Storytelling?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-60/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-60/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re talking about the process of design. How do you build a process to enable your best work? Vitaly Friedman talks to designer Mei Zhang to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Stress Tester Tool for Debugging Your Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-stress-tester-debugging-tool/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-stress-tester-debugging-tool/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T08:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently wrote about how competitive programmers debug their solutions during competitions [/news/debugging-like-competitive-programmers/]. We take advantage of randomization and the computing power in the devices we use daily.  That article was selected as one of the winners of the DebuggingFeb Writeathon [https://townhall.hashnode.com/debuggingfeb-writeathon-winners] and got a lot of visibility from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alberto Gonzalez Rosales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Routing System for a PHP App from Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-routing-system-in-php/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-routing-system-in-php/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T08:36:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re just at the beginning of your journey in PHP development, chances are that you use complete file names in the URL to navigate your application, like  server/contact.php. No worries, we all started that way, and it’s how we learn. Today, I want to help you improve how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abel Lifaefi Mbula</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Object Oriented Programming Basics – OOP, Classes, and Objects in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-oriented-programming-basics-oop-classes-and-objects-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-oriented-programming-basics-oop-classes-and-objects-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T07:33:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Java is a powerful programming language to develop software in. And if you're trying to learn it, that's great. The first thing you'll need to know to develop software in Java is Object Oriented Programming, or OOP for short. Now if you're asking yourself, "What is OOP?" don't worry. We'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Avdhoot Fulsundar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YAML Commenting – How to Add a Multiline Comment in YAML]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-a-multiline-comment-in-yaml/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-a-multiline-comment-in-yaml/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T18:28:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use a YAML file to store data in a format that can be easily read and understood by humans. It is a data serialization language [/news/what-is-yaml-the-yml-file-format/#intro:~:text=Serialization%20is%20a%20process%20where%20one%20application%20or%20service%20that%20has%20different%20data%20structures%20and%20is%20written%20in%20a%20different%20set%20of%20technologies%20can%20transfer%20data%20to%20another%20application%20using%20a%20standard%20format.]  that is often used for configurat]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Python from Harvard University]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-python-from-harvard-university/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-python-from-harvard-university/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T14:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to embark on a journey to learn one of the most popular programming languages in the world? Introducing Harvard University's CS50P: Introduction to Programming with Python, a comprehensive video course tailored to teach Python programming from scratch. Taught by the renowned Dr. David J. Malan, this course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make Your May Magnificent (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May is almost here, so what better occasion could there be for some fresh and inspiring desktop and mobile wallpapers? Created with love by artists and designers from across the globe, the wallpapers in this post come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Hoisting in JavaScript | Hoisting Functions, Variables and Classes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-hoisting-in-javascript-3/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-hoisting-in-javascript-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T14:54:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hoisting is a concept or behavior in JavaScript where the declaration of a function, variable, or class goes to the top of the scope they were defined in. What does this mean? Hoisting is a concept you may find in some programming languages (such as JavaScript) and not in others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pub/Sub in Redis – How to Use the Publish/Subscribe Messaging Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-pub-sub-in-redis/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-pub-sub-in-redis/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T14:33:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working on an application that needs to be easily maintainable, scalable, and performant, the Publish/Subscribe messaging pattern is a good choice. The idea behind it is simple, but powerful. We have senders called publishers.  Their sole role is to send or publish messages. They don’t care about]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mihail Gaberov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Intruders – Top Ways Hackers Can Breach Your Smartphone’s Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-hackers-can-breach-your-smartphones-security/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-hackers-can-breach-your-smartphones-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T14:16:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smartphones are integral to our lives, making them prime targets for hackers. In this article, we will go through 7 ways hackers can gain access to your smartphone and how to protect against these attacks. Smartphones have become an essential part of our daily lives with instant access to information]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Punct in RegEx? How to Match All Punctuation Marks in Regular Expressions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-punct-in-regex-how-to-match-all-punctuation-marks-in-regular-expressions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-punct-in-regex-how-to-match-all-punctuation-marks-in-regular-expressions/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T11:28:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In regular expressions, "punct" means punctuation marks. It is all non-word and non-space characters. "Punct" is a predefined character class in regular expressions, and you can use it in any regex flavor that supports it. The Punct character class is denoted by \p{Punct} or simply \p{P}. It matches any punctuation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write Better CSS By Borrowing Ideas From JavaScript Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/write-better-css-borrow-ideas-javascript-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/write-better-css-borrow-ideas-javascript-functions/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many problems with website layouts happen when we don’t write CSS with the same care we’d use when writing a JavaScript function. Let’s look at how we can borrow best practices and ideas from writing good JavaScript functions for writing CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yaphi Berhanu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Merge – The Definitive Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-definitive-guide-to-git-merge/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-definitive-guide-to-git-merge/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T17:07:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By reading this post, you are going to really understand git merge, one of the most common operations you'll perform in your Git repositories. Notes before we start  1. I also created two videos covering the contents of this post. If you wish to     watch]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Scrapy for Web Scraping in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-scrapy-for-web-scraping-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-scrapy-for-web-scraping-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T15:44:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you tired of manually collecting data from websites? Have you ever wished you could automate the process and gather massive amounts of data in a fraction of the time? We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to scrape websites with Python]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The REST API Handbook – How to Build, Test, Consume, and Document REST APIs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-consume-and-document-a-rest-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-consume-and-document-a-rest-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T13:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this tutorial we're going to take a deep dive into REST APIs. I recently wrote this article [/news/rest-vs-graphql-apis/] where I explained the main differences between common API types nowadays. And this tutorial aims to show you an example of how you can fully implement a REST API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do I Enable Square Brackets in RegEx?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-i-enable-square-brackets-in-regex/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-i-enable-square-brackets-in-regex/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T12:31:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you’ll learn about what square brackets do in regular expressions, how to use them for specifying ranges, and how to match them as a character. What Does Square Bracket Do in RegEx? In regular expressions, square brackets ([ ]) are characters that have a special meaning of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible Target Sizes Cheatsheet]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/accessible-tap-target-sizes-rage-taps-clicks/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/accessible-tap-target-sizes-rage-taps-clicks/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Practical guidelines to prevent rage taps and rage clicks with accessible tap targets for icons, links and buttons — on desktop and on mobile. With useful techniques and guidelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[strcmp in C – How to Compare Strings in C]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/strcmp-in-c-how-to-compare-strings-in-c/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/strcmp-in-c-how-to-compare-strings-in-c/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T20:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comparing strings is a common task in most programming languages. In C, you can use the strcmp function to handle string comparisons.  In this article, I will show you practical examples of the strcmp function, and offer insights into how it compares strings, what its return values mean, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Ternary Operator – Conditional Operators in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-tenary-operator/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-tenary-operator/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T15:29:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use conditional operators in Python to execute code based on a predefined condition(s).  In this article, you'll learn how to use the ternary operator in Python. You'll see its syntax along with some practical examples.  What Is the Ternary Operator Used for in Python? The ternary]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Simple Website with HTML, CSS, JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-simple-website-with-html-css-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-simple-website-with-html-css-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T14:59:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Embark on an exciting journey to master frontend development with this course created by Jess, the expert behind the acclaimed Coder Coder YouTube channel. This comprehensive course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel is tailored to empower you with the knowledge and skills required to excel in JavaScript, HTML, and CSS,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Changes to an Application – Deployment Strategies Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/application-deployment-strategies/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/application-deployment-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T14:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When deploying changes to an application, there are several strategies you can use.  In this article, I'll explain the different strategies with an analogy, and then we'll analyze the benefits and tradeoffs. Deployment Strategies Imagine you are the manager of a popular pizza restaurant that is open 24/7 for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does M Mean in Regular Expressions? M Flag for RegEx]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-m-mean-in-regular-expressions-m-flag-for-regex/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-m-mean-in-regular-expressions-m-flag-for-regex/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T14:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In regular expressions, "m" is a flag that signifies multiple lines. So, it is popularly called the "multiline flag". In this article, I will show you what the "m" flag does and how you can use it in both regex engines and JavaScript. What Does the "m" Flag Do? Sometimes,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Prevent Infinite Loops When Using useEffect() in ReactJS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prevent-infinite-loops-when-using-useeffect-in-reactjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prevent-infinite-loops-when-using-useeffect-in-reactjs/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T14:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The useEffect hook in React has become a common tool for managing side effects in functional components. But there's a common pitfall when using it: the potential for infinite loops. These can cause performance issues and disrupt the intended behavior of components.  In this tutorial, we will explore how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roy Chng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Function Declaration vs Function Expression]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/function-declaration-vs-function-expression/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/function-declaration-vs-function-expression/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T12:11:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When creating functions, you can use two approaches: declaration and expression. What's the difference? When talking about functions in JavaScript, you would often hear function declarations and function expressions. Though these approaches are almost similar, they have notable differences. We'll look at the differences in this article. I have a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Java Used For in 2023? The Java Programming Language and Java Platform Strengths]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-java-used-for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-java-used-for/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T21:26:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Java is a very popular programming language you can use to create a variety of software applications. It's an object-oriented language that was made to be simple to read, write, and learn.  Millions of developers use Java to create everything from desktop programs to sophisticated web apps. This makes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Supercharge Your Studying with Python, Anki, and ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/supercharged-studying-with-python-anki-chatgpt/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/supercharged-studying-with-python-anki-chatgpt/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T20:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have heard how students can use ChatGPT [https://chat.openai.com] to cheat on assignments. But we should also talk about what a fantastic study tool it can be.  In this article we'll discuss how you can use ChatGPT to help you study and learn new skills. You'll see how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Otavio Ehrenberger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Insert into a JavaScript Array at a Specific Index – JS Push]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/insert-into-javascript-array-at-specific-index/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/insert-into-javascript-array-at-specific-index/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T18:14:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript arrays are an important part of the language. They allow you to store and manipulate collections of data. Sometimes, you may need to insert a new element into an array at a specific index. To accomplish this task, you can use the push() method or the splice()  method.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering Zustand: A Simple and Efficient State Management Library for React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/zustand-course-react-state-management/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/zustand-course-react-state-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T17:21:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern web applications demand efficient and easy-to-use state management solutions that don't compromise on flexibility or performance. Zustand, a minimalistic state management library for React, offers just that. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you unlock the full potential of Zustand and create]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Upload Files to Amazon S3 with Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-upload-files-to-aws-s3-with-node/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-upload-files-to-aws-s3-with-node/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T16:31:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[File upload is a common feature in a lot of modern applications. These platforms accept different file formats, including jpeg, png, gif, pdf, txt, zip, and mp3.  Some applications will also restrict uploads to a specific file type. For example, when uploading your resume on LinkedIn, you will see]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fiyinfoluwa Akinsiku</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Interactive Accordion Component with React and GSAP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-interactive-accordion-component-with-react-and-gsap/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-interactive-accordion-component-with-react-and-gsap/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T15:47:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As websites become more sophisticated and user expectations continue to rise, web developers must search for ways to create more engaging and interactive user interfaces.  One powerful tool in a developer's arsenal is the accordion component, a versatile and widely-used element found on nearly every website.  In this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could UX Be The Key To Unlocking Web3 Mass Adoption?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/ux-web3-mass-adoption/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/ux-web3-mass-adoption/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized web is our new reality, but Web3 UX is shockingly bad. In this article, Pete Boyle addresses the major shortcomings in Web3 adoption and how we might be able to solve them and make the entire ecosystem more user-friendly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Pete Boyle)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Large Language Models and Cybersecurity – What You Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/large-language-models-and-cybersecurity/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/large-language-models-and-cybersecurity/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T01:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT has had well over a billion visits since its release. Now, what happens when you combine the greatest language learning model of the decade with malicious hacking...what could go wrong? 💀 In this article, we'll explore what artificial intelligence is, its current state, how large language models like ChatGPT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Iwugo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get the Current URL with JavaScript – JS Location Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-the-current-url-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-the-current-url-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T00:34:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a web developer, you'll work with JavaScript when building dynamic and interactive web applications. One common task that you'll need to perform is getting the current URL of a web page. In this article, you will learn how to get the current URL using JavaScript's Location object. I'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use ChatGPT – Prompts for Data Scientists]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-chatgpt-for-data-scientists/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-chatgpt-for-data-scientists/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T23:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, many people are concerned with the way AI is evolving. They see it effortlessly solving problems, performing tasks quickly and accurately, and doing jobs easily and efficiently.  And while some people are scared, others are actually embracing it. I'm one of those people who are embracing it,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Server Side Rendering in JavaScript – SSR vs CSR Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/server-side-rendering-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/server-side-rendering-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T22:12:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The concept of Server Side Rendering (SSR) is often misunderstood. So my aim in this article is to bring clarity to this process and how it works.  Here's what we'll cover in this guide:  1. What is server side rendering? What are its pros and cons when compared]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Boost Your Creativity – Strategies for Generating Ideas and Overcoming Writer's Block]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-overcome-writers-block-and-boost-creativity/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-overcome-writers-block-and-boost-creativity/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T19:46:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you ever find yourself stuck when it comes to writing or unable to come up with creative solutions to a problem? Don’t worry—you are not alone. Everyone experiences writer's block or a lack of creativity at some point. At times, as writers, we may be really eager to write]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is RAM? How to Access Your Computer's RAM and Read the Contents]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-access-and-read-ram-contents/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-access-and-read-ram-contents/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T19:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is a comprehensive guide on how to read the contents of your computer's RAM.  Random Access Memory (RAM) is a crucial component of any computer system, and it is responsible for temporarily storing data that is required by the system to carry out its functions. But the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gursimar Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Visualization with Matplotlib – a Step by Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-data-vizualization-using-matplotlib/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-data-vizualization-using-matplotlib/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T18:32:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEE [https://tv.apple.com/us/show/see/umc.cmc.3s4mgg2y7h95fks9gnc4pw13m] is a beautiful Apple TV series that depicts a dystopia where humans have lost their sight. Hundreds of years later, it was considered a myth that people could ever see.  Jason Momoa is one of the leads and plays Baba Voss, an elite warrior. Jason's wife gives]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MENE-EJEGI OGBEMI</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Regular Expression in JSON File]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-regular-expression-in-json-file/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-regular-expression-in-json-file/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T12:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JSON stands for JavaScript Object Notation. It is a text-based and lightweight data format for exchanging information between systems, for example, a web server and a web application. JSON files typically contain objects, arrays, strings, and numbers. But you can also have regular expressions in a JSON file. And that’s]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Potentially Dangerous Non-Accessibility Of Cookie Notices]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potentially-dangerous-non-accessibility-cookie-notices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potentially-dangerous-non-accessibility-cookie-notices/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this piece, a Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG) auditor shares some cookie banner error patterns that can massively hurt a page’s overall conformance. Let’s explore what to look out for with this omnipresent piece of the web interface.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcus Herrmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigation in Flutter – How to Add Stack, Tab, and Drawer Navigators to Your Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/navigation-in-flutter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/navigation-in-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T18:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost any app that you design or develop will use some type of navigation.  There are three types of navigation that are common to all apps – stack, tab, and drawer navigation. Flutter supports all three types, and implementing them is similar to how you do it in other]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Difference Between Pseudo-Classes and Pseudo-Elements in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-difference-between-pseudo-classes-and-elements-in-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-difference-between-pseudo-classes-and-elements-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T17:34:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In CSS, pseudo-classes and pseudo-elements are two types of keywords that you can combine with selectors. They are used to target the element's state or specific parts of an element.  In this article, we'll explore the differences between the two along with their history and best practices. Syntax]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie Pina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring The Potential Of Web Workers For Multithreading On The Web]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potential-web-workers-multithreading-web/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potential-web-workers-multithreading-web/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sarah Oke Okolo explores the importance of Web Workers for multithreading on the web, including the limitations and considerations of using them and the strategies for mitigating potential issues associated with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sarah Oke Okolo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Initialize an ArrayList in Java – Declaration with Values]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-initialize-an-arraylist-in-java-with-values/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-initialize-an-arraylist-in-java-with-values/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T06:34:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use an ArrayList in Java to store and manipulate a collection of similar variables.  An ArrayList is just like an array [/news/java-array-how-to-declare-and-initialize-an-array-in-java-example/] but offers more flexibility. An ArrayList is more dynamic with the size of the collection, and gives you more control over the elements in a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use APIs in Your Projects to Practice Your Coding Skills]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-apis-to-practice-coding-skills/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-apis-to-practice-coding-skills/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T22:28:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As web developers, we all know that practice makes perfect. But when it comes to practice, it's easy to get stuck in a programming rut. But how do you come up with new ideas to build? Sooner or later, you will find yourself running out of features to add or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Handle File Uploads on the Back End in Node.js and Nuxt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/handle-file-uploads-on-the-backend-in-node-js-nuxt/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/handle-file-uploads-on-the-backend-in-node-js-nuxt/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T22:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In some previous tutorials, I covered how to upload files using HTML [https://austingil.com/uploading-files-with-html/] and JavaScript [https://austingil.com/upload-files-with-javascript/]. It requires sending HTTP requests with the Content-Type [https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/HTTP/Headers/Content-Type] header set to multipart/form-data. Today, we are going to the back end to receive those multipart/form-data  requests and access the binary data from those]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Austin Gil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Communicate with ChatGPT – A Guide to Prompt Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-communicate-with-ai-tools-prompt-engineering/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-communicate-with-ai-tools-prompt-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T20:54:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI has become an integral part of our lives and businesses. Over the past few years, we’ve seen the rapid rise of AI tools, and their impact on our day-to-day activities can't be ignored. From virtual assistants to chatbots, AI just keeps getting smarter with more functionalities than before. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hillary Nyakundi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prepare for Your JavaScript Interview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-for-your-javascript-interview/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-for-your-javascript-interview/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T17:04:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you preparing for a JavaScript interview and want to ensure that you have a deep understanding of closures, functions, and currying? Then Roadside Coder's video course is just what you need. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help prepare you for a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does the Caret Mean in RegEx? Caret Metacharacter in Regular Expressions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-the-caret-mean-in-regex-how-to-match-the-start-of-a-line-in-regular-expressions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-the-caret-mean-in-regex-how-to-match-the-start-of-a-line-in-regular-expressions/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T16:47:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A caret (^) is one of the many symbols for creating patterns in regular expressions. A caret matches the start of a line or a particular string. But that’s not all there is to the caret (^) symbol. The caret symbol (^) is often referred to as an "anchor" because]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Copy File – Copying Files to Another Directory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-copy-file-copying-files-to-another-directory/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-copy-file-copying-files-to-another-directory/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T14:16:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with Python, there may be times when you need to copy a file. Copying files comes in handy when you need to create a backup. In this article, you will learn how to copy a file in Python using the shutil  module and its different methods. The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>