<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-06-24T00:43:04.427Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Data Analysis? How to Visualize Data with Python, Numpy, Pandas, Matplotlib &amp; Seaborn Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>605abca5687d62084bf6b7cd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/exploratory-data-analysis-with-numpy-pandas-matplotlib-seaborn/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T00:11:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data Analysis is the process of exploring, investigating, and gathering insights from data using statistical measures and visualizations.  The objective of data analysis is to develop an understanding of data by uncovering trends, relationships, and patterns. Data analysis is both a science and an art. On the one hand it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microservices Architecture – Explained in Plain English]]></title>
        <id>6072ffd4d5756f080ba98b27</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/microservices-architecture-for-humans/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T21:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last few years, microservices have gone from an overhyped buzzword to something you should understand as a software engineer.  According to an O'Reilly developer survey in 2020:  61% of companies have been using microservices in the last year29% say at least half of their company systems are built]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TablesNG — Improvements to table rendering in Chromium]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343076</id>
        <link href="https://www.bram.us/2021/06/21/tablesng-improvements-to-table-rendering-in-chromium/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T21:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I blogged “Making Tables With Sticky Header and Footers Got a Bit Easier” recently, I mentioned that the “stickiness” improvement was just one of the features that got better for <table>s in Chrome as part of the TablesNG upgrade…
The post TablesNG — Improvements to table rendering in Chromium appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Performant Next-Gen Images in CSS with image-set]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342750</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-performant-next-gen-images-in-css-with-image-set/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T19:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS image-set() function has been supported in Chromium-based browsers since 2012 and in Safari since version 6. Support recently landed in Firefox 88. Let’s dive in and see what we can and can’t do today with image-set().…
The post Using Performant Next-Gen Images in CSS with image-set appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a REST API with .NET 5 and  C#]]></title>
        <id>60d36eb66e1a1407b6b0b16d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-rest-api-with-dot-net-5-and-c-sharp/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T18:08:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.NET is a popular software framework developed by Microsoft. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create a REST API end-to-end from scratch using the latest .NET 5 innovations and Visual Studio Code. The course uses the C# programming language.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Great Technical Course]]></title>
        <id>60a406bd906c5207e3a7dfcb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-great-technical-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T17:19:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article you will learn how to create a great technical video course. I run the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel where we post technical courses from a variety of contributors. Video courses that follow the guidelines in this article are often a good fit for freeCodeCamp's channel. How to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Weak declaration”]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342669</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/weak-declaration/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T14:27:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PPK looks at aspect-ratio, a CSS property for layout that, for the most part, does exactly what you would think it does. It’s getting more interesting as it’s behind a flag in Firefox and Safari now, so we’ll have …
The post “Weak declaration” appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Online Workshops (July-October 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run [online workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Screen Reader Testing On macOS Using Auto VO]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automated testing is an important part of any software project, including testing for accessibility. There are already tools for linting and integration testing accessibility, but what about end-to-end testing with real assistive technology? Since I hadn’t seen this before, I set out to build Auto VO, a driver for the VoiceOver screen reader.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cameron Cundiff)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[inherit, initial, unset, revert]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342930</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/inherit-initial-unset-revert/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T21:20:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are four keywords that are valid values for any CSS property (see the title). Of those, day to day, I’d say I see the inherit used the most. Perhaps because it’s been around the longest (I think?) but also …
The post inherit, initial, unset, revert appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Scraping with PHP – How to Crawl Web Pages Using Open Source Tools]]></title>
        <id>60d2323d6e1a1407b6b0ac4f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-scraping-with-php-crawl-web-pages/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T21:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web scraping lets you collect data from web pages across the internet. It's also called web crawling or web data extraction.  PHP is a widely used back-end scripting language for creating dynamic websites and web applications. And you can implement a web scraper using plain PHP code.  But since we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Async/Await to Write Better JavaScript Code]]></title>
        <id>60cac8ff4dc1a607ed7b4592</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-async-await-write-better-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a special syntax you can use in JavaScript that makes working with promises easier. It's called “async/await", and it’s surprisingly straightforward to understand and use.  In this article, we'll discuss:  What are asynchronus functions? How promises work in JavaScript Async/Await basics How to use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TypeScript and MongoDB to Build a 100 Days of Code Discord Bot]]></title>
        <id>60c13e71d3126007592d5be2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-100-days-of-code-bot-for-discord-using-typescript-and-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 100 Days of Code challenge is very popular among new coders and developers looking to level up their skills. It's so popular that our Discord server has an entire channel dedicated to it.  By popular demand, we recently built a Discord bot that helps people track their progress in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Python to Create a Visual Novel Game in 10 Minutes]]></title>
        <id>60cfff5a4dc1a607ed7b5e58</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-python-to-create-a-visual-novel/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you have a story idea that you'd like to turn into a novel? How about adding visual appeal and interactivity to that novel?  A Visual Novel might be the game genre you are looking for. And this tutorial is here to help set you up in 10 minutes, with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Custom Elements in Svelte]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342634</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-custom-elements-in-svelte/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T14:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Svelte fully supports custom elements (e.g. <my-component>) without any custom configuration or wrapper components and has a perfect score on Custom Elements Everywhere. However, there are still a few quirks you need to watch out for, especially around …
The post Using Custom Elements in Svelte appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Rich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If we’re gonna criticize utility-class frameworks, let’s be fair about it]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342925</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/if-were-gonna-criticize-utility-class-frameworks-lets-be-fair-about-it/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T14:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not here to raise a shield protecting CSS utility frameworks. I don’t even particularly like the approach, myself, and nothing is above fair criticism. But fair is a key word there. I can’t tell you how many times I’ve …
The post If we’re gonna criticize utility-class frameworks, let’s be fair about it appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing With Code: A Modern Approach To Design (Development Challenges)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of innovation in both tools and processes, the struggle between design and development is still real. This article focuses on the best practices for improving the design to development processes and how cutting-edge solutions, such as UXPin powered by Merge technology, can help in facilitating the change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Exit Vim – Vim Save and Quit Command Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>60c81f774dc1a607ed7b2f66</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-exit-vim/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T21:52:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been using Vim since the first year I started coding. For all the IDEs/editors that I have used, the Vim plugin is always the very first plugin that I install. I know that Vim can be challenging to work in for people who are not familiar with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python List Methods – append( ) vs extend( ) in Python Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>60bce157acb62507dd1d9f11</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-methods-append-vs-extend/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T21:25:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with Python lists, you often need to combine data from multiple lists. So how do you do that? In this tutorial, we'll see the different ways you can combine data from multiple lists. We'll also learn how the list methods append() and extend() work through simple examples.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are we in a new era of web design? What do we call it?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342887</id>
        <link href="https://web.dev/new-responsive/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T21:22:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Una is calling it the new responsive. A nod to the era we were most certainly in, the era of responsive design. Where responsive design was fluid grids, flexible media, and media queries, the new responsive is those things …
The post Are we in a new era of web design? What do we call it? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Redux by Making a Counter Application]]></title>
        <id>60cccd6e4dc1a607ed7b4f81</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-redux-by-making-a-counter-application/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T21:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redux is a state management library for front end applications. Developers commonly use it with React through the react-redux package, but it can also stand alone – so you can use it in any front end framework or library, including Vanilla JavaScript.  Redux can really be intimidating at first. It might]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Portfolio Website with React]]></title>
        <id>60d0d0ff6e1a1407b6b0a506</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-portfolio-website-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T18:15:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today you're going to create one of the most important apps you can build for yourself: your developer portfolio. Every React developer or web developer in general needs to be able to show off what they can do to any potential client or employer. That's exactly what we're going to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Figma? A Design Crash Course [2021 Tutorial]]]></title>
        <id>60cda7104dc1a607ed7b5588</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/figma-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T17:52:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Figma is a powerful design tool that helps you to create anything: websites, applications, logos, and much more. By learning to use Figma, you'll take your first steps into User Interface Design and and User Experience Design. These skills are essential for building a great portfolio for yourself and potentially]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Technical Guide to IPFS – the Decentralized Storage of Web3]]></title>
        <id>60a55b37906c5207e3a7ea78</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/technical-guide-to-ipfs-decentralized-storage-of-web3/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T16:38:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But where do you store your application's content? Storing the content on the blockchain would be expensive and inefficient. Your blockchain application needs decentralized storage!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the CSS Position Property Works – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>6063b9e19618b008528a9d9a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-position-property-explained/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T16:36:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we're gonna learn everything you need to know about the CSS position property along with examples. Let's get started 🎖️ Table of contents What is CSS Position Property?What is the Static Position in CSS?What are the Relative and Absolute Positions in CSS?What is the Fixed Position in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create CSS Charts With Interesting Shapes, Glyphs and Emoji]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342448</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-create-css-charts-with-interesting-shapes-glyphs-and-emoji/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T14:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s forego the usual circles and bars we typically see used in charts for more eccentric shapes. With online presentations more and more common today, a quick way to spruce up your web slides and make them stand out is …
The post How to Create CSS Charts With Interesting Shapes, Glyphs and Emoji appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image To Text Conversion With React And Tesseract.js (OCR)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you have to process data manually because it is served through images or scanned documents? An image-to-text conversion makes it possible to extract text from images to automate the processing of texts on images, videos, and scanned documents. In this article, we look at how to convert an image to text with React and Tesseract.js(OCR), preprocess images, and deal with the limitations of Tesseract (OCR).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ayobami Ogundiran)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using the `outline` Property as a Collapsable Border]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341511</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-the-outline-property-as-a-collapsable-border/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T20:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The outline property in CSS draws a line around the outside of an element. This is quite similar to the border property, the main exception being that outline isn’t a part of the box model. It is often used for …
The post Using the `outline` Property as a Collapsable Border appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carter Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TCP vs UDP – Which Protocol is Faster?]]></title>
        <id>60b46dbd11ffb70827ef9dea</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tcp-vs-udp-which-is-faster/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is TCP?TCP is an acronym for Transmission Control Protocol. It is a transport layer protocol that allows packets to be sent from one location to another.  TCP is a connection-oriented protocol, which means it establishes the connection before any communication between the network’s computer units. Because we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning Specialisation Courses for Advanced ML Practitioners]]></title>
        <id>60cc5a904dc1a607ed7b4c54</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-specialisation-courses-for-advanced-ml-practitioners/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T15:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, you don’t need to go to a university or a college to pursue a career in machine learning or any data-driven domain. But you do need a plan and a roadmap to guide your studies. Once you have charted your own learning roadmap with a goal in mind,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Alternative Voice UI To Voice Assistants]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice assistants are currently the most popular use case for voice user interfaces. However, due to the bad feedback loop resulting from voice assistants can only solve simple user tasks such as setting an alarm or playing music. In order for voice user interfaces to really break through, feedback to the user must be visual, not auditive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ottomatias Peura)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Sorting Algorithms]]></title>
        <id>60cca3294dc1a607ed7b4c76</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-sorting-algorithms/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every programming language uses sorting algorithms. While programming languages have easy-to-use sorting methods, it can be helpful to understand how they work. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you some of the most popular sorting algorithms! Haris Iftikhar developed this course. Haris]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links on Typography]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342326</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/links-on-typography-2/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I studied the fonts of the top 1000 websites. Here’s what I learned. — Michael Li brings the data. San-serif has total dominance. “[…] it is rare to go below 10px or above 24px.” And poor <h5> always being the 
…
The post Links on Typography appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client-Side Routing In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js has a file-based routing system in which each page automatically becomes a route based on its file name. This article will guide you through almost everything you need to know about Routing in Next.js and point you in the direction of related topics and concepts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adebiyi Adedotun)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perfect Tooltips With CSS Clipping and Masking]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341948</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/perfect-tooltips-with-css-clipping-and-masking/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T14:45:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clipping and masking have been around for a while now in CSS and even have pretty decent browser support. I recently worked on a project that needed to use a clipping technique for tooltips showing above links in text.
Those …
The post Perfect Tooltips With CSS Clipping and Masking appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Hoebregts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start Serving Optimized Images in Vue]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342257</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/start-serving-optimized-images-in-vue/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T14:38:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have become extremely important to the effectiveness of websites. They speak a 1000 words, attract attention, and stimulate emotions.
However, web performance is also a growing problem for most websites. And images are at the heart of many web …
The post Start Serving Optimized Images in Vue appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ImageEngine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure AI Fundamentals Certification (AI-900) – Pass the Exam With This Free 4 Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>60c2aa56d3126007592d6226</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/azure-data-fundamentals-certification-ai-900-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-4-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T12:02:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Azure AI Fundamentals Certification?The Azure AI Fundamentals Certification is for those seeking a Machine Learning role such as AI Engineer or Data Scientist. In the last decade companies have been collecting vast amount of data surrounding their service and product offerings. The successful companies of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Image Is Probably Not Decorative]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image placement on the modern web is highly intentional, helping to communicate the overall purpose of a page or view. This means that nearly every image you declare needs to have an alternate description.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Bookmarklets and How to Make Them]]></title>
        <id>60c88bbc4dc1a607ed7b2ffa</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-bookmarklets/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T00:53:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bookmarklets are browser bookmarks that execute JavaScript instead of opening a webpage. They're also known as bookmark applets, favlets, or JavaScript bookmarks. Bookmarklets are natively available in all major browsers, including Mozilla Firefox and Chromium-based browsers like Chrome or Brave. Scripting with JavaScriptLearning how to write scripts provides many benefits,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Split – How to Split a String into an Array in JS]]></title>
        <id>60c088e5d3126007592d56f1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-split-how-to-split-a-string-into-an-array-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T21:19:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In general, a string represents a sequence of characters in a programming language.  Let's look at an example of a string created using a sequence of characters, "Yes, You Can DO It!". In JavaScript, we can create a string in a couple of ways: Using the string literal as a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inline Styles as Classes (lol)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342358</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/inline-styles-as-classes-lol/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T21:11:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re abhorred by using inline styles, just move that style to the class attribute! And then make sure you have CSS in place that, ya know, does what it says on the box. 
I've revolutionized CSS. pic.twitter.com/1AWCldyCwP
— Sam 

…
The post Inline Styles as Classes (lol) appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skewness and Kurtosis – Positively Skewed and Negatively Skewed Distributions in Statistics Explained]]></title>
        <id>60b8cb0aacb62507dd1d82ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/skewness-and-kurtosis-in-statistics-explained/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T20:56:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll explain two important concepts in statistics: skewness and kurtosis. And don't worry – you won't need to know very much math to understand these concepts and learn how to apply them. What are Density Curves?Let's first talk a bit about density curves, as skewness and kurtosis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Better React Apps with These Simple Tricks]]></title>
        <id>60ca25704dc1a607ed7b408c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-better-react-apps-with-these-tricks/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T20:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a list of amazing tricks that you can use to improve your React applications instantly. These tips will not only make your code cleaner and more reliable, but they also aim to make your development experience easier and overall more enjoyable.  Give these techniques a try in your React]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful and Useless Code Comments]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342630</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jim-nielsen.com/2021/useful-and-usless-code-comments/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T19:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Nielsen: 
If somebody says a comment isn’t adding any value, I would ask: to whom?
Personally, I’ve never liked the advice that writing obvious comments is bad practice—probably because I write obvious comments all the time.
Jim showed …
The post Useful and Useless Code Comments appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teach Yourself Data Analytics in 30 Days]]></title>
        <id>60ca30af4dc1a607ed7b4197</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/teach-yourself-data-analytics-in-30-days/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T17:19:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can learn the basics of Data Analytics with 30 days of practice.  We just released a Data Analytics course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. The course includes a 40-minute video, as well as a website and Jupyter notebooks. If you follow the plan laid out in these course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Used the WAAPI to Build an Animation Library]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342353</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-i-used-the-waapi-to-build-an-animation-library/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T14:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Web Animations API lets us construct animations and control their playback with JavaScript. The API opens the browser’s animation engine to developers and was designed to underlie implementations of both CSS animations and transitions, leaving the door open to …
The post How I Used the WAAPI to Build an Animation Library appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okiki Ojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Accessibility Tooling]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new short series of posts, we highlight some of the useful tools and techniques for developers and designers. Recently we’ve covered HTML Emails and SVG Generators. This time we look into different kinds of tools to help you streamline your accessibility testing process. Don’t miss the next one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nic Chan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detect Unused Classes in… HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342198</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/detect-unused-classes-in-html/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T23:24:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Usually, when “unused” comes up in conversation regarding CSS, it’s about removing chunks of CSS that are not used in your site or, at least, the styles not currently in use on a specific page. The minimal amount of CSS …
The post Detect Unused Classes in… HTML appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Engineering Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>60c91b2b4dc1a607ed7b389a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/devops-engineering-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T21:33:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps is becoming an in-demand role at many software companies. We just released a DevOps Engineering course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Learn all about DevOps in this comprehensive course for beginners with three technical tutorials. Colin Chartier created this course. He is the co-founder and CEO at LayerCI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does &#x27;this&#x27; Mean in JavaScript? The this Keyword Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>60c72a0ad3126007592d7e2a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-this-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T21:19:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To understand what this truly means in JavaScript, let's take a look at a very similar concept in the English Language: Polysemy. Let's consider the word "run". Run is a single word which could mean many different things depending on the context. “I will run home” – means to move quickly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Charge as a Freelance Developer – and Why You Should Avoid Being the Cheapest]]></title>
        <id>60c8912c4dc1a607ed7b2fff</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-to-charge-as-a-freelance-developer-dont-be-the-cheapest/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T21:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a freelance developer, knowing how much to charge for a project can often feel like a gamble. It's easy to wonder "Am I setting my price too high?" This is normally the first question that comes to mind. And your brain will probably meet this question with a resounding]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Media Queries in Times of @container]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342519</id>
        <link href="https://mxb.dev/blog/media-queries-in-times-of-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T19:51:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Max Böck took me up on my challenge to look through a codebase and see how many of the @media queries could ultimately become @container queries.
I took the bait and had a look at some of my projects – 
…
The post Media Queries in Times of @container appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Decorators – How to Create and Use Decorators in Python With Examples]]></title>
        <id>60c3dcb3d3126007592d6c6d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-decorators-explained-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T17:57:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python decorators allow you to change the behavior of a function without modifying the function itself. In this article I will show you how to create and use decorators. You will see how easy it is to use this advanced Python feature. In this article I will discuss the following]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Strangler Fig Pattern and How it Helps Manage Legacy Code]]></title>
        <id>602aaaf60a2838549dcc5c7f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-the-strangler-pattern-in-software-development/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T17:43:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Any sufficiently old codebase eventually starts to contain legacy code. Architecture, performance, comments, and more begin to degrade the moment after they are written. Some parts of the codebase last longer than other parts, but inevitably new coding standards emerge to reduce technical debt. Then you have to rework a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Open Any Repo in VS Code Without Cloning It]]></title>
        <id>60b7cb6aacb62507dd1d7c1a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/you-can-now-edit-anything-on-github-in-vs-code-without-cloning/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T16:06:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now open anything (that you have access to) on GitHub directly from VS Code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Aggregate Functions – With Example Data Queries for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>60c6aec3d3126007592d7bd5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-aggregate-functions-with-example-data-queries-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T15:48:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is an Aggregate Function?SQL aggregate functions will seem very familiar if you have worked with spreadsheets.  Have you ever used SUM in Google Sheets or Excel? The SUM function exists in SQL as well, and is called an aggregate function.  Aggregate functions do a particular task across database]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Full Stack? How to Become a Full Stack Developer]]></title>
        <id>60bbdd8dacb62507dd1d9a2d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-fullstack-developer/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T15:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You've probably seen the term "full stack developer" before, either on tech-related websites or in job applications you've perused.  So have you ever wondered what exactly a full stack developer is and what skills you'd need to become one? Well if you're curious like I was, this article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just How Niche is Headless WordPress?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342248</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/just-how-niche-is-headless-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T14:31:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wonder where headless WordPress will land. And by “headless” I mean only using the WordPress admin and building out the user-facing site through the WordPress REST API rather than the traditional WordPress theme structure.
Is it… big? The future …
The post Just How Niche is Headless WordPress? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spinning Up Multiple WordPress Sites Locally With DevKinsta]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing themes and plugins for WordPress, we need to test them in different environments. How can we create multiple testing sites on our computer, quickly and easily, without having to become a sysadmin?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 39 With Addy Osmani: Image Optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about image optimization. What steps should we follow for performant images in 2021? We talk to expert Addy Osmani to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System Design Interview Tutorial – The Beginner&#x27;s Guide to System Design]]></title>
        <id>60873d1fdd38b9088c2c0842</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/system-design-interview-practice-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T22:46:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[System Design is an important topic to understand if you want to advance further in your career as a software engineer. Even if you are just beginning your coding journey, it's a good idea to get a head start on learning about system design.  Early in your career you will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Custom Pagination Component in React]]></title>
        <id>60bce373acb62507dd1d9f19</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-custom-pagination-component-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T22:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often work with web applications that need to fetch large amounts of data from a server through APIs and render it on the screen. For example, in a Social media application we fetch and render users' posts and comments. In an HR dashboard we display information about candidates who]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Tables With Sticky Header and Footers Got a Bit Easier]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342294</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/making-tables-with-sticky-header-and-footers-got-a-bit-easier/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T22:04:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It wasn’t long ago when I looked at sticky headers and footers in HTML <table>s in the blog post A table with both a sticky header and a sticky first column. In it, I never used position: sticky on …
The post Making Tables With Sticky Header and Footers Got a Bit Easier appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Roving tabindex Attribute Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>60c3b862d3126007592d689b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-roving-tabindex-attribute-explained-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever used the CSS order or direction properties? You've probably used them dozens of times, but did you realize that these properties will cause a disconnect between what's being displayed and what's actually in the DOM? Using the order property will create a disconnect between the visual presentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Backup Squarespace-Managed Styles using AWS Cloud]]></title>
        <id>60c794e64dc1a607ed7b25ba</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-backup-squarespace-managed-styles-using-aws-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T19:19:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A while ago, I was doing side gig for a client who had a website hosted on Squarespace. They asked me to implement an advanced design for a page that wasn't possible with the site's current DIY tools. For an experienced and battle-tested web developer like me, this was a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Best African Language Datasets for Data Science Projects]]></title>
        <id>60c4b35ed3126007592d71bc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/african-language-datasets-for-data-science-projects/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T18:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Africa has over 2000 languages, but these languages are not well-represented in the existing Natural Language Processing ecosystem.  One challenge is the lack of useful African language datasets that we can use to solve different social and economic problems. In this article, I have compiled a list of African language]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS-Tricks Chronicle XXXX]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342229</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-tricks-chronicle-xxxx/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T18:20:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just a little link roundup of some off-site stuff I’ve done recently. As I’m wont to do from time to time. 
DevJourney Podcast
#151 Chris Coyier from ceramics to CSS-Tricks and CodePen‘
Chris took us from playing on 
…
The post CSS-Tricks Chronicle XXXX appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing Your Website With Subresource Integrity]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342070</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/securing-your-website-with-subresource-integrity/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T13:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you load a file from an external server, you’re trusting that the content you request is what you expect it to be. Since you don’t manage the server yourself, you’re relying on the security of yet another third party …
The post Securing Your Website With Subresource Integrity appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khari McMillian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When CSS Isn’t Enough: JavaScript Requirements For Accessible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spoiler alert: tooltips, modals, tabs, carousels, and dropdown menus are some of the user interface components that require more than CSS. To ensure accessibility of your interface, JavaScript is a necessary addition to accomplish focus management, respond to keyboard events, and toggle ARIA attributes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Disaster Recovery Plan? How to Use RTO and RPO to Protect your Business]]></title>
        <id>60b72d5facb62507dd1d777b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/disaster-recovery-plan-what-are-rto-and-rpo/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T22:56:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're in the world of tech, you will inevitably run into a work-related disaster now and then. These setbacks come in many forms such as cyber-attacks, theft, leaks, and corruption. And every business must be ready to face these things and plan for them. Sir Benjamin Franklin famously said,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safari 15: New UI, Theme Colors, and… a CSS-Tricks Cameo!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342429</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/safari-15-new-ui-theme-colors-and-a-css-tricks-cameo/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T21:38:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a 33-minute video (and resources) over on apple.com covering the upcoming Safari changes we saw in the WWDC keynote this year in much more detail. Look who’s got a little cameo in there:
Perhaps the most noticeable thing there …
The post Safari 15: New UI, Theme Colors, and… a CSS-Tricks Cameo! appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Possibilities of Syndication]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342237</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-possibilities-of-syndication/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T21:25:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s the one word that isn’t an adjective in the acronym RSS. 
Really Simple Syndication.
RSS isn’t just about RSS readers. Even though, gosh if I don’t love RSS readers. It’s about putting content in a format that is …
The post The Possibilities of Syndication appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Center Anything in CSS Using Flexbox and Grid ✨]]></title>
        <id>6063b9189618b008528a9d81</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-center-objects-using-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T20:40:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I'm gonna show you how you can center and align your content with CSS. Along the way, we'll look at various alignment techniques. So, let's get started! 🥇 Table of Contents -> How to Use Flexbox to center anything horizontally center anything vertically center both horizontally & Vertically How]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Design Keyboard Accessibility for Complex React Experiences]]></title>
        <id>5f9c97e9740569d1a4ca1768</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/designing-keyboard-accessibility-for-complex-react-experiences/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How you can design an inclusive and accessible org chart experience and solutions to common development challenges you will face.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Ask Good Technical Questions – the Ultimate Guide]]></title>
        <id>60bc0444acb62507dd1d9a31</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-ask-good-technical-questions/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T17:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Knowing how to ask effective technical questions is an essential skill every software engineer should have.  You may be stuck with a bug, unable to figure out why your program isn't working correctly, or you might be having trouble learning how to implement a certain algorithm. In all of these]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Level Up Your React Conditionals]]></title>
        <id>60c24cf8d3126007592d61d5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-react-conditionals/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T16:04:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you write conditionals correctly within your React applications?  Good conditionals are an essential part of any React application. We use conditionals to show or hide elements or components in our applications.  In short – to be an effective React developer, you must know how to write good conditionals. Let's go]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: Making Use Of Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design often revolves around visuals, but the other senses deserve love too. In this article, we tune in to audio features that are making sites sing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Shadows to SVG Icons With CSS and SVG Filters]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342164</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/adding-shadows-to-svg-icons-with-css-and-svg-filters/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T14:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why would we need to apply shadows to SVG?
Shadows are a common design feature that can help elements, like icons, stand out. They could be persistent, or applied in different states (e.g. :hover, :focus, or :active) 
…
The post Adding Shadows to SVG Icons With CSS and SVG Filters appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Put a Background on Open Details Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342050</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/put-a-background-on-open-details-elements/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T00:16:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One thing that can be just a smidge funky about the <details> element is that, when open, it’s not always 100% clear what is inside that element and what isn’t. I’m not saying that always matters or that it’s a …
The post Put a Background on Open Details Elements appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Front-End Boilerplates And Starter Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We don’t need to write everything from scratch every single time. With boilerplates and starter kits, we can set up our projects faster, and get to work immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Equal Columns With Flexbox: It’s More Complicated Than You Might Think]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341894</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/equal-columns-with-flexbox-its-more-complicated-than-you-might-think/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T14:34:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As awesome as flexbox is, what it’s doing under the hood is actually a little strange because, by default, it is doing two things at once. It first looks at the content size which is what we would get if by declaring width: max-content on an element. But on top of that, flex-shrink is also doing some work allowing the items to be smaller, but only if needed.
Let’s break those two down and see how they work together.
The post Equal Columns With Flexbox: It’s More Complicated Than You Might Think appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Powell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Headless CMS with Fauna and Vercel Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342182</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/building-a-headless-cms-with-fauna-and-vercel-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T14:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we will learn and use headless CMS, Fauna, and Vercel functions to build a blogging platform, Blogify After that, you can easily build any web application using a headless CMS, Fauna and Vercel functions.
The post Building a Headless CMS with Fauna and Vercel Functions appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikeh Akinyemi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Data Fundamentals Certification (DP-900) – Pass the Exam With This Free 4.5-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>60b93afaacb62507dd1d8915</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/azure-data-fundamentals-certification-dp-900-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-4-5-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T11:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can learn everything you need to know to earn the Azure Data Fundamentals certification by completing this free 4.5 hour course. What is the Azure Data Fundamentals Certification?The Azure Data Fundamentals Certification is for those seeking a data-related role such as Data Analyst, Data Engineer, or Data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Front-End Auditing Tools I Discovered Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a faster website can be a rocket task these days. There are so many things to consider, so it’s challenging to get everything right. Here are some less-known tools that might help you get there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stefan Judis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From the Slums of Mumbai to a Rented Apartment – My 30-Year Developer Journey]]></title>
        <id>60b357ad11ffb70827ef9a90</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/my-journey-into-tech-from-slums-of-mumbai-to-my-own-apartment/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T21:55:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year I tweeted about how I was moving from a Slum where I lived for 29 years to a multi-story rented apartment.  The tech community on Twitter responded with nothing but love. Dan Wahlin posted that he would love to hear more about my story. It's not going to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Cornucopia of Container Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340967</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-cornucopia-of-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T20:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don’t know about y’all, but my feeds have been flooded with articles about CSS Container Queries these past few weeks. The buzz about container queries actually started back in December after Miriam Suzanne posted a proposal (picking up on …
The post A Cornucopia of Container Queries appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Skills You Need to Start Freelancing as a Developer]]></title>
        <id>60c0ccbed3126007592d5781</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-skills-you-need-to-start-freelancing/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T19:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's the bottom line: you don't need much to get started as a freelance developer.  The biggest obstacle developers face when they're thinking about getting started is that they tend to overcomplicate things.  Most are intimidated by the sheer number of different paths or skills deemed necessary by various blog]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Bootstrap 5 and SASS by Building a Portfolio Website]]></title>
        <id>60c10a1dd3126007592d5988</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-bootstrap-5-and-sass-by-building-a-portfolio-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T18:43:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bootstrap is one of the most popular CSS frameworks and Sass is one of the most popular preprocessors for CSS. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you about Bootstrap 5 and Sass by building a portfolio website. Patrick Muriungi developed this course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[target=blank]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341916</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/targetblank/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T14:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Does that make your eye twitch a little bit? Like… it’s a typo. It should be target="_blank" with an underscore to start the value. As in…
<a target="_blank" href="https://codepen.io"Open CodePen in a New Tab
</a
Welp, that’s correct syntax!…
The post target=blank appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet <code>:has</code>, A Native CSS Parent Selector (And More)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What makes relational selector one of the most requested features and how are we, as developers, working around not having it? In this article, we’re going to check the early spec of the :has selector, and see how it should improve the CSS workflow once it’s released.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Your freeCodeCamp Project on AWS – A Beginner&#x27;s Guide to the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>60bfa4d4d3126007592d5160</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-your-freecodecamp-project-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T23:47:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout this post we’ll deploy your freeCodeCamp front end project using various services on AWS like S3, ElasticBeanstalk, and Lambda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Your Own Electronics With Arduino - Full Course]]></title>
        <id>60bfd986d3126007592d53a1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-your-own-electronics-with-arduino-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T21:05:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arduino is an open-source electronics platform based on easy-to-use hardware and software. Arduino boards are able to read inputs - light on a sensor, a finger on a button, or a Twitter message - and turn it into an output - activating a motor, turning on an LED, publishing something]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking at WCAG 2.5.5 for Better Target Sizes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341982</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/looking-at-wcag-2-5-5-for-better-target-sizes/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T18:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever experienced the frustration of trying to tap a button on a mobile device only to have it do nothing because the target size is just not large enough **and it’s not picking up on your press? Maybe …
The post Looking at WCAG 2.5.5 for Better Target Sizes appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Todd Libby</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Pass Data and Events Between Components in React]]></title>
        <id>60b23b8911ffb70827ef954e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pass-data-between-components-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T16:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're trying to implement CRUD operations using API endpoints, you might find that it's hard to manage data across multiple components. Or maybe you have a modal, but you want to trigger it from a different component.  Wrapping your head around how to tackle these scenarios can be difficult.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Complete CSS Grid Tutorial with Cheat Sheet 🎖️]]></title>
        <id>60be6a3cd3126007592d4a03</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-grid-tutorial-with-cheatsheet/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T16:02:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we're going to learn CSS Grid properties so that you can make your own responsive websites. I'll explain how each of Grid's properties work along with a CheatSheet that covers everything you can do with Grid. Let's go. 🎖️ Table of Contents: CSS Grid Architecture CSS Grid Chart Grid Parent]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS-Trickz: An Experiment with Netlify’s On-Demand Builders]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341884</id>
        <link href="https://alex.party/posts/2021-05-31-css-trickz-an-experiment-with-netlify-s-on-demand-builders/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T14:16:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress sites have an API by default. Wanna see this site’s most recent posts, with just a specific set of data… in JSON format? Here ya go. Alex Riviere made a joke site using that.
At first, the site …
The post CSS-Trickz: An Experiment with Netlify’s On-Demand Builders appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From AVIF to WebP: A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s here! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our deep-dive guide to understand how to deliver high-quality images on the web fast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Full Stack App with Supabase and Next.js]]></title>
        <id>60bbd28eacb62507dd1d99fb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-complete-guide-to-full-stack-development-with-supabas/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T23:33:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to build full stack serverless apps with Supabase and Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use OpenCV and Python for Computer Vision and AI]]></title>
        <id>60be863cd3126007592d4c36</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-opencv-and-python-for-computer-vision-and-ai/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T20:54:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenCV is a popular Python library for real-time computer vision. We just released a new OpenCV course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This course comes directly from the creators of OpenCV and is the perfect course for beginners.  You will learn how to use OpenCV for Computer Vision and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links on Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341805</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/links-on-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T19:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Show/Hide password accessibility and password hints tutorial — Nicolas Steenhout goes deep on <input type="password"> accessibility. For one thing, being able to toggle it to type="text" should be possible, while announcing, politely, the change. But also, put the password hints 
…
The post Links on Accessibility appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Closures in JavaScript – A Beginner&#x27;s Guide]]></title>
        <id>5ff625967af2371468bb8645</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/closures-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T18:18:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Closures are a confusing JavaScript concept to learn, because it's hard to see how they're actually used.  Unlike other concepts such as functions, variables, and objects, you don't always use closures conscientiously and directly. You don't say: Oh! Here I will use a closure as a solution. But at the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular NgClass Example – How to Add Conditional CSS Classes]]></title>
        <id>60b136d911ffb70827ef912b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/angular-ngclass-example/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T15:01:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ngClass is a directive in Angular that adds and removes CSS classes on an HTML element. In this article, we are talking about ngClass in Angular only, not ng-class in angular.js. Prerequisites – What is Property Binding?Two things we have to understand first are property binding and interpolation in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code Extensions for HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340390</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/vs-code-extensions-for-html/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T14:13:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s look at some extensions for VS Code that make writing and editing HTML (and languages that are basically HTML with extra powers) better. You may not like all of them. Maybe some of them don’t appeal to you, solve …
The post VS Code Extensions for HTML appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Geocoding App In Vue.js Using Mapbox]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll be taking a general look at the concepts of forward geocoding and reverse geocoding, and will build a mini-app that applies these concepts to display specific locations, using Mapbox and Vue.js 2.6.11 to achieve this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Prince Chukwudire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Search and Filter Components in React]]></title>
        <id>60b3480c11ffb70827ef9a88</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/search-and-filter-component-in-reactjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T21:34:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're building a React app, you want your users to be able to search and get exact results. And if you are getting tons of items from an API, then you need to create a way for users to be able to find various items easily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning in Python – The Top New Scikit-Learn 0.24 Features You Should Know]]></title>
        <id>60ba33d7acb62507dd1d9050</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-python-new-scikit-learn-features-you-should-know/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T20:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scikit-learn is one of the most popular open-source and free machine learning libraries for Python.  The scikit-learn library contains a lot of efficient tools for machine learning and statistical modeling including classification, regression, clustering, and dimensionality reduction. Many data scientists, machine learning engineers, and researchers rely on this library for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Recover from Deployment Hell – What I Learned After My Discord Bot Crashed on a 1000+ User Server]]></title>
        <id>60b8f5c7acb62507dd1d8500</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/recovering-from-deployment-hell-what-i-learned-from-deploying-my-discord-bot-to-a-1000-user-server/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T20:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I deployed a Discord bot to a 1000+ user server. In the first hour, Deployment Hell struck and my bot crashed. In the next hour, I brought it back, surviving and even thriving in Deployment Hell. In this post, I'll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Principles for user-centered front-end development]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341793</id>
        <link href="https://colinoakley.medium.com/the-web-we-choose-to-build-e921510e3f1b"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T20:36:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colin Oakley:
• Accessible — Use semantic HTML, and make sure we meet the WCAG 2.1 AA standard as a minimum and it works with assisted technologies (this sits alongside the DWP Accessibility Manual)
• Agnostic — Build 
…
The post Principles for user-centered front-end development appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn TypeScript Basics in this Beginner&#x27;s Guide]]></title>
        <id>60b2a4c611ffb70827ef9842</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-typescript-basics/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T18:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript has taken the development world by storm. No wonder it has over 15 million weekly downloads on npm. But what is TypeScript, and what do you need to know about it?  In this article, I am going answer those questions. By the end you'll have a grasp of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can I :has()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341968</id>
        <link href="https://bkardell.com/blog/canihas.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T14:37:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just joked that we’re basically getting everything we want in CSS super fast (mostly referring to container queries, my gosh, can you imagine they are actually coming?). Now we might actually get parent selectors?! As in .parent:has(.child) { …
The post Can I :has() appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With Webpack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern browsers provide good support for JavaScript modules, but module bundlers such as webpack stay a critical part of the JavaScript toolchain. Let’s take a deep dive into what webpack is and how to use it in your development workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nwani Victory)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python for Bioinformatics: Use Machine Learning and Data Analysis for Drug Discovery]]></title>
        <id>60b98ebfacb62507dd1d8ec4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-for-bioinformatics-use-machine-learning-and-data-analysis-for-drug-discovery/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T02:32:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking for a way to apply Python and machine learning to a real-world application? You should consider Bioinformatics. Bioinformatics is an interdisciplinary field that develops methods and software tools for understanding biological data, in particular when the data sets are large and complex. We just released a course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Tutorial – How to Set Up a Front End Development Project]]></title>
        <id>60b11ff811ffb70827ef8f94</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-a-front-end-development-project/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T21:44:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s say you plan to build a website. Before you start, you want to set up a few tools to make your life easier. But which tools should you have? The JavaScript ecosystem is changing so fast that it can be overwhelming to pick the best tools to use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Schofield&#x27;s Laws of Computing – What they Are and Why You Should Know Them]]></title>
        <id>60afd68611ffb70827ef86d8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/schofields-laws-of-computing/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T18:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Schofield's Laws of Computing are principles that anyone who works with computers should know. They're focused on data portability, integrity, and security.  Jack Schofield was a British journalist who wrote for The Guardian. During that time, he wrote three particular articles called "Schofield's Laws of Computing". Jack didn't create these]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lists in Python – A Comprehensive Guide]]></title>
        <id>60b7c02cacb62507dd1d7b80</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/lists-in-python-comprehensive-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T18:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s suppose you’re planning to visit your neighborhood store to stock up on essentials. What is the first thing you’d do?  Have the answer already? Yes, you'd probably write down a shopping list! Python also has a built-in data structure called List that’s very similar to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Hackintosh - Install MacOS Big Sur on a PC Using OpenCore]]></title>
        <id>60affbe411ffb70827ef8951</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-hackintosh/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T18:07:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Hackintosh is a non-Mac computer system, made with PC parts, that runs the macOS operating system. In this tutorial, you will learn how to create a Hackintosh. You will learn how to install macOS Big Sur (or any other version of macOS) using OpenCore. The main benefit of a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless vs Fully Managed Services: What&#x27;s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>60aa708711ffb70827ef5f4b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serverless-fully-managed-service-difference/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T16:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're new to cloud technologies, you might be confused about the difference between serverless technologies and managed services.  So in this article you'll learn what these terms mean and what the main differences are.    What Are Managed Services? A managed service let the end-user focus on using a service]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cipher Definition – What is a Block Cipher and How Does it Work to Protect Your Data?]]></title>
        <id>5fff3d3098be260817e495bd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-block-cipher/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T16:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptography is the science of using codes and ciphers to protect messages. And encryption involves encoding messages so that only the intended recipient can understand the meaning of the message. It's often used to protect data in transit. Encryption is a two way function – that is, you need to be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hexagons and Beyond: Flexible, Responsive Grid Patterns, Sans Media Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341584</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/hexagons-and-beyond-flexible-responsive-grid-patterns-sans-media-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T14:25:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little while back, Chris shared this nice hexagonal grid. And true to its name, it’s using —wait for it — CSS Grid to form that layout. It’s a neat trick! Combining grid columns, grid gaps, and creative clipping …
The post Hexagons and Beyond: Flexible, Responsive Grid Patterns, Sans Media Queries appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring Lighthouse Scores and Core Web Vitals with DebugBear]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341494</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/monitoring-lighthouse-scores-and-core-web-vitals-with-debugbear/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T14:25:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DebugBear takes just a few seconds to start using. You literally point it at a URL you want to watch, and it’ll start watching it. You install nothing.
It’ll start running tests, and you’ve immediately got performance charts you can …
The post Monitoring Lighthouse Scores and Core Web Vitals with DebugBear appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Shared State In Vue 3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing large-scale Vue applications can be a challenge. In this article, Shawn Wildermuth dives into the pros and cons of approaches like factories, shared objects, and using Vuex. He also explains what is coming in Vuex 5.0 that might change how we all use shared state in Vue 3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shawn Wildermuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Commit Signing in Git?]]></title>
        <id>60afce3011ffb70827ef869c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-commit-signing-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T23:14:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git has a feature to "sign" commits, but what is signing, and what are the benefits? TL;DR: If you don't care for the details, and just need to get commit signing setup quickly, skip to How to Sign Commits. Signing, or code signing specifically, is the process of using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Environment Variables in VanillaJS]]></title>
        <id>60b3a25211ffb70827ef9b39</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-environment-variables-in-vanillajs/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T22:54:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn about environment variables in Vanilla JavaScript. You'll also learn how to serve API keys to your application through the Netlify build command. What are JavaScript environment variables?Environment variables are very common when you're using JavaScript frameworks like React or Vue for creating frontend]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Design Your Own Learning Plan for Any Tech Stack]]></title>
        <id>60b3ccee11ffb70827ef9bc0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-design-your-own-learning-plan-for-any-tech-stack/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T21:18:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most difficult things about getting started in a new career as a developer is figuring out exactly what you should be learning – and then translating that into an effective plan. There are so many resources out there for learning, so lack of information is not the problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging iOS Safari]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341724</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/debugging-ios-safari/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T21:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do I debug Safari on iOS?
These are my general steps, starting with not even using iOS Safari.
1. Is this just a small-screen problem?
Lemme just use the device mode in Chrome quick.
Note that this does a …
The post Debugging iOS Safari appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vimrc Configuration Guide - How to Customize Your Vim Code Editor with Mappings, Vimscript, Status Line, and More]]></title>
        <id>60a699b0906c5207e3a7f5ab</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vimrc-configuration-guide-customize-your-vim-editor/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T20:44:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Configuring your .vimrc file lets you use the full power of Vim. With a customized .vimrc file you can increase your Vim powers tenfold. In this article I will show you a few ways you can customize your .vimrc file. I will go over: Basic SettingsPluginsFoldingVimscriptStatus lineFirst create the following]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fetch API – How to Make a GET Request and POST Request in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>60b0f11411ffb70827ef8dbc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-api-calls-with-fetch/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T19:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Often times you might want your system to communicate with other web servers to get information. For example, let's say a new user wants to sign up for an account on your website. And instead of having to manually fill out a form to send their information to your system,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Migrate from Vue v.2 to Vue v.3 with a Simple Example Project]]></title>
        <id>60b4ff4711ffb70827ef9eb2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/migrate-from-vue2-to-vue3-with-example-project/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T19:14:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Vue.js? Vue.js is a progressive JavaScript frontend framework written by Evan You. It's one of the most powerful and easy to learn frameworks, and it has over 9.5 million downloads per month.  In September 2020, Vue 3 core was released. The new Vue.js release]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Async/Await Tutorial – Learn Callbacks, Promises, and Async/Await in JS by Making Ice Cream 🍧🍨🍦]]></title>
        <id>60b51f6e11ffb70827ef9f7c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-async-await-tutorial-learn-callbacks-promises-async-await-by-making-icecream/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T14:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we're going to build and run an ice cream shop and learn asynchronous JavaScript at the same time. Along the way, you'll learn how to use: CallbacksPromisesAsync / AwaitHere's what we'll cover in this article:What is Asynchronous JavaScript?Synchronous vs Asynchronous JavaScriptHow Callbacks Work in JavaScriptHow Promises Work in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Crash Course in WordPress Block Filters]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341442</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-crash-course-in-wordpress-block-filters/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T13:35:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blocks in WordPress are great. Drop some into the page, arrange them how you like, and you’ve got a pretty sweet landing page with little effort. But what if the default blocks in WordPress need a little tweaking? Like, what …
The post A Crash Course in WordPress Block Filters appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dmitry Mayorov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Custom Properties a “Menu of What Will Change”?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341572</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/are-custom-properties-a-menu-of-what-will-change/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T13:35:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PPK laid out an interesting situation in “Two options for using custom properties” where he and Stefan Judis had two different approaches for doing the same thing with custom properties. In one approach, hover and focus styles for a …
The post Are Custom Properties a “Menu of What Will Change”? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fix Cumulative Layout Shift (CLS) Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Core Web Vitals initiative has taken the SEO and Web Performance worlds by storm and many sites are busy optimizing their Page Experience to maximize the ranking factor. The Cumulative Layout Shift metric is causing trouble to a lot of sites, so let’s have a look at ways of addressing any issues for that metric.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of An Online Store (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting a good performance score from Google is hard for any website — but doing so for an online store is even harder. We achieved green scores — even several for mobile. Here is how we did it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jennifer Brehm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Discord AI Chatbot that Talks Like Your Favorite Character]]></title>
        <id>60b5025111ffb70827ef9ebe</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/discord-ai-chatbot/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T23:47:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's build an AI model that speaks just like your favorite character and deploy that model as a Discord chatbot. All the coding and deployment happen in the cloud (for free!), so you don't even need a local IDE to follow along.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code blocks, but better]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341720</id>
        <link href="https://ped.ro/blog/code-blocks-but-better"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T22:08:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pedro Duarte made a wishlist for styled code blocks in blog posts and documentation, then hand-rolls a perfect solution for that wishlist. For example, a feature to be able to highlight certain lines or words within the code block. The …
The post Code blocks, but better appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Analytics with Pandas – How to Drop a List of Rows from a Pandas Dataframe]]></title>
        <id>60b1eed311ffb70827ef9504</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/drop-list-of-rows-from-pandas-dataframe/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T20:47:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Pandas dataframe is a two dimensional data structure which allows you to store data in rows and columns. It's very useful when you're analyzing data.  When you have a list of data records in a dataframe, you may need to drop a specific list of rows depending on the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Next.js and Make React Development Simpler]]></title>
        <id>60b668c0acb62507dd1d710b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T17:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js makes developing React applications simpler. It provides a common structure that allows you to build frontend React applications, and transparently handles server-side rendering for you. We just released a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you the basics of Next.js.  Kapehe developed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Developer Journey – How I Got a Remote Job and Increased My Salary While Contributing to Open Source]]></title>
        <id>60acf28e11ffb70827ef6dd9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/my-developer-journey-how-i-increased-my-salary-and-got-a-remote-job/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T16:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone, my name is Santosh. In this article, I will tell you how I ramped up my career and ended up increasing my salary as a developer.  I'll share what I learned from each job along the way, how you can stand out, tips for negotiating salary, and how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get a Cybersecurity Job in 2021]]></title>
        <id>60aff2d711ffb70827ef8829</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-a-cybersecurity-job/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T16:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This informative tutorial goes deep into how to get a cybersecurity job, with insights from senior leaders and hiring managers in the field.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Front-End Testing is For Everyone]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341342</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/front-end-testing-is-for-everyone/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Testing is one of those things that you either get super excited about or kinda close your eyes and walk away. Whichever camp you fall into, I’m here to tell you that front-end testing is for everyone. In fact, …
The post Front-End Testing is For Everyone appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evgeny Klimenchenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jetpack Boost Handles Critical CSS For You]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341296</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/jetpack-boost-handles-critical-css-for-you/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Critical CSS is one of those things I see in my performance reports but always seem to ignore. I know what it means. It means to put only the CSS required to render things immediately visible in a <style>…
The post Jetpack Boost Handles Critical CSS For You appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 38 With Ivan Akulov: Why Is My React App Slow?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about React performance. What factors slow our React apps down, and how can we fix it? Drew McLellan talks to expert Ivan Akulov to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting Up A Currency Convertor With ExchangeRatesApi.io]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon allows visitors to display prices in their own currency. Thanks to *ExchangeRatesApi.io*, we can do the same for our online shops, providing a better experience to our customers. Let’s find out how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logical Fallacies – Definition and Fallacy Examples]]></title>
        <id>607f5fafdd38b9088c2bd0c9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/logical-fallacies-definition-fallacy-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T04:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're debating someone, you want to use all the resources at your disposal to convince them you're right. But you should be careful that you don't end up using a logical fallacy to help you make your point. What is a Logical Fallacy?A logical fallacy is an error]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless Functions: The Secret to Ultra-Productive Front-End Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340465</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/serverless-functions-the-secret-to-ultra-productive-front-end-teams/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T17:16:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern apps place high demands on front-end developers. Web apps require complex functionality, and the lion’s share of that work is falling to front-end devs:
building modern, accessible user interfaces
creating interactive elements and complex animations
managing complex application state
…
The post Serverless Functions: The Secret to Ultra-Productive Front-End Teams appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Lengstorf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local: Always Getting Better]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341482</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/local-always-getting-better/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T17:13:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been using Local for ages. Four years ago, I wrote about how I got all my WordPress sites running locally on it. I just wanted to give it another high five because it’s still here and still great. In …
The post Local: Always Getting Better appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy June Vibes For Your Screen (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What could be a better way to welcome June than with some colorful inspiration? Well, we might have something for you: wallpapers created with love by artists and designers from across the globe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Developer Journey – How I Went from Making $1,000 to $100,000 a Year]]></title>
        <id>60acf28e11ffb70827ef6dd9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/my-developer-journey-how-i-went-from-1000-a-year-to-100000-as-a-dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T22:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone, my name is Santosh. In this article, I will tell you how I ramped up my career and ended up making $100,000 a year as a developer.  I'll share what I learned from each job along the way, how you can stand out, tips for negotiating salary,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Your Android App – Four Security Best Practices Every Android Dev Should Know]]></title>
        <id>60b08d8811ffb70827ef8c7b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-secure-your-android-app/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T16:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've been following the news lately, you may have noticed a worrisome tech trend. The frequency and severity of cybersecurity attacks are exploding.  We've seen news of a sprawling hack involving the SolarWinds management platform. That attack may have compromised the systems of over 18,000 SolarWinds customers.  Then,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic Favicons for WordPress]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341163</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/dynamic-favicons-for-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T14:36:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typically, a single favicon is used across a whole domain. But there are times you wanna step it up with different favicons depending on context. A website might change the favicon to match the content being viewed. Or a site …
The post Dynamic Favicons for WordPress appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Park</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Computer Vision with Python]]></title>
        <id>60b0de2211ffb70827ef8d7c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-computer-vision-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T12:26:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More and more applications are using computer vision these days. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you learn advanced computer vision using Python. You will learn state of the art computer vision techniques by building five projects with libraries such as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding A Commenting System To A WYSIWYG Editor]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/commenting-system-wysiwyg-editor/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/commenting-system-wysiwyg-editor/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be re-using the foundational WYSIWYG Editor built in the first article to build a commenting system for a WYSIWYG Editor that enables users to select text inside a document and share their comments on it. Let’s dig in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To $ or Not to $: Displaying Terminal Code Snippets]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341298</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/to-or-not-to-displaying-terminal-code-snippets/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T18:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s very popular to put a $ on lines that are intended to be a command in code documentation that involves the terminal (i.e. the command line).
Like this:
$ brew install somepackage
The point of that is that it …
The post To $ or Not to $: Displaying Terminal Code Snippets appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve Machine Learning Model Performance by Combining Categorical Features]]></title>
        <id>60af931811ffb70827ef85d3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-machine-learning-model-performance-by-combining-categorical-features/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T17:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're training a machine learning model, you can have some features in your dataset that represent categorical values. Categorical features are types of data that you can divide into groups. There are three common categorical data types: Ordinal – a set of values in ascending or descending order. Example: rating]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a Bouncing Basketball in Unity with Materials and Textures 🏀]]></title>
        <id>60a325c6906c5207e3a7da25</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-a-basketball-in-unity-with-materials-and-textures/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T15:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll teach you how to make a basketball using materials and textures in Unity. You can extend this micro-concept to create any kind of ball like a football, tennis ball, or snooker balls.  That said, these techniques aren't just limited to creating round 3D objects like balls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Show Images on Click]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341020</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-show-images-on-click/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T14:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most images on the web are superfluous. If I might be a jerk for a bit, 99% of them aren’t even that helpful at all (although there are rare exceptions). That’s because images don’t often complement the text they’re …
The post How to Show Images on Click appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Rendle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rethinking Postgres in a Post-Server World]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340910</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/rethinking-postgres-in-a-post-server-world/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T14:23:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless architectures have brought engineering teams a great number of benefits. We get simpler deployments, automatic and infinite scale, better concurrency, and a stateless API surface. It’s hard to imagine going back to the world of managed services, broken local …
The post Rethinking Postgres in a Post-Server World appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Rispoli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful VS Code Extensions For Front-End Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet useful Visual Studio Code extensions for web developers: little helpers to minimize slow-downs and frustrations, and boost developer’s workflow along the way. With auto log messages, auto code formatting, file utils, file labels, code snippets, highlight brackets, tags, indents and workspaces, onboarding and remote SSH.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build And Launch Responsive Websites Faster With Editor X]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While web builders have been around for a long time, it wasn’t until recently that they became practical for professional use. Closing the gap between design and code has become the north star for many companies and we are seeing a wave of tools that deliver on this promise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Miroslav Bekyarov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giphy API Tutorial – How to Generate Animated Text GIFs with ReactJS]]></title>
        <id>60a44b9f906c5207e3a7e098</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/giphy-api-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T21:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial you will create an app that generates dynamic animated text using Giphy's API with ReactJS. After that I'll go over some of the other API features Giphy provides that you can use to make other interesting projects. You can find the code for the tutorial here. Video]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Contribute to Open Source  Projects – A Beginner&#x27;s Guide]]></title>
        <id>60abe7fb11ffb70827ef63a6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-contribute-to-open-source-projects-beginners-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T18:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a developer, you've probably come across the term "open source." If you've ever wondered what it's all about and how to contribute, you are in exactly the right place.  I put aside all my fears about how and what to contribute during Hacktoberfest 2020, and made]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Basic Terraform Syntax in 20 minutes]]></title>
        <id>606f4f5fd5756f080ba96b65</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/terraform-syntax-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T18:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll give you a brief overview of the configuration syntax of Terraform.  Terraform's docs provide the most comprehensive look at its syntax. But this article should serve as a condensed quick start introduction that'll give new users a simplified overview. We'll focus on the basic structures without]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awesome Standalone (Web Components)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339759</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/awesome-standalone-web-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T17:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In his last An Event Apart talk, Dave made a point that it’s really only just about right now that Web Components are becoming a practical choice for production web development. For example, it has only been about a year …
The post Awesome Standalone (Web Components) appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links on Web Components]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340901</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/links-on-web-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T17:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How we use Web Components at GitHub — Kristján Oddsson talks about how GitHub is using web components. I remember they were very early adopters, and it says here they released a <relative-time> component in 2014! Now they’ve got a 
…
The post Links on Web Components appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a GraphQL API Using Laravel]]></title>
        <id>60abc59d11ffb70827ef6304</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-graphql-api-using-laravel/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T16:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll walk you through how to set up your own GraphQL API using PHP and Laravel. Two years ago, I started working professionally as a backend developer. And I was very intimidated by all the technology I didn't yet know. Words like Docker, Kubernetes, and GraphQL seemed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Super Mario Bros, Zelda, and Space Invaders with Kaboom.js]]></title>
        <id>60aced0011ffb70827ef6d96</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-mario-zelda-and-space-invaders-with-kaboom-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T14:12:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this video course I show you how to build three popular games using the latest game development library for JavaScript called Kaboom.js. This course is exciting for two reasons: First of all, I am going to be introducing a new technology designed especially for game development in JavaScript.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Thorough Analysis of CSS-in-JS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340705</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-thorough-analysis-of-css-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T14:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wondering what’s even more challenging than choosing a JavaScript framework? You guessed it: choosing a CSS-in-JS solution. Why? Because there are more than 50 libraries out there, each of them offering a unique set of features.
We tested 10 different …
The post A Thorough Analysis of CSS-in-JS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrei Pfeiffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible SVGs: Perfect Patterns For Screen Reader Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover which SVG patterns we should avoid and which patterns are the most inclusive when comparing different combinations of OSs, browsers, and screen readers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carie Fisher)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keep Calm and Hack The Box – Valentine]]></title>
        <id>60ac3a2711ffb70827ef6aec</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/keep-calm-and-hack-the-box-valentine/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T22:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Walkthrough for Hack The Box Valentine machine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React-Hook-Form to Build Beautiful Forms with Chakra UI]]></title>
        <id>60a93b0011ffb70827ef5b0d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-hook-form-with-chakra-ui/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T20:26:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In HTML, it’s the default behavior for forms to redirect to a new page whenever they're submitted. So in order to provide dynamic functionality, React uses a strategy called controlled components. If you have recently gone through a React course, you probably didn't like this part, because there are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Best Practices for New Developers – How to Create Portfolio-Worthy Work]]></title>
        <id>608706aedd38b9088c2c012c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-design-best-practices-for-new-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T16:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a beginner developer, it can be difficult to find ways to use your limited knowledge to support yourself. And at the same time, you won't be able to hone your skills if you aren't using them full time.  It's a precarious spot that I remember being in when]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I Learned Building a Word Game App With Nuxt on Google Play]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340759</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-i-learned-building-a-word-game-app-with-nuxt-on-google-play/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I fell in love with coding the moment I created my first CSS :hover effect. Years later, that initial bite into interactivity on the web led me to a new goal: making a game.
Table of contents
What’s the game 
…
The post What I Learned Building a Word Game App With Nuxt on Google Play appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Collinsworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistakes. These cruel villains do not even stop at the beautiful world of software development. But although we cannot avoid making mistakes, we can learn to undo them! This post will show the right tools for your daily work with Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>