<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-09-25T00:55:06.726Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python List Methods Explained in Plain English]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-methods-explained-in-plain-english/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-methods-explained-in-plain-english/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-24T14:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often make plans about the things we want, what we need to do, and places we want to visit. These lists could go on forever! However, there are times when we need to build a program that requires us to organize and manipulate information using lists.  In this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GOLD AGBONIFO_ISAAC</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Java Internals: Speed and Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-java-internals-speed-and-performance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-java-internals-speed-and-performance/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-24T13:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In most conversations about programming, speed, and efficiency in Java are reoccurring terms as it's a language native to these features. You might ask, what is Java? You may also wonder what it means for a programming language to be interpreted or compiled. Let's explore these concepts in the following]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoye Victor Chukwuebuka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Word Embeddings: The Building Blocks of NLP and GPTs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-word-embeddings-the-building-blocks-of-nlp-and-gpts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-word-embeddings-the-building-blocks-of-nlp-and-gpts/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-24T12:17:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Word embeddings serve as the foundation for many applications, from simple text classification to complex machine translation systems. But what exactly are word embeddings, and how do they work? Let's find out. What Are Word Embeddings? Word embeddings serve as the digital DNA for words in the world of natural]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction to HTML for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-html/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-html/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-24T11:57:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML, which stands for HyperText Markup Language, serves as the foundation of web development. It enables you to create interactive web pages, structure content, and effectively communicate your message.  In this guide, we'll explore HTML comprehensively, addressing essential questions to provide a strong foundation for budding web developers. The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: How to Run a Tech Conference with Ben Dunphy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-how-to-run-a-tech-event/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-how-to-run-a-tech-event/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T17:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today on the freeCodeCamp Podcast, I interview Benjamin Dunphy, founder of many San Francisco Tech Conferences including Reactathon. Ben studied international relations and had a short career in finance. Among other things, he co-authored a bill that eventually got passed in his state of New Hampshire. But Ben saw the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust Project – Create an Authentication Server]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rust-tutorial-authentication-server/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rust-tutorial-authentication-server/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T16:02:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rust programming language is often used for system-level programming, emphasizing safety, concurrency, and performance, making it a popular choice for building systems software, game engines, and web browsers. An authentication server is another good use case for Rust. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Contribute to Open-Source Projects – Git & GitHub Workflow for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-and-github-workflow-for-open-source/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-and-github-workflow-for-open-source/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T12:35:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first time I learned about open source was through a tweet that promoted Hacktoberfest in 2019. And my first-ever accepted pull request was to add a book title in emojis to a list. You might think, "You can't count that as an open source contribution. That's a joke!" I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayu Adiati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Path To Awesome CSS Easing With The linear() Function]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/path-css-easing-linear-function/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/path-css-easing-linear-function/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the new CSS `linear()` easing function on the horizon, the possibilities of what we can do to create natural-feeling animations and transitions in the future are greatly expanded. Jhey Tompkins looks at the current state of CSS easing in this article and demonstrates what we can expect from `linear()`, including handy tools to get your hands on it today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Hypothesis Testing? Types and Python Code Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-hypothesis-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-hypothesis-testing/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T00:41:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Curiosity has always been a part of human nature. Since the beginning of time, this has been one of the most important tools for birthing civilizations. Still, our curiosity grows — it tests and expands our limits. Humanity has explored the plains of land, water, and air. We've built underwater]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MENE-EJEGI OGBEMI</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binary Classification with TensorFlow Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/binary-classification-made-simple-with-tensorflow/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/binary-classification-made-simple-with-tensorflow/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T14:21:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binary classification is a fundamental task in machine learning, where the goal is to categorize data into one of two classes or categories.  Binary classification is used in a wide range of applications, such as spam email detection, medical diagnosis, sentiment analysis, fraud detection, and many more. In this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Mojo Programming Language for AI Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/new-mojo-programming-language-for-ai-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/new-mojo-programming-language-for-ai-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T14:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mojo combines the usability of Python with the performance of C, leading to greater programmability of AI hardware and extensibility of AI models. It's basically an enhanced version of Python specifically designed for Artificial Intelligence developers. We just posted a full Mojo course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Elliot Arledge]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Self-Playing AI Chess Engine from Scratch with Imitation Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-self-playing-ai-chess-engine-from-scratch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-self-playing-ai-chess-engine-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T08:11:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an article on how I created an AI chess engine, starting completely from scratch to building my very own AI chess engine.  Because creating an AI chess engine from scratch is a relatively complex task, this will be a long article, but stay tuned, as the product]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eivind Kjosbakken</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Design System in Next.js with Tailwind CSS and Class Variance Authority]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-a-design-system-in-next-js-with-tailwind-css-and-class-variance-authority/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-a-design-system-in-next-js-with-tailwind-css-and-class-variance-authority/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T07:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a web application and producing a smooth user experience in the always changing world of web development requires more than just good looks – you also need to make sure that your application's design is efficient and consistent throughout. If you have a design system in place, you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olasunkanmi Balogun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code Dark Mode for Google Sheets with Apps Script and JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-dark-mode-for-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-dark-mode-for-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T22:23:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Sheets is a great tool for working and collaborating on spreadsheets, but it doesn't have native support for dark mode.  In this article, we'll create our own dark mode. One way to do that would be by selecting all the cells and manually changing their background color and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Effects of AI in Cybersecurity Handbook – The Malicious Use of AI in Cyberattacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/effects-of-ai-in-cybersecurity-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/effects-of-ai-in-cybersecurity-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T20:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The field of cybersecurity is engaged in a relentless battle between those who defend systems and data, and those who seek to attack them. In this high-stakes arena, artificial intelligence (AI) has emerged as a new, game-changing ally for the defenders. To understand AI's profound impact, it is important to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonya Moisset</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build an SEO-Optimized Blog with Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-seo-optimized-blog-with-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-seo-optimized-blog-with-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T13:09:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a feature-rich blog is a great way to improve your web development skills.  We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create a blog that is not just visually appealing but also SEO-optimized for higher Google rankings. Codebucks created the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facilitating Inclusive Online Workshops (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/facilitating-inclusive-online-workshops-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/facilitating-inclusive-online-workshops-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To help ensure the success of a workshop, Ben Shih introduces the concept of an inclusive workshop. In Part 2 of the series, you will continue to delve deeper into several key principles and guidelines that you can follow during and after the workshop to encourage an inclusive atmosphere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Shih)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ultimate Beginner's Python Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ultimate-beginners-python-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ultimate-beginners-python-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T12:26:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever considered venturing into the world of Python programming or if you're just looking for a comprehensive guide to help reinforce your existing knowledge, you're in for a treat. I'm excited to announce that Dave Gray, one of our most popular instructors, has returned to the freCodeCamp.org YouTube]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Concepts to Know Before Learning Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-concepts-to-know-before-learning-node-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-concepts-to-know-before-learning-node-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T15:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before Node.js came into existence,  JavaScript could only be run on the browser. It could only be used as a scripting language for frontend web development.  Then, Node.js came to free JavaScript from this confinement. It made JavaScript ubiquitous (meaning it could now be run everywhere). Node.js is a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Musab Habeeb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy an AWS Lambda Function with Serverless Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-aws-lambda-with-serverless/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-aws-lambda-with-serverless/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T23:52:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless computing has revolutionized the way developers build and deploy applications in the cloud. It takes away the complexities of server management, allowing developers to focus solely on writing code and delivering value to their users. In the realm of serverless computing, AWS Lambda stands out as a leading platform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Destiny Erhabor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Smashing Magazine Uses TinaCMS To Manage An Editorial Workflow]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/smashing-magazine-tinacms-manage-editorial-workflow/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/smashing-magazine-tinacms-manage-editorial-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is a peek behind the curtain of how content is managed here at Smashing Magazine. In it, you’ll get a tour of an article’s full lifecycle, from a basic outline to the sort of thing you’re reading right this second.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build and Deploy an AI SaaS with Paid Subscriptions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-deploy-an-ai-saas-with-paid-subscriptions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-deploy-an-ai-saas-with-paid-subscriptions/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T17:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is easier than ever to launch your own Software as a Service (SaaS) company! (The hard part is getting people interested in it). We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will guide you through every step of building and deploying a full-stack AI SaaS application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network File System – How to Confirm Your Application is Using NFS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-confirm-your-application-is-using-nfs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-confirm-your-application-is-using-nfs/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T06:54:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was tasked recently to find which of our processes was accessing a NFS share [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Network_File_System]. During this process, I found that some tools are better adapted than others for the task. In this article, I want to share with you my findings. The whole process was fun and gave]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Disney Data Scientist Eric Leung on Math, Medicine, and Learning to Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-data-scientist-at-disney-eric-leung-on-math-medicine-and-learning-to-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-data-scientist-at-disney-eric-leung-on-math-medicine-and-learning-to-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T20:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I'm joined by Eric Leung, Data Scientist at Disney and long-time open source contributor to freeCodeCamp. Eric Leung grew up in Oklahoma and learned a lot of math in high school. His friends wanted to go to medical school and he originally planned to join them. But instead]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Solana Curriculum: Smart Contracts, dApps, and Command Line Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/solana-curriculum/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/solana-curriculum/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Solana Curriculum is live. You can now learn Solana's blockchain protocol and the Solana tool ecosystem interactively by building a series of projects. This curriculum is made possible by The Solana Foundation, who gave our charity a grant to 100% fund development of this curriculum. What will this curriculum]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Mondloch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Quick Look at Bun 1.0 – The Node.js Alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-quick-look-at-bun-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-quick-look-at-bun-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T07:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A wise man once told me, "When you start eating Bun, Node.js will feel bland". But why is that relevant? JavaScript got way faster with a new JavaScript runtime called Bun, which is now production-ready with its version 1.0 release. But how and why is it faster than Node.js? A]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nishant Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revealing Images With CSS Mask Animations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/revealing-images-css-mask-animations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/revealing-images-css-mask-animations/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s play with images and experiment with CSS masks. The idea is fairly simple: take a single `` tag and harness the power of CSS to accomplish complex hover transitions. Through different demos, you will see how CSS masks combined with gradients allow us to create fancy effects — with efficient, reusable code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Contribute to Open Source Projects – Non-Technical Things You Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-contribute-to-open-source/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-contribute-to-open-source/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T17:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've contributed to open-source projects for a few years and learned a lot from the process. These experiences allowed me to look closer at the open source flow, from the technical, such as Git and GitHub, to the non-technical aspects. Although they are as important as the technical sides, the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayu Adiati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Return Results from a Python Function to Your Program When a Library is Blocking the Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/return-results-from-a-python-function-when-library-is-blocking-the-way/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/return-results-from-a-python-function-when-library-is-blocking-the-way/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T10:46:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Usually a Python function passes its results back using a return statement. The problem is that sometimes it can't, so you need to figure out a different way to return those results.  This happens, most often, when someone else's library's interface is in the way, and you can't change]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David A. Kra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Vector Embeddings to Create an AI Assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vector-embeddings-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vector-embeddings-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T02:18:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vector embeddings are a key concept in the realm of machine learning and artificial intelligence. They bridge the gap between human language and machine understanding. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach out about vector embeddings and how to create an AI assistant. Ania]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Dynamic Programming Techniques in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-dynamic-programming-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-dynamic-programming-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T02:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic programming is a powerful technique that has been a cornerstone in the world of algorithms and computer science. It's a method that breaks down problems into smaller, more manageable sub-problems, solving each one only once and storing their solutions in case they're needed again. This approach is particularly useful]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Things to Consider When Picking Fonts for your Next Project – An In-Depth Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/things-to-consider-when-picking-fonts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/things-to-consider-when-picking-fonts/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T11:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the modern web, we've normalized fetching fonts from client-side, or embedding fonts in resources that are served to users. While this may be tempting, it actually makes very little sense for most use-cases. This isn't suggesting to never use external fonts. Just a reminder that fonts aren't free, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Falco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facilitating Inclusive Online Workshops (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/facilitating-inclusive-online-workshops-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/facilitating-inclusive-online-workshops-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Running a workshop can be an effective alternative to traditional, long-standing meetings. To help ensure its success, Ben Shih introduces the concept of an inclusive workshop. In Part 1 of the series, you discover the fundamentals of inclusivity and get some solid guidance on how to plan an inclusive remote workshop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Shih)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fine-Tune the Donut Model – With Example Use Case]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fine-tune-the-donut-model/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fine-tune-the-donut-model/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T17:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Donut model in Python is a model you can use to extract text from a given image. This can be useful in various scenarios, like scanning receipts, for example.  You can easily download the Donut model from GitHub [https://github.com/clovaai/donut]. But as is common with AI models, you should]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eivind Kjosbakken</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[13 Types of Cyber Attacks You Should Know in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/types-of-cyber-attacks-to-know/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/types-of-cyber-attacks-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T17:28:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2023, the digital landscape is filled with unprecedented cybersecurity risks. From phishing scams to ransomware attacks. This article outlines different types of cyber attacks that individuals and businesses should be vigilant about. Cyber-attacks are a prevalent threat in the online world. They have the potential to cause substantial difficulties]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Communication Design Patterns for Backend Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/communication-design-patterns-for-backend-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/communication-design-patterns-for-backend-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T16:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you’re building the backend of an application, you’ve got to figure out how all the different components are going to talk to each other.  It’s like setting up a communication network for your app’s brain, and the way you do it can seriously impact how well your app]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chinwendu Enyinna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fundamentals of Finance & Economics for Businesses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fundamentals-of-finance-economics-for-businesses/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fundamentals-of-finance-economics-for-businesses/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T14:58:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving landscape of business, understanding the intricacies of finance and economics is essential for success. Topics such as the principles of money and deciphering the impact of macroeconomic changes serve as the bedrock of strategic decision-making. We just posted a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Read a CSV File from S3 Bucket in AWS Lambda - A Definitive Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/read-csv-file-from-s3-bucket-in-aws-lambda/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/read-csv-file-from-s3-bucket-in-aws-lambda/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T10:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Simple Storage Service (S3) is a highly scalable, durable, and available object storage service. It is designed to store any amount of data, anytime, from anywhere on the web.  S3 is a key component of the Amazon Web Services (AWS) cloud platform. AWS Lambda is a serverless computing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikram Aruchamy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Transition vs Animation Handbook – How to Animate Elements in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-transition-vs-css-animation-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-transition-vs-css-animation-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T00:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS transitions and animations provide smooth, gradual ways to change an element's style. But they work in different ways. Here are the main distinctions between them: CSS Transition CSS Animation  * Creates smooth transitions from one CSS value to    another.   * You need triggers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi Sofela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve Your ReactJS Code – Tips for Code Readability and Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-reactjs-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-reactjs-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T20:34:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ReactJS is one of the most popular JavaScript libraries for building scalable and performant applications.  When you're working on ReactJS projects, whether they're large or small, you'll need to focus on code quality, readability, maintainable, and scalability.  Writing good code will also help you reduce PR comments from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neha sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Certified Associate (003) – How to Study for the Exam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/terraform-certified-associate-003-study-notes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/terraform-certified-associate-003-study-notes/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T19:17:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been meaning to get my Terraform associates certification for some time now, but something always got in the way.  Finally I was able to sit down and work my way through the study materials. Currently Andrew Brown and I are creating two Terraform Bootcamps: one for beginners [https://terraform.cloudprojectbootcamp.com/]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a no-code game with GDevelop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-no-code-game-with-gdevelop/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-no-code-game-with-gdevelop/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T19:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever dreamt of designing a video game but found yourself hesitant because of the coding aspect? Well, you can create your own came without code! We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org that will guide you through the creation of a wave defense game, all without having]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gradients, Blend Modes, And A Really Cool Hover Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/gradients-blend-modes-hover-effect/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/gradients-blend-modes-hover-effect/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gradients are a powerful CSS feature. We use them for texture, depth, and even to hide parts of elements with CSS masking. This article covers another interesting way to use gradients — as a hover effect that affects the appearance of other elements around the hovered element.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Samathanam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Requirements.txt – How to Create and Pip Install Requirements.txt in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-requirementstxt-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-requirementstxt-explained/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T14:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many Python packages we use to solve our coding problems daily. Take, for instance, the library "Beautiful Soup," – it doesn't come with Python by default and needs to be installed separately.  Many projects rely on libraries and other dependencies, and installing each one can be tedious]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tantoluwa Heritage Alabi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EternalBlue Explained – An In-Depth Analysis of the Notorious Windows Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/eternalblue-explained-an-analysis-of-the-windows-flaw/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/eternalblue-explained-an-analysis-of-the-windows-flaw/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T08:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Learning to Code in your 30s with Patrick San Juan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-learning-to-code-in-your-30s-patrick-san-juan/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-learning-to-code-in-your-30s-patrick-san-juan/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T17:33:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I'm joined by Patrick San Juan, a software engineer who first learned to code in his 30s. I've known Patrick since the early days of freeCodeCamp. He has always been a positive, supportive force within the community. Patrick grew up the son of first-generation immigrants from the Philippines. His]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rediscovering The Joy Of Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/rediscovering-joy-happiness-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/rediscovering-joy-happiness-design/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pratik Joglekar takes a philosophical approach to remind designers about the lost joy within themselves by effectively placing massive importance on mindfulness, introspection, and forward-looking. Without joy, the work we do would feel meaningless. To prevent it from happening, check out a few ideas that would help rediscover that spark of joy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Pratik Joglekar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Scraping with Google Sheets – How to Scrape Web Pages with Built-in Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-scraping-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-scraping-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T21:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You read that right – you can practice web scraping without leaving your happy place: Google Sheets. Google Sheets has five built-in functions that help you import data from other sheets and other web pages. We'll walk through all of them in order from easiest (most limited) to hardest (most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Java in Ubuntu – JDK Linux Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-java-in-ubuntu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-java-in-ubuntu/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Installing software on Linux is usually easier, or at least that's what it seems like. But this is usually not the case as we've come to a realization that installing and configuring some specific tools on Linux might be more time-consuming than on Windows or MacOS. An example of this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How JavaScript String Concatenation Works – the "+" Operator vs the "+=" Operator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-concatenation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-concatenation/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T18:50:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[String concatenation is a common task that we do often. String concatenation is the operation of joining character strings end-to-end. For example, the concatenation of "snow" and "ball" is "snowball". In this article, I will be showing two methods by which you can concatenate strings in JavaScript. I will also]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Object-Oriented Programming in Python – Explained in Plain English]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-oriented-programming-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-oriented-programming-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T18:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> “Any fool can know. The point is to understand.” - Albert Einstein Object-oriented programming is a popular way to write computer programs. Because of this, all programmers should understand what OOP is, what languages you can use to program this way, and why it is important. When asked in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master the T3 Stack and Build a YouTube Clone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-the-t3-stack-and-build-a-youtube-clone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-the-t3-stack-and-build-a-youtube-clone/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T16:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a full-featured YouTube clone requres a deep understanding of a wide variety of technologies. If you want to gain that understading, we have a course for you. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use the T3 stack to create]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove Empty Rows and Columns in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-empty-rows-and-columns-in-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-empty-rows-and-columns-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T07:10:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn how to remove empty rows and columns from Google Sheets using Google Apps Script. A while ago I wrote an article on how to remove empty rows and columns from Google Sheets [https://kcl.hashnode.dev/how-to-delete-empty-rows-and-columns-in-google-sheets] .  I recently revisited that article and I now present]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nibesh Khadka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Diagrams as Code with Mermaid, GitHub, and Visual Studio Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/diagrams-as-code-with-mermaid-github-and-vs-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/diagrams-as-code-with-mermaid-github-and-vs-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T20:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diagrams are an important part of technical documentation. In this article we will explore how we can use code to generate diagrams and leverage them in Markdown.  Here is an example of how a code generated diagram looks like: Diagram generated by codeNo tools, no dragging, aligning and snapping]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Contribute to Open-Source Projects – A Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-contribute-to-open-source-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-contribute-to-open-source-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T15:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past decade, open-source projects have become the backbone of the technology ecosystem. They power everything from applications to innovations across different fields. These collaborative inventions bring together people with different skill sets including developers, designers, and tech enthusiasts in general with one goal in mind to build: to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hillary Nyakundi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Signal Processing and Systems in Programming – Guide for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/signal-processing-and-systems-in-programming/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/signal-processing-and-systems-in-programming/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T14:49:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Signal processing is an important field in engineering and programming.  Basically, it allows engineers and programmers to improve data so that people can use it more effectively. For example, it is thanks to signal processing that much of the background noise in a phone call is removed. This way,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Azure Kubernetes Service for Container Orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-azure-kubernetes-service-for-container-orchestration/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-azure-kubernetes-service-for-container-orchestration/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T13:56:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containerization has transformed the way applications are built, deployed, and scaled. Containers provide a lightweight, portable, and uniform environment for developers to bundle their programs as well as their dependencies into a single unit.  But when a system's container count rises, controlling and coordinating them becomes more difficult. Fortunately,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Linear Regression Model – Machine Learning Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-linear-regression-model-with-an-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-linear-regression-model-with-an-example/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T13:53:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever since the launch of OpenAI's ChatGPT, everyone wants to learn about AI and ML.  Not only that – everyone wants to build and release an AI product on their own to mark their position in the global competition.  And if you already own a SaaS product, you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML, CSS, and JavaScript Project in Spanish – Create a Pokédex]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-css-and-javascript-project-in-spanish-create-a-pokedex/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-css-and-javascript-project-in-spanish-create-a-pokedex/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T13:25:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building projects is a great way to practice your skills, especially in web development. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org Spanish YouTube channel that will teach you how to build a Pokédex step by step with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, using data from the PokéAPI [https://pokeapi.co/]. If you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Stack Web Dev with Next.js & Firebase – Google Drive Clone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-web-development-by-building-a-google-drive-clone-nextjs-firebase/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-web-development-by-building-a-google-drive-clone-nextjs-firebase/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T12:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to take your web development skills to the next level and learn a bit about how platforms like Google Drive work under the hood?  We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build a Google Drive clone with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Long Live The Test Pyramid]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/long-live-test-pyramid/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/long-live-test-pyramid/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is the Test Pyramid really dead? Discover the more contemporary testing strategies and evaluate the Test Pyramid’s relevance in today’s software development practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ramona Schwering)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Test Driven Development in Android Apps – A Practical Guide to TDD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tdd-in-android-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tdd-in-android-apps/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T06:34:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TDD, or Test-Driven Development, is a software development approach where tests are written before the actual code is implemented.  It requires a clear understanding of "What" and "How" in the the requirements of the project/feature.  TDD helps to write less, but enough code. It helps prevent common software]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siamak Mahmoudi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage Users in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manage-users-in-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manage-users-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T00:08:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux is an open-source operating system that is widely used in various applications due to its flexibility, stability, and security. One of the fundamental aspects of Linux is user management, which enables administrators to control access to resources and maintain security of the system. In the fast-paced world of technology,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Destiny Erhabor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility Resources for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/accessibilty-websites-for-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/accessibilty-websites-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T22:49:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility is never a "nice-to-have" requirement when it comes to developing websites and apps. It's a "must-have" that should be an integral part of your design and development process.  Ensuring good accessibility is a fundamental responsibility for developers. It can help their applications provide an equitable experience for all]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilknur Eren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React Components – Props, Default Props, and PropTypes Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-components/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-components/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T22:21:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're curious about web development, you've probably heard the buzz about React. React is an open-source JavaScript library used for building user interfaces (UIs) in web applications. It has taken the web development world by storm. One of the key concepts in React is components. In this tutorial, we'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casmir Onyekani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use AI-Generated Code in a Safe and Effective Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-ai-generated-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-ai-generated-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T20:46:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the heart of software development lies code. It's a set of sequential instructions that allow computers to run programs and applications.  The act of writing code has always rested squarely upon the shoulders of skilled programmers. It's been a distinctly human endeavor.  But the this process is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonya Moisset</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Prompt Engineering – Full Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-prompt-engineering-full-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-prompt-engineering-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T17:23:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Large Language Models like ChatGPT can be used to increase your productivity on a ton of different types of tasks. To use LLMs effectively, it is important to understand prompt engineering strategies.  We just published a crash course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Animated Bubbles with HTML5 Canvas and JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-animated-bubbles-with-html5-canvas-and-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-animated-bubbles-with-html5-canvas-and-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T14:08:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! Welcome to this tutorial where we're going to dive into the world of creating fun bubbles in code using HTML canvas and JavaScript. The best part? We'll achieve all of this using just a touch of HTML and all JavaScript, no CSS. What we will learn In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shruti Kapoor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SQL Handbook – A Free Course for Web Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-beginners-guide-to-sql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-beginners-guide-to-sql/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T13:57:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SQL is everywhere these days. Whether you're learning backend development [https://www.boot.dev/], data engineering, DevOps, or data science, SQL is a skill you'll want in your toolbelt. This a free and open text-based handbook. If you want to get started, just scroll down and start reading. That said, there are two]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Wagner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Databricks Delta Lake with SQL – Full Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/databricks-sql-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/databricks-sql-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T13:57:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the Databricks Delta Lake with SQL Handbook! Databricks is a unified analytics platform that brings together data engineering, data science, and business analytics into a collaborative workspace.  Delta Lake, a powerful storage layer built on top of Databricks, provides enhanced reliability, performance, and data quality for big]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atharva Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generating Real-Time Audio Sentiment Analysis With AI]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/generating-real-time-audio-sentiment-analysis-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/generating-real-time-audio-sentiment-analysis-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Joas Pambou builds the tool to provide a sentiment score in **real-time** with enhanced user experience by providing multilingual support. You will use an OpenAI library called Whisper that transcribes audio files into text and detects the language, and Gradio, a UI framework, to establish the interface.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use GraphQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/graphql-database-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/graphql-database-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T20:47:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GraphQL has been transforming the way that developers interact with APIs and data-driven applications. And there is a good chance you will need to know about it as a developer. We just posted a full GraphQL course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. In this comprehensive course, designed especially for those]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Automate Your Job Then Keep Climbing with Malindi Colyer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-95-malindi-colyer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-95-malindi-colyer/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:48:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I'm joined by Malindi Colyer. Among her many skills, she's a Python developer and AI engineer. Malindi grew up on a farm in rural Kansas, in the middle of the US. She trained to become a diplomat, and volunteered overseas. But along the way, she discovered a love of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose a Deployment Strategy for Your Next.js Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deployment-strategies-for-nextjs-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deployment-strategies-for-nextjs-apps/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T14:19:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many projects are migrating from React to Next.js in 2023. So now's the right time to understand an important step in creating a Next.js application: deployment. Deploying a Next.js application is an essential step in the lifecycle of your web product. And since various deployment strategies exist, picking the right]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tobenna Okeke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MERN Stack Crash Course – Build a Book Store App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mern-stack-crash-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mern-stack-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T19:03:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MERN stack is a set of technologies often used to build full stack web apps.  We just released a crash course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create full stack apps with the MERN stack. In this comprehensive course, we will take you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Security in Django – How to Build a Secure Web Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-secure-django-web-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-secure-django-web-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T18:52:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web security is an important aspect of the web application development process. Especially as more data is stored, managed, and shared.  As a web developer, it's essential to prioritize security measures to protect your company’s users and data from potential threats.  In this article, I will demonstrate web]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isah Jacob</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI and Cybersecurity Handbook – Past the Hype and Onto the ROI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-and-cybersecurity-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-and-cybersecurity-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T16:36:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) has become one of the most talked about technologies in cybersecurity. Driven by the rising sophistication of cyber threats and large talent shortages, organizations are turning to AI as a force multiplier for security teams.  But integrating AI into security workflows requires thoughtful planning and evaluation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonya Moisset</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Array Handbook – Learn How JS Array Methods Work With Examples and Cheat Sheet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-array-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-array-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T14:22:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In programming, an array is a data structure that contains a collection of elements. Arrays are very useful because you can store, access, and manipulate multiple elements in a single array. In this handbook, you'll learn how to work with arrays in JavaScript. We'll cover the specific rules you need]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A September Of Never Ending Adventures (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-september-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-september-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T08:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s get ready for September with some fresh wallpaper designs! Created with love by artists and designers from across the globe, the wallpapers in this collection come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Social Media Web Authentication using Firebase]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/social-media-based-web-authentication-with-firebase/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/social-media-based-web-authentication-with-firebase/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T00:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[User authentication is extremely important in the context of web development. The way users log in affects their overall experience and engagement with an application. It also affects how they initially perceive it. Authentication techniques are continually evolving as social media sites continue to grow in popularity. The ability to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OWASP API Security Top 10 – Secure Your APIs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/owasp-api-security-top-10-secure-your-apis/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/owasp-api-security-top-10-secure-your-apis/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T19:27:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The OWASP API Security Top 10 is a standard reference guide highlighting the most critical web API vulnerabilities to help developers and organizations understand and mitigate potential security threats. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you about each security risk and techniques to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Online Image-to-PDF Converter with HTML, CSS, JS, and NodeJS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-online-image-to-pdf-converter-with-html-css-js-nodejs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-online-image-to-pdf-converter-with-html-css-js-nodejs/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T17:03:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An online image-to-PDF converter is a website that helps you convert your images to PDFs. This tool is useful because it provides an efficient way to store your images. In this tutorial, you'll learn how you can create your online image-to-pdf converter with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and NodeJS. Table of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gideon Akinsanmi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing freeCodeCamp Press – Free Books for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-press-books-handbooks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-press-books-handbooks/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T16:49:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The freeCodeCamp community has published more than 10,000 tutorials over the years. But lately we've focused on creating even longer resources for learning math, programming, and computer science. This is why we've created freeCodeCamp Press – a division of freeCodeCamp where we publish full-length books and handbooks – all available]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abbey Rennemeyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Machine Learning and Neural Networks without Frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-machine-learning-and-neural-networks-without-frameworks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-machine-learning-and-neural-networks-without-frameworks/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T16:22:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of machine learning course relay on frameworks that abstract the inner workings of what's going on. If you want to become proficient, it's helpful to understand how things work under the hood. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agile Software Development Handbook – Scrum, Kanban, and Other Methodologies Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/agile-software-development-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/agile-software-development-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T14:26:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the fast-paced and ever-evolving world of software development, there's always a need for flexibility, adaptability, and responsiveness. Traditional software development methods often struggled to keep up with changing requirements and market demands. This can lead to delays, cost overruns, and dissatisfied stakeholders. In response to these challenges, the Agile]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adekola Olawale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build and Release a Flutter App in Google Play]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-release-flutter-app-in-google-play/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-release-flutter-app-in-google-play/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T14:23:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the rapidly evolving world of mobile app development, Flutter has gained immense popularity for its ability to create stunning and high-performance apps across multiple platforms.  Flutter's framework allows developers to build beautiful user interfaces, deliver native performance, and streamline development.  In this tutorial, I will walk you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The C Programming Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-c-programming-handbook-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-c-programming-handbook-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T20:38:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C is one of the oldest, most widely known, and most influential programming languages. It is used in many industries because it is a highly flexible and powerful language. Learning C is a worthwhile endeavor – no matter your starting point or aspirations – because it builds a solid foundation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Un-Styled UI Components – Guide for Front-End Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/unstyled-ui-components-for-front-end-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/unstyled-ui-components-for-front-end-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T15:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine this situation: you are working on a time-sensitive project, and you need to implement some specific UI components that comply with accessibility best practices.  You may know about some libraries that are full of pre-designed UI elements, each with their own style. But here's the catch – you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chinenye Anikwenze</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Task Manager CLI Tool with Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nodejs-tutorial-build-a-task-manager-cli-tool/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nodejs-tutorial-build-a-task-manager-cli-tool/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T14:19:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone 👋 In this tutorial, you'll learn how to make a simple Task Manager CLI (Command Line Interface) tool. This means you can use commands to Create, View, Update, or Delete your todos.  We will be building this CLI tool using NodeJS. We'll also use MongoDB as the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krish Jaiswal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Javascript Dates – How to Use the DayJS Library to work with Date and Time in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-date-time-dayjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-date-time-dayjs/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T22:09:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to handling dates and times in JavaScript, developers often find themselves grappling with the complexities of the built-in Date object. While vanilla JavaScript provides fundamental functionality, it can be quite cumbersome to work with, especially when dealing with parsing, formatting, and manipulating dates. This is where external]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Weatherston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Data Science and AI Handbook – How to Start a Career in Data Science]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-data-science-and-ai-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-data-science-and-ai-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T16:44:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this handbook, I'll show you how to use proven strategies and insights to get into the fields of AI and Data Science. I'll help you navigate the exciting world of Data Science and AI in 2023 so you can increase your chances of landing a job.  > Every]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tatev Karen Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Functions and Scope – a Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-functions-and-scope/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-functions-and-scope/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T14:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the exciting world of JavaScript Functions and Scope. Have you ever wondered how programs remember things and do tasks over and over again? Well, that's where functions and scope come into play. Whether you're a curious beginner or someone looking to strengthen your coding skills, get ready to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casmir Onyekani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Falling For Oklch: A Love Story Of Color Spaces, Gamuts, And CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/oklch-color-spaces-gamuts-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/oklch-color-spaces-gamuts-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Color Module Level 4 specification defined a slew of new color features when it became a candidate recommendation in 2022, including Oklab and Oklch, which have widened the field of color we have to work with. Explore the Oklch color space and how to start using it in CSS today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Earn a Free C# Certification from Microsoft and freeCodeCamp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-microsoft-c-sharp-certification/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-microsoft-c-sharp-certification/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T12:53:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm excited to announce that Microsoft and freeCodeCamp have teamed up to bring you a new free professional certification: the Foundational C# Certification. This professional certification includes 35 hours of training from Microsoft and an online certification exam by freeCodeCamp. By the end of this process, you'll have earned your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>