<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-10-27T01:38:21.481Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find a Meeting Time and Schedule a Meeting on Microsoft 365]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/find-meeting-time-schedule-meeting-microsoft-365/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/find-meeting-time-schedule-meeting-microsoft-365/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T21:34:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A common functionality that many work apps have is letting users schedule a meeting with others in their organization. Here's how to do it on Microsoft 365. Work Apps Need Work Data If your organization uses Microsoft 365, it should consider integrating it with apps that it uses for work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Waldek Mastykarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Can DevSecOps Improve Cloud Security?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-devsecops-can-improve-cloud-security/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-devsecops-can-improve-cloud-security/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T21:28:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s no doubt that DevSecOps is on the rise, as the need for fast but highly secure application delivery increases. A report by Emergen Research [https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/devsecops-market-size-to-reach-usd-23-42-billion-in-2028--rising-need-for-repeatable-and-adaptive-processes-and-increasing-need-for-custom-code-security-are-key-factors-driving-industry-demand-says-emergen-research-301481508.html]  shows that the DevSecOps market is set to reach a $23.42 billion value in 202]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrej Kovacevic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set an Environment Variable in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-an-environment-variable-in-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-an-environment-variable-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T18:38:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In programming, you use variables to store information like strings and numbers temporarily.  Variables can be used repeatedly throughout the code or by your operating system to provide values. You can edit them, overwrite them, and delete them. In this tutorial, I'll teach you what environment variables are and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve Website Accessibility – 7 Helpful Tips]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-website-accessibility-with-these-tips/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-website-accessibility-with-these-tips/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T18:09:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An accessible website is designed in such a way that anyone can use it without difficulty.  During the website development process, you want to make sure that the end user has the best user experience. And that includes people with disabilities or those who faces challenges when using a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tooba Jamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holographic Trading Card Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374609</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/holographic-trading-card-effect/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T17:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simon Goellner (@simeydotme)’s collection of Holographic Trading Cards have captured our attention.
Under the hood there is a suite of filter(), background-blend-mode(), mix-blend-mode(), and clip-path() combinations that have been painstakingly tweaked to reach the desired effect. I …
Holographic Trading Card Effect originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Kouchi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computer Science VS Information Technology – What's the Difference Between CS and IT?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/computer-science-vs-information-technology-whats-the-difference/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/computer-science-vs-information-technology-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T16:24:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To the average person, computer science and information technology might just seem like different names for the same thing. Well, computer science and information technology are related, but in the actual sense, they are two distinct fields when it comes to studying and choosing a career path. In this article,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typographic Hierarchies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/typographic-hierarchies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/typographic-hierarchies/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Alma Hoffmann discusses six basic variables to establish a typographic hierarchy, explains how to look at each differently, and in turn, designs pieces by intentionally modifying each variable to create a typographic hierarchy effectively.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alma Hoffmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How Graph Algorithms Work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-how-graph-algorithms-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-how-graph-algorithms-work/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T13:42:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Graph algorithms and data structures are used to solve many real-word problems and are commonly needed to solve coding challenges. A graph data structures is a non-linear data structure consisting of vertices and edges. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you learn how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Python Lambda Function Works – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-lambda-function-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-lambda-function-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T20:37:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the beautiful things about Python is that it is generally one of the most intuitive programming languages out there. Still, certain concepts can be difficult to grasp and comprehend. The lambda function is one of them.  I've been there. When I first started learning Python, I skipped]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ibrahim Abayomi Ogunbiyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Production Ready eCommerce Website with ReactJS, TailwindCSS, PlanetScale and Stripe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-ecommerce-website-using-next-js-and-planetscale/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-ecommerce-website-using-next-js-and-planetscale/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T16:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, welcome to this tutorial. Today we're going to build a production-ready eCommerce website using ReactJS, TailwindCSS, PlanetScale, and Stripe. Before we begin, you should be familiar with the basics of React.js and Next.js to get the most out of this guide. If you're not and need to brush up,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharvin Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Animated, Clickable Cards With the :has() Relational Pseudo Class]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374690</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-animated-clickable-cards-with-the-has-relational-pseudo-class/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T14:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS :has() pseudo class is rolling out in many browsers with Chrome and Safari already fully supporting it. It’s often referred to it as “the parent selector” — as in, we can select style a parent element from a …
Creating Animated, Clickable Cards With the :has() Relational Pseudo Class originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brecht De Ruyte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp Turns 8 Years Old: Data Science Courses + University Degrees Update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-math-computer-science-degree-update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-math-computer-science-degree-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T13:52:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the global freeCodeCamp community. 8 years ago, we started this grass-roots community of learners. Back then, freeCodeCamp sounded like an improbable dream. But we all rolled up our sleeves and got to work making it a reality. Today, more than a million people use freeCodeCamp each day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Payment Request API in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/payment-request-api-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/payment-request-api-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T22:40:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Payment Request API provides a cross-browser standard that lets you collect payments, addresses, and contact information from your customers. You can then use this info to process their order. It also facilitates the exchange of this information between the browser and the website. The fundamental idea behind this is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atta ✨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Contribute to Open Source – a Guide for Technical Writers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-contribute-to-open-source-for-technical-writers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-contribute-to-open-source-for-technical-writers/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T21:20:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Contributing to open source can be a daunting prospect, especially if you haven't done so before, or if you're used to working on documentation rather than code. This guide will help technical writers get started contributing to open-source projects, and outline some of the common pitfalls you might encounter when]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Swift Handbook – Learn Swift for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-swift-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-swift-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T21:04:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Swift The Swift programming language was created by Apple in 2014. It's the official language that works with the whole Apple Operating Systems lineup: iOS, iPadOS, watchOS, macOS, and tvOS. Swift is an open source, general purpose, compiled programming language that's statically typed. Every value has a type]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flavio Copes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State Of CSS Survey: Influence The Future Of CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/state-css-survey-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/state-css-survey-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The annual survey for anyone who writes CSS, [State of CSS](https://stateofcss.com/), is nearing the end of its response period for 2022. The survey is available in many different languages while all questions are optional, i.e. reaching 100% completion is not required. Please do make sure to [join in](https://stateofcss.com/) — it will only take a few minutes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lea Verou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Select – Statement and Query Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-select-statement-and-query-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-select-statement-and-query-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T18:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Structured Query Language (SQL) is a programming language that you use to manage data in relational databases. You can use SQL to create, read, update, and delete (CRUD) data in a relational database. You can write SQL queries to insert data with INSERT, read data with SELECT, update with UPDATE,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Monetize Your Website with Microtransactions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-monetize-your-website/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-monetize-your-website/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T15:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web Monetization means that you can get money for every person that visits your website. Sounds good right? But how does it work?  We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to monetize your website using microtransactions and the Interledger Protocol.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Cloud Firestore in a React App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-firebase-database-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-firebase-database-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T15:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firebase provides some great services like NoSQL databases, authentication, cloud storage, and much more. In this tutorial, we will learn how to use your React application to read and add data to your Firebase database.  To demonstrate this, we will learn how to build a Todo app using React]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gradient Descent – Machine Learning Algorithm Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gradient-descent-machine-learning-algorithm-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gradient-descent-machine-learning-algorithm-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T13:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Gradient Descent Algorithm? Gradient descent is probably the most popular machine learning algorithm. At its core, the algorithm exists to minimize errors as much as possible.  The aim of gradient descent as an algorithm is to minimize the cost function of a model. We can tell]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salim Oyinlola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is There Too Much CSS Now?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374364</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/is-there-too-much-css-now/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T12:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As front-end developers, we’ve wished for a lot of things over the years — ways to center things in CSS, encapsulate styles, set an element’s aspect ratio, get finer-grained control over our colors, select an element based on its children’s …
Is There Too Much CSS Now? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sacha Greif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Upload Files to Azure using NestJS and typeORM with MySQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/upload-files-to-azure-using-nestjs-and-typeorm-with-mysql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/upload-files-to-azure-using-nestjs-and-typeorm-with-mysql/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T23:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images and videos are examples of huge files that might be stored in your database. And this might impact the performance of your applications because of the amount of space that those files can take up.  Also, it expands the database, which makes backups larger and slower. Because of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Destiny Erhabor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Layouts – How to Use CSS Grid and Flex to Create a Responsive Web Page]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-layouts-use-css-grid-and-flex-to-create-responsive-webpages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-layouts-use-css-grid-and-flex-to-create-responsive-webpages/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T23:12:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your web layout is to your website what a floor plan is to a building. Without them, you’re just building castles in the air.  The first thing to do when you have a website or application to build or design is to decide on the layout. This is important]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ophy Boamah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is an ORM – The Meaning of Object Relational Mapping Database Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-an-orm-the-meaning-of-object-relational-mapping-database-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-an-orm-the-meaning-of-object-relational-mapping-database-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T18:18:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Object Relational Mapping (ORM) is a technique used in creating a "bridge" between object-oriented programs and, in most cases, relational databases [/news/what-is-a-relational-database-rdbms-definition/]. Put another way, you can see the ORM as the layer that connects object oriented programming [/news/four-pillars-of-object-oriented-programming/] (OOP) to relational databases.  When interacting with a database using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Ethernet Protocol Works – A Complete Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-complete-guide-to-the-ethernet-protocol/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-complete-guide-to-the-ethernet-protocol/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T17:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you’ve been aware of it or not, you’ve probably used the Ethernet in the past. Does this cable look familiar? (Source: Wikipedia [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ethernet_physical_layer#/media/File:EthernetCableYellow3.jpg] )Ethernet is extremely popular, and is the most widely used Data Link Layer protocol, at least where the devices are linked by physical cables (rather than]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fancy Image Decorations: Masks and Advanced Hover Effects]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374194</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/fancy-image-decorations-masks-and-advanced-hover-effects/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T12:46:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Part 2 of this three-part series! We are still decorating images without any extra elements and pseudo-elements. I hope you already took the time to digest Part 1 because we will continue working with a lot of gradients …
Fancy Image Decorations: Masks and Advanced Hover Effects originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Futuristic CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/futuristic-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/futuristic-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sacha Greif tries to anticipate future CSS trends and takes a look at some far-fetched and futuristic CSS features that might one day make their way to the browser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sacha Greif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Object Oriented Programming in Python – Full Crash Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crash-course-object-oriented-programming-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crash-course-object-oriented-programming-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T22:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Object Oriented programming, or "OOP" for short, is a way of writing code that relies on the concepts of classes and objects.  The main benefit of writing your code in an object-oriented way is to structure your program into simple, reusable pieces of code. Stick with me through this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Wagner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CRUD Operations – Crud Definition in Programming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crud-operations-crud-definition-in-programming/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crud-operations-crud-definition-in-programming/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T21:54:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When interacting with a database or working with an API, you'll often encounter the term CRUD. It is a popular acronym for the four basic operations or functions that a model (in the case of an API) or a database management system uses. This is an acronym everyone learning computer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instant Articles, Proprietary Syndication, and a Web Built on User Fidelity Preferences]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374470</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/instant-articles-proprietary-syndication-user-fidelity-preferences/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T19:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love it when there’s a sense of synergy in the blogosphere. First, I caught Nick Heer’s coverage of Meta ending support for Instant Articles, its proprietary format for stripped-down performant news articles. He also compares it to the similar …
Instant Articles, Proprietary Syndication, and a Web Built on User Fidelity Preferences originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computer Programmer Salary – How Much Do Coders Make?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/computer-programmer-salary-how-much-do-coders-make/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/computer-programmer-salary-how-much-do-coders-make/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T19:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coding is one of the most popular and in-demand careers. There are many reasons why people choose a career in coding and computer science. The technology field offers promising and diverse job prospects in several industries, job security, a generally comfortable starting salary, and increased high-earning potential as developers gain]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tableau VS Power BI – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tableau-vs-power-bi-whats-the-difference/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tableau-vs-power-bi-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T17:48:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tableau and Power BI are both data visualization and business intelligence tools. You can extract data with both tools, visualize the data, analyze it, and turn it into a piece of actionable information. In this article, you will learn what both Power BI and Tableau are in detail. I will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code Google Docs with Flutter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-google-docs-with-flutter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-google-docs-with-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T14:15:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a Google Docs clone will help you learn a lot of new concepts. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Flutter to create a Google Docs clone. Rivaan Ranawat created this course. Rivaan has created many popular technical]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New In DevTools: Halloween Edition 🎃]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/devtools-updates-halloween-edition/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/devtools-updates-halloween-edition/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Patrick Brosset gives an update on the most impactful new features that are now available in DevTools, across Firefox, Chrome, Safari, and Edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Patrick Brosset)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsive Animations for Every Screen Size and Device]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374345</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/responsive-animations-for-every-screen-size-and-device/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T12:42:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before I career jumped into development, I did a bunch of motion graphics work in After Effects. But even with that background, I still found animating on the web pretty baffling.
Video graphics are designed within a specific ratio and …
Responsive Animations for Every Screen Size and Device originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cassie Evans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Reverting to Previous Commit – How to Revert to Last Commit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-reverting-to-previous-commit-how-to-revert-to-last-commit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-reverting-to-previous-commit-how-to-revert-to-last-commit/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T22:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git [/news/git-and-github-for-beginners/] is a great tool for version control. It also makes collaborating with others more efficient. In this article, you'll learn how to revert to previous commits when tracking your project with Git. The two commands we'll discuss in this article are git reset and git revert. These commands]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard CS50 – Free Computer Science University Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/harvard-cs50/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/harvard-cs50/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T14:07:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard University's CS50 is one of the most popular beginner computer science courses in the world.  We just released the entire CS50 course–all 25 hours–on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. David J. Malan is widely considered to be one of the best computer science instructors. He teaches this course. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a Folder “Slit” Effect With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374376</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-make-a-folder-slit-effect-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T12:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you put something — say a regular sheet of paper — in a manilla folder, a part of that thing might peek out of the folder a little bit. The same sort of thing with a wallet and credit …
How to Make a Folder “Slit” Effect With CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Privacy: A New Smashing Book Is Here]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/understanding-privacy-book-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/understanding-privacy-book-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Understanding Privacy, our brand new Smashing Book to make sense of privacy, and learn how to create inclusive, safe and privacy-aware digital experiences. eBook now available, print shipping in November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Command Line Tutorial – How to Use Common Terminal Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linux-command-line-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linux-command-line-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T23:33:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An operating system is a set of software layers between you and your computer's hardware.  The operating system (or OS) is a piece of software that controls all other application programs and helps you manage the hardware and software of your computer. Examples of popular operating systems are Windows,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Destiny Erhabor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wi-Fi Hacking 101 – How to Hack WPA2 and Defend Against These Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/wi-fi-hacking-101/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/wi-fi-hacking-101/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T20:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the world of Wi-Fi hacking, everybody. 💻. In my previous article [/news/linux-basics/], we talked about some basic Linux skills and tricks. In this article you are going to learn a basic Wi-Fi hacking procedure using those skills. You'll learn things such as how to:  1. Monitor Wi-Fi]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Iwugo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Append a String in Python – STR Appending]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/append-a-string-in-python-str-appending/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/append-a-string-in-python-str-appending/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T19:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll learn the different methods of appending strings in Python.  Another term commonly used when talking about appending strings is concatenation. So you'll often see these terms — append and concatenate — used interchangeably.  Either way, to append or concatenate strings means to add or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Go Handbook – Learn Golang for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/go-beginners-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/go-beginners-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T18:35:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Golang is an awesome, simple, modern, and fast programming language. It’s compiled, open source, and strongly typed. Golang – also called Go – was created by Google engineers with these main goals:  * make their projects compile (and run) faster  * be simple so people can pick it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flavio Copes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Cross-Platform Application with Next.js and Tauri]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-cross-platform-app-with-next-and-tauri/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-cross-platform-app-with-next-and-tauri/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T16:38:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tauri is a new Rust-based framework that builds an x86_64 cross-platform application for Windows, macOS, and Linux.  In this tutorial, we'll use Tauri and Next.js to build a desktop-based cross-platform application and publish it to the Snap store and AppImage. So why is building a cross-platform app, that works]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manuel Matuzovic: max() Trickery]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374466</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/manuel-matuzovic-max-trickery/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T13:54:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By way of a post by Manuel Matuzović which is by way of a demo by Temani Afif.
.wrapper {
  margin-inline: max(0px, ((100% - 64rem) / 2)); 
}
You’d be doing yourself a favor to read Manuel’s breakdown of …
Manuel Matuzovic: max() Trickery originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Search Tips – How to Search Issues, Repos, and More Effectively on GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/github-search-tips/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/github-search-tips/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T19:27:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I was a beginner to open-source contributions, one of my greatest challenge was finding the correct projects/issues to work on. For the longest time I relied on resources curated by different writers on the internet (which were good, by the way). But I always wanted to find a way]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hillary Nyakundi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Explode – How to Split a String into an Array]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/php-explode-how-to-split-a-string-into-an-array/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/php-explode-how-to-split-a-string-into-an-array/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T17:19:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The PHP explode() function converts a string to an array. Each of the characters in the string is given an index that starts from 0. Like the built-in imlode()  function, the explode function does not modify the data (string). Syntax of the explode() Function The explode() function takes in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Show Upcoming Meetings for a Microsoft 365 User]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-show-upcoming-meetings-for-a-microsoft-365-user/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-show-upcoming-meetings-for-a-microsoft-365-user/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T17:08:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a web developer and you work with an organization that uses Microsoft 365, you probably use it to manage your meetings. In this tutorial, you'll learn how you can build a simple personal assistant in under 10 minutes that'll show a Microsoft 365 user the meetings they have]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Waldek Mastykarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Architect a Blockchain on Kubernetes – K8S Microservice Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-architect-a-blockchain-on-kubernetes-k8s-microservice-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-architect-a-blockchain-on-kubernetes-k8s-microservice-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T16:02:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will describe how to use microservices architecture and Kubernetes to build a blockchain.  The technologies usually used for blockchains are purpose-driven, and you can use them for other projects as well. The examples in this article can readily handle heavy loads and remain responsive and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kayode Adeniyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Lowercase a String in JavaScript – toLowerCase() in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-lowercase-a-string-in-javascript-tolowercase-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-lowercase-a-string-in-javascript-tolowercase-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T15:51:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strings are a fundamental part of working with JavaScript. And the toLowerCase()  method is one of the many integrated methods that you can use to work with strings. In this article, we'll see how to make strings lowercase with the toLowerCase()  method in Python. What is a String?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilenia Magoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pure CSS Bezier Curve Motion Paths]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373600</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/pure-css-bezier-curve-motion-paths/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T15:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a Bezier curve lover like I am?
CodePen Embed Fallback
Besides being elegant, Bezier curves have nice mathematical properties due to their definition and construction. No wonder they are widely used in so many areas:
As a 
…
Pure CSS Bezier Curve Motion Paths originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lu Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Svelte in 23 Hours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-svelte-complete-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-svelte-complete-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T15:14:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Svelte is a front-end JavaScript framework for making interactive webpages. Svelte has grown in popularity quite a bit over the last few years. We just published a free 23-hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Svelte. Li Hau Tan developed this course. Li]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Interpret Black Box Models using LIME (Local Interpretable Model-Agnostic Explanations)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/interpret-black-box-model-using-lime/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/interpret-black-box-model-using-lime/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T15:12:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning models are black box models. By giving input to these models, we can get output based on the particular model we're using.  The way humans interpret things is different from how machines interpret them. So it's helpful to use tools that can turn the output from certain]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josua Antonius Naiborhu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Python? How the Interpreter Works and How to Write "Hello World" in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-python-beginners-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-python-beginners-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T13:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I am going to explain what Python is and how the Python interpreter works. Then you'll write your first "Hello World" program. What is Python? Python is a high-level programming language designed to do many tasks. It's based on the CPython interpreter which translates the Python code]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Five Layers Model? The Framework of the Internet Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-five-layers-model-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-five-layers-model-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T13:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computer Networks are a beautiful, amazing topic. Networks involve so much knowledge from different fields, from physics to algorithms.  When dealing with Computer Networks, there is one framework that puts everything into place – and that is the layers model.  In this post you'll learn why we need]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Full-Site Editing: A Deep Dive Into The New Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/wordpress-full-site-editing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/wordpress-full-site-editing/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Nick Schäferhoff will take a deep dive into WordPress Full-Site Editing, examine the tools it provides for theme development, and provide a tutorial on how to use it to make changes to your site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nick Schäferhoff)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[find() vs filter() in JavaScript – Differences Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/find-vs-filter-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/find-vs-filter-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T22:22:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A common interview question that JavaScript developers often get asked is to explain the difference between the find() and filter() methods.  In this tutorial today, I'll walk you through what these methods are and when you should use them. What is the filter() method? This method returns all the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aman Kalra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the CSScenes, October 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374393</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/behind-the-csscenes-october-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T21:40:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, hey, welcome back to Behind the CSScenes! These posts are like little check-ins we’re doing each month to give you a peek behind what we’re doing here at CSS-Tricks, as well as a chance for us to pause …
Behind the CSScenes, October 2022 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haley Mills</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Copy Text to the Clipboard with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/copy-text-to-clipboard-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/copy-text-to-clipboard-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T21:18:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building advanced web pages and applications, you'll sometimes want to add the copy feature. This lets your users simply click a button or icon to copy text rather than highlighting the text and clicking a couple of buttons on the keyboard. This feature is mostly used when someone]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Add to an Array – JS Append]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-add-to-an-array-js-append/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-add-to-an-array-js-append/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T18:29:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use arrays in JavaScript to store a group of variables, often referred to as elements or items of the array. Each of these elements will have an index number assigned to them starting from zero.  By default, you can use the index of an element in an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UX vs UI – What's the Difference? Definition and Meaning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ux-vs-ui-whats-the-difference-definition-and-meaning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ux-vs-ui-whats-the-difference-definition-and-meaning/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T16:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing a website or an app, the finished product needs to be functional, intuitive, and aesthetically pleasing. This is where UX and UI design come in. UX and UI design are two technical terms that can often be confusing. Many people may use these two terms interchangeably, incorrectly, or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Developer Journey – How I Learned to Code with Dyslexia and ADHD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/developer-journey/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/developer-journey/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T16:01:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone, I'm Jalmari Ikävalko, a software developer in my early 30s. In this article, I’ll share my whole journey from my first contact with code to becoming the professional developer I am today.  I'll start from my childhood when I first got interested in programming. My Introduction to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jalmari Ikävalko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fancy Image Decorations: Single Element Magic]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373965</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/fancy-image-decorations-single-element-magic/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T15:37:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the title says, we are going to decorate images! There’s a bunch of other articles out there that talk about this, but what we’re covering here is quite a bit different because it’s more of a challenge. The challenge? …
Fancy Image Decorations: Single Element Magic originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Things I Took Away From An Event Apart 2022 in Denver]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374401</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-things-i-took-away-from-an-event-apart-2022-in-denver/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T20:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Event Apart 2022 Denver wrapped up yesterday. And while I was unable to make it to all three days this time, I did catch yesterday’s action — and it was awesome. I’m not very social or outgoing, but …
Some Things I Took Away From An Event Apart 2022 in Denver originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Avoid Prop Drilling with the React Context API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/avoid-prop-drilling-with-react-context-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/avoid-prop-drilling-with-react-context-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T16:52:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The React Context API provides a way to pass data through multiple nested levels of components without having to manually pass that data to each level.  React context is one sure way of globally managing your data in your app, and it's a good way to avoid prop drilling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Pure CSS Gallery Focus Effect with :not]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373508</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-pure-css-gallery-focus-effect-with-not/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T15:10:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oftentimes in the past, I needed to figure out how to add styles to all elements inside the container but not the hovered one.
Demo of the expected “fade-out” effect on siblings to let users “focus” on a particular element.…
A Pure CSS Gallery Focus Effect with :not originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krzysztof Gonciarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effective Communication For Everyday Meetings]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/effective-communication-everyday-meetings/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/effective-communication-everyday-meetings/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article about conducting productive meetings, Andrii Zhdan will give you a step-by-step guide on preparing a solid meeting structure that will let you follow the original plan and reach the meeting goals, and he will also share a few tips based on his design experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andrii Zhdan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code a project three different ways (JavaScript + REST API + Database)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-project-three-different-ways-javascript-rest-api-database/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-project-three-different-ways-javascript-rest-api-database/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T14:06:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you code a similar project using different methods it helps you understand each method more. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to code a flight widget in JavaScript using multiple methods. First you will learn to create the project using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Machine Learning Model in Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-machine-learning-model-in-rust/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-machine-learning-model-in-rust/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T22:31:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning is a really interesting concept in computer programming. It involves using data to train a computer program to carry out tasks.  During the process, the program learns from data by discovering patterns. This reduces the need for programmers to hard code rules in some applications. Languages like]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chigozie Oduah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Email Alias – How to Set Up a Professional Email for Free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/email-alias-set-up-a-professional-email-for-free/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/email-alias-set-up-a-professional-email-for-free/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T22:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I needed to log in to AWS. But my main email address was rejected. Apparently I'd done this in the past and the account had been irreversibly deleted.  No reset option – just a message saying the account was permanently deleted: There are about a million ways to get]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Visualization Tools – 2022 Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-visualization-tools-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-visualization-tools-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T17:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data visualization is the process of interpreting or representing data graphically. Generally, it is the graphical or visual representation of data using charts, tables, histograms, and other info-graphics.  Data plays a major role in any type of organization. Data visualization helps us understand certain trends and insights, and make]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Docker and Kubernetes – Free Hands-On Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-docker-and-kubernetes-hands-on-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-docker-and-kubernetes-hands-on-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker and Kubernetes are important technologies that can help you scale your applications. Docker is a platform for packaging, deploying, and running applications in containers. Kubernetes is a system for managing containerized applications across a cluster of nodes. It provides basic mechanisms for deployment, maintenance, and scaling of applications. We]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement a Whitelist in Smart Contracts (ERC-721 NFT, ERC-1155, and others)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-whitelist-in-smartcontracts-erc-721-nft-erc-1155-and-others/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-whitelist-in-smartcontracts-erc-721-nft-erc-1155-and-others/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I will show you three ways you can create a whitelist in a smart contract. Here's what we'll discuss:  * On-chain whitelists  * Digital signatures  * Merkle trees All methods are available in the repo here [https://github.com/gapon2401/smartcontract-whitelist]. A whitelist is useful if you want]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Igor Gaponov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Web Storage Works – Local vs Session Storage Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-web-storage-works/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-web-storage-works/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone who works with the web needs to store data for a later use. Backend developers have some powerful databases in their toolkit. But if you are a frontend developer, you can still store and process data using web storage. In this article, you'll learn what is a web storage,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tooba Jamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Database Management Systems and SQL – Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dbms-and-sql-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dbms-and-sql-basics/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T13:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Database Management Systems and SQL are two of the most important and widely used tools on the internet today.  You use a Database Management System (DBMS) to store the data you collect from various sources, and SQL to manipulate and access the particular data you want in an efficient]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bikash Daga (Jain)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your Personal Brand as a Freelance Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/branding-for-developer-freelancers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/branding-for-developer-freelancers/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T13:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You probably didn’t get into freelance development to become a marketer.  You got into freelancing so you could work when you want, make more money, and control your life. But, if you haven’t realized it yet, building a career as a freelancer requires you to embrace more than just]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Cruz Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Webshop with Angular, Node.js, TypeScript, & Stripe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-webshop-with-angular-node-js-typescript-stripe/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-webshop-with-angular-node-js-typescript-stripe/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T13:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to build a webshop from scratch! We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build a webshop or e-commerce store using Angular/TypeScript, Express.js, and Stripe.  You will learn how to use Angular material and Tailwind to structure the UI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early Days of Container Style Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374330</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/early-days-of-container-style-queries/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T13:06:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re still in suuuuuper early days with container queries. Too early for broad browser support, but Chromium already supports it, Safari started supporting it in version 16, and Firefox is presumably not far behind.
Most early days conversations …
Early Days of Container Style Queries originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Recognize a Phishing Email – And What to Do When You Get One]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-recognize-phishing-email/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-recognize-phishing-email/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T00:52:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know the drill: you open your email client and there is it an email saying that you will be in trouble if you do not follow certain instructions in short time, no questions asked. All it takes is a single click, and you're in trouble. This kind of email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix TypeError: Cannot read Property 'push' of Undefined in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fix-typeerror-cannot-read-property-push-of-undefined-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fix-typeerror-cannot-read-property-push-of-undefined-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T23:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with JavaScript arrays, you have to be careful that you are not calling the push(), pop(), shift(), unShift(), or splice() methods on a variable that is meant to be an array but has a value of undefined. If you mistakenly do this, you'll get this error: If you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Free Resources to Learn Golang – Go Coding Courses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-resources-to-learn-golang-for-free/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-resources-to-learn-golang-for-free/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T23:11:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Golang has been around for a while now, and it's become quite popular among developers. It is a simple yet compelling programming language that's well-loved because of its powerful features like concurrency and the fact that it is developed by Google. Golang is a server-side language that's used in many]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Avdhoot Fulsundar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Programming Tips to Help You Level Up Your Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-programming-tips/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-programming-tips/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T19:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python is one of the most popular programming languages out there today. Its simplicity and readability make it a favorite among many programmers. So in this tutorial, I'm sharing a few pointers and strategies to help you improve your Python programming skills. How to Reverse a String in Python In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Fagbuyiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rendering External API Data in WordPress Blocks on the Front End]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373952</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/rendering-external-api-data-in-wordpress-blocks-on-the-front-end/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T16:15:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’ve been some new tutorials popping here on CSS-Tricks for working with WordPress blocks. One of them is an introduction to WordPress block development and it’s a good place to learn what blocks are and to register them in WordPress …
Rendering External API Data in WordPress Blocks on the Front End originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manoj Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sustainable Web Development Strategies Within An Organization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/sustainable-web-development-strategies-organization/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/sustainable-web-development-strategies-organization/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Climate change and sustainability are increasing concerns for digital organizations, as well as individuals working in tech. In this article we’ll explore some of the ways we can raise awareness and effect change within an organization, to create a more positive environmental impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delightful UI Animations With Shared Element Transitions API (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/ui-animations-shared-element-transitions-api-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/ui-animations-shared-element-transitions-api-part2/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adrian Bece will show how to create same-document page transitions for Single Page Apps using Shared Element Transitions API and check out its future implementation and potential for creating cross-document transitions in Multi-Page Apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript Generics – Use Case and Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typescript-generics-use-case-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typescript-generics-use-case-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T20:49:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn the basics of generics in TypeScript. We'll discuss how to use them and when they're useful in your code. Use Case for Generics Let's start with a simple example, where you want to print the value of an argument passed: function printData(data: number) {]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aman Kalra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Check if a String Contains a Substring in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-check-if-a-string-contains-a-substring-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-check-if-a-string-contains-a-substring-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T18:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with a JavaScript program, you might need to check whether a string contains a substring. A substring is a string inside another string. Specifically, you might need to check whether a word contains a specific character or a specific set of characters. Thankfully, there are a few]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does Recursion Work? Simplified in JavaScript with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/recursion-in-javascript-simplified/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/recursion-in-javascript-simplified/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T17:51:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recursion works similarly to how loops do in JavaScript. Loops allow you to execute a set of code multiple times as long as a condition is true. In this article, I will explain what Recursion is and how it works in JavaScript. In loops, when the condition becomes false, the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Fluid Typography Support to WordPress Block Themes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373905</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/fluid-typography-wordpress-block-themes/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T13:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fluid typography is a fancy way of “describing font properties, such as size or line height, that scale fluidly according to the size of the viewport”. It’s also known by other names, like responsive typography, flexible type, fluid type, …
Adding Fluid Typography Support to WordPress Block Themes originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Dahal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Roadmap For Building A Business Chatbot]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/roadmap-building-business-chatbot/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/roadmap-building-business-chatbot/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Owing to tremendous advancements in Machine Learning and other technologies, chatbots have increased in popularity in the past few years. This article will show you, step by step, how to build a chatbot that meets your business goals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Devansh Bansal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js Authentication With Twilio Verify]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/nodejs-authentication-twilio-verify/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/nodejs-authentication-twilio-verify/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrate two-factor authentication into your Express.js app by building an application that authenticates users using password-based authentication and OTPs powered by the Twilio Verify service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alexander Godwin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python For Beginners Courses Ranked from Best to Worst – freeCodeCamp Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-python-courses-ranked-from-best-to-worst/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-python-courses-ranked-from-best-to-worst/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T19:54:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Does freeCodeCamp really need yet another Python course?   Click for answer.  Between the curriculum and the YouTube channel, freeCodeCamp has quite a few Python programming courses. But which Python course should you take? In this article, I'll rank every singe freeCodeCamp beginner's Python course from best to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Stack Data Structure to Solve Coding Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/stack-data-structure-solve-coding-challenges/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/stack-data-structure-solve-coding-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T18:48:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stack data structure is used frequently in programming, sometimes behind-the-scenes. And questions involving the stack data structure are very common in coding interviews. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use the stack data structure to solve the type of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Implode – Convert Array to String with Join]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/php-implode-convert-array-to-string-with-join/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/php-implode-convert-array-to-string-with-join/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T16:14:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In PHP, the implode() function is a built-in function that takes an array and converts it to a string. implode() doesn’t modify the original array. It doesn’t matter whether the array is an indexed or associative array. Once you pass in the array to implode(), it joins all the values]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn PyTorch for Deep Learning – Free 26-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-pytorch-for-deep-learning-in-day/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-pytorch-for-deep-learning-in-day/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T14:48:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My comprehensive PyTorch course is now live on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel.   * You can view the full 26 hour course here [https://youtu.be/V_xro1bcAuA].  * Read the course materials online for free at learnpytorch.io    [https://learnpytorch.io/].  * See all of the course materials on GitHub]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Bourke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Safely Share Your Email Address on a Website]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373798</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-safely-share-your-email-address-on-a-website/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T12:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spammers are a huge deal nowadays. If you want to share your contact information without getting overwhelmed by spam email you need a solution. I run into this problem a few months ago. While I was researching how to solve …
How to Safely Share Your Email Address on a Website originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lorenzo Bonannella</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React Helmet – With Example Use Case]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-helmet-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-helmet-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T16:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because of the nature of single page applications (SPAs), modifying metadata in React apps can be tricky without using a helper library. Lucky for us, that library already exists – and it's called React Helmet. Leveraging Helmet for metadata inclusion can significantly simplify the process of making a React app SEO]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VLOOKUP in Excel – Formula and Example Function]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vlookup-in-excel-formula-and-example-function/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vlookup-in-excel-formula-and-example-function/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T16:26:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Excel, VLOOKUP() means vertical lookup. It is a powerful built-in function you can use to quickly search for a value in a spreadsheet. VLOOKUP() searches for a value in a vertical manner across the sheet – unlike the HLOOKUP() function which does it horizontally. Before using VLOOKUP(), make sure]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Functions Tutorial – IIFE, Function Parameters, and Code Blocks Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-function-iife-parameters-code-blocks-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-function-iife-parameters-code-blocks-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T16:06:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Functions are one of the most widely-used features in programming. So, it helps to have a solid understanding of how they work. This tutorial discusses everything you need to know to use JavaScript functions like a pro. Table of Contents  1.  What Is a Function?  2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi Sofela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big O Cheat Sheet – Time Complexity Chart]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/big-o-cheat-sheet-time-complexity-chart/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/big-o-cheat-sheet-time-complexity-chart/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T15:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An algorithm is a set of well-defined instructions for solving a specific problem. You can solve these problems in various ways. This means that the method you use to arrive at the same solution may differ from mine, but we should both get the same result. Because there are various]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Validate your Machine Learning Models Using TensorFlow Model Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-validate-machine-learning-models-with-tensorflow-model-analysis/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-validate-machine-learning-models-with-tensorflow-model-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T14:37:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My first deployed Machine Learning model was a failure. It was a simple Diabetes Diagnosis Model for potential diabetes mellitus patients – and quite frankly, I was beyond excited on deployment.  But the excitement soon disappeared when I received feedback from users. Simply put, the users felt the model]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salim Oyinlola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Web Components With Next (or Any SSR Framework)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373787</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-web-components-with-next-or-any-ssr-framework/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T13:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous post we looked at Shoelace, which is a component library with a full suite of UX components that are beautiful, accessible, and — perhaps unexpectedly — built with Web Components. This means they can be used …
Using Web Components With Next (or Any SSR Framework) originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easy Fluid Typography With clamp() Using Sass Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/fluid-typography-clamp-sass-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/fluid-typography-clamp-sass-functions/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can use the `clamp()` method today because of the great browser support. In this article, Brecht De Ruyte explains how it can be a beautiful addition to your upcoming project or as an upgrade to a previous one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF)? Laravel Web Security Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/laravel-web-security-csrf/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/laravel-web-security-csrf/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T21:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn about Laravel web security and how to secure your web applications and protect them from Cross-Site Request Forgery, or CSRF attacks. CSRF is a malicious activity that involves an attacker performing actions on behalf of an authenticated user. Fortunately, Laravel provides out-of-the-box measures to prevent]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sule-Balogun Olanrewaju Ganiu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Print Function in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-does-print-work-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-does-print-work-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T21:16:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Often, you'll need to print something to the console output when you're coding in Java. And the first thing that likely comes to your mind is the print function or print statement. But very few people know about the three different print functions/statements in Java. In this article, I am]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State of CSS 2022 Survey Now Open]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374217</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/state-of-css-2022-survey-now-open/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T18:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The State of CSS survey recently opened up. Last year, the survey confirmed everyone’s assumptions that TailwindCSS is super popular and CSS variables are mainstream. It also codified what many of us want from CSS, from Container Queries to …
State of CSS 2022 Survey Now Open originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Architect a Full-Stack Application from Start to Finish]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-full-stack-application-from-start-to-finish/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-full-stack-application-from-start-to-finish/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T17:49:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software architecture is a massive topic. That said, I think I can give you a simple method you can use to approach the architecture of a full-stack application.  In particular, I want to talk about the order in which you should think about and build out the pieces of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Wagner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your First Microsoft 365 Application in 10 minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-microsoft-365-application-in-10-minutes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-microsoft-365-application-in-10-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T17:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a web developer and work with an organization that uses Microsoft 365, or you build applications that you sell to customers, I've got great news for you: you can use your existing skills to build applications that integrate with Microsoft 365. What's Microsoft 365? Microsoft 365 [https://www.microsoft.com/microsoft-365] is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Waldek Mastykarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Subquery – How to Sub Query in SELECT Statement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-subquery-how-to-sub-query-in-select-statement/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-subquery-how-to-sub-query-in-select-statement/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T17:08:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A SQL subquery is a query inside a query. So, in SQL, a subquery is also called a nested query or an inner query. The outer query in which the inner query is inserted is the main query. SQL admins usually use subqueries inside the WHERE clause to narrow down]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docker vs Virtual Machine (VM) – Key Differences You Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/docker-vs-vm-key-differences-you-should-know/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/docker-vs-vm-key-differences-you-should-know/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T16:48:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, you'll learn the differences between a virtual machine and a  Docker container. Both virtual machines and containers help replicate the development environment, and manage dependencies and configurations better. But there are certain differences you should be aware of that will help you choose a VM or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bala Priya C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Python by Thinking in Types]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-python-by-thinking-in-types/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-python-by-thinking-in-types/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T15:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you check Instagram today or watch YouTube? Well, you used a Python-based application! Python is one of the most popular programming languages. We just published a new Python course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. We have quite a few Python courses on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel so you may]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Shoelace, a Framework-Independent Component-Based UX Library]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373703</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/shoelace-component-frameowrk-introduction/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T13:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a post about Shoelace, a component library by Cory LaViska, but with a twist. It defines all your standard UX components: tabs, modals, accordions, auto-completes, and much, much more. They look beautiful out of the …
Introducing Shoelace, a Framework-Independent Component-Based UX Library originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Modal with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-modal-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-modal-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T23:49:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's probably happened to you before: you unintentionally attempted to perform an action on a webpage, but luckily got a pop-up window asking you to confirm your decision. This pop-up window is called a modal. It's a web page element that pops up and displays in front of other page]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Eke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is rem in CSS? rem Unit Font Size, Padding, Height, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-rem-in-css-rem-unit-font-size-padding-height-and-more/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-rem-in-css-rem-unit-font-size-padding-height-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T22:57:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rem measurement unit is a relative unit that you can use for length values in CSS. I will explain what this unit is, and how it is different from other units in this article. In my previous article, I explained the two categories of units in CSS: Absolute and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Your Jupyter Notebook into a User-Friendly Web App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-web-app-with-flask/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-web-app-with-flask/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T22:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being able to build predictive models is a superpower – but you can't make much of these models if users can't use them.  In this article, we will go through the process of building and deploying a machine learning web app using Flask and PythonAnywhere.  Flask is a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tooba Jamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use map(), filter(), and reduce() in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/map-filter-reduce-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/map-filter-reduce-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T22:06:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to learn React, it's important to get a fair understanding of some core JavaScript concepts first.  So if that's what you're doing, first of all – great job! You have made a wise decision by not starting directly with React.  Second, React builds on key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bhavesh Rawat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy a React Router App to Netlify and Fix the "Page Not Found" Error]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-a-routed-react-app-to-netlify/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-a-routed-react-app-to-netlify/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T17:16:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever experienced a “PAGE NOT FOUND” error when trying to access or refresh an application that uses React Router? Don't worry, you're not alone. In this article, you will learn how to deploy a React application that uses react-router without any problems. The Problem with Deploying react-router Apps]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delightful UI Animations With Shared Element Transitions API (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/ui-animations-shared-element-transitions-api-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/ui-animations-shared-element-transitions-api-part1/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shared Element Transitions API is a game-changing feature that will enable us to create impressive and elaborate UI animations easily. In this article, Adrian Bece will explore its incredible potential by building four real-life examples from scratch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeError: only size-1 arrays can be converted to Python scalars]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fix-typeerror-only-size-1-arrays-can-be-converted-to-python-scalars/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fix-typeerror-only-size-1-arrays-can-be-converted-to-python-scalars/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T21:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, you can use the numpy library when working with arrays and certain math concepts like matrices and linear algebra.  But like every other aspect of learning and working with a programming language, errors are unavoidable.  In this article, you'll learn how to fix the "TypeError: only]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Absolute and Relative Units in CSS? Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/absolute-and-relative-css-units/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/absolute-and-relative-css-units/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T21:19:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In CSS, we categorize measurement units as either absolute or relative units. In this article, I'll explain what these categories are with examples of units that fall under each of them. CSS Measurement Units You can use different measurement units in CSS. You use these units with length or size]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rename a File in Linux – Bash Terminal Command]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rename-file-linux-bash-command/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rename-file-linux-bash-command/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T15:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Renaming files is a very common operation whether you are using the command line or the GUI.  Compared to the GUI (or Graphical User Interface), the CLI is especially powerful. This is in part because you can rename files in bulk or even schedule the scripts to rename files]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DNS Server Not Responding – How to Fix the Error in Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fix-dns-server-not-responding-error-windows-10/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fix-dns-server-not-responding-error-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T15:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think it's safe to say that the vast majority of professionals depend on the internet these days.  So being denied access to the internet when you are trying to mine nuggets of valuable information from your go-to web sites can be quite an ordeal. Especially when you are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gavin Lon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the DOM? A Behind-the-Scenes Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-dom-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-dom-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T14:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding how the DOM and events work in JavaScript is key if you want to be an effective front end developer. In this article, you'll learn what the DOM is and how it works. What is the DOM? DOM stands for Document Object Model. It's the interface between JavaScript and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[October Vibes For Your Desktop (2022 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How about a little inspiration boost? Well, we might have something for you: desktop wallpapers created with love by artists and designers from across the globe. They are available in versions with and without a calendar for October and can be downloaded for free. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With WordPress Block Development]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373732</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/getting-started-with-wordpress-block-development/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T13:04:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s acknowledge that developing for WordPress is weird right now. Whether you’re new to WordPress or have worked with it for eons, the introduction of “Full-Site Editing” (FSE) features, including the Block Editor (WordPress 5.0) and the Site Editor (WordPress …
Getting Started With WordPress Block Development originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arjun Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unconscious Biases That Get In The Way Of Inclusive Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/unconscious-biases-inclusive-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/unconscious-biases-inclusive-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout the research and design processes, our unconscious biases are the greatest risk to delivering inclusive experiences. From who we include and exclude in our research to how we plan and conduct research to how we analyze findings, it’s crucial that we understand how our unacknowledged biases can perpetuate systems of exclusion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Trina Moore Pervall)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Swap Two Array Elements in JavaScript – Switch Elements in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/swap-two-array-elements-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/swap-two-array-elements-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T20:15:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with arrays, there are times when you need to swap two elements in an array in JavaScript. Maybe you're working on an algorithm question such as the bubble sort algorithm where you need to compare two values and then swap them if your condition is true. Aside]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Authentication vs Authorization – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/whats-the-difference-between-authentication-and-authorisation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/whats-the-difference-between-authentication-and-authorisation/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T17:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're starting out in web development, you'll likely hear the terms authentication and authorization all the time. And it doesn't help that they're both usually abbreviated 'auth', so it's very easy to get the two confused. In this article, you will learn:  * The differences between authentication and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Weatherston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bubble Sort – Algorithm in Java, C++, Python with Example Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/bubble-sort-algorithm-in-java-cpp-python-with-example-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/bubble-sort-algorithm-in-java-cpp-python-with-example-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T17:34:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bubble sort is a type of sorting algorithm you can use to arrange a set of values in ascending order. If you want, you can also implement bubble sort to sort the values in descending order. A real-world example of a bubble sort algorithm is how the contact list on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Selectors – Cheat Sheet for Class, Name, Child Selector List]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-selectors-cheat-sheet-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-selectors-cheat-sheet-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T15:22:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS selectors target and select the HTML elements you want to style. Specifically, CSS selectors allow you to select multiple elements at once. They are helpful when you want to apply the same styles to more than one HTML element, because you will not repeat yourself by writing the same]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Low-Code Ecommerce App with Stripe, Postgres, & REST API Backend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-low-code-ecommerce-app-with-stripe-postgres-rest-api-backend/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-low-code-ecommerce-app-with-stripe-postgres-rest-api-backend/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T13:43:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building apps can be much quicker with low-code tools. A low-code platform can give you pre-built UI components packed with functionality like tables, buttons, and text inputs. This allows you to skip the frontend templates and build your own quickly. We just published a tutorial on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Your Security Strategy (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/ten-principles-consider-building-security-strategy-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/ten-principles-consider-building-security-strategy-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Wix security experts share ten “security by design” principles that emerged from their work in keeping the Wix platform secure. If you’re a developer, these tried-and-true principles can help you build your own secure applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Wix Security Team)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parameters vs Arguments in JavaScript – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-the-difference-between-parameters-and-arguments-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-the-difference-between-parameters-and-arguments-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T21:18:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is one of the most popular programming languages out there for web development. The dynamic values passed in a JavaScript function can change when the function gets called in another location in the code. The keywords we use to name these data are parameters and arguments, but some developers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Segun Ajibola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code a 2D Game Using JavaScript, HTML, and CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-a-2d-game-using-javascript-html-and-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-a-2d-game-using-javascript-html-and-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T19:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript can be a surprisingly good programming language to use for creating 2D games. Especially games you want to be playable on almost any device.  We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to code a 2D game using JavaScript, HTML, CSS,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GIFs Without the .gif: The Most Performant Image and Video Options Right Now]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373484</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/gifs-without-the-gif-the-most-performant-image-and-video-options-right-now/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T13:09:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So you want an auto-playing looping video without sound? In popular vernacular this is the very meaning of the word GIF. The word has stuck around but the image format itself is ancient and obsolete. Twitter, for example, has …
GIFs Without the .gif: The Most Performant Image and Video Options Right Now originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phone Numbers For Web Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/phone-numbers-web-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/phone-numbers-web-designers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The customer journey is not limited to a website alone. Simply by combining the world of website design and telephony, far better results can be obtained for your organization. And thanks to the similarities and mutual benefits, it is an easy step to take.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Onno Westra)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Test Your Express.js and Mongoose Apps with Jest and SuperTest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-test-in-express-and-mongoose-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-test-in-express-and-mongoose-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T23:26:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Testing is a vital part of software development. The sooner you start testing, the better.  In this article, I'll show you how to write tests for your NodeJs/ExpressJS and MongoDB/Mongoose applications with Jest and Supertest. Let's get started First let's set up a demo Express.js app. Let's say we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rakesh Potnuru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js Server-Side JavaScript – What is Node Used For?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/node-js-server-side-javascript-what-is-node-used-for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/node-js-server-side-javascript-what-is-node-used-for/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T21:34:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release of Node.js in 2009 by Ryan Dahl increased the scope of what developers could do with JavaScript. Prior to that, you could only use JavaScript on the client side (the browser) or frontend of web applications. With Node.js, developers can create server side applications, command line tools, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Command Line Interface – for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-cli-beginner-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-cli-beginner-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T21:11:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a lot to learn when you're getting into tech. But fortunately there are some skills that you can use across different programming languages, operating systems, and tools.  And knowing how to use the command line interface (also known as the command prompt or terminal, depending on your operating]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maybell Obadoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Debug Your Python Code with the Python Debugger (pdb)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/debugging-in-python-using-pdb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/debugging-in-python-using-pdb/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T17:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging tools are at the heart of any programming language. And as a developer, it's hard to make progress and write clean code unless you know your way around these tools. This article will help you get acquainted with one such tool: The Python Debugger (pdb) [https://docs.python.org/3/library/pdb.html#:~:text=The%20module%20pdb%20defines%20an,context%20of%20any%20stack%20frame] Note that this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jagruti Tiwari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Vertical Scrolling in React Using react-router-hash-link]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-vertical-scrolling-in-react-using-react-router-hash-link/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-vertical-scrolling-in-react-using-react-router-hash-link/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T17:42:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smooth scrolling is a feature that makes webpages more usable and allows for a better user scrolling experience in most browsers. Implementing a smooth page scroll while using react-router-dom has been a problem in React.js. So this article, you are going to learn how to implement smooth vertical scrolling using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Information Systems? Definition for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-information-systems-definition-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-information-systems-definition-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T16:43:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have heard the term "information systems" as a type of degree some people get from a college or university. Or maybe you've heard it as a general term used to describe information and communication systems in general. Information systems are more than a degree or a general term.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five Data-Loading Patterns To Boost Web Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/data-loading-patterns-improve-frontend-performance/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/data-loading-patterns-improve-frontend-performance/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You don’t need a framework for everything, but if you use one, this article will help you use it in the most performant way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Agustinus Theodorus)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>