<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-06-21T01:01:24.950Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Generative AI Handbook – How GenAI is Impacting Business and Innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/generative-ai-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/generative-ai-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T17:43:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The emergence of Generative Artificial Intelligence (GenAI) is both shaping the future of innovation management and revolutionizing it. This handbook delves into the groundbreaking research presented in "Generative Artificial Intelligence in Innovation Management: A Preview of Future Research Developments" by Marcello Mariani and Yogesh K. Dwivedi (2024) [https://ideas.repec.org/a/eee/jbrese/v175y2024ics0148296324000468.html]. It's a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Technical Writer – A Guide for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-technical-writer-guide-for-devs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-technical-writer-guide-for-devs/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:54:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being a top-notch developer was my dream – until I realized I could combine my passion for writing with my technical knowledge to earn a living. That's right: I'm talking about becoming a technical writer. And if you're a developer, you may be in a good position to get into]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tooba Jamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn to Create a 3D RPG Game with Godot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-create-a-3d-rpg-game-with-godot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-create-a-3d-rpg-game-with-godot/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:20:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Godot is an open-source game engine that is perfect for creating both 2D and 3D games. It is known for its user-friendly interface, robust features, and active community support. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Accessibility in Web Development? Best Practices for Web Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-practices-for-accessibility-in-web-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-practices-for-accessibility-in-web-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T11:33:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone should be able to use technology, regardless of their abilities or disabilities. An accessible website or platform attracts a broader audience and has a high chance of achieving user retention. This article will discuss the importance of accessibility, best practices for accessibility in frontend web development, and their implementations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria (Burah) Poromon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniting Web And Native Apps With 4 Unknown JavaScript APIs]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/uniting-web-native-apps-unknown-javascript-apis/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/uniting-web-native-apps-unknown-javascript-apis/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you heard of the Screen Orientation API? What about the Device Orientation API, Vibration API, or the Contact Picker API? Juan Diego Rodriguez is interested in these under-the-radar web features and discusses how they can be used to create more usable and robust progressive web apps if and when they gain broader support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Time To Live in Event-Driven Architecture in AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-time-to-live-in-event-driven-architecture/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-time-to-live-in-event-driven-architecture/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T18:08:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Distributed systems generally involve the storage and exchange of huge amounts of data. Not all data is created the same, and some of it can even expire – by design.  As the Buddha said, "All conditioned things are impermanent." In this article, we'll look at how the concept of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anant Chowdhary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does Python's For-Else Loop Construct Work?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/for-else-loop-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/for-else-loop-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T13:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python supports the for-else loop construct that is lesser known but super helpful. If you’ve programmed in Python, you may have used the for loop to iterate over items in iterables such as lists. But for some use cases, using the for loop in conjunction with the else clause can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bala Priya C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[T-Shaped vs. V-Shaped Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/t-shaped-vs-v-shaped-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/t-shaped-vs-v-shaped-designers/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Job openings typically cast a very restrictive frame for candidates, with long lists of expectations and requirements. But what if this narrow focus can overlook the value of “V”-shaped designers who excel by crossing boundaries, connecting dots, and innovating beyond rigid boxes?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Arrays in Practice: How to Rebuild the Football Team Cards Project with PHP and MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/php-arrays-how-to-rebuild-the-football-team-cards-with-php-and-mongodb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/php-arrays-how-to-rebuild-the-football-team-cards-with-php-and-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T20:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the second part of my PHP array handbook. You can find the first part here [/news/php-array-handbook/], where I cover array basics. In the first part, you learned about arrays, how to create arrays, array functions, and how to loop through arrays. This second part will teach you how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Decorators in Python? Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/decorators-in-python-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/decorators-in-python-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T18:53:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn about Python decorators: what they are, how they work, and when to use them.  But before diving into decorators, it's helpful to understand two foundational concepts in Python: first-class functions and closures. First-Class Functions in Python First-class functions mean that functions in Python]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samyak Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Non-Technical Introduction to Generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-non-technical-introduction-to-generative-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-non-technical-introduction-to-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T15:39:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to learn about the concepts around generative AI without getting bogged down with the technical details, we have a great course for you. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is a non-technical intro to g...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Intelligent Apps with Mistral AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/building-intelligent-apps-with-mistral-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/building-intelligent-apps-with-mistral-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T15:11:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open source LLMs can help you create intelligent apps without having to pay for each API call. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use the open source models from Mistral AI to create intellig...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Trunk Based Development? A Different Approach to the Software Development Lifecycle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-trunk-based-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-trunk-based-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T12:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC) is different at every company. The version control system used, peer review process, code review process, design review process, how you do CI, automated testing, and manual testing – all vary greatly depending on where you work. How a company plans, writes, builds, reviews, deploys,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kealan Parr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Masonry Layout Using HTML and CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-mansory-layout-using-html-and-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-mansory-layout-using-html-and-css/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T12:22:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A masonry layout is a grid-based design where items are arranged in a way that minimizes vertical gaps between them.  an example of a masonry layoutUnlike traditional grids with fixed row heights, masonry layouts adjust the positioning of items dynamically based on their content height, creating a visually appealing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fanny Nyayic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve Your Digital Security and Privacy – Best Practices for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-your-digital-security-and-privacy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-your-digital-security-and-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T12:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, there are many different types of attacks that can jeopardize your digital security and privacy. So it’s a good idea to stay up-to-date with best practices to keep you safe online.  But it can be hard to understand exactly how to do this. So I built this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Privacy Tipster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Host Static Sites on Azure Static Web Apps for Free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-host-static-sites-on-azure-static-web-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-host-static-sites-on-azure-static-web-apps/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T10:59:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will show you how you can host your React/Next.js app or any static web app on Azure Static Web Apps.  I will be showing you both ways of doing it – through the GUI and with the CLI. I assume you already have built a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shrijal Acharya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide to Object-Oriented Programming Principles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-guide-to-object-oriented-programming-principles/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-guide-to-object-oriented-programming-principles/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T09:13:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A programming language is generally classified based on its support for one or more paradigms. Object-oriented programming is one such paradigm, where the code is organized as objects. It is used to develop desktop and mobile applications or more complex web or enterprise applications. Using object-oriented programming, you can build]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anjan Baradwaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enhance Embedded Links in React with Microlink]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-enhance-embedded-links-in-react-with-microlinks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-enhance-embedded-links-in-react-with-microlinks/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T02:56:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The web has evolved from rigid color coding and 2D rendering to an era of complex, aesthetically pleasing animations and 3D rendering options. Additionally, there have been integrations with new technologies, such as virtual reality tools and frameworks, to make the user experience worthwhile. In this article, we'll optimize]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oluwatobi Joshua</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Auto Scaling and Load Balancing Work in Software Architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/auto-scaling-and-load-balancing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/auto-scaling-and-load-balancing/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T18:52:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While auto scaling and load balancing are two separate techniques in software architecture management, they are often implemented simultaneously. In the software architecture wild, one rarely exists without the other, as they complement each other to handle unpredictable changes in demand. This article will explain how auto scaling and load]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write QA Documentation That Will Actually Work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-qa-documentation-that-will-actually-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-qa-documentation-that-will-actually-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T18:29:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine developing a complex software product without taking any action to protect against errors. Human error and unexpected code combinations can cause a wide range of defects. This is where quality assurance (QA) documentation comes in.  Usually, a QA tester creates a report after discovering a bug. The next]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oleg Romanyuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Handle KeyErrors in Python – with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-keyerror-exceptions-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-keyerror-exceptions-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T18:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with dictionaries in Python, you’d often run into KeyError  exceptions. Dictionaries are built-in data structures of key value pairs. So you can look up a value—in constant time—using the corresponding key like so: dict[key] returns  value. But what if the key doesn't exist in the dictionary?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bala Priya C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Email Newsletters For Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/useful-email-newsletters-for-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/useful-email-newsletters-for-designers/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you want to take your user research skills to the next level, get better at UX writing, or stay up-to-date on the latest design trends, a newsletter is the perfect opportunity to get the best of the best resources delivered straight to your inbox on a regular basis. In this post, we highlight some design newsletters that you might want to consider subscribing to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Black-Scholes Equation Works – Explained with Python Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-the-black-scholes-equation-works-python-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-the-black-scholes-equation-works-python-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T16:42:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[$$\frac{\partial V}{\partial t} + \frac{1}{2}\sigma^2 S^2 \frac{\partial^2 V}{\partial S^2} = rV - r S \frac{\partial V}{\partial S}$$  Black-Scholes Equation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Frameworks vs Laravel – Which Should You Choose for Web Development?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-frameworks-vs-laravel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-frameworks-vs-laravel/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T14:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a long time, developers in the JavaScript ecosystem have tried to launch Laravel-like frameworks for JavaScript. We've seen Blitz for NextJS, Adonis for NodeJS, RedwoodJS, and more. All these frameworks tried to build a Laravel for JavaScript. But none of them were really successful. Why? We'll figure it out]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Afan Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Multi-Page Animations Using Framer Motion & React-Router-Dom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-multi-page-animations-using-framer-motion-and-react-router-dom/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-multi-page-animations-using-framer-motion-and-react-router-dom/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T05:57:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animations are what make plain websites turn into exciting and unforgettable experiences. They give your website a bit of personality and uniqueness and leave the visitor admiring the overall aesthetic. It's a no-brainer that humans love beautiful things. We all love products that look easy on the eyes.  In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okosa Leonard Onyekachukwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Attention Mechanisms in Deep Learning?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-attention-mechanisms-in-deep-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-attention-mechanisms-in-deep-learning/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T05:46:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attention mechanism is a fundamental invention in artificial intelligence and machine learning, redefining the capabilities of deep learning models. This mechanism, inspired by the human mental process of selective focus, has emerged as a pillar in a variety of applications, accelerating developments in natural language processing, computer vision, and beyond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oyedele Tioluwani Taiwo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lambda Functions in Python – How to Use Lambdas with Map, Filter, and Reduce]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/lambda-functions-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/lambda-functions-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T14:44:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we will explore the various aspects of lambda functions in Python, including their syntax, use cases, and limitations.  By understanding how to effectively utilize lambda functions, you can write more concise and efficient Python code. This will enhance your programming skills and make your codebase cleaner]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samyak Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are CSS Container Style Queries Good For?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/what-are-css-container-style-queries-good-for/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/what-are-css-container-style-queries-good-for/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are these CSS Container Style Queries, and why should you use them? Juan Diego Rodríguez delves deeply into style queries, and not at the syntax level, but at what exactly they are solving and what sort of use cases you would find yourselves reaching for them in your work if and when they gain browser support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quincy Interviews Colby Fayock: Dev, Designer, Male Model, Prolific fCC Contributor [Podcast #128]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/quincy-interviews-colby-fayock-dev-designer-male-model-prolific-fcc-contributor-podcast-128/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/quincy-interviews-colby-fayock-dev-designer-male-model-prolific-fcc-contributor-podcast-128/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T23:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Colby Fayock. He's a Software Engineer and prolific teacher who has created 68 tutorials for freeCodeCamp, and more than 100 videos on his YouTube – all freely available. We talk about: Colby's earl...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2-Page Login Pattern, And How To Fix It]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/2-page-login-pattern-how-fix-it/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/2-page-login-pattern-how-fix-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2-page login pattern is becoming pervasive. Here are the reasons behind this design choice and alternative solutions to create a more efficient and user-friendly authentication experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Linux Crash Course with Labs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-linux-crash-course-with-labs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-linux-crash-course-with-labs/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T13:36:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Linux is important because it powers the majority of the world's servers, from web hosting to cloud infrastructure. Its open-source nature ensures that it remains versatile, secure, and continually updated by a global community of developers...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Viewing Patterns in Your Website Designs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-viewing-patterns-in-your-website-design/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-viewing-patterns-in-your-website-design/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T14:33:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While going through a website or an application, people tend to take in the information displayed differently. You may notice that sometimes a person may miss information that others wouldn't miss. This may have happened to you before, as well. This is because everyone has a particular way they process]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Three.js By Building Five Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-threejs-by-building-five-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-threejs-by-building-five-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T13:33:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three.js is a powerful JavaScript library that simplifies the process of creating 3D graphics in the browser. We just released a video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Three.js by guiding you through build...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Scent Of UX: The Unrealized Potential Of Olfactory Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/scent-ux-unrealized-potential-olfactory-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/scent-ux-unrealized-potential-olfactory-design/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kristian Mikhel covers various practical applications of scents in product experience, from immersive entertainment to healing spaces and medical appliances, and how designers can drive innovation across spheres and disciplines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kristian Mikhel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next-Gen Large Language Models: The Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/retrieval-augmented-generation-rag-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/retrieval-augmented-generation-rag-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T21:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) signifies a transformative advancement in large language models (LLMs). It combines the generative prowess of transformer architectures with dynamic information retrieval.  This integration allows LLMs to access and incorporate relevant external knowledge during text generation, resulting in outputs that are more accurate, contextual, and factually]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Hack Your Google Lighthouse Scores In 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/how-hack-google-lighthouse-scores-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/how-hack-google-lighthouse-scores-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do perfect Lighthouse scores mean the performance of your website is perfect? As it turns out, Lighthouse is influenced by a number of things that can be manipulated and bent to make sites seem more performant than they really are, as Salma Alam-Naylor demonstrates in several experiments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Salma Alam-Naylor)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn High-Level System Design by Building a YouTube Clone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-high-level-system-design-by-building-a-youtube-clone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-high-level-system-design-by-building-a-youtube-clone/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T16:33:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High-Level System Design involves creating a blueprint for complex systems, focusing on architecture, component interactions, and scalability. It addresses how different parts of a system communicate, manage data, and handle user requests efficiently...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Python for Data Science – Hands-on Projects with EDA, AB Testing & Business Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-python-for-data-science-hands-on-projects-with-eda-ab-testing-business-intelligence/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-python-for-data-science-hands-on-projects-with-eda-ab-testing-business-intelligence/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T15:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data science skills are increasingly in-demand. We just published a hands-son data science with Python course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This comprehensive, 5.5+ hour course is designed to provide aspiring data scientists with essential...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix Common Python Installation Errors on macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fix-python-installation-errors-on-mac/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fix-python-installation-errors-on-mac/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T22:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python's popularity keeps growing as more developers adopt it for data science and machine learning, although it is already among the most popular programming languages.  I recently wrote an article for freeCodeCamp titled "How to Install Python on a Mac [/news/how-to-install-python-on-a-mac/]", which provides a clear guide to installing Python]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kehoe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Unit Tests in Python – with Example Test Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/unit-testing-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/unit-testing-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T16:33:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unit testing is a software testing technique in which individual components or units of a software application are tested independently from the rest of the application.  In software development, it's beneficial to break your application into small, isolated units. This approach allows you to write independent tests to check]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damilola Oladele</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=378111</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T16:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The main idea of CSS Container Queries is to register an element as a “container” and apply styles to other elements when the container element meets certain conditions. 
CSS Container Queries originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Notice Blocks in Markdown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-notice-blocks-in-markdown/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-notice-blocks-in-markdown/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T09:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Markdown is a very popular lightweight markup language. It is used for writing documentation and even for creating a complete website. Therefore, almost all of us frequently use this markup language every once in a while. However, there are some limitations to this language. In some cases, we can not]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Outsmart AI as a Developer [Dr. Chuck Interview #127]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-outsmart-ai-as-a-developer-dr-chuck-interview-127/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-outsmart-ai-as-a-developer-dr-chuck-interview-127/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T00:54:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews Dr. Chuck. He's a software engineer and Computer Science professor at University of Michigan, which has one of the top-ranked CS programs in the world. Dr. Charles "...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use WeakMap and WeakSet in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/weakmap-and-weakset-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/weakmap-and-weakset-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T16:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript offers a number of tools for organizing and managing data. And while developers often use widely recognized tools like Maps and Sets, they may often overlook certain other valuable resources.  For example, are you familiar with WeakMap and WeakSet? They're special tools in JavaScript that help store and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful CSS Tips And Techniques]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/css-tips-and-techniques/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/css-tips-and-techniques/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The times for CSS have probably never been more exciting than today. In this quick read, we’ve got some useful CSS tips and techniques for you that you can apply to your work right away. Let’s dive deeper into self-modifying CSS variables, hanging punctuation, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Real-Time Chat App With Go, Fiber and HTMX]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/real-time-chat-with-go-fiber-htmx/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/real-time-chat-with-go-fiber-htmx/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T18:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll build a simple real-time chat app using Go, Fiber and HTMX.  You will learn how to leverage the versatility of Fiber by making use of a WebSocket. You'll also learn how to create a reactive frontend without the use of JavaScript. Prerequisites  * A]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Akinwumi Iyanuoluwa Ayomiposi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master the Azure DevOps Engineer Expert Certification (AZ-400)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-the-azure-devops-engineer-expert-certification-az-400/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-the-azure-devops-engineer-expert-certification-az-400/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T14:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Azure DevOps Engineer Expert Certification (AZ-400) is for professionals who aim to demonstrate their expertise in integrating people, processes, and technologies to continuously deliver valuable products and services. It’s ideal for those who ar...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How to Build a Decentralized File Storage System with Go]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-how-to-build-a-decentralized-file-storage-system-with-go/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-how-to-build-a-decentralized-file-storage-system-with-go/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T21:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just posted a 10-hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build a decentralized, fully distributed, content-addressable file storage system using Go. This course is perfect for those interested in system desig...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Presenting UX Research And Design To Stakeholders: The Power Of Persuasion]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/presenting-ux-research-design-stakeholders/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/presenting-ux-research-design-stakeholders/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s more to achieving good UX than research and design. We need to effectively communicate our ideas to gain buy-in from key stakeholders. Victor covers how UX practitioners can harness the power of persuasion and other tactics from the field of communication when presenting research findings and design concepts to key stakeholders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Yocco)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript this Keyword Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-this-keyword-explained-with-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-this-keyword-explained-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T14:58:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All leading web browsers support JavaScript, a popular and versatile programming language. The this keyword is a very important concept to know in JavaScript. The this keyword is a reference to an object, but the object varies based on where and how it is called. In this article, you'll learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kamaldeen Lawal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Virtual DOM in React?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-the-virtual-dom-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-the-virtual-dom-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T14:51:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As web applications become more complex, managing updates to the user interface becomes a challenging task. This is where the Virtual DOM (Document Object Model) comes into play – particularly in React, the leading JavaScript library for building user interfaces. The virtual DOM is a lightweight copy of the real]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Go in Spanish – Golang Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-go-in-spanish-golang-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-go-in-spanish-golang-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T12:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Go is a powerful programming language that is quickly growing in popularity. It's easy to learn and works great for building powerful applications. Whether you're new to coding or already know other programming languages, Go is a great choice for exp...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Guide to Linear Algebra in Data Science and AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linear-algebra-roadmap/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linear-algebra-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T20:22:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> "In God we trust; all others bring data." – W. Edwards Deming This famous quote from Edwards Deming perfectly captures the essence of modern Data Science and AI.  Data is the lifeblood of Data Science and AI fields – Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Generative AI and much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tatev Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Coding Challenges For Beginner Developers – Code and Explanations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-coding-challenges-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-coding-challenges-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T20:18:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Python can be challenging, especially if you're not actually writing enough code. As a beginner, you may go through lessons and tutorials without practicing on your own – and this makes it harder to learn the language. The truth is, you cannot truly learn programming without writing code. It]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhilekh Gautam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a YouTube Clone with Flutter, Firebase, and Riverpod]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-youtube-clone-with-flutter-firebase-and-riverpod/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-youtube-clone-with-flutter-firebase-and-riverpod/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T19:07:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just released a new course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build a full stack application. This beginner-friendly course will guide you through the process of creating a fully functional YouTube clone app, utiliz...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn to Code REST APIs using Next.js 14]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-code-rest-apis-using-nextjs-14/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-code-rest-apis-using-nextjs-14/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T19:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just posted a new course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is designed to help you master the creation of RESTful APIs using Next.js 14, a popular React framework. Umair Jameel developed this course. Next.js is a framework built on top ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applied Data Science with Python – Business Intelligence for Developers [Full Book]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/applied-data-science-with-python-book/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/applied-data-science-with-python-book/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T17:14:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the high-stakes game of modern business, data isn't just an asset – it's the power you need to outpace your competition. But as a developer, you know that turning raw data into actionable insights can be a frustrating battle. Imagine having the power to effortlessly transform raw data into]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Success: Key Insights And Practical Takeaways]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/scaling-success-key-insights-pratical-takeaways/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/scaling-success-key-insights-pratical-takeaways/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The web is still a young platform, and we’re only now beginning to recognize what “success” looks like for large projects. In his recent Smashing book, [Success at Scale](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/printed-books/success-at-scale/), Addy Osmani presents practical case studies featuring the web’s most renowned companies and their efforts to make big changes to existing apps and sites. In this article, Addy shows some of the key insights he has learned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build and Deploy a Smart Contract With Rust and the Gear Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-deploy-smart-contract-rust-gear-protocol/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-deploy-smart-contract-rust-gear-protocol/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T10:36:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart contracts are like digital agreements that run on blockchain technology, making transactions automatic and secure. While many people use Ethereum and Solidity to create these contracts, there are other options that can be just as powerful.  One great combination is using Rust with the Gear Protocol. In this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rocky Essel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Rating Component with the React Compound Component Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-rating-component-with-the-react-compound-component-pattern/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-rating-component-with-the-react-compound-component-pattern/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T22:03:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever watched a captivating movie or used a fantastic product and wanted to share your experience? In today's world, feedback is critical, and ratings are like currency.  Rating systems are everywhere, from the classic star ratings on movie review websites to the ubiquitous thumbs up/down on streaming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose the Right IaC Tool – AWS CDK, CloudFormation, and Terraform Compared]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/comparing-iac-tools-aws-cdk-cloudformation-terraform/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/comparing-iac-tools-aws-cdk-cloudformation-terraform/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:27:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infrastructure as Code (IaC) has become a cornerstone of modern cloud resource management. It enables developers and engineers to manage their cloud resources with the same level of control and precision as application code.  When you're working with AWS, among the tools at the forefront of utilizing IaC are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ifeanyi Otuonye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Quickly Add Auth to your Flutter Apps with Supabase Auth UI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/add-auth-to-flutter-apps-with-supabase-auth-ui/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/add-auth-to-flutter-apps-with-supabase-auth-ui/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T19:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to use Supabase's auth package [https://pub.dev/packages/supabase_auth_ui] to quickly and efficiently add authentication functionality to your Flutter apps. We will go through the entire process, from setting up a Flutter project to configuring Email/Password, OAuth, and Magic link flows. In the end, you'll have]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fatuma Abdullahi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Length Units]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375815</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-length-units/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T19:22:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A comprehensive guide covering nine types of lengths that CSS uses to size elements in terms of dimensions, space, time, and even sound.
CSS Length Units originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use AI to Automate Unit Testing with TestGen-LLM and Cover-Agent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automated-unit-testing-with-testgen-llm-and-cover-agent/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automated-unit-testing-with-testgen-llm-and-cover-agent/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T14:45:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's important to write clear and efficient unit tests that actually work during the software development process. Unit tests separate out individual code elements and confirm that they work as intended.  Effective unit tests not only catch errors but also help you be confident that your code can be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwadamisi Samuel Praise</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ice Cream Ahead (June 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s kick off June with some fresh inspiration! Artists and designers from across the globe once again tickled their creativity to celebrate the beginning of the new month with a collection of beautiful and unique wallpaper calendars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Suz Hinton went from Dev to White Hat Hacker [Podcast #126]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-suz-hinton-went-from-dev-to-white-hat-hacker-podcast-126/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-suz-hinton-went-from-dev-to-white-hat-hacker-podcast-126/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T15:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews Suz Hinton. She's a software engineer, security researcher, and one of the first ever people to live-stream her coding on Twitch. We talk about: How Suz started her...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Prototypal Inheritance in JavaScript? Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-prototypal-inheritance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-prototypal-inheritance/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T08:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prototypal inheritance can feel like a complex concept shrouded in technical jargon. But fear not! This guide will break it down using clear, relatable examples that go beyond the typical textbook explanations.  We'll ditch the confusing terms and focus on real-world scenarios that you can easily understand. By the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asoluka Tochukwu Austin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the Basics of Go by Building a Full Stack Web App with React and Go]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-basics-of-go-by-building-a-full-stack-web-app-with-react-and-go/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-basics-of-go-by-building-a-full-stack-web-app-with-react-and-go/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T15:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Go can work great on the backend for a React project. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org channel that will leach you how to build a full stack web app with React and Go. This comprehensive course is designed to teach you the fundamenta...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Complete C Programming Course from Dr. Chuck]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-c-programming-course-from-dr-chuck/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-c-programming-course-from-dr-chuck/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T15:21:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just released a comprehensive C course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This course, developed by Dr. Charles Severance (aka Dr. Chuck), is designed to help you understand computer architecture and low-level programming using the classic C...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Praise Of The Basics]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/in-praise-of-the-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/in-praise-of-the-basics/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What does it mean to learn the “basics”, or fundamentals, of front-end web development? Is starting with HTML and CSS still the best entry point to learn how to make websites and apps when we have a seemingly endless supply of frameworks? Geoff Graham thinks so and discusses why you might consider going “back to basics” to start or move forward in your career.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Context API Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-context-api-explained-with-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-context-api-explained-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T08:13:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing state has always been a critical aspect of making web applications with React. The most basic way to do this is prop drilling. In prop drilling, you pass props around from the parent component to other components that need it, no matter how deeply nested they are. The problem]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do Numerical Conversions Work in Computer Systems? Explained With Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-numerical-conversions-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-numerical-conversions-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T19:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computers perform complex calculations when carrying out their assigned tasks. At the very core, the calculations boil down to operations like comparisons, assignments, and addition. Have you ever wondered how they are performed under the hood and wh...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decision Trees For UI Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/decision-trees-ui-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/decision-trees-ui-components/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine finally resolving never-ending discussions about UI decisions for good. Here are some practical examples of decision trees for UI components and how to use them effectively. An upcoming part of [Smart Interface Design Patterns](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust Tutorial – Learn Advanced Iterators & Pattern Matching by Building a JSON Parser]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rust-tutorial-build-a-json-parser/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rust-tutorial-build-a-json-parser/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T10:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Iterators and match patterns are two of the most used language features in Rust. If you have written any real world application, big or small, chances are that you've already used these, whether knowingly or unknowingly. In this tutorial, I aim to help you understand how they actually work, the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshul Sanghi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linear Algebra Crash Course - Mathematics for Machine Learning and Generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linear-algebra-crash-course-mathematics-for-machine-learning-and-generative-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linear-algebra-crash-course-mathematics-for-machine-learning-and-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T20:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linear algebra is a useful skill for professionals in data science, machine learning, and AI. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you linear algebra. This crash course spans just over 6 hours and is a great...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an EKS Cluster Across AWS Local Zones using the AWS CDK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-eks-cluster-using-aws-local-zones-with-aws-cdk/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-eks-cluster-using-aws-local-zones-with-aws-cdk/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T14:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Local Zones are a new type of infrastructure that enables you to build and run applications closer to end-users, providing low latency and improved performance.  They are designed to provide the same high availability and reliability as an AWS Region, but with the added benefit of low-latency connections]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gursimar Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linear vs Logistic Regression:  How to Choose the Right Regression Model for Your Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linear-regression-vs-logistic-regression/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linear-regression-vs-logistic-regression/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T13:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regression models identify trends in a dataset and predict outcomes based on the trends they have analyzed and identified.  Linear and Logistic Regression are two types of regression models that are similar but carry out their functions in distinct ways. They're also two fundamental techniques in machine learning that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwadamisi Samuel Praise</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React 19 – New Hooks Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-19-new-hooks-explained-with-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-19-new-hooks-explained-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T12:56:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi fellow readers! Web Development is a constantly evolving landscape. The whole ecosystem consists of different libraries and technologies. React is one of the most widely used libraries in web development.  There are small releases every now and then. However, this year, the React team has made a significant]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Era Of Platform Primitives Is Finally Here]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/netlify-platform-primitives/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/netlify-platform-primitives/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Application frameworks have built whole ecosystems on top of them. Let’s take a closer look at serverless platforms such as Netlify’s [Platform Primitives](https://www.netlify.com/platform/primitives) and explore how they can increase our productivity with a serverless fullstack experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide to the Node.js Event Loop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-guide-to-the-node-js-event-loop/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-guide-to-the-node-js-event-loop/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T07:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js is an open-source JavaScript runtime environment that allows you to run JavaScript outside the browser. Although Node.js is single-threaded, it has an event loop that makes it multi-threaded. The Node.js event loop is a crucial mechanism in Node.js that makes Node.js programs run concurrently and asynchronously. Mastering the Node.js]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Musab Habeeb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manipulate Strings in JavaScript – With Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manipulate-strings-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manipulate-strings-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T21:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[String manipulation is a common task for programmers, whether it is extracting information from the string, converting letter cases, joining strings, or trimming extra white spaces. This tutorial covers various methods and techniques for manipulating strings using JavaScript, offering you a comprehensive guide on how to work with strings in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Hu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build CRUD Operations with .NET Core – A Todo API Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-crud-operations-with-dotnet-core-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-crud-operations-with-dotnet-core-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T14:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to this comprehensive guide on building CRUD operations with .NET Core. We'll use a Todo API as our practical example so you can get hands-on experience as you learn. Throughout this tutorial, you'll learn how to create, read, update, and delete Todo items, and how to leverage Entity Framework]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaiah Cliford  Opoku</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source is Changing. The Changelog Host Jerod Santo on How to Keep Up [Podcast #125]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/open-source-is-changing-the-changelog-host-jerod-santo-on-how-to-keep-up-podcast-125/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/open-source-is-changing-the-changelog-host-jerod-santo-on-how-to-keep-up-podcast-125/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T14:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Jerod Santo, host of The Changelog, a podcast about open source software development that has been going strong for 15 years. Jerod is plugged in to the world of Open Source, going to all the big con...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an MVP for Your Project – and Why You Should Do It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/minimum-viable-product-between-an-idea-and-the-product/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/minimum-viable-product-between-an-idea-and-the-product/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proof of concept, prototypes, wireframes, mockups… what actually constitutes a Minimum Viable Product (MVP)? Well, it's a product with just enough features to gather comprehensive qualitative feedback. In practice, it's as easy to understand the concept of an MVP as it is to ride a bicycle. Let's do it then.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oleg Romanyuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching It Up With HTML’s Latest Control]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/switching-it-up-html-latest-control/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/switching-it-up-html-latest-control/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of relying on checkbox hacks to create a “switch” control for forms that toggle between two states, HTML may be gaining a native way to go about it by adding a `switch` attribute to checkbox inputs. Daniel Yuschick walks us through a first impression of switch controls and discusses current and ongoing considerations that need to be explored further before it is ready for prime time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Daniel Yuschick)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose a Tech Stack for Your SaaS Product – Lessons from a Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/choose-a-tech-stack-for-your-saas-product/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/choose-a-tech-stack-for-your-saas-product/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T08:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a developer, I've seen how choosing the "right" tech stack can be a double-edged sword. I often fell into the trap of chasing shiny new technologies, thinking they were the key to building the next great product. But experience has taught me that prioritizing speed to market trends often]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Cruz Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Partition Queues for Distributed Workloads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-partition-queues-for-distributed-workloads/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-partition-queues-for-distributed-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T20:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technology, like human lives, evolves, and with this evolution comes the use of better solutions to existing problems. You might wonder: does this complicate systems or make them more efficient?  In this article, we will discuss some measures you can take to make systems much more efficient and reliable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoye Victor Chukwuebuka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pass the AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate Certification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pass-the-aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-certification/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pass-the-aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-certification/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T20:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you trying to earn the AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate certification? We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is is designed to help you pass the certification exam and showcase your expertise in AWS t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Practices For Naming Design Tokens, Components, Variables, And More]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/naming-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/naming-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can we get better at naming? This post is dedicated to naming conventions, tips, and real-world examples that help you name things in a robust and flexible way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Your Django App – Best Practices and Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-secure-your-django-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-secure-your-django-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T15:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a software developer or engineer, it's not enough to know how to build useful solutions – you must also ensure that they are secure. Prioritizing your users is crucial when developing and deploying your software because if users can't use your app, it becomes useless. In this guide, we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Iroegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern CSS Layouts: You Might Not Need A Framework For That]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/modern-css-layouts-no-framework-needed/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/modern-css-layouts-no-framework-needed/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easy to get lost in a sea of CSS frameworks and libraries, each promising easier styling and smoother layouts. Brecht De Ruyte demonstrates four CSS utility classes (plus a bonus) using techniques that allow them to be used practically anywhere you need a particular layout — be it Grid or Flexbox — with configurable options.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>