<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-12-13T00:58:48.635Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up a Django Development Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-a-django-development-environment/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-a-django-development-environment/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T15:52:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Django is a high-level web framework written in Python that encourages a rapid and realistic functional design. The Django web framework is free and open-source and is widely used to create both small and large web applications. In this tutorial, you will learn the following:  * What a development]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Poromon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[innerHTML vs innerText vs textContent – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/innerhtml-vs-innertext-vs-textcontent/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/innerhtml-vs-innertext-vs-textcontent/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In HTML, innerHTML, innerText, and textContent are properties of the DOM (Document Object Model). They allow you to read and update the content of HTML elements. But they have different behaviours in terms of the content they include and how they handle HTML markup. By the end of this article,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Comment Your JavaScript Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/comment-your-javascript-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/comment-your-javascript-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing comments in JavaScript is crucial for code readability, maintainability, and developer collaboration. Comments serve as notes within the codebase, explaining its functionality and logic, or providing context.  In this article, I will explain the significance of commenting your code, best practices to follow, and examples showcasing effective commenting]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asynchronous JavaScript – How to Use Promises in Your JS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-promises-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-promises-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:52:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a versatile programming language that powers the dynamic behavior of websites.  As web applications become more sophisticated, the need to handle asynchronous operations efficiently becomes crucial. Asynchronous JavaScript allows you to execute code without blocking the main thread, ensuring a smoother user experience.  Promises are a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is an API Gateway and Why is it Useful?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-api-gateways/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-api-gateways/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:40:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[APIs are often referred to as the front-door for applications to access data and business logic from backend services. As explained here [https://lightcloud.substack.com/p/api-integration-patterns], an API is essentially the interface that a piece of software presents to other humans or programs, allowing them to interact with that software. When creating an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Components For Consumption, Not Complexity (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/building-components-consumption-not-complexity-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/building-components-consumption-not-complexity-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design systems can be of immense help, but failure to adopt them invalidates the hard work that goes into building the thing in the first place! In this two-part series of articles, Luis shares his experience with design systems and how you can overcome the potential pitfalls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Luis Ouriach)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install MongoDB with OpenSSL 3 Support on Fedora 39]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-mongodb-with-openssl-3-support-on-fedora-39/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-mongodb-with-openssl-3-support-on-fedora-39/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T18:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn how to install MongoDB with support for the latest version of OpenSSL on the Fedora Linux operating system.  If you already have it installed, this tutorial will help you fix the mongosh OpenSSL configuration error. To follow along, you will need a terminal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus A. S. Freitas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ Tutorial – What Are the constexpr and constinit Specifiers?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cpp-constexpr-and-constinit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cpp-constexpr-and-constinit/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T18:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we write programs, many operations which are performed at runtime can actually be done at compile time – that is, baked into code.  This improves program performance since operations are no longer being computed on the fly, during runtime.  While these techniques of offloading operations to compile]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jayant Chowdhary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automation with Python – How to Build an Automated Email System for Job Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-automated-email-system-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-automated-email-system-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T18:39:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all receive promotional emails from companies like Swiggy and Amazon encouraging us to check out their new dish or flash sales.  Have you ever wondered how they manage to send emails to millions of customers? It’s impossible to do it manually! Instead, they use Automated Email Systems to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jess Wilk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Handle Null References in the Latest Version of C#]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-null-references-in-csharp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-null-references-in-csharp/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T18:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C# 12 has just been released, and it continues the long tradition of improvements in the safety of the language's software design and execution. One of these improvements relates to manipulating null references, a programming concept that many developers don't really love. Using null references in your code can cause]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zoran Horvat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vector Search and RAG Tutorial – Using LLMs with Your Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vector-search-and-rag-tutorial-using-llms-with-your-data/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vector-search-and-rag-tutorial-using-llms-with-your-data/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T18:12:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use Vector Search and embeddings to easily combine your data with large language models like GPT-4. I just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to implement Vector Search on three different projects. First, you will learn about the concepts and then]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn REST APIs by Building a JavaScript Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-rest-apis-javascript-project/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-rest-apis-javascript-project/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T15:18:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, you've been learning JavaScript. I bet you're loving it. You've learned the basics and you're starting to get the hang of it. So you might be wondering what to do next.  Well, let me introduce you to REST APIs, a powerful tool that you are going to add]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spruce Emmanuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn to Control GPT in the OpenAI Playground]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-control-gpt-in-openai-playground/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-control-gpt-in-openai-playground/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T17:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT is the interface most people use to work with OpenAI's large language model. But for someone who needs the versatility and power of programmatic access, there's no replacement for OpenAI's API.  The API is the interface you can use to connect programming code running on your own PC]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Start Learning to Code – Coding for Everyone Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-coding-for-everyone-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-coding-for-everyone-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T17:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this handbook, I'll address a question you may be asking yourself: should you learn how to code? After explaining why you definitely should, I'll cover some of the benefits and challenges of being a software developer. I'll also discuss some key strategies for approaching learning to code to help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fatos Morina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: The History of Online Courses with Class Central Founder Dhawal Shah]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-history-of-online-courses-dhawal-shah/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-history-of-online-courses-dhawal-shah/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T10:29:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's podcast, I'm joined by Dhawal Shah, the creator of Class Central, a popular search engine for online courses. Dhawal shares the history of online courses and the Massive Open Online Course revolution of the early 2010s.  We also talk about his childhood growing up in India,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manipulate the DOM in JavaScript – Most Commonly Used Techniques]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-document-object-model-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-document-object-model-explained/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T22:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article, I’m going to cover everything you need to know about manipulating the DOM. Basically, each Element object in the DOM has properties and methods that you can use to interact with that element. The following are the most common and practical ways you might want]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTMLCollection vs NodeList – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dom-manipulation-htmlcollection-vs-nodelist/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dom-manipulation-htmlcollection-vs-nodelist/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T22:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a web developer or have worked with the DOM (Document Object Model), you may have come across the terms HTMLCollection and NodeList before. But what do they mean and when do you need to use them? By the end of this article, you will learn all about HTMLCollection]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Java Interview Prep Handbook – 50 Questions Solved + Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-interview-prep-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-interview-prep-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:28:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're trying to get a job in big tech or you want to refine your skills in software development, a strong grasp of Java is indispensable.  Java is well-known for its robustness in Object-Oriented Programming (OOP), and it provides a comprehensive foundation essential for developers at every level.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preparing For Interaction To Next Paint, A New Web Core Vital]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/preparing-interaction-next-paint-web-core-vital/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/preparing-interaction-next-paint-web-core-vital/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting in March 2024, Interaction to Next Paint will formally replace First Input Delay as a Core Web Vital metric. Learn how the two metrics differ, why we needed a new way to measure interaction responsiveness, and how you can start optimizing the performance of your site now for a seamless transition to the latest Core Web Vital metric.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🐍 🕹️ 💻]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-beginners-project-snake-game/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-beginners-project-snake-game/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T15:57:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improve your JavaScript skills by building a snake game inspired by the iconic Nokia Snake game! We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you to create the project using vanilla HMTL, CSS and JavaScript. Ademir Alijagic created this course. You will build this.This coruse]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use setTimeout in React Using Hooks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-settimeout-in-react-using-hooks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-settimeout-in-react-using-hooks/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T23:37:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React has emerged as a powerful and widely used JavaScript library for building user interfaces. Its component-based architecture allows developers to create modular and reusable code, making it easier to manage and maintain complex applications.  One common requirement in web development projects is the ability to delay the execution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Static Initialization Order Fiasco in C++? [Solved]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cpp-static-initialization-order-fiasco/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cpp-static-initialization-order-fiasco/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T23:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll be covering a subtle but egregious problem that can occur in C++ programs. This problem is popularly called the 'Static Initialization Order Fiasco'.  I'll first go over what the problem is, then go onto some solutions and explore how they work. Let's get started.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jayant Chowdhary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Software Engineer Internship Handbook – How to Launch Your Coding Career]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/software-engineer-internship-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/software-engineer-internship-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T18:21:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the fiercely competitive world of software engineering, the question isn’t whether internships matter, but how much. Many large tech firms emphasize internship experience when hiring. So, if you’re an aspiring software engineer, listen closely. This carefully curated guide, grounded in data and expert consensus, is designed to be your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Launch Your Coding Career and Land Your First Software Engineering Internship]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/launch-your-coding-career-and-get-an-internship/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/launch-your-coding-career-and-get-an-internship/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T18:21:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the fiercely competitive world of software engineering, the question isn’t whether internships matter, but how much. According to a survey by the National Association of Colleges and Employers, 89% of large tech firms emphasize internship experience when hiring. So, if you’re an aspiring software engineer, listen closely. This carefully]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five-Second Testing: Taking A Closer Look At First Impressions (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/five-second-testing-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/five-second-testing-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five-second testing is a popular method of usability research used in the industry, yet in essence, its core belief boils down to virtually a superstition. Eduard Kuric looks under the hood at how first impressions are affected by various factors and how UX researchers and product owners can ensure that the user’s first steps can get off on the right foot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eduard Kuric)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the SWR Library for Better Data Fetching in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/swr-library-for-data-fetching-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/swr-library-for-data-fetching-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T21:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is un-opinionated about how you fetch and manage the remote data in your application. You may think of using the useEffect hook for simple fetching operations, but it will not help you with caching, request deduplication, always serving real-time data, and so on. Things will get more complicated when]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Furkan Emin Can</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Use Cases – What is Python Best For?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-python-best-for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-python-best-for/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T21:22:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers are often very passionate about their tech stack, and they'll likely recommend it for anything.  It is very common to see devs on social media sharing how you can build anything with JavaScript or how Python is great for data scientists. As a Python fanatic myself, I actually]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Cruz Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up GitHub OAuth in a Django App for User Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-github-oauth-on-django-for-user-authentication/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-github-oauth-on-django-for-user-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T21:19:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maintaining safe and frictionless user authentication is paramount in today's fast-changing web application landscape.  Among the many authentication methods available, GitHub OAuth has emerged as a useful tool for improving user login experience while strengthening security measures.  Django [https://docs.djangoproject.com/en/4.2/], a Python web framework, has recently gained popularity in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Iroegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Contribute to Open Source as a Community Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/contributing-to-open-source-as-a-community-manager/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/contributing-to-open-source-as-a-community-manager/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T21:14:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The proverb "it takes a village" applies to more than child-rearing. It also takes a village to maintain an open source project.  Community is a large part of open source. After all, Open Source projects can't thrive without a strong network of people (community) who contribute towards it, either]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amarachi Johnson-Ubah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Study Course – Pass the Exam With This Free 14-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-study-course-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-13-hour-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-study-course-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-13-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T19:51:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Passing the AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam is one of the first steps to a career in cloud development. And freeCodeCamp just published a free 14-hour course that will help you prepare for the exam.  This exam mostly deals with cloud computing concepts. Even if you are new to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping Time in C++: How to use the std::chrono API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cpp-std-chrono-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cpp-std-chrono-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T23:38:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping track of time is a very important aspect of computer programs. Some common use cases are:  * Measure/profile the performance of certain parts of code.  * Do work at certain periods of time, from within a program.   * Detect whether threads are in a deadlock]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jayant Chowdhary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React Hooks – useEffect, useState, and useContext Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-hooks-useeffect-usestate-and-usecontext/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-hooks-useeffect-usestate-and-usecontext/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T18:38:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is a powerful JavaScript library for building user interfaces. And it has undergone significant changes over the years.  One of the most noteworthy additions is the introduction of hooks, which revolutionized the way developers manage state and side effects in functional components.  In this guide, we'll explore]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MLOps Course – Learn to Build Machine Learning Production Grade Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mlops-course-learn-to-build-machine-learning-production-grade-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mlops-course-learn-to-build-machine-learning-production-grade-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T17:50:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MLOps, short for Machine Learning Operations, refers to the practice of applying DevOps principles to machine learning. Understanding MLOps can help you build production grade machine learning projects. We just posted an MLOps course the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. MLOps is a cutting-edge field at the intersection of machine learning, data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Marketing Changed OOP In JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/marketing-changed-oop-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/marketing-changed-oop-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussing the decisions surrounding JavaScript prototypes, the article by Juan Diego Rodriguez scrutinizes their origin, examines missteps in the design, and explores how these factors have affected the way we write JavaScript today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add a Table of Contents to Your Article on Ghost]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-a-table-of-contents-to-your-article-on-ghost/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-a-table-of-contents-to-your-article-on-ghost/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T19:47:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A table of contents (or TOC) is a list of chapters or section titles in an article. You'll usually find it at the beginning of an article, right after the introduction. When you write a long blog post or an article with independent sections, consider adding a table of contents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayu Adiati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SVG Tutorial – How to Code Images with 7 Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/svg-tutorial-learn-to-code-images/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/svg-tutorial-learn-to-code-images/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T19:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever needed an icon for your website, but you couldn't quite find the right one? Or perhaps you wanted to have a simple diagram, but didn't want to learn a whole new library just for that? Well, good news – you can do all that and more without]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hunor Márton Borbély</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recovering Deleted Files From Your Git Working Tree]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/recovering-deleted-files-git-working-tree/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/recovering-deleted-files-git-working-tree/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is designed to assure us that we can track a project’s files at different points in time. But it doesn’t assure us that those files are always safe along the way. For those of you who have dealt with the sinking feeling that you’ve irrevocably deleted and lost files, Sanmi has a couple of approaches that, in the right situations, may help bring them back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Oluwasanmi Akande)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use JavaScript Arrow Functions – Explained in Detail]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-arrow-functions-in-depth/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-arrow-functions-in-depth/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T19:26:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! In this article, I’m going to explain one of the most useful features in JavaScript: the arrow function. I’ll compare the arrow function with the regular function syntax, I'll show you how to convert a regular function into an arrow function easily, and I'll discuss why the arrow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create HTML Accordion Elements With and Without JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-html-accordions-with-and-without-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-html-accordions-with-and-without-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T19:10:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accordion elements are very handy for displaying topic titles and expandable details below them when you click the title. In this article, I'll walk you through creating an FAQ section with some expandable accordion elements. I'll show you how to do this without any JavaScript, and then we'll add a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Clang AST-Based C++ Static Analysis Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/clang-ast-based-static-analysis-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/clang-ast-based-static-analysis-tools/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T19:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clang is a set of tools and projects that provides infrastructure for languages in the C family like C, C++, OpenCL, and CUDA. It is a part of the LLVM [https://www.llvm.org/] project. This article will show you how to use Clang's front end libraries to build a simple static analysis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jayant Chowdhary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code and Deploy an Instagram Clone with React and Firebase]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-and-deploy-an-instagram-clone-with-react-and-firebase/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-and-deploy-an-instagram-clone-with-react-and-firebase/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T16:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating an Instagram clone is a fun project that can help you master important front end development skills. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that teaches you how to create an Instagram clone using React and Firebase. Burak Orkmez developed this course. This course is perfect]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API Documentation Best Practices Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/api-documentation-best-practices-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/api-documentation-best-practices-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T16:17:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since APIs are the backbone of software development, effective API documentation is critical.  We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to write good documentation for APIs. You will learn how to craft, automate, and publish API documentation that is not only]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cold Days, Shining Lights (December 2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-december-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-december-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could there be a better way to welcome the new month than with a collection of desktop wallpapers? We’ve got some eye-catching designs to sweeten up the last few weeks of the year and, if you’re celebrating, to get you in the holiday mood.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Logic in JavaScript – Operators, Conditions, Truthy/Falsy, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/logic-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/logic-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T21:50:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a versatile programming language that empowers developers to create dynamic and interactive web pages.  One of the foundational elements of JavaScript programming is the application of logical operations to make decisions and control program flow.  In this guide, we'll delve into the basics of logical operations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Music Production with FL Studio – Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-music-production-fl-studio/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-music-production-fl-studio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T21:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the right tools and training, anyone can become a music producer. We just release a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you advanced music production skills using FL Stuio. Tristan Willcox developed this course. Tristan is a professional music producer with over 10,000 hours in music]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Might Want to Move Your Workloads Out of the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-you-might-want-to-move-your-workloads-out-of-the-cloud/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-you-might-want-to-move-your-workloads-out-of-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T21:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is a public cloud like AWS or Microsoft's Azure the right place to host every  deployment workload at every stage of its life? To be honest, I once thought that that was true – at least 95% of the time. But things have changed. Even though new services are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use JavaScript's Array reduce() Method – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-javascript-array-reduce-method/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-javascript-array-reduce-method/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T18:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello again, friends! The reduce() method is one of the most confusing Array methods in JavaScript. So in this article, I’m going to help you clearly see how the method works.  I'm also going to show some examples that'll help you understand how and where you may want to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's New in JavaScript in 2023 – Changes with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-biggest-changes-in-javascript-this-year/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-biggest-changes-in-javascript-this-year/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T18:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ECMAScript 2023, the 14th edition of the language, has some great changes that will make your programming life easier.  In this article, I'll go through each of the changes and explain why they're helpful. So let’s dive in and see some new methods we got as an early Christmas]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nishant Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How JavaScript Promises Work – Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-promise-object-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-promise-object-explained/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T15:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article, I’m going to teach you one of the most confusing JavaScript topics, which is the Promise object. Promises may seem difficult at first, but they're actually quite simple once you understand how they work. Here's what we'll cover:  1. How a Promise Works]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Movie Recommendation System Based on Collaborative Filtering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-movie-recommendation-system-based-on-collaborative-filtering/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-movie-recommendation-system-based-on-collaborative-filtering/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T15:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s world of technology, we get more recommendations from Artificial Intelligence models than from our friends.  Surprised? Think of the content you see and the apps you use daily. We get product recommendations on Amazon, clothing recommendations on Myntra, and movie suggestions on Netflix based on our past]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jess Wilk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practice HTML, CSS, and JavaScript in Spanish by Building 7 Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/practice-html-css-and-javascript-by-building-7-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/practice-html-css-and-javascript-by-building-7-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T15:17:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating projects is very important for expanding your web development portfolio. Transforming an idea into a real project can help you to practice and understand key concepts and techniques. We just published a 3-hour course in Spanish on freeCodeCamp's Spanish YouTube channel [https://www.youtube.com/freecodecampespanol] that will teach you how to build]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is base64 Encoding and Why is it Necessary?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-base64-encoding/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-base64-encoding/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll thoroughly explore base64 encoding. You'll learn how it came into being and why it's still so prevalent in modern systems. Here's what we'll cover:  1.  What is base64?  2.  Why use base64?  3.  When to use base64  4.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergei Bachinin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python One-Liners to Help You Write Simple, Readable Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-one-liners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-one-liners/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T16:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python's beauty lies in its simplicity and readability. And mastering the art of writing concise yet powerful code can significantly enhance your productivity as a developer. I'm talking about really short lines of code that do big things. In this article, we'll explore 8 essential Python one-liners that every Pythonista]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crafting A Killer Brand Identity For A Digital Product]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/crafting-killer-brand-identity-digital-product/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/crafting-killer-brand-identity-digital-product/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sasha guides you through crucial processes and factors to achieve a consistent brand presence across platforms. She offers an overview of the entire brand identity process, explores collaboration with UI teams, and provides essential details on the assets required for the successful implementation of a digital brand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sasha Denisova)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Web3.js Basics – Ethereum Development for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-web3js-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-web3js-basics/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:39:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum is one of the major pioneers in the decentralized ecosystem. And Web3.js is an essential tool if you're working on Ethereum-based projects.  To fully understand why this tool is important, we must first take a deeper dive into Ethereum development. Grab your coffee, young Web3 enthusiast. We're going]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatise Okuwobi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Two-Factor Authentication with PyOTP and Google Authenticator in Your Flask App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-two-factor-authentication-in-your-flask-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-two-factor-authentication-in-your-flask-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two-Factor Authentication, or 2FA, is like having an extra lock on the door to your online accounts. Instead of just using a password, 2FA adds another layer of security. It's a bit like needing both a key and a special code to open a vault. Think of it as a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feature Engineering Techniques for Structured Data – Machine Learning Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/feature-engineering-techniques-for-structured-data/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/feature-engineering-techniques-for-structured-data/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:13:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feature engineering is an essential step in the data preprocessing process, especially when dealing with tabular data.  It involves creating new features (columns), transforming existing ones, and selecting the most relevant attributes to improve the performance and accuracy of machine learning models.  Feature engineering helps the model understand]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwafunmilola Obisesan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fetch Data from an API Using the Fetch API in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fetch-data-from-an-api-using-the-fetch-api-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fetch-data-from-an-api-using-the-fetch-api-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interacting with external APIs, or Application Programming Interfaces, has become an essential skill in web development.  APIs allow different software applications to communicate with each other, enabling developers to access and retrieve data from various sources.  One popular way to perform API requests in JavaScript is by using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Scroll Animations with React, Tailwind CSS, and Framer Motion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-scroll-animations-with-framer-motion-and-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-scroll-animations-with-framer-motion-and-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:47:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scroll-based animations are triggered when a user scrolls on a webpage. Recently, I built a Scroll Animation with Framer Motion [https://www.aceternity.com/components/container-scroll-animation] that moves grids in uneven directions. This project prompted me to write a tutorial about how I did that here on freeCodeCamp. The Framer Motion library makes it super]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manu Arora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free 107-Hour AWS Cloud Project Bootcamp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-107-hour-aws-cloud-project-bootcamp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-107-hour-aws-cloud-project-bootcamp/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:43:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Cloud Project Bootcamp is a free comprehensive training program to equip you with the skills and knowledge to successfully design, build, and implement a cloud project. We just published the entire 107-hour bootcamp on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Andrew Brown from ExamPro developed this course. The AWS Cloud]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Hardware Engineering with Bruno Haid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-hardware-engineering-bruno-haid/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-hardware-engineering-bruno-haid/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T21:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the freeCodeCamp Podcast, I interview hardware engineer and tech founder from Austria. We talk about growing up in the European countryside, his early passion for computers, and ultimately his move to San Francisco, where he's founded several tech companies. Bruno's super excited about embedded systems]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Programming Language Should I Learn First in 2024? [Solved]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-programming-language-should-i-learn-first-19a33b0a467d/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-programming-language-should-i-learn-first-19a33b0a467d/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T08:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most people’s journey toward learning to program starts with a single late-night Google search. Usually it’s something like “Learn ______” But how do they decide which language to search for? > “They always joke about Java on Silicon Valley. I guess I should learn that.” Or: > “Haskell. So hot]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Few Ways CSS Is Easier To Write In 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/few-ways-css-easier-write-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/few-ways-css-easier-write-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re living in somewhat of a CSS renaissance with new features, techniques, experiments, and ideas coming at us to an extent we haven’t seen since “CSS3”. It’s easy to feel overwhelmed when your profession seems to be advancing at breakneck speed, but Geoff Graham considers the ways “modern” CSS in 2023 has actually made CSS “easier” to write.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp's Top Open Source Contributors of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/top-open-source-contributors-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/top-open-source-contributors-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T03:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2023 has been an amazing year for the freeCodeCamp community.  I'm so grateful for the many kind volunteers who have helped us advance our mission of creating open learning resources. Over the past 12 months, the freeCodeCamp community has:  * Merged 2,753 code contributions into our open source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To Full Stack Composability]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/introduction-full-stack-composability/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/introduction-full-stack-composability/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A well-designed composable system should not only consider the technical aspects but also take into account the nature of the content it handles. To help us with that, we can use a Headless Content Management system such as Storyblok.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOM Manipulation in JavaScript – A Comprehensive Guide for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dom-manipulation-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dom-manipulation-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T08:16:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript, the language of the web, empowers developers to create dynamic and interactive web pages. One of the key features that enables this interactivity is Document Object Model (DOM) manipulation.  DOM manipulation allows developers to interact with and modify the structure, style, and content of web pages. In this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Django Model Fields – Common Use Cases and How They Work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/common-django-model-fields-and-their-use-cases/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/common-django-model-fields-and-their-use-cases/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T00:03:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Django model fields define the structure of a database within a Django web application. Using this essential component will keep your work organized and help you make fewer mistakes in your code. This article will discuss some common Django model fields and how to use them in your code. To]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Poromon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Keep Branches Up-to-Date and Resolve Merge Conflicts in GitHub and VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/keep-branches-up-to-date-resolve-merge-conflicts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/keep-branches-up-to-date-resolve-merge-conflicts/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T23:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Hey {username}, we've merged a PR before yours. Please resolve the merge conflicts so we can review and merge your PR. Have you ever received that kind of message from a maintainer while waiting for your pull request to be reviewed and merged? And then, you're panicking because you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayu Adiati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Your First Data Science Internship]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-your-first-data-science-internship/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-your-first-data-science-internship/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T23:01:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to break into Data Science in 2024? Then you should consider trying to get your first Data Science internship.  Internships can help you gain invaluable experience and set you up for success in the ever-evolving field of Data Science. But with fierce competition, limited opportunities, unclear]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tatev Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Structures Handbook – The Key to Scalable Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-structures-the-key-to-scalable-software/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-structures-the-key-to-scalable-software/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T20:44:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're regularly confronted by the complexity of modern data, you’re not alone. In our data-centric world, understanding data structures isn’t optional — it’s essential.  Whether you’re a novice coder or an experienced developer, this handbook is your concise guide to the critical skill of data management through data structures. Data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning with Python and Scikit-Learn]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-with-python-and-scikit-learn/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-with-python-and-scikit-learn/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T16:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scikit-learn is an open-source machine learning library for Python, known for its simplicity, versatility, and accessibility. The library is well-documented and supported by a large community, making it a popular choice for both beginners and experienced practitioners in the field of machine learning. We just published an 18-hour course on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Responsive Multi-Line Ribbon Shapes (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/css-responsive-multi-line-ribbon-shapes-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/css-responsive-multi-line-ribbon-shapes-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1 of the series, Temani Afif demonstrated how creating ribbon patterns in CSS has evolved with the availability of new CSS features. In this second installment of this brief two-part series, we look at two additional ribbon variations that introduce techniques for masking a repeated background gradient in CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go Language for Encryption – Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/go-language-for-encryption-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/go-language-for-encryption-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T04:21:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Go, or Golang, is a powerful programming language known for its simplicity, efficiency, and strong support for concurrent programming. It's a favorite among developers for building scalable web applications, cloud services, and more. We just released a Go course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that walks you through building three]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn LangChain to link LLMs with external data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-langchain-to-link-llms-with-external-data/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-langchain-to-link-llms-with-external-data/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T04:10:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LangChain is an AI-first framework designed to enable developers to create context-aware reasoning applications by linking powerful Large Language Models with external data sources. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you all about LangChain. The course will equip you with the cutting-edge skills]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Career Mistakes to Avoid as a Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/career-mistakes-to-avoid-as-a-dev/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/career-mistakes-to-avoid-as-a-dev/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T00:04:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What does the word career mean to you? To me, it is a roller coaster journey during which we find opportunities, progress, and growth in life. The journey involves learning objectives, work, and other personal and professional aspects. A promising career is one where you enjoy most (if not all)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Successful Projects as a Junior Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-projects-as-a-junior-developer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-projects-as-a-junior-developer/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T21:25:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several months ago, I stumbled upon a coding challenge that intrigued me. Here's what it was: > Fun frontend question I was asked in an interview one time Build six squares with no color Every time you click one, it turns green When the last square turns green, they all]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spruce Emmanuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Visualization for Leetcode's Two Sum Problem – HTML, CSS, & JavaScript Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-visualization-for-leetcode-two-sum-problem/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-visualization-for-leetcode-two-sum-problem/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T21:08:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the current state of the job market, there are a lot of people grinding out  LeetCode [https://leetcode.com/] as a way to prepare for technical interviews.  But sometimes it would be nice if there were a visualization showing the algorithms behind these problems.  In this tutorial, we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Secure User Authentication Flow in Flutter with Firebase and Bloc State Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/user-authentication-flow-in-flutter-with-firebase-and-bloc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/user-authentication-flow-in-flutter-with-firebase-and-bloc/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T15:21:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[User authentication is critical to mobile app development. It helps make sure that only authorized users can access sensitive information and perform actions within an application. In this tutorial, we will explore how to build secure user authentication in Flutter using Firebase for authentication and the Bloc state management pattern]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justice Nwogu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating And Maintaining A Voice Of Customer Program]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/creating-maintaining-voice-customer-program/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/creating-maintaining-voice-customer-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Product teams benefit from knowing their users’ needs and how they respond to product updates as they build out the roadmap of a product. This article covers Voice of Customer programs and is aimed at those who work on a product team as well as executives who are looking for how to better inform your products using insight from users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Yocco &amp; Dana Daniels)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use If Statements in JavaScript – a Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/if-statements-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/if-statements-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T21:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a powerful and versatile programming language that is widely used for creating dynamic and interactive web pages.  One of the fundamental building blocks of JavaScript programming is the if  statement. if statements allow developers to control the flow of their programs by making decisions based on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build and Deploy a python-telegram-bot v20 Webhook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-and-deploy-python-telegram-bot-v20-webhooks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-and-deploy-python-telegram-bot-v20-webhooks/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T20:43:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The python-telegram-bot v20 release introduced major structural changes. According to the documentation, > “All networking and I/O-related logic now works via coroutine functions (i.e.  async def ... functions). In particular, all methods of the telegram.Bot class that make requests to the Bot API are now coroutine functions and need]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chua Hui Shun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Data Visualization with Dr. Curran Kelleher]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-data-visualization-curran-kelleher/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-data-visualization-curran-kelleher/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T21:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I'm joined by Dr. Curran Kelleher. He's a data visualization expert and has taught a number of in-depth data visualization courses on freeCodeCamp's YouTube channel. We talk about what it's like to get a Ph.D. under one of the pioneers of data visualization. We also talk about how he]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Efficient Design-to-Code Handoff Process Using Uno Platform For Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/design-to-code-handoff-process-uno-platform-figma/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/design-to-code-handoff-process-uno-platform-figma/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Effective collaboration between designers and developers is vital to creating good user experiences. However, bridging the handoff between design and development with the many tools and workflows available today has its pitfalls. Matthew Mattei introduces you to the Uno Platform, which offers a robust set of productivity boosters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthew Mattei)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Game Tutorial – Build a Stick Hero Clone with HTML Canvas + JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-game-tutorial-stick-hero-with-html-canvas/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-game-tutorial-stick-hero-with-html-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T19:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn how to create a game that's inspired by Stick Hero – using pure JavaScript and HTML canvas. We are going to recreate Stick Hero [https://apps.apple.com/us/app/stick-hero/id918338898], a mobile game published by KetchApp. We'll go through how the game works in general, how to use JavaScript to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hunor Márton Borbély</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Localize Your Django App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/localize-django-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/localize-django-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:07:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how websites can offer their content in multiple languages, perfectly tailored to different cultures and regions?  Well, that magic is called localization, and it's a game-changer for web development – especially when using Django, a super versatile Python framework.  It's not just about translating]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jess Wilk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT vs BARD AI – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chatgpt-vs-bard/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chatgpt-vs-bard/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T17:19:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November of 2022, Artificial Intelligence took center stage in the tech world. AI was not a new concept, but OpenAI had just released its ChatGPT Large Language Model, and devs started diving into using it.  Large Language Models, or LLMs, let users enter a prompt (some question or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maybell Obadoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React Suspense to Improve your React Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-suspense/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-suspense/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T17:04:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React's ecosystem is always growing, and it seems like there are always new features and enhancements to make development more effective and user-friendly.  React Suspense is one such feature that has become quite popular among React devs. In this guide, you'll learn all about React Suspense and examine its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okosa Leonard Onyekachukwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Technical Interviews]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-technical-interviews/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-technical-interviews/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T15:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You need to prepare if you want to perform well in technical developer job interviews. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will guide you through every aspect of the technical interview process, as well as prepare you for the type of questions you might get]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TypeScript with React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-typescript-with-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-typescript-with-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T18:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to use TypeScript with React. By the end, you will have a solid understanding of how to write React code with TypeScript. Want to watch the video version of this tutorial? You can check out the video below: Table of Contents  *]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yogesh Chavan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the PaLM 2 API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-palm-2-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-palm-2-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T14:31:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PaLM 2 is a cutting-edge AI tool from Google that opens up tons of possibilities for developers. The PaLM 2 API allows people to easily add generative AI to their apps. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.or YouTube channel that will teach you all about the PaLM 2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Responsive Multi-Line Ribbon Shapes (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/css-responsive-multi-line-ribbon-shapes-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/css-responsive-multi-line-ribbon-shapes-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ribbons have been used to accent designs for many years now. But, the way we approach them in CSS has evolved with the introduction of newer features. In this article, Temani Afif combines background and gradient tricks to create ribbon shapes in CSS that are not only responsive but support multi-line text and are easily adjustable with a few CSS variables.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transform Your Engineering Management Career Path]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-engineering-management/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-engineering-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T19:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you an aspiring engineering leader or a software developer looking to climb the ladder of success in your technical career? We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to be an exceptional engineering manager. Ankita Kulkarni teaches this course. She is an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Dynamic API Routes in Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/next-js-dynamic-api-routes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/next-js-dynamic-api-routes/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T18:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js is a React-based framework that enables developers to create full-stack web applications by extending the latest React features.  Next helps you add additional features and optimizations to your React apps like static site generation (SSG), server-side rendering (SSR), automatic code splitting and bundling, and dynamic API routes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Musab Habeeb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make an Interactive and Dynamic Table of Contents in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-a-dynamic-table-of-contents-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-a-dynamic-table-of-contents-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T15:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While reading some technical articles on various platforms, I kept noticing the Table of Contents section in the sidebar. Some were interactive and some were just links to those sections.  A Table of Contents usually ends up being pretty helpful to readers. It lets you easily skim through what]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bhavesh Rawat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scope in JavaScript – Global vs Local vs Block Scope Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/scope-in-javascript-global-vs-local-vs-block-scope/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/scope-in-javascript-global-vs-local-vs-block-scope/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-13T17:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the vast world of programming, scope is a fundamental concept. It underpins the behavior of variables in any given programming language. In the context of JavaScript, a language renowned for its widespread use in web development, understanding scope is crucial to writing efficient and bug-free code. Whether you're a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adekola Olawale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Handle Processing Multilingual Names in Your Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/handling-multilingual-names-in-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/handling-multilingual-names-in-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-13T17:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year, my team at work and I were looking at the errors occurring in one of our signup APIs. We saw that nearly 5% of our requests were getting failed, all due to 400 BAD REQUEST [https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/HTTP/Status/400] errors. And the root cause was traced back to a regex]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Apoorv Tyagi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Web Design Documentation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/designing-web-design-documentation/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/designing-web-design-documentation/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words alone aren’t enough to safeguard best practices in the world of web design and development. Web design documentation must be like its medium — interactive and constantly evolving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>