<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-11-22T01:00:13.552Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Secure User Authentication Flow in Flutter with Firebase and Bloc State Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/user-authentication-flow-in-flutter-with-firebase-and-bloc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/user-authentication-flow-in-flutter-with-firebase-and-bloc/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T15:21:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[User authentication is critical to mobile app development. It helps make sure that only authorized users can access sensitive information and perform actions within an application. In this tutorial, we will explore how to build secure user authentication in Flutter using Firebase for authentication and the Bloc state management pattern]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justice Nwogu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating And Maintaining A Voice Of Customer Program]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/creating-maintaining-voice-customer-program/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/creating-maintaining-voice-customer-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Product teams benefit from knowing their users’ needs and how they respond to product updates as they build out the roadmap of a product. This article covers Voice of Customer programs and is aimed at those who work on a product team as well as executives who are looking for how to better inform your products using insight from users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Yocco &amp; Dana Daniels)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use If Statements in JavaScript – a Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/if-statements-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/if-statements-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T21:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a powerful and versatile programming language that is widely used for creating dynamic and interactive web pages.  One of the fundamental building blocks of JavaScript programming is the if  statement. if statements allow developers to control the flow of their programs by making decisions based on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build and Deploy a python-telegram-bot v20 Webhook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-and-deploy-python-telegram-bot-v20-webhooks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-and-deploy-python-telegram-bot-v20-webhooks/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T20:43:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The python-telegram-bot v20 release introduced major structural changes. According to the documentation, > “All networking and I/O-related logic now works via coroutine functions (i.e.  async def ... functions). In particular, all methods of the telegram.Bot class that make requests to the Bot API are now coroutine functions and need]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chua Hui Shun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Data Visualization with Dr. Curran Kelleher]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-data-visualization-curran-kelleher/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-data-visualization-curran-kelleher/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T21:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I'm joined by Dr. Curran Kelleher. He's a data visualization expert and has taught a number of in-depth data visualization courses on freeCodeCamp's YouTube channel. We talk about what it's like to get a Ph.D. under one of the pioneers of data visualization. We also talk about how he]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Efficient Design-to-Code Handoff Process Using Uno Platform For Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/design-to-code-handoff-process-uno-platform-figma/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/design-to-code-handoff-process-uno-platform-figma/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Effective collaboration between designers and developers is vital to creating good user experiences. However, bridging the handoff between design and development with the many tools and workflows available today has its pitfalls. Matthew Mattei introduces you to the Uno Platform, which offers a robust set of productivity boosters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthew Mattei)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Game Tutorial – Build a Stick Hero Clone with HTML Canvas + JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-game-tutorial-stick-hero-with-html-canvas/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-game-tutorial-stick-hero-with-html-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T19:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn how to create a game that's inspired by Stick Hero – using pure JavaScript and HTML canvas. We are going to recreate Stick Hero [https://apps.apple.com/us/app/stick-hero/id918338898], a mobile game published by KetchApp. We'll go through how the game works in general, how to use JavaScript to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hunor Márton Borbély</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Localize Your Django App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/localize-django-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/localize-django-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:07:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how websites can offer their content in multiple languages, perfectly tailored to different cultures and regions?  Well, that magic is called localization, and it's a game-changer for web development – especially when using Django, a super versatile Python framework.  It's not just about translating]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jess Wilk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT vs BARD AI – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chatgpt-vs-bard/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chatgpt-vs-bard/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T17:19:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November of 2022, Artificial Intelligence took center stage in the tech world. AI was not a new concept, but OpenAI had just released its ChatGPT Large Language Model, and devs started diving into using it.  Large Language Models, or LLMs, let users enter a prompt (some question or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maybell Obadoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React Suspense to Improve your React Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-suspense/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-suspense/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T17:04:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React's ecosystem is always growing, and it seems like there are always new features and enhancements to make development more effective and user-friendly.  React Suspense is one such feature that has become quite popular among React devs. In this guide, you'll learn all about React Suspense and examine its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okosa Leonard Onyekachukwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Technical Interviews]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-technical-interviews/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-technical-interviews/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T15:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You need to prepare if you want to perform well in technical developer job interviews. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will guide you through every aspect of the technical interview process, as well as prepare you for the type of questions you might get]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TypeScript with React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-typescript-with-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-typescript-with-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T18:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to use TypeScript with React. By the end, you will have a solid understanding of how to write React code with TypeScript. Want to watch the video version of this tutorial? You can check out the video below: Table of Contents  *]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yogesh Chavan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the PaLM 2 API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-palm-2-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-palm-2-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T14:31:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PaLM 2 is a cutting-edge AI tool from Google that opens up tons of possibilities for developers. The PaLM 2 API allows people to easily add generative AI to their apps. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.or YouTube channel that will teach you all about the PaLM 2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Responsive Multi-Line Ribbon Shapes (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/css-responsive-multi-line-ribbon-shapes-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/css-responsive-multi-line-ribbon-shapes-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ribbons have been used to accent designs for many years now. But, the way we approach them in CSS has evolved with the introduction of newer features. In this article, Temani Afif combines background and gradient tricks to create ribbon shapes in CSS that are not only responsive but support multi-line text and are easily adjustable with a few CSS variables.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transform Your Engineering Management Career Path]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-engineering-management/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-engineering-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T19:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you an aspiring engineering leader or a software developer looking to climb the ladder of success in your technical career? We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to be an exceptional engineering manager. Ankita Kulkarni teaches this course. She is an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Dynamic API Routes in Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/next-js-dynamic-api-routes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/next-js-dynamic-api-routes/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T18:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js is a React-based framework that enables developers to create full-stack web applications by extending the latest React features.  Next helps you add additional features and optimizations to your React apps like static site generation (SSG), server-side rendering (SSR), automatic code splitting and bundling, and dynamic API routes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Musab Habeeb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make an Interactive and Dynamic Table of Contents in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-a-dynamic-table-of-contents-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-a-dynamic-table-of-contents-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T15:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While reading some technical articles on various platforms, I kept noticing the Table of Contents section in the sidebar. Some were interactive and some were just links to those sections.  A Table of Contents usually ends up being pretty helpful to readers. It lets you easily skim through what]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bhavesh Rawat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scope in JavaScript – Global vs Local vs Block Scope Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/scope-in-javascript-global-vs-local-vs-block-scope/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/scope-in-javascript-global-vs-local-vs-block-scope/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-13T17:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the vast world of programming, scope is a fundamental concept. It underpins the behavior of variables in any given programming language. In the context of JavaScript, a language renowned for its widespread use in web development, understanding scope is crucial to writing efficient and bug-free code. Whether you're a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adekola Olawale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Handle Processing Multilingual Names in Your Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/handling-multilingual-names-in-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/handling-multilingual-names-in-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-13T17:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year, my team at work and I were looking at the errors occurring in one of our signup APIs. We saw that nearly 5% of our requests were getting failed, all due to 400 BAD REQUEST [https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/HTTP/Status/400] errors. And the root cause was traced back to a regex]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Apoorv Tyagi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Web Design Documentation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/designing-web-design-documentation/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/designing-web-design-documentation/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words alone aren’t enough to safeguard best practices in the world of web design and development. Web design documentation must be like its medium — interactive and constantly evolving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Commit Messages that Project Maintainers Will Appreciate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-commit-messages-maintainers-will-like/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-commit-messages-maintainers-will-like/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-11T01:16:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know the saying “If you keep looking at the past, you’ll miss the future”? Well in the context of coding and working with Git, that’s not the case.  Your commit history plays a huge role in the future of the open source projects that you contribute to, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CHRISTINE T. BELZIE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: From MIT to Startup Land with Arian Agrawal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-arian-agrawal-from-mit-to-startup-land/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-arian-agrawal-from-mit-to-startup-land/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T22:11:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's podcast, I meet with Arian Agrawal in New York City to talk about her journey into tech startups. Arian grew up in New York and studied at MIT. She worked in finance for a few years, then built her own ecommerce Marketplace startup with a friend. Along]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Become an Azure Solutions Architect Expert – Pass the AZ-305 Exam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/become-an-azure-solutions-architect-expert-pass-the-az-305-exam/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/become-an-azure-solutions-architect-expert-pass-the-az-305-exam/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T16:03:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to elevate your expertise in designing cloud and hybrid solutions on Azure? The Azure Solutions Architect Expert Certification exam measures your ability to accomplish the following technical tasks: design identity, governance, and monitoring solutions; design data storage solutions; design business continuity solutions; and design infrastructure solutions. We]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Accessible UI Animations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/creating-accessible-ui-animations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/creating-accessible-ui-animations/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animation and accessibility are often seen as two separate powers at odds with one another. How is it possible to strike a balance between elements that move and the possible negative effects they expose to users who are sensitive to motion? Oriana García explains how her team at Mercado Libre tackled the challenge by creating guiding principles for applying animation to user interfaces and incorporating them into the team’s design system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Oriana García)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Setup Authentication and Protected Routes in Next.js 13 with next-auth.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-setup-authentication-and-protected-route-in-next-js-13-with-next-auth-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-setup-authentication-and-protected-route-in-next-js-13-with-next-auth-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide demonstrates the straightforward process of incorporating authentication into your Next.js app using the next-auth.js [https://next-auth.js.org/] library. While the library provides numerous options (providers), this tutorial focuses on the implementation using the Google Provider. You'll also gain insight into effortlessly setting up protected routes within your application, a task]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olasunkanmi Balogun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Java Fundamentals – How to Build a Solid Foundation in Object-Oriented Programming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-java-object-oriented-programming/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-java-object-oriented-programming/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:35:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you just getting into software development, or do you need to upgrade your coding skills? Java's significance within the tech sector stands unchallenged, so it's a great place to start. Java is at the foundation of Object-Oriented Programming (OOP). This is an approach to programming that mirrors our complexity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure Next.js Applications with Role-Based Authentication Using NextAuth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/secure-next-js-applications-with-role-based-authentication-using-nextauth/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/secure-next-js-applications-with-role-based-authentication-using-nextauth/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you create Next.js apps, chanced are you are going to have to include user authentication at some point.  We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that teaches how to implement authentication in Next.js 13.5 with the powerful library, NextAuth – which will soon be known]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Playground: From 5-Minute Install To Instant Spin-Up]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/wordpress-playground-5-minute-install-instant-spin-up/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/wordpress-playground-5-minute-install-instant-spin-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Playground began as an experiment to see what a self-hosted WordPress experience might look like without the requirement of having to actually install WordPress. A year later, the experiment has evolved into a full-fledged project. Ganesh Dahal demonstrates how WordPress Playground works and gets deep into how it might be used.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ganesh Dahal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Segment Anything Model (SAM) to Create Masks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-segment-anything-model-to-create-masks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-segment-anything-model-to-create-masks/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T20:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey there! So, you know that buzz about Tesla's autopilot being all futuristic and driverless? Ever thought about how it actually does its magic? Well, let me tell you – it's all about image segmentation and object detection.  What is Image Segmentation? Image segmentation, basically chopping up an image]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jess Wilk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Course in Spanish  – Learn JavaScript for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-course-in-spanish/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-course-in-spanish/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T16:25:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is one of the most popular programming languages out there, and it's essential for web development. Learning JavaScript can be your next step into this amazing world of web dev. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org Spanish YouTube channel [https://www.youtube.com/freecodecampespanol] that will teach you JavaScript from the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arduino for Everybody]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/arduino-for-everybody/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/arduino-for-everybody/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T15:12:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arduino is an open-source electronics platform that allows you to create interactive devices with sensors and outputs. With Arduino, you can build DIY electronics projects with minimal technical knowledge. We just published a comprehensive Arduino course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. The course covers the basics of Arduino, from hardware]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Online Résumé on AWS Using S3, Route 53, CloudFront, and ACM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/aws-project-build-a-resume/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/aws-project-build-a-resume/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T00:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're new to AWS, you can probably appreciate the sense of overwhelm that comes from trying to understand all the different services (seriously, like,  hundreds of them). What are they all for, and how do they work together?  And then once you've conquered some basic skills, the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amber Israelsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Avoid Prop Drilling in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/avoid-prop-drilling-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/avoid-prop-drilling-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T22:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In order to write scalable, reusable, and maintainable applications with React, you'll need to go beyond the surface of using React components, useEffect, useContext, useState, and the like. It involves learning in detail how React works in more depth.  And if you don't properly understand these key React concepts,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ogundiran Ayobami</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Whiteboard App with Python and Tkinter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-whiteboard-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-whiteboard-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T22:23:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn how to build a simple whiteboard app using Python and Tkinter. Some months ago, I was teaching a Python course. I was struggling to convey certain concepts because it was an online course, and I couldn't use a whiteboard or even a traditional board.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan P. Romano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Declare Variables in JavaScript – var, let, and const Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-declare-variables-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-declare-variables-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T22:16:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Declaring variables is something you'll do all the time in JavaScript. And if you know the variable declaration process inside and out, you'll have the confidence to start writing great JS code. Through this article, you will learn how to declare and mutate variables using  var, let, and const,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Furkan Emin Can</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Addressing Accessibility Concerns With Using Fluid Type]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/addressing-accessibility-concerns-fluid-type/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/addressing-accessibility-concerns-fluid-type/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS `clamp()` function is often paired with viewport units for “fluid” font sizing that scales the text up and down at different viewport sizes. As common as this technique is, several voices warn that it opens up situations where text can fail WCAG Success Criterion 1.4.4, which specifies that text should scale up to at least 200% when the user’s browser reaches its 500% maximum zoom level. Max Barvian takes a deep look at the issue and offers ideas to help address it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maxwell Barvian)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an Animated Hamburger Menu in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-animated-hamburger-menu-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-animated-hamburger-menu-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T17:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're looking to add some polished animations to your React apps, Framer Motion is the tool for the job.  In this tutorial, I'll walk you through creating a fully animated mobile menu using Framer Motion in React. What Are We Going to Build? In this tutorial, I'll guide]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yazdun Fadali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a WordPress Store that Sells Real AI-Generated Products]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-wordpress-store-that-sells-real-ai-generated-products/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-wordpress-store-that-sells-real-ai-generated-products/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T15:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The combination of artificial intelligence (AI) and web development has revolutionized the way we create and manage online content. I just created and released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use AI to help create an e-commerce store powered by WordPress. You will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Components that Work in Any Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/write-components-that-work-in-any-framework/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/write-components-that-work-in-any-framework/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T20:25:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The browser has a built-in way of writing reusable components in the form of web components. They’re an excellent choice for building interactive and reusable components that work in any frontend framework.  With that said, writing highly interactive and robust web components isn’t simple. They require a lot of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrico Karoulla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Trello and Stack Overflow Founder Joel Spolsky]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/trello-stack-overflow-founder-joel-spolsky-podcast-interview/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/trello-stack-overflow-founder-joel-spolsky-podcast-interview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-04T00:08:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I'm joined by Joel Spolsky. He's co-founder of Trello and Stack Overflow, and author of the iconic developer blog Joel on Software. I hung out with Joel in his New York City home to discuss his 4-decade-long career as a developer and a CEO. He shared his insights]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Call an API in JavaScript – with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/make-api-calls-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/make-api-calls-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T18:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calling an API (Application Programming Interface) in JavaScript is a fundamental action that web developers need to know how to perform. It allows you to fetch data from external sources and integrate it into your web applications.  In this tutorial, I'll walk you through the process of making API]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How TypeScript Helps You Write Better Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/benefits-of-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/benefits-of-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T15:16:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript is taking over the web. In this article I'll give you a high-level overview of the benefits of TypeScript and how can it help you create websites with fewer bugs.  You'll learn how TypeScript helps with handling edge cases, catching typos, refactoring code, and how types make code]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hunor Márton Borbély</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get started with Quarkus and JPAStreamer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-started-with-quarkus-and-jpastreamer-2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-started-with-quarkus-and-jpastreamer-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T14:32:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Note: This article is by Julia Gustafsson. In the world of software development, innovation often arrives in the form of powerful tools that transform the way we build applications - enter Quarkus, a development platform that's reshaping the Java landscape.  If you are new to the Quarkiverse, this tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julia Gustafsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktoberfest 2023 Contributors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hacktoberfest-2023-contributors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hacktoberfest-2023-contributors/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T00:03:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The freeCodeCamp community just finished participating in this year's Hacktoberfest – a month-long celebration of open source. Our core team is excited to recognize all of our wonderful open source contributors. A big thank you to all of these folks for the effort they put into helping improve our curriculum]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Naomi Carrigan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Helper Functions in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/helper-functions-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/helper-functions-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T20:11:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Helper functions in React.js are like your trusty assistants, and they play a crucial role in simplifying complex tasks. When these functions are well-structured, they make your code easier to read, maintain, and reuse.  In this article, we'll explore the significance of helper functions in React.js projects. We'll also]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adeeko Tobiloba Israel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Web Development with This Free 20-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-web-development-with-this-free-20-hour-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-web-development-with-this-free-20-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T17:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a complete beginner interested in learning web development? Look no further! We just published a comprehensive course about web development with HTML and CSS on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This course is thoughtfully designed and taught by Aakash N S, the CEO and co-founder of Jovian, a platform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Search Of The Ideal Privacy Icon]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/search-ideal-privacy-icon/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/search-ideal-privacy-icon/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Icons are capable of enhancing the content that surrounds them, but they have to be self-explanatory for that to happen. We have icons for things we like (a thumbs up), things we can share (a box topped with an up arrow), and even for protection against malicious online attacks (a shield), but what are the options we have for representing “privacy”?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Sam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Accessibility Tips for Developers – A11y Principles Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-accessibility-for-devs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-accessibility-for-devs/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T14:17:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Delete Check Send Add]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adeola Ajiboso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn to Code & Get a Developer Job [Full Book]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-code-book/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-code-book/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T23:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to learn to code and get a job as a developer, you're in the right place. This book will show you how. And yes this is the full book – for free – right here on this page of freeCodeCamp. Update October 20, 2023: I've recorded a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Cypress for End-to-End Testing Your React Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cypress-for-end-to-end-testing-react-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cypress-for-end-to-end-testing-react-apps/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T22:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is a popular framework for building web applications. It's is one of the best options for frontend engineering because of its declarative approach to user interface design and component-based architecture.  But it can be difficult to make sure your React application functions as intended in various different scenarios.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okosa Leonard Onyekachukwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create and Deploy IaC by Chatting with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-and-deploy-iac-by-chatting-with-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-and-deploy-iac-by-chatting-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T13:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infrastructure as Code (IaC) is a revolutionary approach to managing and provisioning computing infrastructure. With IaC, you can automate the process of provisioning, configuring, and managing infrastructure using code and software development techniques. This approach provides a more efficient, consistent, and reliable way of managing infrastructure compared to traditional manual]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Loop Through Arrays in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/loop-through-arrays-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/loop-through-arrays-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looping through arrays in JavaScript is a fundamental concept that every JavaScript developer should understand. Whether you're a beginner or an experienced developer, understanding how to loop through an array is crucial for many programming tasks.  In this article, we'll explore the different ways to loop through an array]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Answering Common Questions About Interpreting Page Speed Reports]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/answering-questions-interpreting-page-speed-reports/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/answering-questions-interpreting-page-speed-reports/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a closer look at how various performance tools audit and report on performance metrics, such as core web vitals. Geoff Graham answers a set of common questions that pop up during performance audits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tales Of November (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T09:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November is just around the corner, and with it, a new collection of desktop wallpapers to celebrate the beginning of the month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Let’s make this November colorful!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Scrape Amazon Product Reviews Behind a Login]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-scrape-amazon-product-reviews-behind-a-login/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-scrape-amazon-product-reviews-behind-a-login/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T16:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon is the most popular e-commerce website for web scrapers, with billions of product pages being scraped every month.  It is also home to a vast database of product reviews, which can be very useful for market research and competitor monitoring.  You can extract relevant data from the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Satyam Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin and Android Development – Build a Chat App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kotlin-and-android-development-build-a-chat-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kotlin-and-android-development-build-a-chat-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T16:24:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to dive into the world of Android development using Kotlin? We just posted a 10-hour Android course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Alexandru Cristian created this course. I will help you understand how to develop with Kotlin and Android. This course will take you on a journey]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automate Data Exports and Email Reports with Python – a Step-by-Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-data-exports-email-reports-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-data-exports-email-reports-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T16:08:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's data-driven world, automation is key to streamlining tasks and saving time. In this beginner-friendly tutorial, I'll walk you through the process of automating data exports from a PostgreSQL database and sending them as an email attachment using Python.  This step-by-step guide will help you grasp the fundamentals]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Frameworks vs Custom CSS – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-frameworks-vs-custom-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-frameworks-vs-custom-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T14:51:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to styling web pages, CSS or Cascading Style Sheets is the go-to tool for web developers. CSS is what gives your website that visually appealing look and feel, from colors and fonts to layout and positioning.  But there are two distinct approaches to applying CSS: using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys: A No-Frills Explainer On The Future Of Password-Less Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/passkeys-explainer-future-password-less-authentication/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/passkeys-explainer-future-password-less-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys are beginning to make their way into popular apps, from password managers to multi-factor authenticators, but what exactly are they? As this new technology promises to make passwords a thing of the past, Neal Fennimore explains the concepts behind passkeys, demonstrates how they work, and speculates what we might expect from them in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Neal Fennimore)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Overcoming 3 Layoffs with Senior Dev Kevin Miller]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-kevin-miller-coder-conversations/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-kevin-miller-coder-conversations/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T17:22:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's podcast, I interview Kevin Miller. He's a senior developer and host of the Coder Conversations YouTube channel. Kevin studied accounting in Texas and worked overnight for 7 years at hotels, making only $11 an hour. But his knowledge of spreadsheets lead to him learning more about]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I Wish I Knew About Working In Development Right Out Of School]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/beginner-web-development-working-career/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/beginner-web-development-working-career/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Victoria Johnson began a career in front-end development upon graduating from college. Now, roughly one year later, she reflects back on the decisions she made to crack into the field and find her first full-time job. This is her story, and she’s sharing it to provide those who are just starting out with another beginner’s perspective.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victoria Johnson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Good Documentation with Docsify]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-good-documentation-with-docsify/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-good-documentation-with-docsify/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T19:21:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Documentation is critical to a successful product. Without documentation, it's more difficult for people to use your product, and it's just as important if you're running an open-source project, too. Creating a documentation site can be challenging, especially if you're not familiar with front-end development.  I have been a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Created a SQL-like Language to Run Queries on Local Git Repositories]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gql-design-and-implementation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gql-design-and-implementation/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! I'm a Software engineer who's interested in low-level programming, compilers, and tool development.  Three months ago I decided to learn the Rust programming language and build a Git client that focuses on simplicity and productivity. ‌I started to think about how I could build the Git client]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amr Hesham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Algorithmic Trading Using Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-algorithmic-trading-using-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-algorithmic-trading-using-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T12:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the realm of financial markets, algorithmic trading has revolutionized the way trades are executed, providing a systematic approach to analyzing data and making investment decisions. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to implement algorithmic trading with Python using a variety]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Actionable And Reliable Usability Questionnaire With Only 7 Items: <span style="font-variant: small-caps">Inuit</span>]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/actionable-reliable-usability-questionnaire-inuit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/actionable-reliable-usability-questionnaire-inuit/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inuit (short for “**In**terface **U**sability **I**nstrumen**t**”) is a new questionnaire you can use to assess the usability of your user interface. It has been designed to be more diagnostic than existing usability instruments like, e.g., SUS and for use with machine learning, all the while asking fewer questions than other questionnaires. This article explores how and why Inuit has been developed and why we can be sure that it actually measures usability, and reliably so.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maximilian Speicher &amp; Johanna Jagow)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Structure JSON Responses in ChatGPT with Function Calling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-json-back-from-chatgpt-with-function-calling/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-json-back-from-chatgpt-with-function-calling/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T18:09:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT's Problem With JSON Open up the ChatGPT UI [https://chat.openai.com/] and ask it for some JSON. Chances are you will get a response like you can see in the cover photo above: a JSON object presented to you in markdown format, with some text to either side explaining what the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Charlesworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn MySQL – Beginner's Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-mysql-beginners-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-mysql-beginners-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T12:43:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Databases have become an integral part of storing and managing data efficiently. MySQL, a widely used open-source relational database management system, empowers users to handle data in a structured manner, facilitating easier retrieval and manipulation of information. Understanding MySQL is vital for developers, data analysts, and anyone aspiring to delve]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fight For The Main Thread]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/speedcurve-fight-main-thread/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/speedcurve-fight-main-thread/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having access to a free reporting tool like Lighthouse in DevTools is a great start for diagnosing performance issues by identifying bottlenecks on the main thread. Even better are paid tools like [SpeedCurve](https://www.speedcurve.com/?utm_source=smashingmag&utm_medium=magazine&utm_campaign=sm7_2023&utm_id=sm7_2023&utm_term=sm7_2023) to dig deeper into the data for more targeted insights and to produce visual reports to help make a case for performance improvements for your team and other stakeholders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Host and Deploy a React App with Firebase]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-a-react-app-with-firebase/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-a-react-app-with-firebase/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T15:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a front-end developer, you may have used a free hosting platform like Vercel, Netlify, or GitHub pages to deploy your front-end projects. Personally, I typically use Vercel and Netlify. But I also like trying out different web technologies, and I've used Firebase's authentication and storage features on different projects]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juliet Ofoegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning Fundamentals Handbook – Key Concepts, Algorithms, and Python Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T14:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're planning to become a Machine Learning Engineer, Data Scientist, or you want to refresh your memory before your interviews, this handbook is for you.  In it, we'll cover the key Machine Learning algorithms you'll need to know as a Data Scientist, Machine Learning Engineer, Machine Learning Researcher,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tatev Karen Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose the Right Build Tool for Your Java Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/choose-the-right-build-tool-for-your-java-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/choose-the-right-build-tool-for-your-java-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T14:57:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of Java development, selecting the right build tool is a crucial decision. Build tools automate various tasks, making the development process smoother and more efficient.  In this article, we'll explore three popular build tools used in Java development: Maven, Gradle, and Ant. We'll discuss their features,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Swap the Values of Two Variables Without a Temporary Variable in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/swapping-values-of-two-variables-without-a-temporary-variable-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/swapping-values-of-two-variables-without-a-temporary-variable-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T14:50:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swapping the values of two variables is a common task in programming. While the most straightforward approach involves using a temporary variable, Python provides several elegant techniques to achieve the same result without the need for that extra variable.  In this tutorial, we will take a look at some]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isah Jacob</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard CS50 – Free Computer Science Course (2023 Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/harvard-university-cs50-computer-science-course-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/harvard-university-cs50-computer-science-course-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T12:43:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard University's CS50 is one of the most popular beginner computer science courses in the world. We just released the entire 26-hour CS50 course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This is the updated 2023 edition of the course. Dr. David J. Malan is widely considered to be one of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Excel as a New Developer and Beat the Dunning-Kruger Trap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-dunning-kruger-effect/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-dunning-kruger-effect/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T21:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Dunning-Kruger Effect? Hey there, fellow developers! Imagine this. You've just landed your first tech job or maybe you're fresh out of a coding boot camp/university. You're pumped, excited, and ready to show the world with everything you've got.  But wait a minute—ever heard of the Dunning-Kruger]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Ren Jie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Center Text Vertically with CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-center-text-vertically-with-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-center-text-vertically-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T19:44:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have some text inside a div, and nothing else, the div's height will match the text height. Suppose, though, you have some text and an image. Your text will be aligned at the bottom of the div, which is usually not what you want. In this article, you'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Attardi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Writing for Developers – Why You Should Have a Blog and How to Start One]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/technical-writing-for-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/technical-writing-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T17:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having a blog is a useful asset for developers. It can be a lead magnet, as well as a place where you can sell digital products you create.  It can also simply be the place where you build a loyal audience within your niche, share your knowledge and ideas,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankur Tyagi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Docker Containers Work – Explained for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-docker-containers-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-docker-containers-work/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T16:45:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A container is a lightweight, standalone, and executable software package that includes everything needed to run a piece of software. And one of the most popular tools for working with containers is Docker. Docker is both the name of the company (Docker Inc) and the software they have created which]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>