<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-03-01T00:59:57.972Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Methods in Java – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-methods/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-methods/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T20:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Methods are essential for organizing Java projects, encouraging code reuse, and improving overall code structure.  In this article, we will look at what Java methods are and how they work, including their syntax, types, and examples. Here's what we'll cover:  1. What are Java Methods?  2. Types]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Syslog Handbook – How to Collect and Redirect Logs to a Remote Server]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-syslog-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-syslog-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T19:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're in information technology, you'll likely agree that logging is important. It helps you monitor a system, troubleshoot issues, and generally provides useful feedback about the system’s state. But it’s important to do logging right. In this handbook, I'll explain what the syslog protocol is and how it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Serhii Orlivskyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Gemini Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-gemini-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-gemini-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T18:47:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Gemini is a cutting edge AI model that is a competitor of GPT-4.  We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you harness the power of the advanced AI technology. Developed by the popular instructor Ania Kubów, this beginner's course offers a deep]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Machine Learning in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-machine-learning-in-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-machine-learning-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T17:38:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you curious about machine learning but don't know where to start? We just published a comprehensive Machine Learning course on the freeCodeCamp.org  that will teach you how to get started in 2024. Whether you're aspiring to become a Data Scientist, a Machine Learning Engineer (MLE), a Product Manager, or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Mobile Quiz App with React Native, ChatGPT and Supabase]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-mobile-quiz-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-mobile-quiz-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T17:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn how to build a mobile quiz application that authenticates users, allows them to take tests, and ranks them based on their scores.  The application leverages some of Supabase's features, such as authentication and database storage, to build a secured full-stack mobile application. Additionally, you'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Asaolu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build A House Price Prediction Model – Linear Regression Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-house-price-prediction-model/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-house-price-prediction-model/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T13:25:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever wondered how algorithms predict future house prices, stock market trends, or even your next movie preference? The answer lies in a fundamental yet powerful tool called linear regression.  Don't be fooled by its seemingly simple equation – this article will unveil its magic, empowering you to build and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwadamisi Samuel Praise</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Apply Math with Python – Numerical Analysis Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/numerical-analysis-explained-how-to-apply-math-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/numerical-analysis-explained-how-to-apply-math-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T11:41:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Numerical analysis is the bridge between math and computer science.  Essentially, it is the development of algorithms that approximate solutions that pure math would also solve, but using less computational resources and faster. This field is very important. Because for most solutions in the real world, we only need]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waiting For Spring (March 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new batch of desktop wallpapers is for you. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for March 2024. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Access Properties from an Array of Objects in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-access-properties-from-an-array-of-objects-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-access-properties-from-an-array-of-objects-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T00:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with JavaScript applications, it's common to work with arrays, nested arrays, and an array of objects. But a lot of beginners sometimes struggle with knowing how to access properties from these different data structures. In this article, we will discuss how to access properties from a variety]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Idempotence? Explained with Real-World Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/idempotence-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/idempotence-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T00:44:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Idempotence is a property of an operation that ensures that, if the operation is repeated once or more than once, you get the same result. Apply it once or more and the outcome's the same, idempotence is the name. All rhyming aside, idempotence is an important concept often used in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless Node.js Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serverless-node-js-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serverless-node-js-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T20:59:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The shift towards serverless architectures is rapidly becoming a pivotal aspect of application development. Even Node.js, which is traditionally used with servers, can be used to build a serverless application. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to develop serverless applications using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Reusable React Components]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-reusable-react-components/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-reusable-react-components/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T19:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are reusable React components? You can think of them as building blocks. They are independent pieces of code that can be reused throughout your website to save you time and effort. They can be anything from simple buttons to complex forms. Why Use Reusable Components? As your website grows,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shahan Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do Open Source Licenses Work? Permissive and Protective Software Licenses Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/permissive-and-protective-software-licenses/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/permissive-and-protective-software-licenses/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T17:07:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're going to use or work with open source resources, you'll need to understand the fine print on various classes of an open source license. Otherwise, how can you be sure you're not infringing on someone else's rights?  This article will introduce you to the big players and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Music Bot Using Discord.js – Step-by-Step Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-music-bot-using-discord-js-4436f5f3f0f8/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-music-bot-using-discord-js-4436f5f3f0f8/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Discord API provides you with an easy tool to create and use your own bots and tools.  In this tutorial, you'll learn how you can create a basic music bot and add it to your server. The bot will be able to play, skip, and stop the music,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabriel Tanner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build A Text Summarizer Using Huggingface Transformers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-text-summarizer-using-huggingface-transformers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-text-summarizer-using-huggingface-transformers/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T10:13:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s fast-paced world, we’re bombarded with information. It’s like trying to drink water from a fire hose. That's where a text summarizer comes in. Imagine it as a filter that separates the essential bits from the overwhelming flood of words. In this article, I'll walk you through what a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regular Expressions (RegEx) in JavaScript – A Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/regex-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/regex-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T20:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regular expressions, also known as regex, are powerful tools for pattern matching and text manipulation. Whether you're validating user input, extracting data from strings, or performing advanced text processing tasks, understanding regex is essential for developers. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the fundamentals of regular expressions in JavaScript,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samyak Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Render an Array of Components in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-render-array-of-components-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-render-array-of-components-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T19:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, I will show you how using indices to render an array of components in React can be problematic. I'll also teach you how to mitigate array rendering issues with unique ids. As always, we'll work on a real world example and solve problem I stumbled across while]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Generative AI in 30 Hours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-generative-ai-in/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-generative-ai-in/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T18:25:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving landscape of artificial intelligence, staying ahead of the curve is important for both enthusiasts and professionals alike. And one of the most popular elements of AI right now is Generative AI. We just posted a comprehensive course about Generative AI on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This course,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How TypeScript Generics Work – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-typescript-generics-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-typescript-generics-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T13:45:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript, with its powerful type system, offers a feature called Generics, which enables developers to write reusable and type-safe code. Generics allow you to create components that can work over a variety of types rather than a single one. This article delves into TypeScript Generics, providing thorough explanations and code]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Ternary Operator in JavaScript – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-ternary-operator-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-ternary-operator-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T13:04:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tired of bulky if-else statements? JavaScript's ternary operator offers a powerful solution. This handy tool lets you condense complex conditional logic into a single line, making your code cleaner, more elegant, and efficient. In this article, we'll take a deep dive into the ternary operator, understanding its syntax and showcasing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Franklin Okolie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reporting Core Web Vitals With The Performance API]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/reporting-core-web-vitals-performance-api/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/reporting-core-web-vitals-performance-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Performance API is a set of standards for measuring and evaluating performance metrics with JavaScript. This article demonstrates how to use the Performance API to generate performance metrics directly in the DOM to create your own reporting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Tailwind CSS to Your React Native Expo App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tailwindcss-in-react-native-expo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tailwindcss-in-react-native-expo/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T09:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tailwind CSS has been quite popular in the web development world due to its utility-first approach and seamless integration.  However, when developing mobile apps with React Native, integrating Tailwind CSS may be challenging. But guess what? Not anymore. With the development of tools such as NativeWind [https://www.nativewind.dev/], React Native]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Caleb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Essential SQL Concepts for Data Analysts – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-concepts-for-data-analysts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-concepts-for-data-analysts/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T00:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the vast and ever-growing realm of data analytics, Structured Query Language [/news/what-is-sql-database-definition-for-beginners/] (SQL) serves as a fundamental building block.  While SQL's roots lie in database management, it has expanded its reach, becoming the go-to tool for data extraction, manipulation, and analysis.  Whether you're just starting your journey]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Hereth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Publish Google Docs to WordPress in an SEO-Optimized Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/publish-google-docs-to-wordpress/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/publish-google-docs-to-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T23:21:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress is a popular content management system (CMS) known for its flexibility and user-friendly interface. But its built-in editor is not ideal for collaborative editing. Many publishers who work with writers need collaborative writing and editing features. This is where Google Docs comes into the picture. It’s a collaborative platform,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikram Aruchamy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Geolocation API in JavaScript – with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-javascript-geolocation-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-javascript-geolocation-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T22:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Geolocation API is a standard API implemented in browsers to retrieve the location of the people who are interacting with a web application. This API enable users to send their location to a web application to enable relevant services, such as seeking a restaurant or hotel near the user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn the Hard Parts of React – and Tips to Conquer Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hard-parts-of-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hard-parts-of-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T21:07:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you started learning React, only to face bugs that made you contemplate a career in goat herding? Don't worry – we've all been there.  In this guide, you'll join me on a quest through the quirky wonders of React. I'll help you navigate the perplexing moments, ensuring you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perform Performance Testing on Your Web Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/performance-testing-for-web-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/performance-testing-for-web-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T19:52:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Performance testing is an important yet underrated field of software development. And it’s a must-have skill that can help you prevent common software failures that occur in production applications.  Performance testing is a routine software practice which is carried out to determine the stability of a system in terms]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oluwatobi Joshua</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Web Designer’s Accessibility Advocacy Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-designer-accessibility-advocacy-toolkit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-designer-accessibility-advocacy-toolkit/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital designer Yichan Wang has put together this collection of strategies and selling points to help you encourage and advocate for accessibility in your place of work, including useful scripts you can use as starting points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yichan Wang)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced CSS Selectors – How and When to Use Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-css-selectors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-css-selectors/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T17:12:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing CSS is often painful for a lot of developers, because many of us lose our curiosity very early in the learning journey. For instance, as soon as we learn basic CSS selectors, we settle into a pattern of using only those, thinking they're all we need. But what if]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ophy Boamah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work with Redux-Thunk – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-redux-thunk/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-redux-thunk/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T02:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redux has become the go-to state management library for many JavaScript applications due to its predictable state container and unidirectional data flow. However, handling asynchronous actions in Redux can be a bit tricky. That's where Redux middleware like Redux-Thunk comes to the rescue. In essence, Redux-Thunk enhances the capabilities of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Configure Google Workspace Addon For Tier 2 CASA Security Assessment – Step by Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tier-casa-security-assessment/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tier-casa-security-assessment/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T16:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of the Google CASA process [https://appdefensealliance.dev/casa], developers can run static analysis on their application’s source code using an inline integration with OpenText’s Fortify Source Code Analyzer (SCA) via the CASA portal. Naturally, I had to prepare my source code as per instruction. In this article, I will share]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nibesh Khadka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: What it's like working at ChatGPT Creator Open AI. My Interview with Logan Kilpatrick]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-chatgpt-open-ai-logan-kilpatrick/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-chatgpt-open-ai-logan-kilpatrick/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T16:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Logan Kilpatric, a software engineer and ChatGPT creator Open AI's first-ever Developer Advocate hire. The week Logan started, ChatGPT hit 100 million users. During our conversation, Logan shares his journey from Illinois to Harvard, NASA, and now the world's most-watched tech]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Fetch API For Beginners – Explained With Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-fetch-api-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-fetch-api-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T12:14:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fetch API is a JavaScript function that you can use to send a request to any Web API URL and get a response. In this article, I'm going to show you how to make HTTP requests to external APIs using the JavaScript Fetch API. You're going to learn how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How TypeScript Interfaces Work – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-typescript-interfaces-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-typescript-interfaces-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T10:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript, a superset of JavaScript, has gained widespread adoption among developers due to its ability to provide static typing, enhancing code robustness and maintainability. One of TypeScript's key features is interfaces, which play a pivotal role in defining the shape of objects, enabling type checking and facilitating better code organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Camera App on the Web – No Plugins Required]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-camera-app-on-the-web/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-camera-app-on-the-web/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T00:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever had to make a video call right on your browser with Google Meet, Zoom, or any other video chat app? Well, here’s what you might have never thought to ask—how does it work? Well, there are a number of things that make a real-time video chat application fully functional]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Favour C. Felix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanilla JavaScript, Libraries, And The Quest For Stateful DOM Rendering]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/vanilla-javascript-libraries-quest-stateful-dom-rendering/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/vanilla-javascript-libraries-quest-stateful-dom-rendering/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s well-established that the web faces wide-ranging usability and performance issues, from user-hostile UI patterns and twisted search results to sluggish performance and battery-draining bloat. In this article, Frederik examines one small-but-significant aspect where developers take the reins: Painting pixels on the screen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederik Dohr)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the :has() Selector in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-has-selector-in-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-has-selector-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T14:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For most of the history of CSS, selectors have been limited to targeting elements based on their parents in the DOM tree. Consider this HTML structure: 
     
Paragraph 1
       
     	
Paragraph 2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Charlesworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use the Fullscreen API in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-use-full-screen-api-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-use-full-screen-api-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T14:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you run a game created for the web in fullscreen? In this quick tutorial, you'll see how to display a game or any other HTML element in fullscreen, how to exit fullscreen, and how to make a nice fullscreen toggle button in SVG. Recently I published a long]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hunor Márton Borbély</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the JavaScript Map and Set Objects – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-map-and-set-objects-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-map-and-set-objects-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T21:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Map and Set are two JavaScript data structures you can use to store a collection of values, similar to Objects and Arrays. They are specialized data structures that can help you store and manipulate related values.  In this tutorial, we will see how Map and Set work in detail]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure AI Fundamentals Certification (AI-900) 2024 UPDATE – Pass the Exam With This Free 4 Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/azure-data-fundamentals-certification-ai-900-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-4-hour-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/azure-data-fundamentals-certification-ai-900-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-4-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T15:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Azure AI Fundamentals Certification is for those seeking a Machine Learning role such as AI Engineer or Data Scientist. The certification has recently been updated for 2024 and I've released an updated course to teach you how to pass the exam. In the last decade companies have been collecting]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Brown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Type Aliases work in TypeScript – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-typescript-type-aliases-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-typescript-type-aliases-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T14:14:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of TypeScript's powerful features is type aliases, which allow developers to create custom names for types, enhancing code readability and maintainability. In this article, we'll explore TypeScript type aliases through examples. Table of Contents  * TypeScript Type Aliases  * Examples  * Conclusion What are Type Aliases]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use Node Version Manager In Your React Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-nvm-in-react-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-nvm-in-react-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T13:51:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide,  you'll learn how to effectively manage multiple Node versions for different projects using Node Version Manager (NVM). Whether you're developing React, Angular, Vue.js, or Node applications, you can always use NVM to set up the project and tailor it down to a specific Node version. Prerequisites Before]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Debug Coding Problems When Building Your Own Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/debug-coding-problems-in-your-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/debug-coding-problems-in-your-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T21:47:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ah, the joy of coding! There you are, cruising through your project, when suddenly – bam! – you hit a bug. It's like hitting a wall in a maze. But fear not, fellow coder, for I bring you the trusty map to navigate the treacherous bug-infested waters of programming. Whether]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Blakely</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use LocalStorage in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-local-storage-in-modern-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-local-storage-in-modern-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T21:37:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In modern web development, having a way to persist data helps developers improve performance and create a better user experience. And using local storage is an effective way of persisting data in an application. In this article, you will learn what local storage is and how to use it in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Types Work in TypeScript – Explained with JavaScript + TypeScript Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/basic-typescript-types/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/basic-typescript-types/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T21:05:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript is a superset of JavaScript that introduces static typing to JavaScript. TypeScript's enhanced type safety and code maintainability empower developers to write code more confidently. A fundamental aspect of TypeScript's static typing system is its support for basic types. These provide a foundation for defining the shape and behavior]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Python Basics – A Guide for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-python-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-python-basics/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T19:04:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you eager to dive into the world of programming but unsure where to begin? Look no further – Python is an excellent starting point for both newcomers and seasoned developers.  In this guide, I'll take you through the basics so you can get started on your Python journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chepkirui dorothy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Entering into the World of Concurrency with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/concurrency-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/concurrency-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T18:53:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we will explore concurrency in Python. We'll discuss Threads and Processes and how they're similar and different. You'll also learn about Multi-threading, Multi-processing, Asynchronous Programming, and Concurrency in general in Python.  Many tutorials discuss these concepts, but they can be challenging to grasp due to the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hemachandra Routhu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Data Structures and Algorithms in 48 Hours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-data-structures-and-algorithms-2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-data-structures-and-algorithms-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T18:20:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the realm of software development, mastering Data Structures and Algorithms could be a critical step towards securing your dream job.  We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will equip you with the knowledge to excel in coding interviews and problem-solving. You will learn the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Console Logging Tips – How to Debug and Understand Your Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/console-logging-tips/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/console-logging-tips/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T18:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Console logging is an essential tool for developers to use to debug and understand the behavior of their code.  While most developers are familiar with basic console logging using  console.log(), there are many other powerful methods provided by the console object that can make debugging more efficient and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS Flexbox in Spanish – Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-flexbox-in-spanish-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-flexbox-in-spanish-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T15:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With CSS Flexbox, you can easily create responsive websites that adapt to different screen sizes and devices. It's an essential skill for any modern web developer. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org Spanish YouTube channel [https://www.youtube.com/freecodecampespanol] that will teach you Flexbox from the fundamentals. By the end of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Practical Guide To Designing For Colorblind People]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-for-colorblindness/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-for-colorblindness/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Color accessibility is more than just ticking boxes. Even with good contrast, some color palettes can make interfaces challenging for users. Here are some practical guidelines to ensure more inclusive design for colorblind people. An upcoming part of Smart Interface Design Patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Connect a Domain Name to a Website Hosted on AWS EC2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-connect-a-domain-to-a-website-hosted-on-aws-ec2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-connect-a-domain-to-a-website-hosted-on-aws-ec2/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T23:51:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may want to host your website on a virtual private server or a virtual machine like AWS EC2. But it can be a challenge to connect a domain name that you purchased from providers like Namecheap or Godaddy. But if you know the steps to follow, this doesn't have]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Obed Ehoneah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How JavaScript's Reduce Method Works – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-reduce-method-code-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-reduce-method-code-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T18:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduced alongside other array methods in ECMAScript 5, reduce() offers a unique and powerful way to transform arrays into single values.  In this article, you'll learn about the reduce() method by understanding what it is, its syntax, and finally you'll see some use cases where you can use it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set up Swiper Element in a React Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-swiper-element-in-a-react-application/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-swiper-element-in-a-react-application/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T16:25:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carousels or image sliders are an integral part of many web applications. They help you group multiple elements in a single view. Using carousels, you can implement image slides, video slides, text slides, interactive image galleries, product catalogs, team profiles, and more. Swiper.js [https://swiperjs.com/] comes with powerful functionalities that make]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Anie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile Accessibility Barriers For Assistive Technology Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/mobile-accessibility-barriers-assistive-technology-users/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/mobile-accessibility-barriers-assistive-technology-users/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility goes beyond making products user-friendly. It can significantly impact the quality of life for people with disabilities. Kate Kalcevich shares lessons she learned from assistive technology users — challenges and barriers they encounter on mobile devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep Learning Fundamentals Handbook – What You Need to Know to Start Your Career in AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deep-learning-fundamentals-handbook-start-a-career-in-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deep-learning-fundamentals-handbook-start-a-career-in-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T23:47:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to get into the field of Artificial Intelligence (AI), one of the most in-demand career paths these days, you've come to the right place. Learning Deep Learning Fundamentals is your essential first step to learning about Computer Vision, Natural Language Processing (NLP), Large Language Models, the creative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tatev Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: How the Insane Pressure of Classical Music Prepared Jessica Wilkins for Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-jessica-wilkins-classical-music-learning-to-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-jessica-wilkins-classical-music-learning-to-code/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T18:47:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview orchestral musician-turned software engineer Jessica Wilkins. Jessica found success in the extremely competitive field of classical music, playing the Oboe in orchestras, recording sessions, and even at major events such as the NFL awards on national television. She started her own]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flexbox vs Grid in CSS – Which Should You Use?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flexbox-vs-grid-in-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flexbox-vs-grid-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T11:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever had issues with replicating a particular user interface from a Figma design? Do you find it difficult displaying elements in different sections of your browser screen? A major cause of rift between user interface (UI) designers and frontend developers is the issue of having an awesome UI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maybell Obadoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Optimization Techniques to Help You Write More Performant Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-performance-optimization-techniques/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-performance-optimization-techniques/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T00:57:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Performance optimization is a critical aspect of developing web applications. Users expect applications to load quickly and respond to their interactions smoothly.  In the React ecosystem, performance optimization techniques can significantly enhance the user experience by reducing load times and improving responsiveness. In this article, we will discuss eight]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temitope Oyedele</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get the Most of Video Coding Tutorials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-the-most-out-of-video-coding-tutorials/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-the-most-out-of-video-coding-tutorials/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T00:50:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever spent hours watching a coding tutorial, only to get to the end and feel like you haven't learned very much?  We've all been there, and it can be a frustrating experience when learning to code.  In this article, I will show you some of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Blakely</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Argo Workflows on Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-argo-workflows-on-kubernetes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-argo-workflows-on-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T23:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argo Workflows is an open source project that enables the orchestration of multiple Kubernetes jobs. Argo Workflows is implemented as a Kubernetes custom resource definition (CRD), which means it is native to the Kubernetes ecosystem and can run on any Kubernetes cluster. Workflows are set steps by which individual jobs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abraham Dahunsi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the JavaScript Filter Method Works – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-filter-method/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-filter-method/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T23:08:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript's filter method serves as a powerful tool for selectively extracting elements from arrays based on certain conditions.  Introduced alongside other array methods in ECMAScript 5, the filter method has since become a fundamental feature in JavaScript programming. In this article, we will delve into the JavaScript filter method,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript in the Browser – How the Document Object Model (DOM) and Events Work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-in-the-browser-dom-and-events/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-in-the-browser-dom-and-events/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T20:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this in-depth tutorial, you'll learn all about the Document Object Model, or DOM for short. As a web developer, understanding the DOM is fundamental for interacting with web browsers and creating dynamic web applications.  Throughout this guide, we will explore the DOM's hierarchical tree structure, essential properties, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samyak Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn SvelteKit in 2 hours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-sveltekit-full-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-sveltekit-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T18:47:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SvelteKit is the next evolution of Svelte, a modern JavaScript framework that compiles your code to highly efficient, vanilla JavaScript at build time. It's a great framework to learn for developers seeking to hone their skills or dive into modern web frameworks. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to Make Art with Code – p5.js Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/art-of-coding-with-p5js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/art-of-coding-with-p5js/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T18:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[p5.js is a JavaScript library that's transforming the way artists and designers approach make art with code. If you're intrigued by the intersection of art and programming, freeCodeCamp's YouTube course on p5.js is an ideal starting point.  Patt Vira created this course. She loves making art with code and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Draw with JavaScript on an HTML Canvas Element – Gorilla Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-draw-a-gorilla-with-javascript-on-html-canvas/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-draw-a-gorilla-with-javascript-on-html-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T16:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drawing from code can be fun for many reasons. You can generate art that follows a certain logic. You can create animations by moving only parts of an image. And you can even build up a whole game as I covered in this tutorial [/news/gorillas-game-in-javascript/]. In my last article, we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hunor Márton Borbély</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Chrome DevTools – Simple Strategies for Smarter Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chrome-devtools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chrome-devtools/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T16:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a web developer, there are many tools out there – in addition to your code editor – that can make you more efficient.  It doesn't matter if you're just starting out or have been coding for years. Knowing how to effectively use Developer Tools (DevTools for short) can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ophy Boamah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the App Directory in Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/app-directory-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/app-directory-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T00:52:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building a project using the latest version of Next.js, you'll be prompted to select between using the app/ directory or the pages/ directory. The  app/ directory is now the recommended way of building apps in Next.js. In this article, you'll learn how to maximize the potential of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Oghenetejiri Ukumakube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Map Method – Syntax and Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-map-method/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-map-method/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T00:50:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript's map method, introduced in ECMAScript 5, is a fundamental tool for array manipulation and transformation. This method is versatile and simple, and has become a staple in modern JavaScript programming.  In this article, we'll explore the map method's syntax and its wide array of applications, ranging from basic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Custom React Hook – a Hands-on Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-custom-react-hooks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-custom-react-hooks/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T17:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have been working with React, I bet you've had the opportunity to use hooks. But have you ever tried to create your own hook?  Today I will help you create your first custom hook and explain how they can improve your codebase. Why Create Custom Hooks? You]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dive into Backend Development by Building a CRUD API with Node and MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crud-api-with-node-js-express-mongodb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crud-api-with-node-js-express-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T15:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A key part of most backend development projects is CRUD.  We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will throw you into the world of backend development by guiding you through building a CRUD API from scratch. You will use Node.js, Express, and MongoDB. The course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Accessibility Standards Can Empower Better Chart Visual Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/accessibility-standards-empower-better-chart-visual-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/accessibility-standards-empower-better-chart-visual-design/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility for data visualization extends well beyond web standards, at least if you’re trying to create an experience that’s actually useful. This article focuses on techniques for creating useful and accessible visualizations that extend well beyond compliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kent Eisenhuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with Golang – a Developer Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/golang-developer-roadmap/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/golang-developer-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Go programming language – also known as Golang – is now almost 15 years old. And it's become a popular choice for web development and microservices thanks to its performance and efficient resource utilisation.  Go jobs are also quite well-paid. As per the Glassdoor report [https://www.glassdoor.com/Salaries/golang-developer-salary-SRCH_KO0,16.htm?countryPickerRedirect=true] , the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubham Chadokar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How JavaScript Promises Work – Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-promises-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-promises-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T23:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many operations, such as network requests, are asynchronous in nature. One of the most useful and powerful tools for working with asynchronous code is the Promise. In this handbook, you'll learn all about JavaScript Promises and how to use them. Table of Contents  1.  What is a Promise?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Attardi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optional Chaining in JavaScript – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/optional-chaining-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/optional-chaining-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T21:54:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript development often involves navigating through nested objects, which can be cumbersome and error-prone, especially when dealing with null or  undefined values. Enter optional chaining—a game-changer in modern JavaScript syntax. In this article, we'll explore optional chaining through practical examples, demonstrating how it streamlines code and makes development more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best CSS Frameworks to Use in Your Projects for 2024 and Beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-css-frameworks-for-frontend-devs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-css-frameworks-for-frontend-devs/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T21:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS has come a long way over the past few years. In the past, you'd use CSS to create simple-looking web applications that rely on HTML tables and CSS floats as their layout systems. And now you can architect complex interactive user interfaces that are appealing with elegant designs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Ikechukwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Custom HTML5 Video Player Using TailwindCSS and JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-custom-video-player-using-javascript-and-tailwind-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-custom-video-player-using-javascript-and-tailwind-css/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T15:14:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML5 comes equipped with a native video player. It's shipped with a simple user interface, functionality, and some basic controls in the browser. And while the functionality of the default video player via the browser works perfectly, the user interface isn't so beautiful and fancy, and it's just not generally]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Franklin Okolie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Practical Guide To Designing For Children]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/practical-guide-design-children/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/practical-guide-design-children/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to design for children aged 3–12, with insights into user behavior, considerations for parents, and practical UX guidelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Greater Than and Less Than Operators in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/greater-than-and-less-than-operators-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/greater-than-and-less-than-operators-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T11:02:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In your JavaScript programs, you'll often need to compare two values to see if one is greater than or less than the other. This is where the greater than and less than operators come in handy. In this article, we'll look at how to use these operators in greater detail]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debouncing in JavaScript – Explained by Building Auto-Complete Functionality in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deboucing-in-react-autocomplete-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deboucing-in-react-autocomplete-example/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T23:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi readers, I hope you are doing great! I am back with another tutorial on web development. If you are someone who enjoys developing web apps with JavaScript and React, then this post is for you. When you roll out a new app into production, you want to make sure]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the querySelector() Method and How Does it Work in JavaScript?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/queryselector-method-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/queryselector-method-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T23:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, there will be times when you need to access an HTML element. The  querySelector method is a web API that selects the first element that matches the specified CSS selector passed into it. But how does this work in more detail? In this article, we will look]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does Short-Circuiting Work in JavaScript?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/short-circuiting-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/short-circuiting-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T18:38:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, understanding truthy and falsy values is fundamental to writing efficient and concise code. Combined with the concept of short-circuiting, developers can write elegant solutions to common programming challenges.  In this hands-on guide, we'll explore truthy and falsy values, and understand the mechanics of short-circuiting in JavaScript. You]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Compare Two Dates in JavaScript – Techniques, Methods, and Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/compare-two-dates-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/compare-two-dates-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T17:57:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, you can use the date object to work effectively with dates, times, and time zones within an application.  Date objects help you efficiently manipulate data, handle various date-related tasks, and perform some calculations when creating real-world applications. In this article, we will learn about the following topics:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kamaldeen Lawal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve Your Communication Skills as a Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-communication-skills/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-communication-skills/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T13:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You built an application that solves a problem most business owners face. You registered yourself at a local event to speak about your product, but no one cares. You try selling it on social media groups, but don't receive more than "Wow, that's an interesting idea." Do these sound familiar?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tooba Jamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: AI Engineering with Engineer + Scrimba CEO Per Borgan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-ai-engineering-scrimba-ceo-per-borgan/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-ai-engineering-scrimba-ceo-per-borgan/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T17:28:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Per Borgen about the burgeoning field of AI Engineering, and his work in interactive developer education. Per is the co-founder and CEO of Scrimba and is a software engineer. Be sure to follow The freeCodeCamp podcast in your favorite podcast app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Search Form in Google Sheets – Google Apps Script Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-search-form-in-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-search-form-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T15:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever struggled with navigating a massive spreadsheet? You can do away with the endless scrolling and unlock the power of targeted data retrieval with a custom search form using Google Apps Script.  In this hands-on guide, we'll craft a search tool that seamlessly integrates with your spreadsheet,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nibesh Khadka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Data Types in Python – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-data-types-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-data-types-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T15:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, a data type communicates with the interpreter about how the programmer intends to use the data and information stored. The classification of data specifies the type of value a variable can hold. In Python programming, you don't need to explicitly declare the data type of your variable. Instead,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kamaldeen Lawal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Draw Radar Charts In Web]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/draw-radar-charts-web/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/draw-radar-charts-web/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A radar chart — also commonly called a spider chart — is yet another way to visualize data and make connections. Radar charts are inherently geometric, making them both a perfect fit and fun to make with CSS, thanks to the `polygon()` function. Read along as Preethi Sam demonstrates the process and sprinkles it with a pinch of JavaScript to make a handy, reusable component.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Sam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Animations in React 18]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-animations-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-animations-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T23:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are surrounded by gorgeous web applications. Sometimes I catch myself admiring visual effects on some website and wondering how they were made.  Well today I'll show you how you can create awesome CSS animations in React 18. As always, we'll work on the real world example but we'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Spread and Rest Operators – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-spread-and-rest-operators/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-spread-and-rest-operators/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T23:27:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In modern JavaScript, the spread and rest operators are indispensable tools for simplifying array manipulation and function parameters. These operators provide elegant solutions for tasks like array expansion and function arguments handling.  Let's dive deeper into understanding how they work so you can leverage their power. You can get]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Download a Kaggle Dataset Directly to a Google Colab Notebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-download-kaggle-dataset-to-google-colab/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-download-kaggle-dataset-to-google-colab/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T19:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kaggle [https://www.kaggle.com/]is a popular data science-based competition platform that has a large online community of data scientists and machine learning engineers. The platform contains a ton of datasets and notebooks that you can use to learn and practice your data science and machine learning skills. They even have competitions you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn Golang – A Beginner's Guide to the Basics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/golang-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/golang-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T17:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Go programming language, also known as Golang, was developed at Google in 2007 by Robert Griesemer, Rob Pike, and Ken Thompson. It was open-sourced in 2009.  Go is expressive, concise, clean, and efficient. The language is statically typed with syntax similar to the C programming language.  Go]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adeola Ajiboso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn ASP.NET Core by Building an Auction Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-asp-net-core-by-building-an-auction-application/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-asp-net-core-by-building-an-auction-application/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T16:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ASP.NET course can be used to create robust, scalable, and dynamic applications. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is an opportunity for learners to dive deep into the world of fullstack development using ASP.NET Core. Alen Omeri designed the course to guide you through the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frequently Heard In My Beginning Front-End Web Development Class]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/frequently-heard-beginning-front-end-web-development-class/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/frequently-heard-beginning-front-end-web-development-class/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What could we learn from entry-level students in front-end web development? As seasoned professionals, you might think you’ve seen it all, but the truth is that the newcomers are asking the most intriguing questions and making connections that those of us who have spent years on the front end may have never considered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Draw with JavaScript on an HTML Canvas Element – Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/drawing-on-a-canvas-element-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/drawing-on-a-canvas-element-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T00:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many ways to code graphics for the web. You can create art with CSS [https://codepen.io/search/pens?q=css+art]. You can code an SVG [/news/svg-tutorial-learn-to-code-images/] image as part of an HTML file. Or you can generate graphics from JavaScript using the Canvas API. In this article, we'll explore how to use JavaScript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hunor Márton Borbély</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Back-End Development – Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-back-end-development-the-beginners-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-back-end-development-the-beginners-guide/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T00:04:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to dive into the world of Python back-end development? Whether you’re a beginner looking to learn the basics or an experienced developer wanting to upgrade your skills, this handbook is your ultimate guide. Imagine being able to build full-featured web applications, handle large-scale data analysis, and create]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Motion Sensitivity? How to Design Accessible Web Animations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-sensitivity-how-to-design-accessible-animations/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-sensitivity-how-to-design-accessible-animations/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T21:51:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As web developers, we love a good animation, right? But let's be honest, sometimes we get caught up in the wow factor and forget that our websites exist for real people with diverse needs.  One hidden hurdle for some users is motion sensitivity. It might not be something we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth  Meshioye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work with the Console Object in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-the-console-object-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-the-console-object-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T21:29:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you run into errors inside your code, it's important to know how to debug and find the source of the problem. The console object is a powerful tool that can help you with this. In this article, we will explore the console object and the variety of methods that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Destructuring Works in JavaScript – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/destructuring-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/destructuring-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T19:31:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Destructuring is a powerful JavaScript feature introduced in ES6 (ECMAScript 2015). It makes it easier to extract values from arrays or properties from objects and assign them to variables in a readable way.  Let's delve into how destructuring works and explore various use cases with examples. You can get]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work with useMemo in React – with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-usememo-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-usememo-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T18:13:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[useMemo is a valuable tool in the React framework, designed to optimize performance by memoizing expensive computations.  With useMemo, React can store the result of a function call and reuse it when the dependencies of that function haven't changed, rather than recalculating the value on every render.  useMemo]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Career Change to Code Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/career-change-to-code-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/career-change-to-code-guide/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T17:47:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many people who want to change careers to become a software developer but don't know what the optimal path is. There are many challenges and uncertainties that accompany such a significant change. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is a guide for those]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the JavaScript insertAdjacentHTML() method for Efficient DOM Manipulation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-insertadjacenthtml-method-efficient-dom-manipulation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-insertadjacenthtml-method-efficient-dom-manipulation/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T16:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, developers need to be able to dynamically update a page without replacing the entire content. A traditional method like innerHTML can cause performance issues, because these methods tend to replace the entire content of an element. The insertAdjacentHTML() method leads to better performance because you use it to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kamaldeen Lawal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Development Is Getting Too Complex, And It May Be Our Fault]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-development-getting-too-complex/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-development-getting-too-complex/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overwhelming number of frameworks and tooling available today gives the impression that web development has gotten perhaps too complex. Juan Diego Rodríguez explores if web development really is that complex and, most importantly, how we can prevent it from getting even more difficult than we already perceive it to be.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Master Boot Record Disk Partitioning Works in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-mbr-works-in-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-mbr-works-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T10:29:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Efficient storage management is a crucial aspect of maintaining a well-organized computing environment.  In this detailed guide, we'll explore the features of Master Boot Record (MBR) disk partitioning using the parted command on Linux.  Additionally, we'll cover the process of adding a new hard disk in VMware, as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Project – How to Build a Simple Parking Lot Management System]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-project-parking-lot-management-system/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-project-parking-lot-management-system/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T00:25:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! It's good to be back with another tutorial – this time on Java, one of the most popular programming languages out there today.  Java is used by developers and enterprises to build powerful applications that serve many different purposes. The object-oriented nature of Java makes writing clean,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Personal Branding for Developers – A Step by Step Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/personal-branding-for-devs-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/personal-branding-for-devs-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T23:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this handbook, you'll learn how to build your personal brand as a developer to help you make your mark in the tech industry.  With a focus on practicality and professionalism, this guide is designed for developers at all levels, from industry veterans to those just starting their coding]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Job Board Scraper with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-job-board-scraper-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-job-board-scraper-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T22:56:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to learn how to navigate the ever-evolving job market by scraping job posting sites like Indeed.com, then this guide is for you.  What is a Job Scraper? In the digital age, tools known as Job Board Scrapers (or just Job Scrapers) have become indispensable for people]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jess Wilk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the C# Programming Language – Full Book for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-csharp-book/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-csharp-book/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T22:35:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C# version 1 was released in January 2002. It is a modern, general purpose programming language designed and developed from the ground up by the renowned Danish software engineer, Anders Heijleberg and his team at Microsoft.  I’ve heard Anders Heijlsberg say in an interview that with C# the goal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gavin Lon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master React by Building 25 Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-react-by-building-25-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-react-by-building-25-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T17:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is one of the most popular frontend JavaScript frameworks.  We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build twenty-five different projects using React. Each project is designed to challenge and enhance your understanding of React's capabilities. Sangam Mukherjee developed this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Spring Boot and Spring Data JPA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-spring-boot-and-spring-data-jpa/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-spring-boot-and-spring-data-jpa/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T16:05:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By mastering Spring Boot and Spring Data JPA, you'll be equipped to build efficient, scalable, and secure applications with ease, making you a valuable asset in the job market and a more effective developer. We just published a comprehensive video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that teaches Spring Boot]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Strict Mode in JavaScript? Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-strict-mode-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-strict-mode-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T11:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a JavaScript developer, you may come across the string "use strict" at the top of your JavaScript code. This means that JavaScript's strict mode is in use. But what does this mean, and why does it matter? In this article, you'll learn what it means to write]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vim Key Bindings – Vim Keys List Reference]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vim-key-bindings-reference/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vim-key-bindings-reference/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T09:28:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Vim key bindings is crucial for navigating and editing text efficiently in Vim or Vim-based text editors like Neovim.  In this article, we'll explore the most common Vim key bindings that will help you navigate your text editor seamlessly. Table of Content  * Vim Modes  *]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Designing For Older Adults]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/guide-designing-older-adults/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/guide-designing-older-adults/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With one billion people aged 60 or older worldwide, inclusivity is more important than ever. Learn how to create digital experiences that empower independence and competence for older adults while enhancing usability for all. An upcoming part of Smart Interface Design Patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Databases Guarantee Isolation – Pessimistic vs Optimistic Concurrency Control Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-databases-guarantee-isolation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-databases-guarantee-isolation/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T22:41:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ACID (Atomicity, Consistency, Isolation, and Durability) is a set of guarantees when working with a DBMS. Pessimistic and optimistic concurrency control explains how databases achieve the “I” in ACID. Isolation is a guarantee that concurrently running transactions should not interfere with each other. This is arguably the most important ACID]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State Management in React – When and Where to use State]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-state-management/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-state-management/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T21:06:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State management is a crucial concept in React, which is one of the most popular JavaScript libraries in the world for building dynamic user interfaces.  Due to its importance in handling data, it is essential know how to manage state, when you need it, and where it can be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Olanrewaju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Filtering, Sorting, Limiting, and Pagination to Your Nest.js App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-filtering-sorting-limiting-pagination-to-nestjs-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-filtering-sorting-limiting-pagination-to-nestjs-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T19:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are reading this article, you are probably a developer who has used an API to call data for your application. You may have also used features such as filtering and pagination to limit the amount of data you want to receive.  These API features are important when]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okure U. Edet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is box-sizing: border-box in CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-box-sizing-border-box-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-box-sizing-border-box-css/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T18:26:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In CSS, there is a property called box-sizing that allows you to determine how the width and the height for an element is calculated.  A lot of CSS resets [/news/how-i-style-my-websites-with-my-favorite-css-resets-7ace41dbc43d/] will change the default box model from content-box to border-box to make the layouts easier to work with. But]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable JavaScript – How to Improve the Performance of Your JS Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/immutable-javascript-improve-application-performance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/immutable-javascript-improve-application-performance/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T15:09:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Javascript has become a very popular programming language thanks to its growing use in frontend and backend development.  And as devs build JavaScript applications for different companies and organizations, the size and complexity of these applications can pose interesting performance challenges. As developers, we seek to create applications that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clinton Joy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install React – A Step-by-Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-react-a-step-by-step-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-react-a-step-by-step-guide/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T12:43:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is an open-source JavaScript library that helps you build dynamic user interfaces (UIs). You can use it to build components that represent logically reusable parts of the UI. Because React is open source, anyone can access its source code, inspect it, modify it, and enhance it for their personal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoro Emmanuel Nzube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use OpenTelementry to Trace Node.js Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-opentelementry-to-trace-node-js-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-opentelementry-to-trace-node-js-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-03T00:21:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Observability refers to our ability to "see" and understand what's happening inside a system by looking at its external signals (like logs, metrics, and traces). Observability involves collecting and analyzing data from sources within a system to monitor its performance and address problems effectively. Why is Observability Useful?  1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abraham Dahunsi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Libraries to Use in Your Projects in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-libraries-to-use-in-your-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-libraries-to-use-in-your-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T18:42:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're building applications with React, you should learn how to use some helpful libraries that'll make it easier to add the features you need. For example, to add features like authentication or styling, you'll need to find a good third-party library to handle it. In this comprehensive guide, I'm]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Boot Process – What Happens when Booting RHEL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linux-boot-process-in-rhel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linux-boot-process-in-rhel/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T17:49:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The boot process is made up of a series of necessary actions that a computer goes through upon startup. These range from powering on to the complete loading of the operating system (OS) for optimal functionality.  It is vital to familiarize yourself with the boot process for various reasons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Mobile Swiping Component in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-mobile-swiping-component-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-mobile-swiping-component-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T17:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone wants to be able to access the web from their mobile phones these days. So it's important to consider the accessibility of your web app on Android and iPhones.  The most difficult part is building the navigation – and swiping in particular can cause a lot of headaches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Oh My Zsh creator and Dev Shop CEO Robby Russell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-oh-my-zsh-creator-and-ceo-robby-russell/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-oh-my-zsh-creator-and-ceo-robby-russell/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T17:11:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Robby Russell. Robby created the open-source project Oh My ZSH.  Oh My Zsh is a framework for managing your Zsh configuration for your command line terminal. It's been extremely popular among developers for more than a decade. Robby is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asynchronous Programming in JavaScript – Callbacks, Promises, & Async/Await Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/asynchronous-programming-in-javascript-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/asynchronous-programming-in-javascript-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T16:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All programming languages have runtime engines that execute their code. In JavaScript, the runtime engine is single-threaded, which means that it runs code line by line or sequentially. The JavaScript runtime engine makes it a synchronous programming language where programs run sequentially. Programming languages that are not synchronous are called]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Musab Habeeb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Words Cannot Describe: Designing For AI Beyond Conversational Interfaces]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-ai-beyond-conversational-interfaces/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-ai-beyond-conversational-interfaces/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Artificial Intelligence evolves the computing paradigm, designers have an opportunity to craft more intuitive user interfaces. Maximillian Piras examines how the latest AI capabilities can reshape the future of human-computer interaction beyond conversation alone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maximillian Piras)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Fast.ai – A Beginner-Friendly Gateway to Deep Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-fast-ai-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-fast-ai-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T00:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fast.ai is a user-friendly library that brings the power of deep learning to your fingertips, regardless of your skill level. Let’s learn how it works. Have you ever felt curious about deep learning but found the technical complexity overwhelming? Fast.ai [https://fast.ai/] is your answer. Fast.ai simplifies the journey into deep]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Your Web Sites Accessible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-your-web-sites-accessible/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-your-web-sites-accessible/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T16:16:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ensuring that web content is accessible to everyone, including people with disabilities, is not just a noble goal—it's a necessity. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you all about web accessibility. This course is designed to empower developers with the knowledge and skills]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Array Length – How to Find the Length of an Array in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-array-length-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-array-length-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T15:56:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript arrays are fundamental data structures that allow you to store and manipulate collections of elements efficiently. While working with arrays, you'll often need to know their length. The length of an array tells us how many elements are present in the array. You can use this to check if]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tantoluwa Heritage Alabi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Documentation Libraries to Help You Write Good Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/documentation-libraries-to-help-you-write-good-docs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/documentation-libraries-to-help-you-write-good-docs/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T15:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good project documentation is key to success for every company, startup, or individual project. Without documentation, it's much harder for new developers or others to use your project. In this article, I'll discuss some of my favourite libraries you can use for building your documentation site.  And don't worry]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Shadcn with Next.js 14]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/shadcn-with-next-js-14/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/shadcn-with-next-js-14/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T15:21:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shadcn is a collection of beautifully designed, accessible, and customizable React components that you can use to build modern web applications with Next.js. With Shadcn, you can quickly and easily create user interfaces that are both stylish and functional. If you are looking for a way to build modern, stylish,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Dynamic Segments with useParams in React Router]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-dynamic-segments-in-react-router/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-dynamic-segments-in-react-router/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T22:34:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a traditional website, when a user clicks on a URL, the browser makes a full-page request from the server and directs the user to a new page. This is referred to as static routing. This is very useful if you just need to navigate the user to a new]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Anie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pass the GitHub Foundations Certification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pass-the-github-foundations-certification-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pass-the-github-foundations-certification-course/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T21:54:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub Foundations Certification was released just a few weeks ago. And you can now watch a 9-hour exam prep course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel! Andrew Brown from ExamPro created this course. He has created a bunch of popular exam prep courses for the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This certification]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[nth-child() vs nth-of-type() Selectors in CSS – What’s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nth-child-vs-nth-of-type-selector-in-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nth-child-vs-nth-of-type-selector-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T18:33:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The :nth-child() and :nth-of-type() CSS selectors select items from a group of HTML elements. But they work in different ways. Here is the main distinction between them: nth-child() selects its items from any group of elements. nth-of-type() selects its items from a specified type of element. * :nth-child() selects items]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi Sofela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>