<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-05-09T00:58:24.833Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Array Handbook – How to Create, Work with, and Loop Through Arrays]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/php-array-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/php-array-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T22:25:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In every programming language, arrays provide a flexible option to store more than one data type in a single variable. They are one of the most versatile data structures in the programming world, which is one reason a lot of external data and many APIs come as arrays. When you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run a Postgres Database in Azure Kubernetes Service and Integrate it with a Node.js Express Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-run-postgres-in-kubernetes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-run-postgres-in-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T20:43:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone! Today, you're going to learn about deploying a Postgres container in Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) and connecting it to a Node.js application. In this fast-paced development landscape, deploying via containers, particularly with Kubernetes, is becoming increasingly popular. Some companies perform numerous deployments daily, so it's crucial for you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayomide Wilfred</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a React Native Splash Screen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-native-splash-screen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-native-splash-screen/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T19:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll get a hands-on practical guide for creating a native splash screen for React Native CLI applications.  Note that this tutorial is not applicable for apps created with Expo. SVG Icon Image and Background The first thing you need is an image. It can be in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucas Garcez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Analysis with Python – How I Analyzed My Empire State Building Run-Up Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/empire-state-building-run-up-analysis-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/empire-state-building-run-up-analysis-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T16:56:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A tower running race [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tower_running] is a race that you run up the stairs of a building. These happen around the world. I got the chance to participate in the Empire State Run Up in NYC, 2023 edition.  > The Empire State Building Run-Up (ESBRU)—the world’s first and most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement an OAuth2 Resource Server with Spring Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/oauth2-resourceserver-with-spring-security/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/oauth2-resourceserver-with-spring-security/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T15:39:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone! Imagine you are building an awesome application, with lots of cool features. Picture a backend server at its core that hosts a majority of the business logic and exposes functionality through APIs. Once you have planned out your APIs, there's one crucial step you need to take care]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Git in Detail to Manage Your Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-git-in-detail-to-manage-your-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-git-in-detail-to-manage-your-code/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:42:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version control is an essential skill for anyone involved in software development, from solo hobbyists to professional developers working in large teams. Understanding how to effectively manage changes and collaborate on code is critical, and Git is ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pass the GitHub Actions Certification Exam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pass-the-github-actions-certification-exam/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pass-the-github-actions-certification-exam/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:29:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub recently launched a GitHub Actions certification exam. And we just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will prepare you to pass this exam. This course is ideal for developers, DevOps professionals, and anyone interes...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep Learning Course – Math and Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deep-learning-course-math-and-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deep-learning-course-math-and-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:17:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the math behind deep learning is important if you want to become proficient in machine learning techniques. We just published a 14-hour deep learning course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This course is specifically tailored t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML for Beginners – HTML Basics With Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-html-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-html-basics/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T19:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the exciting world of web development! In this beginner's guide, you will learn the fundamentals of HTML, the backbone of every web page.  Imagine a tree: its roots anchor and nourish the entire plant. Similarly, HTML, the root of web development, provides the foundation for every webpage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casmir Onyekani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Git Submodules – Explained With Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-git-submodules/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-git-submodules/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:40:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is undeniably a very important tool for developers, as it helps us collaborate seamlessly, track changes efficiently, and maintain project integrity across distributed environments. However, as projects grow in complexity and scope, so does their dependencies. For this reason, there is a need for a mechanism to properly manage]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jima Victor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Concatenate Strings – How JS String Concatenation Works]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-js-string-concatenation-works/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-js-string-concatenation-works/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When coding in JavaScript, you may need to combine multiple strings to create a new, longer string. This operation is known as concatenation. In this article, you will learn five ways to concatenate strings in JavaScript. How to Concatenate Strings i...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Run UX Research Without Access To Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/how-run-ux-research-without-access-users/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/how-run-ux-research-without-access-users/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do we conduct UX research when there is no or only limited access to users? Here are some workarounds to run UX research or make a strong case for it. An upcoming part of Smart Interface Design Patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How is Flutter Platform-Agnostic?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-is-flutter-platform-agnostic/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-is-flutter-platform-agnostic/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T07:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter builds applications for multiple platforms (desktop, mobile, and web) from the same codebase. Flutter does this in a pixel-perfect and platform-agnostic manner.  In this article, we will explore how Flutter is platform-agnostic through how it renders user interfaces and through platform channels. Table of Contents  * What]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Obum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do Closures Work in JavaScript? Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understand-javascript-closures/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understand-javascript-closures/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T07:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sally and Joe are two love birds. They shared everything with each other and soon enough it was almost impossible to think that anything could come between them. One day, they had a quarrel which built up to a break up.  It was hard for Joe and he wanted]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asoluka Tochukwu Austin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React Developer Tools – Explained With Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-devtools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-devtools/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T20:12:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traditional browser developer tools are designed to inspect and debug web pages by interacting with your HTML, CSS, and JavaScript code. However, you can't use them to inspect and debug React applications efficiently due to the nature of React. This is where the React Developer Tools, AKA React DevTools comes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-amazon-ec2-auto-scaling/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-amazon-ec2-auto-scaling/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T16:32:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Auto scaling is like having a smart system that keeps an eye on how many people are visiting your website. When you have a lot of people, it quickly adds more servers to handle the extra traffic. And when things quiet down, it scales back to save you money. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Destiny Erhabor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decoding Chaos: How True Randomness Works in Software Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/true-randomness-in-software-engineering/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/true-randomness-in-software-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T16:27:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Randomness When you hear the word "randomness," what usually comes to mind? You may think of  something intangible, an abstract concept without a specific shape or form  – it's random.  But randomness is much more than an abstract idea – it's a fundamental aspect of our daily decisions]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gor Grigoryan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Harness Mouse Interaction Data For Practical Machine Learning Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/harness-mouse-interaction-data-machine-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/harness-mouse-interaction-data-machine-learning/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Eduard Kuric discusses mouse interaction data, what kind of magic can be done with it, and some of the hidden pitfalls to watch out for so you get a head start incorporating them in your solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eduard Kuric)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the useReducer Hook in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-usereducer-hook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-usereducer-hook/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T17:48:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll take a deep look at the useReducer hook in React. It can look confusing, especially if you are coming across the hook for the first time. This article breaks down the useReducer hook concept into understandable bits with both code and real-world examples to enable you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Olanrewaju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Construction Worker to Teaching Millions of Developers with John Smilga [Podcast #122]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-construction-worker-to-teaching-millions-of-developers-with-john-smilga-podcast-122/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-construction-worker-to-teaching-millions-of-developers-with-john-smilga-podcast-122/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T16:07:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview prolific programming teacher John Smilga. John grew up in the Soviet Union. He worked construction for 5 years before becoming a developer. Today he has taught millions of fellow devs through his man...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run SQL-Like Queries on C/C++ Files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/run-sql-like-queries-on-cplusplus-files/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/run-sql-like-queries-on-cplusplus-files/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T19:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! I'm a Software engineer who's interested in low-level programming, compilers, and tool development. At the end of 2023, I published my first article on freeCodeCamp about how I created a SQL-like Language to run queries on local Git repositories [/news/gql-design-and-implementation/]. If you want a bit more context, give]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amr Hesham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code A Chess Game with AI Opponent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-chess-game-with-ai-opponent/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-chess-game-with-ai-opponent/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T18:35:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you interested in combining your love for chess with your passion for coding? We just posted a comprehensive video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to code your own chess game with JavaScript and Angular. Eve...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Higher Order Functions in JavaScript? Explained With Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/higher-order-functions-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/higher-order-functions-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T18:31:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript offers a powerful feature known as higher order functions (HOFs). These functions elevate your code by treating other functions as citizens of the language itself.  In simpler terms, HOFs can accept functions as arguments and even return functions as results. This ability allows developers to write clean, reusable, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Combining CSS :has() And HTML &lt;select&gt; For Greater Conditional Styling]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/combining-css-has-html-select-conditional-styling/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/combining-css-has-html-select-conditional-styling/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amit Sheen demonstrates using `:has()` to apply styles conditionally when a certain `` in a `` element is chosen by the user and how we gain even more conditional styling capabilities when chaining `:has()` with other pseudo-classes, such as `:not()` — no JavaScript necessary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Amit Sheen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Realtime Chart with React, HighCharts, and Pusher]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-realtime-chart-with-react-and-pusher/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-realtime-chart-with-react-and-pusher/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T00:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's tutorial, you are going to learn about WebSockets and how you can use them to create interactive realtime data applications.  To illustrate just how innovative real time technologies are, we will build a chart application which automatically updates with new dynamic online data. This is going to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Baisden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use DefaultDict in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-defaultdict-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-defaultdict-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T21:15:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout my time working with datasets in Python, the dictionary has been my most used data structure. It’s versatile and easy to use. Need to count occurrences of a character? Use a dictionary! Want to create a list of soccer players and associated stats? Dictionary! They’re not fool-proof, though. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gage Schaffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Your Personalized  GitHub Profile Page – GitHub Profile README Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-personalized-github-profile-page/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-personalized-github-profile-page/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T18:51:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wanted to spruce up your GitHub profile page and make it stand out? Well, you're in luck!  With just a few simple steps, you can create a personalized GitHub profile that showcases your skills, projects, and personality. Let's dive in.  Create A New Repository Go]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Throttling in JavaScript? Explained with a Simple React Use Case]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/throttling-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/throttling-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T15:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back, fellow developers! Today, we are once again delving into JavaScript and Web Development and learning about throttling.  As a developer, making your website user-friendly is important. This goes a long way toward the product's success, and a key part of the user experience is the website's performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code a Full Stack Fiverr Clone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-full-stack-fiverr-clone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-full-stack-fiverr-clone/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T15:38:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just posted a course available now on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This comprehensive tutorial will walk you through the process of building a Fiverr clone using a stack of cutting-edge technologies. Vuk Rosić created this course. Vuk is ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn TypeScript in Spanish – Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-typescript-in-spanish-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-typescript-in-spanish-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T14:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript is a superset of JavaScript that adds static typing to your code, preventing type errors and other potential bugs. Learning TypeScript can be super helpful for you as a web developer. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org Spanish YouTube channel [https://www.youtube.com/freecodecampespanol] that is designed to teach you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Object-Oriented Programming in C# – Explained With Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-oop-in-c-sharp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-oop-in-c-sharp/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T12:14:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to this comprehensive guide on object-oriented programming (OOP) using C#. This article will delve into the four fundamental pillars of OOP:  * Inheritance  * Encapsulation  * Polymorphism  * Abstraction Whether you're a seasoned programmer or a beginner stepping into the world of C#, this article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaiah Cliford  Opoku</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Checkout Remote Branch – How to Fetch and List Remote Branches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-checkout-remote-branch-how-to-fetch-and-list-remote-branches/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-checkout-remote-branch-how-to-fetch-and-list-remote-branches/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T16:53:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use branches in Git to work on different features without affecting your main codebase. For example, you can experiment with a new layout for your webpage on a different branch without affecting the main branch where your website is being dep...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's the difference between React and Next.js?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/whats-the-difference-between-react-and-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/whats-the-difference-between-react-and-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T16:47:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are interested in web development but find yourself a bit confused by the variety of technologies and terms like React, Next.js, and Vite? Our brand new video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel is here to clear up the confusion and set yo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Longing For May (2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May is almost here, so what better occasion could there be for some fresh and inspiring desktop wallpapers? Created with love by artists and designers from across the globe, the wallpapers in this post come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn AI Engineering with OpenAI and JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-ai-engineering-with-openai-and-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-ai-engineering-with-openai-and-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T15:34:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding AI to your applications can open up a bunch of great features and uses. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will introduce you to AI Engineering using the OpenAI API and JavaScript. Created by expert Scrimba in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lessons Learned After Selling My Startup]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/lessons-learned-after-selling-startup/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/lessons-learned-after-selling-startup/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Business acquisitions are common but often shrouded in mystery because they happen behind closed doors. In this article, Yaakov details the story of his company and the journey it took him on, shedding light on the process of selling a business and what he learned from the experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yaakov Karda)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an Interactive Terminal-Based Portfolio Website]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-interactive-terminal-based-portfolio/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-interactive-terminal-based-portfolio/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T14:49:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to create an interactive terminal-based portfolio and resume in JavaScript. We'll use the jQuery Terminal library [https://terminal.jcubic.pl/] (and a few other tools) to create a website that looks like a real terminal. This article will show more advanced usage of the jQuery Terminal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakub T. Jankiewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Login Page with the Material Tailwind Framework – Step by Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-login-page-with-material-tailwind-framework/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-login-page-with-material-tailwind-framework/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T14:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Login pages are like the front doors to our web apps. They should be inviting, easy to use, and safe. If you're looking to create one that combines both style and function, you're in the right place. In this guide, we'll explore how to build a login page with Material]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandru Paduraru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work on a Multi-Library Project in Android – Locally and Remotely]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/working-on-a-multiple-library-project-in-android/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/working-on-a-multiple-library-project-in-android/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T22:37:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we're going to talk about multi-library projects in Android. It's not something ordinary, but not something out of the ordinary either.  You may have come across multi-library projects in your line of work, or you may be looking into converting your library into sub-modules for better]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Ben Rachel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Difference Between <b> and <Strong> in HTML – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/difference-between-b-and-strong-in-html/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/difference-between-b-and-strong-in-html/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T23:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is important text. The text within the  tag will no longer appear bold and will be displayed in red, as specified by the CSS rules. Similarly, you can override the default styles for the  tag using CSS, although it's less common to do so since the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Piping and Redirection in the Linux Terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linux-terminal-piping-and-redirection-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linux-terminal-piping-and-redirection-guide/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T23:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The command line interface in Linux provides a powerful way of perfoming a range of tasks on your system. Because of its roots, Linux has many features baked into the terminal. Two of these powerful features are piping and redirection. These features enable you to redirect the output and input]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin Wanjala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter Tutorial – How to Develop an App with Flutter From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-develop-a-flutter-app-from-scratch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-develop-a-flutter-app-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T18:11:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I've been working on a marketing strategy for a new app based on the Flutter framework. An entire development team has been teaching me the ins and outs of Flutter as a cross-platform technology.  And from what I've learned, I believe that the framework is accessible to almost]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oleg Romanyuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Awad is a GameDev Who Sleeps 9 Hours EVERY NIGHT to be Productive [Podcast #121]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ben-awad-is-a-gamedev-who-sleeps-9-hours-every-night-to-be-productive-podcast-121/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ben-awad-is-a-gamedev-who-sleeps-9-hours-every-night-to-be-productive-podcast-121/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T15:29:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews Ben Awad, a game developer who creates developer tutorials on YouTube and TikTok. I hope you enjoy our conversation. Can you guess what bass line I'm playing on my b...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End Of The Free Tier]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/end-of-free-tier/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/end-of-free-tier/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Free-tier pricing is a common marketing strategy. “Free” gets people in the door and allows them to settle in and see how things work. But, as Juan Diego Rodriguez explains, the practice of free *tiers* is often conflated with free *trials*. And while the distinction may be nuanced, the consequences of sunsetting free-tier pricing may be huge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mac Control Keyboard Shortcuts – Hotkeys that Work Everywhere in MacOS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mac-control-keyboard-shortcuts-hotkeys-that-work-everywhere-in-macos/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mac-control-keyboard-shortcuts-hotkeys-that-work-everywhere-in-macos/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T23:31:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MacOS has several keyboard shortcuts that work everywhere – in your browser, in your terminal, in any place where you can input text. I call these the "Control Hotkeys" since they all involve holding the Control key. These shortcuts seem to originate...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code a Kirby Clone with TypeScript and Kaboom.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-kirby-clone-with-typescript-and-kaboomjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-kirby-clone-with-typescript-and-kaboomjs/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T19:54:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are learning programming, it should be fun! We just posted a video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will guide you through the process of creating a Kirby game clone using TypeScript and Kaboom.js. JSLegendDev created this c...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conducting Accessibility Research In An Inaccessible Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/conducting-accessibility-research-inaccessible-ecosystem/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/conducting-accessibility-research-inaccessible-ecosystem/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conducting UX research that includes participants with a variety of disabilities is vital to building inclusive technology, but most prototypes used for testing are inaccessible. Rather than continuing to leave out feedback from disabled consumers, which ultimately leads to exclusive technology, researchers must get creative in their workarounds and be relentless in their efforts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michele Williams)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Set Up TypeORM DataSource in Your NestJS Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-setup-typeorm-datasource-nestjs-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-setup-typeorm-datasource-nestjs-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T11:22:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey there! 👋 Ever since I started working with NestJS, I've been looking for a reliable way to manage my database with TypeORM. Today, I'll share my journey and the steps I took to get it all set up. Alright, before we dive in, let's try to understand what TypeORM]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayobami Alaran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement JSON Web Tokens (JWTs) in PHP – PHP Authentication Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/php-jwt-authentication-implementation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/php-jwt-authentication-implementation/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T18:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll explore the process of creating JSON Web Tokens (JWTs) from scratch in PHP, presenting a superior and more secure authentication scheme.  By implementing this advanced approach, we unveil a robust and highly secure authentication mechanism that significantly enhances data protection and user authentication. Table Of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oghenekparobo stephen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Procedural Macros in Rust – A Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/procedural-macros-in-rust/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/procedural-macros-in-rust/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T17:49:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this handbook, you'll learn about procedural macros in Rust, and what purposes they serve. You'll also learn how to write your own procedural macros with both hypothetical and real-world examples. This guide assumes that you're familiar with Rust and its basic concepts, such as data-types, iterators, and traits. If]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshul Sanghi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webflow Crash Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/webflow-crash-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/webflow-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T17:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to master Webflow and build stunning websites without writing a single line of code? We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will guide you through everything you need to know about Webflow. Ashokkumar Chava...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Google Photos Clone with Next.js and Cloudinary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-google-photos-clone-with-nextjs-and-cloudinary/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-google-photos-clone-with-nextjs-and-cloudinary/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T17:07:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a Google Photos clone will help you learn a lot about web development. We just posted a video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create a powerful photo management app using Next.js and Cloudinary. Colb...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Responsive Website with HTML and CSS - Course in Spanish]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-responsive-website-with-html-and-css-full-course-in-spanish/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-responsive-website-with-html-and-css-full-course-in-spanish/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T15:36:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building websites that look great on any device – like a phone, tablet, or computer screen – is what responsive web development is all about. In this course, you will learn how to build a responsive website step by step in Spanish using HTML and CSS....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using AI For Neurodiversity And Building Inclusive Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/ai-neurodiversity-building-inclusive-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/ai-neurodiversity-building-inclusive-tools/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article illustrates how AI can be leveraged to build tools that can be inclusive with a little bit of an additional effort.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Pratik Joglekar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Object-Oriented Programming in Python – Explained With Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-oop-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-oop-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T14:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Object-oriented programming (OOP) is a style of programming that heavily relies on objects. These objects can have attributes and methods. While attributes store data, methods define behavior. Like many other programming languages, Python supports both OOP and functional programming. However, OOP becomes valuable when writing large-sized and complex programs. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damilola Oladele</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Biophilic Design? How to Reconnect with Nature through Web Design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-biophilic-design/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-biophilic-design/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T18:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a world where we're constantly glued to screens and distracted by digital noise, it's easy to forget about nature.  But here's the exciting part: biophilic design offers a cool solution. Usually, it's all about bringing nature into buildings, but now nature is branching out into web design as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Media to Your HTML Email Template]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-media-to-your-html-email-template/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-media-to-your-html-email-template/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T17:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous article, "How to Create a Responsive HTML Email Template [/news/how-to-create-a-responsive-html-email-template/]," we explored the fundamentals of designing and coding a simple HTML email template that adapts beautifully across different devices and email clients.  I got a couple of questions about adding media to the HTML email template.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fanny Nyayic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[F-Shape Pattern And How Users Read]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/f-shape-pattern-how-users-read/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/f-shape-pattern-how-users-read/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scrolling, scanning, skipping: How do users consume content online? Here’s what you need to know about reading behavior and design strategies to prevent harmful scanning patterns. An upcoming part of Smart Interface Design Patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Feature Flags and Role-Based Access Control Can Help Secure Your DevOps Process]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/feature-flags-and-role-based-access-control-devops/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/feature-flags-and-role-based-access-control-devops/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T21:26:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, software is being developed and deployed at a very rapid pace. It makes it easy to understand how the saying “move fast and break things” became commonplace.  In an era where agile development is the go-to practice for quick feature releases and feedback, it's easy for security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kayode Adeniyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Debug Node.js Applications Using the debugger; Statement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-debug-node-js-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-debug-node-js-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T19:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn the easiest and most efficient way to debug Node.js application code. So let's get started. Want to watch the video version of this tutorial? You can check out the video below: Table Of Contents  * How You Usually Debug Node.js Applications  *]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yogesh Chavan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn SQL for Analytics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-sql-for-analytics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-sql-for-analytics/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T17:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking to enhance your data skills and become proficient in SQL? We just posted a comprehensive, 11-hour SQL course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. It will teach you to handle complex database queries. Vlad Gheorghe created this cou...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CTO Andrew Brown Passed Dozens of Cloud Certification Exams [freeCodeCamp Podcast Episode #120]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cto-andrew-brown-passed-dozens-of-cloud-certification-exams-freecodecamp-podcast-episode-120/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cto-andrew-brown-passed-dozens-of-cloud-certification-exams-freecodecamp-podcast-episode-120/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T14:39:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Andrew Brown, a CTO-turned co-founder of ExamPro.co. Andrew created this cloud certification exam prep website with another Andrew – also from Canada, who also loves Star Trek. We talk about Andrew's early career fixing computers in the 90s, and his early]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demystifying Screen Readers: Accessible Forms & Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377733</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/demystifying-screen-readers-accessible-forms-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T14:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the 3rd post in a small series we are doing on form accessibility. If you missed the 2nd post, check out Managing User Focus with :focus-visible. In this post we are going to look at using a …
Demystifying Screen Readers: Accessible Forms & Best Practices originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris DeMars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Work With GraphQL In WordPress In 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/how-work-graphql-wordpress-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/how-work-graphql-wordpress-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What options do we have for integrating GraphQL with WordPress in 2024? Leonardo Losoviz describes the developments that have taken place in this space over the last three years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn WebSockets with Socket.IO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-websockets-socket-io/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-websockets-socket-io/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T00:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebSockets a critical technology in the development of real-time applications such as live notifications, multiplayer games, and real-time chats. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is designed to help you understand the fundamentals of WebSockets and how to implement real-time, bidirectional communication in web applications]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quincy's 5 freeCodeCamp Resources Worth Your Time Email – You Need to Re-subscribe Real Quick]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/quincys-5-worth-your-time-update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/quincys-5-worth-your-time-update/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T16:43:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been sending my "5 freeCodeCamp resources worth your time" for 8 years now. That's nearly 400 emails that I've authored and sent out over the years. Don't worry. I'm not tired. I love doing this, I'm going to keep working hard to share helpful learning resources with you. I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set a Different Location to Save All Screenshots on macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-a-different-location-to-save-screenshots-on-mac/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-a-different-location-to-save-screenshots-on-mac/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T22:02:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're coming to macOS from a different operating system (like Windows or Linux), it might feel odd that, by default, macOS saves screenshots in the Desktop folder. This make the desktop look messy after a while if you take a lot of screenshots! But it doesn't look messy if]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy a Next.js App Using Fly.io and Tigris]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-a-nextjs-app-with-fly-io-and-tigris/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-a-nextjs-app-with-fly-io-and-tigris/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T21:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you're going to learn about the app deployment platform Fly.io and the globally distributed S3-compatible object storage service Tigris.  Both platforms are deeply connected, which makes them a great choice for your projects. You get the app deployment experience from Fly.io and the object storage features]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Baisden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Dynamic Dropdown Component in React – React Compound Component Pattern Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-dynamic-dropdown-component/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-dynamic-dropdown-component/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T19:21:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dropdowns have been an important part of websites and apps for a long time. They're an unsung heros of user interactions, silently facilitating countless actions and decisions with just a click or tap.  You probably encountered one today, whether it was selecting a category on your favourite online store]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn RAG from Scratch – Python AI Tutorial from a LangChain Engineer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-rag-from-scratch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-rag-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T17:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) can be extremely helpful when developing projects with Large Language Models. It combines the power of retrieval systems with advanced natural language generation, providing a sophisticated approach to generating ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use JSON Web Tokens for Secure Authentication in Flask Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/jwt-authentication-in-flask/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/jwt-authentication-in-flask/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T16:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Passwords, credit card information, personal identification numbers (PINs) – these are all critical assets used for authorization and authentication. This means they need to be protected from unauthorized users. As developers, we are tasked with safeguarding these sensitive bits of info, and it's important to implement strong secure measures in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yemi Ojedapo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C Print String – How to Print a String in C]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-print-a-string-in-c/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-print-a-string-in-c/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T13:50:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Printing strings is a fundamental operation in programming. It helps you output information, inspect and debug your code, and display prompts to users. In this article, you will learn some of the different techniques to print strings in C. What is a ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Converting Plain Text To Encoded HTML With Vanilla JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/converting-text-encoded-html-vanilla-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/converting-text-encoded-html-vanilla-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What do you do when you need to convert plain text into formatted HTML? Perhaps you reach for Markdown or manually write in the element tags yourself. Or maybe you have one or two of the dozens of online tools that will do it for you. In this tutorial, Alexis Kypridemos picks those tools apart and details the steps for how we can do it ourselves with a little vanilla HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alexis Kypridemos)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Function Components vs Class Components in React – With Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/function-component-vs-class-component-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/function-component-vs-class-component-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T22:37:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In React, there are two primary ways to create components: function and class components. Each has its own syntax and use cases, although with the introduction of React Hooks, the gap between them has narrowed significantly. But the selection of appropriate component types is still very crucial for building efficient]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applied Data Science: A / B Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/applied-data-science-a-b-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/applied-data-science-a-b-testing/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T20:53:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A/B testing is a key technique used in data science for making data-driven decisions in business. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will tech you this important data science technique. Developed by Tatev, a seaso...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to deploy to Digital Ocean]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-how-to-deploy-to-digital-ocean/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-how-to-deploy-to-digital-ocean/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T20:42:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DigitalOcean is a cloud infrastructure provider that offers developers cloud services that help to deploy and scale applications that run simultaneously on multiple computers. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Bytes to String – How to Convert a Str to Bytes and Back Again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-bytes-to-string-code-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-bytes-to-string-code-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T20:07:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use bytes in Python to represent data in binary form. In this article, you'll learn how to convert bytes to a string, and vice versa. Before we look at the conversions, let's talk about how bytes work in Python. You can skip to the next secti...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust Tutorial – How to Build a Naïve Star Detector for Images]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rust-tutorial-naive-star-detector-for-images/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rust-tutorial-naive-star-detector-for-images/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T19:34:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Star detection is a crucial step in many of the processing and analysis routines that we perform on astronomical images. It is extremely important for a process called plate-solving, which is the process of figuring out which part of the sky an image shows, or which part of the sky]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshul Sanghi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Length of C String – How to Find the Size of a String in C]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-find-length-of-c-string-with-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-find-length-of-c-string-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T15:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with strings in C, you need to know how to find their length. Finding the length of a string in C is essential for many reasons. You may need to perform string manipulation, and many string manipulation functions require the length of th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Monitor And Optimize Google Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/monitor-optimize-google-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/monitor-optimize-google-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The three Core Web Vitals metrics don’t only tell you how visitors experience your website but also impact your Google search result rankings. In this article, we’ll look at what Core Web Vitals are, how they are measured, and how you can use DebugBear to monitor them continuously.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matt Zeunert)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Responsive HTML Email Template]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-responsive-html-email-template/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-responsive-html-email-template/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T23:11:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this beginner-friendly guide, you'll learn how to create a responsive email template. You'll follow step-by-step instructions with code snippets to design an email template that looks great on any device.  This project is perfect for newcomers eager to master email design basics! Step 1: Set Up the Basic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fanny Nyayic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does "Shift Left" Mean in Software Development?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-shift-left-in-software/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-shift-left-in-software/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T22:25:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I once had a manager who, in a discussion about our project, mentioned that we needed to try and shift our work left as much as we could.  A few months later in an interview, the interviewer asked me if I knew what " shift left" meant. Unless there's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kealan Parr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a GitHub Wiki and How Do You Use it?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-github-wiki-and-how-do-you-use-it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-github-wiki-and-how-do-you-use-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T20:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A GitHub wiki is a great place for your project's documentation. You can use the wiki to create, manage, and host documentation for your repository so others can use and contribute to your project. GitHub wikis are easy to start using without installing any other software. The best part is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Aliases to Terminal Commands in Linux and Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-aliases-to-terminal-commands/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-aliases-to-terminal-commands/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T15:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll explore a simple trick that can save you hours of typing repetitive commands in the terminal. As developers, we spend a substantial amount of time executing commands on the terminal. Whether it's navigating through directories, running scripts, changing Node.js versions, or version control commands, manually typing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kaushal Joshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up a Custom Email with Cloudflare and Mailgun]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-custom-email/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-custom-email/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T13:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a software engineer, you may consider having a professional email account along with your own website, like "info@example.com". But this may cost a certain amount that you'll not be willing to pay. But do you know you can do it for free? There is actually a way to do]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>San B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Statistics for Data Science, Machine Learning, and AI – Full Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/statistics-for-data-scientce-machine-learning-and-ai-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/statistics-for-data-scientce-machine-learning-and-ai-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T23:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Karl Pearson was a British mathematician who once said "Statistics is the grammar of science". This holds true especially for Computer and Information Sciences, Physical Science, and Biological Science.  When you are getting started with your journey in Data Science, Data Analytics, Machine Learning, or AI (including Generative AI)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tatev Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Mocking? Mocking in .NET Explained With Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/explore-mocking-in-net/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/explore-mocking-in-net/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T19:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's go on a journey to demystify the concept of mocking in .NET software development. Let's delve into how straightforward and accessible mocking truly is. Join me as we navigate through this subject, as I cover:  * Understanding mocking: Why it's necessary for building a robust testing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Riordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Production-Grade Movie Recommender in Python – A Machine Learning Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-movie-recommendation-system-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-movie-recommendation-system-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T19:33:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building projects is one of the most effective ways to thoroughly learn a concept and develop essential skills.  Projects immerse you in real-world problem-solving, solidifying your knowledge and cultivating critical thinking, adaptability, and project management expertise. This guide will walk you through building a movie recommendation system that's tailored]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Claim Your Supporter Role on Discord]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/discord-supporter-role/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/discord-supporter-role/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T19:27:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have donated to support freeCodeCamp's efforts, you can now claim a special Supporter role in our Discord community. Claim Your Role In any channel within our Discord server, type /supporter and you should see a command window pop up. Click C...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Naomi Carrigan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manually Deploy a React and TypeScript Project on Netlify]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manually-deploy-a-react-and-typescript-project-on-netlify/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manually-deploy-a-react-and-typescript-project-on-netlify/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T18:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, I'll teach you how to manually deploy a React and TypeScript project with Vite on Netlify. I will show you a few quick and simple steps to get live versions of your projects up and running. To follow along with this tutorial, there are a few prerequisites:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Losalini Rokocakau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sliding 3D Image Frames In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/sliding-3d-image-frames-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/sliding-3d-image-frames-css/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating 3D effects in CSS isn’t an entirely new concept, but typical approaches use additional elements in the markup and pseudo-elements in the styles to pull it off. Temani Afif applies 3D effects and sliding transitions to a single `` using clever CSS techniques that demonstrate advanced, modern styling practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Def in C – How to Define a Function in C]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-define-a-function-in-c/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-define-a-function-in-c/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T17:54:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Functions play a fundamental role in programming in C. They allow you to write code that is organized and easier to maintain. In this article, you'll learn the basics of defining functions in C. What is a Function in C? In programming, a function is ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a TODO App from Scratch with React.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-todo-app-from-scratch-with-reactjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-todo-app-from-scratch-with-reactjs/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T16:23:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're new to React.js and you're eager to dive into application development, then you've come to the right place!  Join me in this tutorial as I walk you through building a basic TODO app from the ground up. The Importance of a TODO App for Beginners A TODO]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spruce Emmanuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Artist Kass Moreno talks Art & Code [freeCodeCamp Podcast #119]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-artist-kass-moreno-freecodecamp-podcast-119/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-artist-kass-moreno-freecodecamp-podcast-119/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T15:26:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Kass Moreno, a Senior Front End Developer and CSS Artist. Kass started learning coding at age 28 and has since built a reputation as one of the most skilled artists who work with CSS. We talk about:  * Her childhood]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use LangChain to Build With LLMs – A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/beginners-guide-to-langchain/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/beginners-guide-to-langchain/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T23:11:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are incredibly powerful general reasoning tools that are useful in a wide range of situations.  But working with LLMs presents challenges that are different from building traditional software:  * Calls tend to be long-running, and stream generate output as it becomes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Accessible Technical Documentation – Best Practices with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-practices-for-writing-accessible-technical-documentation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-practices-for-writing-accessible-technical-documentation/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T23:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're writing technical documentation for a project or a tool you're working on, you'll want it to be accessible. This means that it will cater to and be usable by the diverse global audience on the web. Web accessibility aims to make it possible for anyone to access web]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ezinne Anne Emilia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn GitHub-Flavored Markdown Syntax and Formatting – With Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/github-flavored-markdown-syntax-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/github-flavored-markdown-syntax-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T19:08:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Markdown [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Markdown] is a lightweight, open-source, easy-to-read and easy-to-write method of formatting text that you can use as plain text in any IDE or editor. When writing on GitHub, you can use Markdown syntax and HTML elements to extend Markdown's functionality. You can use Markdown syntax everywhere in GitHub, such]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Backend Development by Building Three Projects [Full Course]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/backend-web-development-three-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/backend-web-development-three-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T15:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To become a great backend developer, you need to build a lot of projects. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you improve your backend development skills by teaching you to build three full projects. Tomi Tokko developed this course. He's a popular teacher,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One-Click AI Web Development Tutorial - Learn how to Turn Figma Designs into Working Code using AI [Full Course]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-web-development-tutorial-figma-designs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-web-development-tutorial-figma-designs/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T14:12:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many ways that AI can help speed up web development. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will show you how to convert Figma designs into working code with just one click using AI. Ania Kubów developed this course. She is one of our]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React State vs Refs – Differences and Use Cases]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-state-vs-ref-differences-and-use-cases/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-state-vs-ref-differences-and-use-cases/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T13:07:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll delve into a thorough comparison of React state and refs, exploring their suitability for specific scenarios. When faced with the need to store data in your React application, the first question that comes to mind is: "Will the data change at some point during the component's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Olanrewaju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Penpot’s CSS Grid Layout: Designing With Superpowers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/penpot-css-grid-layout-designing-superpowers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/04/penpot-css-grid-layout-designing-superpowers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Penpot helps designers and developers work better together by offering a free, open-source design tool based on open web standards. Today, let's explore Penpot’s latest feature, CSS Grid Layout. Penpot’s latest release is about efficiency and so much more. It gives designers superpowers and a better place at the table. Excited? Let’s take a look at it together.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Error Handling in Python – try, except, else, & finally Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/error-handling-in-python-introduction/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/error-handling-in-python-introduction/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T00:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just recently, my manager tasked me to create an automatic report. I designed the report to be simple. It included a few numbers from a database and some basic mathematical operations. I was excited to finally be able to show off my  amazing Python skills to the company. I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gage Schaffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust Tutorial – Learn Multi-Scale Processing of Astronomical Images]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/multi-scale-analysis-of-images-in-rust/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/multi-scale-analysis-of-images-in-rust/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T15:48:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, there's been a massive amount of effort put into developing novel image processing techniques. And many of them are derived from digital signal processing methods such as Fourier and Wavelet transforms.  These techniques have not only enabled a wide range of image processing techniques such as noise reduction,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshul Sanghi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AI Models Think: The Key Role of Activation Functions with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/activation-functions-in-neural-networks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/activation-functions-in-neural-networks/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T15:44:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning is the foundation of most revolutionary AI applications. From language processing to image recognition, Machine Learning is everywhere. Machine Learning relies on algorithms, statistical models, and neural networks. And Deep Learning is the subfield of Machine Learning focused only on neural networks. A key piece]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Git in Spanish – Git Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-git-in-spanish-git-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-git-in-spanish-git-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T15:06:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is the version control system that most software companies use around the world. It's an essential tool for managing and tracking code changes effectively. If you are learning to code, you should definitely learn Git. We just published a 1-hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org Spanish YouTube channel [https://www.youtube.com/freecodecampespanol] that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Send Emails With Nodemailer in NestJS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-nodemailer-in-nestjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-nodemailer-in-nestjs/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T11:52:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While learning Nestjs, I wanted to be able to send test emails with Nodemailer but I had difficulty doing this in the context of a NestJS application. I searched the internet for a solution and after much research, I found one. It turned out to be really simple. In this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okure U. Edet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>