<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-04-08T01:04:38.643Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design a Scalable Mobile App With Figma Variants]]></title>
        <id>624ca9a4ac55f60686c2e7f9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/design-a-scalable-mobile-app-with-figma-variants/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T12:15:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Figma is a popular graphics editor and prototyping tool. Figma variants can streamline your frontend design process by allowing you to group and organize similar components into a single container. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you learn how to use Figma variants]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[flushdns – How to Flush DNS with the Windows ipconfig /flushdns Command]]></title>
        <id>624bfc9bac55f60686c2e0ff</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flushdns-how-to-flush-dns-with-the-windows-ipconfig-flushdns-command/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T03:41:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You've probably noticed that, after visiting a website for the first time, the website loads much quicker the next time you visit. This is because your operating system, or browser in the case of Google Chrome, cache IP addresses and DNS (Domain Name System) information of any website you visit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS IAM – Policy, Access Roles, Resources Explained, and Why They're Useful]]></title>
        <id>62435e6e138a19064b068027</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-introduction-to-iam-i-wish-i-had/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T02:50:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IAM, or Identity and Access Management, is one of the most common terms you'll hear in cloud-native environments. But what does it do? And if you're already familiar with IAM, how long did it take you to fully understand it? I will explain the main concepts behind this massive family]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Periklis Gkolias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Better Breadcrumbs]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/designing-better-breadcrumbs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/designing-better-breadcrumbs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this series of articles, we highlight design patterns and techniques to design better interfaces. You can also find more examples in [“Smart Interface Design Patterns”](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com/), a 6h-video course with 100s of hand-picked examples, curated by Vitaly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Devs For Ukraine, A Free Online Charity Conference 🇺🇦]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/devs-for-ukraine/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/devs-for-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Devs For Ukraine](https://www.devsforukraine.io/) is a free online charity conference organized by the lovely people at Remote. Two days filled with talks from engineering leaders around the globe, in support of Ukraine. April 25–26.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Command Line for Beginners – How to Use the Terminal Like a Pro]]></title>
        <id>6244f93a138a19064b068b9e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/command-line-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-05T16:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we'll take a good look at the command line (also known as the CLI, console, terminal or shell). The command line is one of the most useful and efficient tools we have as developers and as computer users in general. But using it can feel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Get Work Done: Wrangling Stakeholders And Overcoming Obstacles]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/stakeholders-overcoming-obstacles/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/stakeholders-overcoming-obstacles/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you work in-house or for an external agency, we all share one challenge — dealing with stakeholders, be they your boss, colleagues, or clients. In this post, veteran web designer Paul Boag shares his approach to getting things done in even the most challenging organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Package Manager – Complete Guide to NPM and Yarn]]></title>
        <id>624b0547ac55f60686c2d2e1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-package-manager-npm-and-yarn/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-05T00:08:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A package manager is a tool developers use to automate finding, downloading, installing, configuring, upgrading, and removing a system's packages. This article will show you all you need to get started with package managers like NPM and Yarn. But why exactly do we need a package manager in our development]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi Sofela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Beginner's Guide to Sass]]></title>
        <id>6233c160cdcd57069ddfadb8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-beginners-guide-to-sass/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T23:39:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered what SASS stands for? Or perhaps you already know what it is but haven't taken the time to study and use it. Whether you're learning about it for the first time, or want to brush up on your knowledge of the subject, this is the article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Mitolu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Types of Hard Drives – SATA, PATA, SCSI, and SSD]]></title>
        <id>624ad0f4ac55f60686c2d118</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/types-of-hard-drives-sata-pata-scsi-and-more-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T23:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hard drive is a non-volatile hardware component on a computer that acts as the storage for all digital content. It holds program files, documents, pictures, videos, music, and more. The non-volatile nature of hard drives means they don’t lose data, even if power is lost. Due to this, they]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make an Image Search App in React using the Unsplash API]]></title>
        <id>6249d59dac55f60686c2ce11</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-an-image-search-app-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T22:19:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unsplash is a site where you can download free and unlicensed images and use them as you see fit. In this tutorial, we will make an Image Search App using the Unsplash API to get access to its enormous collection of images and also download them. Before starting the development]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ateev Duggal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Project – How to Build a Wordle Clone using Python and Rich]]></title>
        <id>624a520eac55f60686c2cfa0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-wordle-clone-using-python-and-rich/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T20:21:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wordle is a popular game where you guess a five-letter word in six tries. After each guess, the color of the tiles will change to show how close your guess was to the word.  It is similar to the Hangman game [https://ireadblog.com/posts/124/hangman-game-using-python] which I've already shown you how to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docker Mount Volume – How To Mount a Local Directory]]></title>
        <id>62402130138a19064b0666c6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/docker-mount-volume-guide-how-to-mount-a-local-directory/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T20:08:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers make software engineering easier and more efficient, and Docker [https://www.docker.com/] containers are popular and easy to use.  Containers are essential for local development. They let you test-run your applications in local environments and start building out the required infrastructure. Docker containers are immutable by nature. This means that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sigl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thunder Client – An Alternative Way to Test Restful APIs]]></title>
        <id>623646bccdcd57069ddfb98f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/thunder-client-for-vscode/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T19:09:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article will teach you an alternative approach to testing client APIs using Thunder Client, an open-source extension available on VS Code marketplace [https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=rangav.vscode-thunder-client] .  You will not need to download any tools to do this, since you can get it done right within VS Code. The article covers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sule-Balogun Olanrewaju Ganiu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding CDN Caching to a Vite Build]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364166</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/adding-cdn-caching-to-a-vite-build/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T18:25:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content delivery networks, or CDNs, allow you to improve the delivery of your website’s static resources, most notably, with CDN caching. They do this by serving your content from edge locations, which are located all over the world. When a …
Adding CDN Caching to a Vite Build originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientific Computing in Golang with the Gonum Package]]></title>
        <id>624515df138a19064b068e7c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/scientific-computing-in-golang-using-gonum/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T15:49:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll introduce you to Gonum, a package you can use to perform scientific computations in the Go programming language. Here's what we'll cover in this intermediate tutorial:  * What is Gonum?  * Why use Gonum  * How to install and set up Gonum]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ukeje Chukwuemeriwo Goodness</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The freeCodeCamp World Translation Summit 2022 – Join the Translation Effort]]></title>
        <id>6244b25c138a19064b0686d0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-freecodecamp-world-translation-summit-2022-join-the-translation-effort/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T14:23:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Translation is a powerful tool that can change lives. Everyone should have access to free learning resources in their native language.  To achieve this, freeCodeCamp has started translating our curriculum into dozens of world languages, with the help of thousands of volunteers around the world. To honor our translators]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ExamPro Cloud Developer Environment Certification — Pass the Exam with This 12 Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>623f380c138a19064b06605b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/exampro-cloud-developer-environment-certification-gitpod-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T13:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a web-application developer looking to learn how to leverage the cloud or want to become a cloud developer, the ExamPro Cloud Development Environment (EXP-CDE-01) is the first step. What is a Cloud Developer Environment?  A Cloud Developer Environment (CDE) is a:  *  code editor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Brown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Progressively Enhanced, Accessible, Filterable And Paginated List]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/accessible-filterable-paginated-list-11ty-alpinejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/accessible-filterable-paginated-list-11ty-alpinejs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever wondered how to build a paginated list that works with and without JavaScript? In this article, Manuel explains how you can leverage the power of Progressive Enhancement and do just that with Eleventy and Alpine.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Manuel Matuzović)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Pass Callback Functions to String.replace() in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>6246e84d138a19064b06a1c9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-pass-callback-functions-to-string-replace-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T20:14:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that the string .replace() method accepts a callback function? I just discovered it today and thought I'd share. What do you need this function for? Why does it exist? I'll answer all these questions as you go through this article. The replace() Method The replace() string method]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Rate Limiter using Bucket4J and Redis]]></title>
        <id>6245914c138a19064b0690bb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rate-limiting-with-bucket4j-and-redis/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T19:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial we will learn how to implement rate limiting in a scaled service. We will use the Bucket4J [https://github.com/vladimir-bukhtoyarov/bucket4j]  library to implement it and we will use Redis [https://redis.io/] as a distributed cache. Why Use Rate Limiting? Let's get started with some basics to make sure we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhinav Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Full Stack Developer? 2022 Full Stack Engineer Guide]]></title>
        <id>6228642863ded806bb9e6f73</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-full-stack-developer-full-stack-engineer-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T18:42:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Full-stack developer roles are among the most highly sought after positions in the current job market. But what exactly is full-stack web development, and how do you become a full-stack developer? In this article, you will first learn what the term full-stack means. Then, you will see some suggested technologies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Inner Join – How to Join 3 Tables in SQL and MySQL]]></title>
        <id>6164065d804854468fda843b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-inner-join-how-to-join-3-tables-in-sql-and-mysql/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T18:19:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with your database, you might need to put together data from a few different tables. This article will show you how. I have already written about SQL joins here [/news/sql-join-types-inner-join-vs-outer-join-example/] and here [/news/sql-left-join-example-join-statement-syntax/], but let's take a moment to review how a join works first, and particularly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilenia Magoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NextJS and HarperDB Tutorial –Build a Full Stack Productivity Timer App]]></title>
        <id>6244a14e138a19064b0686c7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nextjs-and-harperdb-tutorial-build-a-full-stack-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T16:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building full stack applications can be tough. You have to think about frontend, APIs, databases, authentication - and how all of these things work together. So, in this article, I'll show you how to do all of those things using NextJS and HarperDB. We'll be building a full stack task]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The What, When, Why And How Of Next.js’ New Middleware Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/next-js-middleware-feature/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/next-js-middleware-feature/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js’ recent 12.0 release included a new beta feature: middleware. For a detailed explanation, you can read all about it in Sam’s previous article, “[Next.js Wildcard Subdomains](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/nextjs-wildcard-subdomains/)”. This article, on the other hand, dives into the overall concept of middleware and how handy it can be in building things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sam Poder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Apps with Firebase]]></title>
        <id>6245d985138a19064b069946</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-apps-with-firebase/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T00:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firebase is a platform developed by Google for creating mobile and web applications.  We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Firebase. This is the perfect course for beginners.  After learning the basics of Firebase, you will learn how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shell Scripting for Beginners – How to Write Bash Scripts in Linux]]></title>
        <id>623cc7e0138a19064b06474d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/shell-scripting-crash-course-how-to-write-bash-scripts-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T19:26:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shell scripting is an important part of process automation in Linux. Scripting helps you write a sequence of commands in a file and then execute them.  This saves you time because you don't have to write certain commands again and again. You can perform daily tasks efficiently and even]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shopify Email Automation – How to Automatically Send Emails]]></title>
        <id>62421c54138a19064b0672c6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/shopify-email-automation/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T17:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Email automation is not something new in the e-commerce space. And it's a pretty simple and straightforward concept. Email automation is all about sending emails to customers based on events that occur on your website, like abandoned cart emails, order confirmation emails, shipping confirmation emails, and so on. The result?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edan Ben-Atar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Augmented Reality Full Course]]></title>
        <id>6245d736138a19064b0698d9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/augmented-reality-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T16:40:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Augmented reality is a technology that lets people superimpose digital content, such as images, sounds & text, over a real-world environment. We just published a 12-hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you about augmented reality from a theoretical and practical perspective. Priyanshu Bhattaharjee developed this course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[charAt() in Java – How to Use the Java charAt() Method]]></title>
        <id>62445137138a19064b068407</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/charat-in-java-how-to-use-the-java-charat-method-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T16:10:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The charAt() method in Java returns the char value of a character in a string at a given or specified index. In this article, we'll see how to use the charAt() method starting with it's syntax and then through a few examples/use cases.  How to Use the Java charAt()]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Convert Video Files to a Gif in Python]]></title>
        <id>6245705d138a19064b068f59</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-video-files-to-gif-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T16:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I was able to convert some video files to a gif as I needed them in gif format for some of my articles. I decided to show you how I did it in 3 lines of code, so you can save yourself the extra effort of looking up a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Time For Reflection (April 2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s welcome the new month with some new wallpapers. Designed with love by artists and designers from across the globe, they are available in versions with and without a calendar for April 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Migrate a Database in PHP Using Phinx]]></title>
        <id>62418eca138a19064b066d98</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/easy-database-migrations-in-php-using-phinx/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T23:59:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building modern web applications usually involves a lot of data. Managing these data (databases) during development and production can be a lot.  This is especially tru if there's more than one developer, and multiple environments where changes have to be manually implemented. Database migrations help developers manage these changes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zubair Idris Aweda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Undo Merge – How to Revert the Last Merge Commit in Git]]></title>
        <id>62442bd2138a19064b06836a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-undo-merge-how-to-revert-the-last-merge-commit-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Branching is an integral part of Git because it lets you work without tampering with code that's already in production. When you finish working with a branch other than main, you'll want to merge it with the main so the feature or bug fix you just integrated will be reflected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Schedule a Task With Firebase Scheduled Cloud Functions]]></title>
        <id>62418f22138a19064b066da1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-schedule-a-task-with-firebase-cloud-functions/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T17:14:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I work on an app that removes the background of any image. The app will have a freemium plan, which means that I will offer a free number of credits to all users, and if they need more credits, they will need to buy more. My Android and iOS app]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dragos Ivanov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Benefits of a Student Email Address]]></title>
        <id>623d7224138a19064b06490a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/top-benefits-of-student-email-address/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T17:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent years, various tech companies and organizations have started supporting students who have an interest in and passion for tech. Many companies give their premium services to students for free, and others offer discounts on their products. If you're a student, basically all you need to take advantage of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hillary Nyakundi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tricks to Cut Corners Using CSS Mask and Clip-Path Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364279</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/cut-corners-using-css-mask-and-clip-path-properties/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T16:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently covered creating fancy borders with CSS mask properties, and now we are going to cut the corners with CSS mask and clip-path! A lot of techniques exist to cut different shapes from the corners of any element. …
Tricks to Cut Corners Using CSS Mask and Clip-Path Properties originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing A Better Infinite Scroll]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/designing-better-infinite-scroll/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/designing-better-infinite-scroll/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this series of articles, we highlight design patterns and techniques to design better interfaces. You can also find more examples in [“Smart Interface Design Patterns”](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com/), a 6h-video course with 100s of hand-picked examples, curated by Vitaly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solid Principles – Single Responsibility Principle and Object-Oriented Design Basics]]></title>
        <id>62153d68c4d0d306772ee7ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/solid-principles-single-responsibility-principle-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T21:16:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SOLID design principles help us create maintainable, reusable, and flexible software designs. Each letter in the acronym SOLID stands for a specific principle.  Here is what each letter in the acronym stands for:  * S: Single responsibility principle.  * O: Open–closed principle.  * L: Liskov]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Full-Stack Real-Time Voting App With Hasura and React]]></title>
        <id>62417eec138a19064b066d4f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-full-stack-real-time-voting-app-with-hasura-and-react/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T19:07:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article will teach you how to build a voting application that displays the poll results in real-time. Each time someone votes, the application updates automatically and shows the new results. Even though you will build a full-stack application, you will not write any backend code thanks to Hasura! The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Catalin Pit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Google – Search Tips for Better Results]]></title>
        <id>60e4a8d6134ad707be00dec6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-google-search-tips/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T18:21:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is the most powerful tool in the world if you know how to use it properly. Let me show you how to get better at Googling. 1. Use Quotes for Exact-Match Search You can use quotes to force an exact-match search. This is super useful if you know exactly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marko Denic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When to Use the keyExtractor Prop in React Native's FlatList]]></title>
        <id>62409608138a19064b06686d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/when-to-use-keyextractor-prop-in-react-natives-flatlist/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T18:05:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In React Native, you can use the FlatList component [https://reactnative.dev/docs/flatlist] to render a long list of data. It renders only the items shown on the screen in a scrolling list and not all the data at once. To render a scrollable list of items using FlatList, you need to pass]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aman Mittal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git List Branches – How to Show All Remote and Local Branch Names]]></title>
        <id>6242cbe5138a19064b06767e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-list-branches-how-to-show-all-remote-and-local-branch-names/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T17:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a version control system used by software developers to track changes in applications and collaborate on projects. One feature that makes Git more dynamic is branches. Developers working on a project can work in different branches before merging their changes with the original code or the main branch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Rational Number? Definition and Rational Number Example]]></title>
        <id>6242b0df138a19064b067633</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-rational-number-definition-and-rational-number-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T17:44:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A rational number is any number that can be written as a fraction, where both the numerator (the top number) and the denominator (the bottom number) are integers, and the denominator is not equal to zero. In other words, a rational number can be expressed as p/q, where p and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Koishigawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git diff Command – How to Compare Changes in Your Code]]></title>
        <id>623acc1dcdcd57069ddfd4fd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-diff-command/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T16:50:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey friends, have you ever been working in Git and found yourself wondering if you're going to stage the correct changes?  Or maybe you want to see what changes you're going to commit compared to your last commit. Perhaps you want to see the differences between two branches, commits,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi⚡</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Portfolio with React featuring Cool Animations]]></title>
        <id>62431cce138a19064b067a32</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-portfolio-with-react-featuring-cool-animations/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T15:13:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a portfolio website is a great way to improve your frontend development skills.  We just published a React tutorial that will teach you how to build a frontend portfolio with neat animations. Slobodan developed this course. He is an experienced developer who has created many popular courses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SmashingConf Is Back In 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/smashingconf-workshops-conferences-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/smashingconf-workshops-conferences-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After two years where almost everything moved online, 2022 marks the return of in-person conferences. In fact, [SmashingConf is back](https://smashingconf.com/conferences): coming to  San Francisco and Austin in June, Freiburg (Germany) in September, and New York in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jarijn Nijkamp)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jobs For Designers And Developers Affected By The War In Ukraine 🇺🇦]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/jobs-designers-developers-war-ukraine/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/jobs-designers-developers-war-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a designer or developer affected by the war in Ukraine? Here are some options to consider if you’re looking for a design or tech job.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React.js Basics – The DOM, Components, and Declarative Views Explained]]></title>
        <id>62356a07cdcd57069ddfb6f6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/reactjs-basics-dom-components-declarative-views/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T09:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React.js is an open source JavaScript library for creating user interfaces. It was created by Facebook back in 2013.  Demand for React developers is skyrocketing, which means that having knowledge of this library is definitely going to be worth it! Some of the popular websites built using ReactJS include]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adwaith KS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TypeScript – Beginner-Friendly TS Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>623f3840138a19064b066060</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/an-introduction-to-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T01:28:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we'll talk about what Typescript is, why is it cool, and how can you use it. Table of Contents  * Intro  * About types * Strings     * Numbers     * Booleans     *]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docker Cache – How to Do a Clean Image Rebuild and Clear Docker's Cache]]></title>
        <id>623ed24e138a19064b065a33</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/docker-cache-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T18:51:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers enable you to package your application in a portable way that can run in many environments. The most popular container platform is Docker [https://www.docker.com/].  This tutorial will explain how to use the Docker build cache to your advantage. Docker Build Cache Building images should be fast, efficient, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sigl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSRF Protection Problem and How to Fix it]]></title>
        <id>6230d0cfc3e3d106805db5c1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/csrf-protection-problem-and-how-to-fix-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T18:39:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One day I was working on a feature at work. I had many branches created in JIRA tickets, so I wanted to open a bunch of PRs (Pull Requests) all at once in different tabs.  This is how I usually work – I have a lot of tabs open]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakub T. Jankiewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Useful Bookmarklets to Boost Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364118</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/web-development-bookmarklets/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T18:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bookmarklet is a JavaScript-based bookmark that adds to a web browser. I’d like to show you some awesome web browser hacks to aid your web development workflow and how to convert those hacks into time-saving bookmarklets.
Activating design mode
…
6 Useful Bookmarklets to Boost Web Development originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roman Numerals – the Roman Numeral for 4, 6, 9, and Others]]></title>
        <id>624145ac138a19064b066afd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/roman-numerals-the-roman-numeral-for-4-6-9-and-others/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T17:41:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roman numerals are a numerical system that originated in ancient Rome. They are used to represent numbers in the decimal system, but they are not used for mathematical operations. In this system, symbols are used to represent different numbers, with I representing 1, V representing 5, X representing 10, L]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Koishigawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Hover And Pointer Media Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/guide-hover-pointer-media-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/guide-hover-pointer-media-queries/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll talk about how to adapt our sites to the different scenarios of a device pointer: whether it has a pointer or not, or how accurate it is. To adapt our site to those devices’ needs we’ll talk about how to properly use media queries `hover`, `pointer`, `any-hover` and `any-pointer`.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cristian Díaz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computer Skills for Résumé – Software Skill Proficiency Guide]]></title>
        <id>62190ea1c4d0d306772efc9b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/computer-skills-for-resume-software-skill-proficiency-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T15:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having strong computer skills is necessary for almost any job. That knowledge can set you apart from others who don't possess it. But what are the most necessary computer skills to have? And when you acquire those skills, how do you showcase them effectively to prospective employers? In this article,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is it Like to Work as a Junior Developer?]]></title>
        <id>6236efafcdcd57069ddfbd4f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-a-junior-developer-do-on-the-job/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T13:51:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're studying to become a professional developer, you might be wondering what a junior developer does on the job. In this article, I will talk about the typical day of a junior developer and what to expect on the job. The Onboarding Process When you get started with a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Starter Template – A Basic HTML5 Boilerplate for index.html]]></title>
        <id>62310caec3e3d106805db8b3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-starter-template-a-basic-html5-boilerplate-for-index-html/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T23:18:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML has different tags, some of which have semantic meanings. A basic boilerplate for an HTML file looks like this:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a UX Engineer? User Experience Engineer Role Explained]]></title>
        <id>602b31e00a2838549dcc6253</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-ux-engineer/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T21:47:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am currently a User Experience or UX Engineer for D2iQ. And lots of people ask me what exactly is a UX Engineer.  This question comes from designers and developers alike. So, I figured it was time to write about it to create awareness and demystify the role. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie Pina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Enum – Enumeration in Java Example]]></title>
        <id>623c71ec138a19064b0642c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-enum-enumeration-in-java-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T21:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An enumeration (enum for short) in Java is a special data type which contains a set of predefined constants.  You'll usually use an enum when dealing with values that aren't required to change, like days of the week, seasons of the year, colors, and so on. In this article,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Color and Text Styles in Figma]]></title>
        <id>62351427cdcd57069ddfb5e4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-color-and-text-styles-in-figma/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T21:24:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll be learning how to create, edit, and use color and text styles in Figma. We'll also learn how to combine color and text styles and use them to create beautiful designs. Styles help you simplify your workflow, keep text and layers consistent, and save valuable time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remix Routes Demystified]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/remix-routes-demystified/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/remix-routes-demystified/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the past months, there have been lots of talks dedictaed to Remix. Routing is not only one of the things that sets it apart from other frameworks, but it also fuels great performance and improves the overall experience for developers. Let’s dig in to all  of the features that build up routing in this powerful framework.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a freeCodeCamp Student Started a Business and Teaches Kids to Code]]></title>
        <id>6236afa1cdcd57069ddfb9e6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-student-started-business-teaches-kids-about-computers/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T22:55:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original Article: 脑瘫、面包店、志愿者——“编程让我变得更真实” [https://chinese.freecodecamp.org/news/cerebral-palsy-bakery-volunteer-programming-makes-me-real/] Original Author: Miya Liu [https://chinese.freecodecamp.org/news/author/miyaliu/] In 2019, the freeCodeCamp Chinese community launched the DevTalk interview program. We invited senior developers, Internet practitioners, and people with development backgrounds to share their experiences learning programming, working experiences, and other exciting stories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Luo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to SSH into a Docker Container – Secure Shell vs Docker Attach]]></title>
        <id>6234b763cdcd57069ddfb192</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-ssh-into-a-docker-container-secure-shell-vs-docker-attach/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T19:47:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers are the bread and butter for running applications today. And the most popular container technology is called Docker [https://www.docker.com/].  Knowing how to SSH into a container is essential to using, debugging, and operating containers on your local operating system or remote setup.  This article will describe different]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sigl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Int Object is Not Iterable – Python Error [Solved]]]></title>
        <id>623c45ea138a19064b064195</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/int-object-is-not-iterable-python-error-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T16:46:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are running your Python code and you see the error “TypeError: 'int' object is not iterable”, it means you are trying to loop through an integer or other data type that loops cannot work on. In Python, iterable data are lists, tuples, sets, dictionaries, and so on. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Microservices with FastAPI]]></title>
        <id>623c9dd5138a19064b06449b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-microservices-with-fastapi/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T16:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FastAPI is a Web framework for developing RESTful APIs in Python. It is a great choice when you want to build an app based on microservices. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to develop microservices app using FastAPI. In this course,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[indexOf in Java – How to Find the Index of a String in Java]]></title>
        <id>62389b37cdcd57069ddfc5a0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/indexof-in-java-how-to-find-the-index-of-a-string-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T16:11:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A string is a collection of characters nested in double quotes. The indexOf  method returns the index position of a specified character or substring in a string. In this article, we'll see the syntax for the different indexOf methods. We'll also look at some examples to help you understand]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use UISearchController in iOS Apps]]></title>
        <id>62388dc7cdcd57069ddfc4d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-use-uisearchcontroller-in-ios-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T15:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! In this article we are going to learn how to use UISearchController in iOS Apps. What are we going to build? We are going to build a movie search application which uses the TMDB [https://www.themoviedb.org/] API to fetch movie info and display it using a UICollectionView based on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sai Balaji K</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a List in Python – Lists in Python Syntax]]></title>
        <id>623af0d3cdcd57069ddfd5bb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-list-in-python-lists-in-python-syntax/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T20:32:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lists are one of the core data structures in Python. We use them for storing any data type, whether it's an integer, string, boolean, or even an object. Because one list can store multiple types of data, lists are one of the most powerful and widely used tools for storing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Security – Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures for K8s Programs]]></title>
        <id>6230d789c3e3d106805db72a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kubernetes-security-common-vulnerabilities-and-exposures/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T19:06:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes has become the go-to tool for orchestration, scaling, automated deployment, and management of containerized applications.  Simply put, Kubernetes is a system that maintains coordination between diverse applications across a group of machines. It is important to note that this system mostly deals with containerized applications, like Docker images.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prajwal Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use *args and **kwargs in Python]]></title>
        <id>623a9306cdcd57069ddfd494</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/args-and-kwargs-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T18:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll discuss *args and **kwargs in Python along with their uses and some examples. When writing a function, we often need to pass values to the function. These values are called function arguments.  Problem with Function Arguments Let's define a function to add two numbers in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add a MetaMask Login to Your Laravel Web Application]]></title>
        <id>6238bd3dcdcd57069ddfc5ad</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/add-a-metamask-login-to-your-laravel-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T18:38:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Logging into a website via third parties is ubiquitous online. Almost every other member-based website allows you to log in with accounts like Facebook, Twitter, and Google. If you’ve ever visited NFT marketplaces like OpenSea or Rarible, you would have noticed they allow you to sign in with a crypto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darren Chowles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Those HTML Attributes You Never Use]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/html-attributes-you-never-use/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/html-attributes-you-never-use/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Louis Lazaris describes and demonstrates some interesting HTML attributes that you may or may not have heard of and perhaps find useful enough to personally use in one of your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taxes for Freelance Developers – How Much Tax You Should Pay as a Freelancer]]></title>
        <id>6238d5a4cdcd57069ddfc7db</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/taxes-for-freelance-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T13:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disclaimer: This article should not be construed as advice for tax management or investment decisions.  Neither the author of this article, nor freeCodeCamp, are professionals in these areas. The discussion below is a matter of personal opinion only and you should discuss such matters with a licensed professional. If]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Ciciliano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is WordPress a Code or No-code Tool?]]></title>
        <id>6236e318cdcd57069ddfbc09</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/is-wordpress-a-code-or-no-code-tool/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T01:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress is an open-source content management system (CMS) for building any kind of website – an eCommerce site, a portfolio, a forum, and many more. WordPress started out as a simple platform for creating blogs, but today WordPress powers over 43% of the total websites on earth, and that number]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Else-If in Python – Python If Statement Example Syntax]]></title>
        <id>623848d7cdcd57069ddfc40d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/else-if-in-python-python-if-statement-example-syntax/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T20:41:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're coding, you need to be able to check certain conditions and change the control of the program execution accordingly.  Python provides many conditional statements for decision making, and if-else is one of them. In this blog post, we will learn:  1. The default order of execution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Go Programming by Building 11 Projects]]></title>
        <id>623a17b2cdcd57069ddfd0b3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-go-by-building-11-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T18:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Go programming language is an open-source and compiled language designed by Google. Go is popular for cloud-based or server-side applications. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you improve your Go skills by teaching you how to create eleven projects. Akhil Sharma developed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove the Start Text from PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>62358f0ccdcd57069ddfb8b4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-starting-text-from-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T17:18:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are using a Windows operating system, you have likely used the latest Windows PowerShell at least once.  Whenever you open the PowerShell, you get a text message inside the terminal which shows the terminal version, the link to download the latest PowerShell, and so on.  Sometimes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Design Is All About Good Timing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/design-is-all-about-good-timing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/design-is-all-about-good-timing/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this shorter series of articles, we highlight design patterns, techniques, and strategies to design better digital interfaces. You can also learn much more in [“Smart Interface Design Patterns”](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com/), a 6h-video course with 100s of hand-picked examples, curated by Vitaly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Operator – Logical Operators in Python]]></title>
        <id>62346eeacdcd57069ddfae72</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/operators-in-python-how-to-use-logical-operators-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T00:21:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Operators in any programming language are the basic building blocks using which we can construct powerful, complex statements for problem solving.  Python offers different types of operators, like arithmetic operators, logical operators, relational operators and so on. In this post, let's dive into logical operators in Python and learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suchandra Datta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage State in a React App – With Hooks, Redux, and More]]></title>
        <id>62376c2ecdcd57069ddfbf7f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manage-state-in-a-react-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T23:31:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi! In this article we'll take a look at the many ways you can manage state in a React app. We'll start by talking about what state is, and then go through the many tools you can use to manage it. We'll look at the simple useState hook and also]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code Extensions to Increase Developer Productivity]]></title>
        <id>6238da58cdcd57069ddfc85e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vs-code-extensions-to-increase-developer-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T20:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code is one of the most popular code editors used by software developers. While it has many great features built-in, there are a lot of extensions you can install to increase your productivity.  We just published a video on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write HTML, the HTML Way (Not the XHTML Way)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363745</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/write-html-the-html-way-not-the-xhtml-way/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T20:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may not use XHTML (anymore), but when you write HTML, you may be more influenced by XHTML than you think. You are very likely writing HTML, the XHTML way.
What is the XHTML way of writing HTML, and what …
Write HTML, the HTML Way (Not the XHTML Way) originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jens Oliver Meiert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Solve freeCodeCamp's Record Collection Challenge]]></title>
        <id>6236cc8acdcd57069ddfba7a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-solve-the-record-collection-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T18:14:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp's JavaScript certification [https://www.freecodecamp.org/learn/javascript-algorithms-and-data-structures/]  is filled with hundreds of interactive challenges. But one of the hardest ones to tackle for most beginners is the Record Collection [https://www.freecodecamp.org/learn/javascript-algorithms-and-data-structures/basic-javascript/record-collection] . In this article, I will walk you through Record Collection [https://www.freecodecamp.org/learn/javascript-algorithms-and-data-str]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chmod Command – How to Change File Permissions in Linux]]></title>
        <id>62375a8dcdcd57069ddfbec1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-change-file-permissions-with-the-chmod-command-on-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T15:33:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the first commands I learned on Linux was the touch command that creates a file using the command line.  If you ever try to create, for instance, a text file, all you have to do is type  touch filename.txt, press Enter, and the file is created]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Rosa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get the Current Time in Python with Datetime]]></title>
        <id>6236e160cdcd57069ddfbbbf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-the-current-time-in-python-with-datetime/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T13:52:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In your Python applications, you might want to work with time to add functionalities like timestamps, check the time of a user’s activity, and more. One of the modules that helps you work with date and time in Python is datetime. With the datetime module, you can get the current]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SyntaxError Unexpected EOF While Parsing Python Error [Solved]]]></title>
        <id>6237b189cdcd57069ddfc248</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/syntaxerror-unexpected-eof-while-parsing-python-error-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T13:47:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Error messages help us solve/fix problems in our code. But some error messages, when you first see them, may confuse you because they seem unclear.  One of these errors is the "SyntaxError: unexpected EOF while parsing" error you might get in Python. In this article, we'll see why this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows High Contrast Mode, Forced Colors Mode And CSS Custom Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/windows-high-contrast-colors-mode-css-custom-properties/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/windows-high-contrast-colors-mode-css-custom-properties/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Custom Properties can be used for far more than just color, and their values update in realtime, both via display mode updates and JavaScript logic. This is powerful stuff. Eric explains how modern CSS is a powerful piece of assistive technology that can thread into it to create flexible, maintainable and adaptive digital experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing SVG Patterns to Their Smallest Size]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364090</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/optimizing-svg-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-18T22:31:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently created a brick wall pattern as part of my #PetitePatterns series, a challenge where I create organic-looking patterns or textures in SVG within 560 bytes (or approximately the size of two tweets). To fit this constraint, I have …
Optimizing SVG Patterns to Their Smallest Size originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bence Szabó</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Compare Strings – How to Check for String Equality]]></title>
        <id>6233b95bcdcd57069ddfadb1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-compare-strings-how-to-check-for-string-equality/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-18T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When crafting the logic in your code, you may want to execute different commands depending on the similarities or differences between two or more strings.  In this article, we'll see various operators that can help us check if strings are equal or not. If two strings are equal, the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend VS Backend – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>6228643563ded806bb9e6f77</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/frontend-vs-backend-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-18T20:48:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the start of your web development journey, you will often hear about the frontend and the backend parts of an application. But what do these terms mean exactly? In this article, you will learn about the differences between the two by examining the frontend and backend separately. Here is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Make A Drag-and-Drop File Uploader With Vue.js 3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/drag-drop-file-uploader-vuejs-3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/drag-drop-file-uploader-vuejs-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-18T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building on a previous article on How to Build a Drag-and-Drop File Uploader, we’ll be adding some new features, but more importantly (maybe), we’ll be learning how to build it in Vue 3 and learn some best practices for Vue along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joseph Zimmerman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python String to Int – Convert a String Example]]></title>
        <id>62333a16cdcd57069ddfa7f3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-string-to-int-convert-a-string-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T23:53:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When creating a program, you may need to get numerical input from users and perform various mathematical operations on the value.  Similarly, there are cases where you might want to perform mathematical operations on string values.  In both cases, the values returned are strings so we cannot perform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn WebGPU – A next-generation graphics API for the web]]></title>
        <id>62322496cdcd57069ddfa225</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-webgpu-a-next-generation-graphics-api-for-the-web/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T21:33:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebGPU is the next-generation graphics API and future web standard for graphics and compute, aiming to provide modern 3D graphics and computation capabilities with the GPU acceleration. We just published a WebGPU course on the freeCodeCmap.org YouTube channel.  Dr. Jack Xu developed this course. Dr. Xu has over 25]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Search for Files from the Linux Command Line]]></title>
        <id>62331abccdcd57069ddfa72f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-search-for-files-from-the-linux-command-line/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T19:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Searching for files is relatively easy when you are using a GUI. But in certain environments like GUI-less servers, you need to search for files using the command line.  There is a powerful command in Linux that helps you search for files and folders called find. In this article,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS REM – What is REM in CSS?]]></title>
        <id>621d17ecc4d0d306772f1b2f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-rem-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T19:47:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I'm going to discuss some use cases of REM (Root EM) in CSS.  I will begin with some background knowledge about CSS properties and values, which I think is necessary. Then I'll discuss the differences between absolute length values and relative ones. REM is a relative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slimane Aguersif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Sleep – time.sleep() in Python]]></title>
        <id>623308b9cdcd57069ddfa696</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-sleep-time-sleep-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T17:22:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While running a Python program, there might be times when you'd like to delay the execution of the program for some seconds. The Python time module has a built-in function called time.sleep() with which you can delay the execution of a program. With the sleep() function, you can get more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Portfolio Website Using HTML, CSS, & JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>6233481fcdcd57069ddfa86c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-portfolio-website-using-html-css-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T14:49:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are looking for a web developer job it can be helpful to have a portfolio website. It can also be helpful to have projects you've created to show to potential employers. You can accomplish both tasks at once by creating your own portfolio website with HTML, CSS, &]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Contact Book Application in Python using Rich, Typer, and TinyDB]]></title>
        <id>6231a5b3c3e3d106805db9fc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-contact-book-application-in-python-using-rich-typer-and-tinydb/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T00:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Python tutorial, we'll learn how to build a terminal application (CLI app) to manage our contact book.  We'll use Typer for building the CLI app, Rich for a colorized terminal output, and TinyDB for the database. Get your tools ready We'll be using a few external libraries]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Debugging? How to Debug Your Code for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>62321616cdcd57069ddfa114</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-debugging-how-to-debug-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T21:31:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article we'll talk about what debugging is, how to debug your code, and how you can get better at it. Table of contents  * How Debugging Started  * Why Should You Learn About Debugging?  * How to Debug Your Code  * How to Get]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Functions – How to Define and Call a Function]]></title>
        <id>6231fec0cdcd57069ddfa05d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-functions-define-and-call-a-function/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T17:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In programming, a function is a reusable block of code that executes a certain functionality when it is called. Functions are integral parts of every programming language because they help make your code more modular and reusable. In this article, I will show you how to define a function in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Python Crash Course]]></title>
        <id>623204d4cdcd57069ddfa080</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-python-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T15:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python is one of the most popular programming languages in the word. It is used everywhere from web development, to simple scripts, to machine learning and AI. We just published a Python tutorial on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you the basics of Python. Bobby Stearman developed this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claymorphism: Will It Stick Around?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/claymorphism-css-ui-design-trend/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/claymorphism-css-ui-design-trend/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This fresh new design trend has been picking up steam with the rising popularity of colorful inflated 3D graphics in web illustrations and with the latest Virtual Reality projects like “Horizon Worlds”. Let’s see if there is room for Claymorphism on the UI, and how we can create this effect with CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Get Last Element in List – How to Select the Last Item]]></title>
        <id>62310fbac3e3d106805db8d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-get-last-element-in-list-how-to-select-the-last-item/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T23:26:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lists are one of the built-in data types in Python. You use them to store multiple elements in one variable.  Lists enable us group similar data together, and we can also perform operations on these grouped elements at the same time. In this article, we will talk about how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Hooks Fundamentals for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>62245d2ac4d0d306772f4e3a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-hooks-fundamentals/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T19:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React.js is an open-source JavaScript-based user interface library. It is hugely popular for web and mobile app development.  React follows the principle of component-based architecture. A component in React is an isolated and reusable piece of code. The components can be of two types – class components and functional]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn React in Spanish – Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>6213cb7d21bfb3068cf2c271</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-react-in-spanish-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T15:41:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi! If you speak Spanish and you want you learn React, you're in the right place. In this article, you will find a brief introduction to React. You will learn why it is so important for web development and why you should learn it.  Then, you will find a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced OpenGL Animation Technique – Skeletal Animations with Assimp]]></title>
        <id>6230acbbc3e3d106805db524</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-opengl-animation-technique-skeletal-animations/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T15:37:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want your 3D animated characters to move in realistic-looking ways, you need to have a good understanding of skeletal animations. We just posted a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel well teach you how to do skeletal animations with OpenGL and the Assimp library. Etay Meiri created]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS-Tricks is joining DigitalOcean!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365042</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-tricks-is-joining-digitalocean/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T12:18:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey hey!
I’ve got a big announcement to make here. (Where’s my gong? I feel like this really needs a good gong hit.)
CSS-Tricks, this very website you’re looking at, has been acquired by DigitalOcean!
You can hear …
CSS-Tricks is joining DigitalOcean! originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Add to Dictionary – Adding an Item to a Dict]]></title>
        <id>622b887163ded806bb9e8566</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-add-to-dictionary-adding-an-item-to-a-dict/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T00:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data structures help us organize and store collections of data. Python has built-in data structures like Lists, Sets, Tuples and Dictionaries.  Each of these structures have their own syntax and methods for interacting with the data stored.  In this article, we'll talk about Dictionaries, their features, and how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose a Topic for Your Technical Article]]></title>
        <id>622ce4df63ded806bb9e8dae</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/choose-a-topic-for-your-next-article/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T23:52:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After you write your first couple of articles, a problem most technical writers face is: "So, what do I write about next?" It can be a frustrating question, so I wrote this article to help. In it, I will give you tips that will save you the headache the next]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Akinyemi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Plugins in Figma]]></title>
        <id>622acecd63ded806bb9e8101</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/plugins-in-figma/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T20:42:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll learn how to install plugins in Figma. You'll also get to know some really cool Figma plugins that every designer and developer should use.  Plugins help make your design process easier and smoother. From image assets to embedding maps into your designs, plugins are easy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove All Docker Images – A Docker Cleanup Guide]]></title>
        <id>622cecd663ded806bb9e8dfd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-all-docker-images-a-docker-cleanup-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T20:25:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers are everywhere in today’s tech world. The most popular technology for container management is Docker [https://www.docker.com/]. It makes using containers easy and helps you easily get applications up and running.  Unfortunately, this can take a lot of disk space, and you will eventually end up with a full]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sigl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perform CRUD Operations using Angular 13]]></title>
        <id>622c9d4363ded806bb9e8a9f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-perform-crud-operations-using-angular-13/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T19:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a full-stack application can be tough. And the base of building such an application is learning how to perform CRUD operations – Create, Read, Update, and Delete.  It's by using these operations that we manage the data flow between the client application and the server. So, in this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nishant Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Music for Programming – Coding Music Playlists, Radio Stations, Videos, and Lives]]></title>
        <id>622c7bf563ded806bb9e8a20</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/music-for-programming-youtube-channels-twitchtv-web-radios-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T19:16:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you like listening to music while you code? If so, you're in luck. This blog post is all about music for programming.  In this reference guide, I'll be sharing a variety of different playlists, radio stations, and videos that you can listen to while coding. Whether you're a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaël Thomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Compiler? Compilers in C Explained for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>62239491c4d0d306772f4a00</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-compiler-in-c/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T18:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that it is thanks to compilers that software exists? Exactly – compilers are very important, and some form of a compiler exists in all programming languages. But, what is a compiler? What do they do exactly? This article will teach you:  1. What a compiler is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Securely Erase a Disk and File using the Linux shred Command]]></title>
        <id>622b53f963ded806bb9e8436</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/securely-erasing-a-disk-and-file-using-linux-command-shred/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T14:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Removing files and formatting disks is a common task for users. And Linux provides a number of utilities to delete files and folders from the command line.  The most common command to delete files and folders is rm and rmdir, respectively. You can read in detail about the rm]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Dictionary in Python – Python Dict Methods]]></title>
        <id>6221c8d2c4d0d306772f3f43</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-dictionary-in-python-python-dict-methods/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T14:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn the basics of dictionaries in Python. You will learn how to create dictionaries, access the elements inside them, and how to modify them depending on your needs. You will also learn some of the most common built-in methods used on dictionaries. Here is what]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Break and Python Continue – How to Skip to the Next Function]]></title>
        <id>62134fa821bfb3068cf2bf43</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-break-and-python-continue-how-to-skip-to-the-next-function/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T13:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you ever need to skip part of the current loop you are in or break out of the loop completely, then you can use the break and continue statements. In this article, I will cover how to use the break and continue statements in your Python code. How to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The CI/CD Flow For Your Application]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/improving-ci-cd-flow-application/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/improving-ci-cd-flow-application/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for ways to create a smooth CI/CD flow for your software? In this article, Tom Hastjarjanto shares some useful concepts that can be combined with GitHub Actions and NPM packages. With this setup, you will be able to release multiple times per hour with a fully documented trace managed by Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tom Hastjarjanto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Comment Block – How to Comment Out Code in Python]]></title>
        <id>622ae68d63ded806bb9e81de</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-comment-block-how-to-comment-out-code-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-11T20:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll talk about comments in Python, why they are important, and how to use them effectively in your code.  When to Use Comments In this section, we'll talk about some of the general use cases for comments. These aren't only applicable to Python, but to most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a New Stacking Context with the Isolation Property in CSS]]></title>
        <id>61e5c35ab837d507ba0a4b06</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-css-isolation-property/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-11T20:03:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is the CSS Isolation Property? In CSS, you can use the isolation property to create a new stacking context. Here's what that looks like: .container-for-new-stacking-context {   isolation: isolate; } The default value for isolation is auto, which is a bit more nuanced as a stacking context can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie Pina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Concatenate Strings – How to Combine and Append Strings in Python]]></title>
        <id>622a2a6663ded806bb9e7d22</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-concatenate-strings-how-to-combine-and-append-strings-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-11T17:19:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're learning a programming language, you're likely to come across a data type called a string. A string usually contains a series of characters nested in quotation marks that can be represented as a text.  In this article, we will talk about string concatenation in Python. This is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Mobile App Marketing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/guide-mobile-app-marketing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/guide-mobile-app-marketing/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Standing out among the millions of mobile apps can be challenging, but proper marketing can give you that crucial edge. This piece shares how to start your mobile app marketing strategy and improve it as you go while keeping up with the latest trends in the market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sona Dabaghyan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CNCF Kubernetes and Cloud-Native Associate Study Course – Pass the Exam With This Free 13-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>6220e4a7c4d0d306772f366e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cncf-kubernetes-cloud-native-associate-exam-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T20:19:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This exam mostly deals with cloud-native concepts. Even if you are new to cloud-native, you should be able to prepare for this exam and earn the CNCF certification. This entire free course is now live on YouTube, and linked below. Before you dive into it, read this guide to help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Brown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CNCF Kubernetes and Cloud-Native Associate Study Course – Pass the Exam With This Free 13-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>6220e4a7c4d0d306772f366e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cncf-kubernetes-and-cloud-native-associate-study-course-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-13-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T20:19:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This exam mostly deals with cloud-native  concepts. Even if you are new to cloud-native, you should be able to prepare for this exam and earn the CNCF certification. This entire free course is now live on YouTube, and linked below. Before you dive into it, read this guide to help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Brown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Execute and Run Java Code from the Terminal]]></title>
        <id>6226651763ded806bb9e60eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-execute-and-run-java-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T19:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you work with Java, you've probably used one of the well known text editors like Sublime Text, VS Code, Brackets, Atom, and Notepad++ as well as IDEs like Apache NetBeans and IntelliJ IDEA.  Running code in your IDE is straightforward, but you don't often get to see how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Rename a Local or Remote Branch in Git]]></title>
        <id>622a09b763ded806bb9e7c6f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-rename-a-local-or-remote-branch-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T19:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a version control system that software developers use to keep track of changes in their applications and collaborate with others. One helpful feature of Git is branches. Different people working on a software project can work in different branches before merging their changes with the original code. You]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Print Without New Line – Print on the Same Line]]></title>
        <id>6228676363ded806bb9e6fa7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-print-without-new-line-print-on-the-same-line/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T18:11:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The print function is an important function in Python, as it is used to redirect output to the terminal. The output can also be redirected to a file.  The print function, by default, prints on a new line every time. This is due to the definition of print() in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/introduction-aws-cloud-development-kit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/introduction-aws-cloud-development-kit/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Vivek Maskara introduces Amazon Web Services’ (AWS) Cloud Development Kit (CDK) which is increasingly becoming a popular tool for managing AWS-based infrastructure. We’ll take a closer look into CDK concepts, and then how to use the AWS CDK toolkit to deploy a sample application to an AWS account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vivek Maskara)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Developed My First Adventure Game]]></title>
        <id>60c5b9d1d3126007592d75b4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-i-developed-my-first-game/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T20:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's hard to tell exactly when my journey creating Occulto, a point and click adventure game, started. But I have a significant date in mind: 3 May 2018. Here's one thing that got the ball rolling: > Luigi: Hello Andrea. Sorry to bother you. I would like to learn how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrea Koutifaris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[git config – How to Configure Git Settings to Improve Your Development Workflow]]></title>
        <id>6222908cc4d0d306772f4477</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-config-how-to-configure-git-settings/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T19:14:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[git config is a powerful command in Git. You can use the Git configuration file to customize how Git works. This file exists in the project level where Git is initialized ( /project/.git/config) or at the root level (~/.gitcongig). If no configurations are specified, Git uses its default settings. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React State for Absolute Beginners]]></title>
        <id>6216b67dc4d0d306772ef0ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-state/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T16:48:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most essential concepts that any modern JavaScript developer needs to understand is state.  If you don't understand state, you're not going to be able to fully use and take advantage of powerful libraries such as React to build your applications.  Let's see exactly what state]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Vim – Beginner's Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>6228c8f663ded806bb9e72e2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-vim-beginners-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T16:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vim is a highly configurable text editor that you can use for software development or any kind of text editing.  We just published a full Vim course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Vim. Florian Dedov from NeuralNine developed this course. When someone]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>