<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-06-02T01:04:41.234Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ice Cream Ahead (June 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s kick off June with some fresh inspiration! Artists and designers from across the globe once again tickled their creativity to celebrate the beginning of the new month with a collection of beautiful and unique wallpaper calendars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Suz Hinton went from Dev to White Hat Hacker [Podcast #126]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-suz-hinton-went-from-dev-to-white-hat-hacker-podcast-126/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-suz-hinton-went-from-dev-to-white-hat-hacker-podcast-126/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T15:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews Suz Hinton. She's a software engineer, security researcher, and one of the first ever people to live-stream her coding on Twitch. We talk about: How Suz started her...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Prototypal Inheritance in JavaScript? Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-prototypal-inheritance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-prototypal-inheritance/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T08:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prototypal inheritance can feel like a complex concept shrouded in technical jargon. But fear not! This guide will break it down using clear, relatable examples that go beyond the typical textbook explanations.  We'll ditch the confusing terms and focus on real-world scenarios that you can easily understand. By the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asoluka Tochukwu Austin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the Basics of Go by Building a Full Stack Web App with React and Go]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-basics-of-go-by-building-a-full-stack-web-app-with-react-and-go/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-basics-of-go-by-building-a-full-stack-web-app-with-react-and-go/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T15:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Go can work great on the backend for a React project. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org channel that will leach you how to build a full stack web app with React and Go. This comprehensive course is designed to teach you the fundamenta...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Complete C Programming Course from Dr. Chuck]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-c-programming-course-from-dr-chuck/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-c-programming-course-from-dr-chuck/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T15:21:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just released a comprehensive C course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This course, developed by Dr. Charles Severance (aka Dr. Chuck), is designed to help you understand computer architecture and low-level programming using the classic C...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Praise Of The Basics]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/in-praise-of-the-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/in-praise-of-the-basics/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What does it mean to learn the “basics”, or fundamentals, of front-end web development? Is starting with HTML and CSS still the best entry point to learn how to make websites and apps when we have a seemingly endless supply of frameworks? Geoff Graham thinks so and discusses why you might consider going “back to basics” to start or move forward in your career.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Context API Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-context-api-explained-with-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-context-api-explained-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T08:13:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing state has always been a critical aspect of making web applications with React. The most basic way to do this is prop drilling. In prop drilling, you pass props around from the parent component to other components that need it, no matter how deeply nested they are. The problem]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do Numerical Conversions Work in Computer Systems? Explained With Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-numerical-conversions-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-numerical-conversions-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T19:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computers perform complex calculations when carrying out their assigned tasks. At the very core, the calculations boil down to operations like comparisons, assignments, and addition. Have you ever wondered how they are performed under the hood and wh...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decision Trees For UI Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/decision-trees-ui-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/decision-trees-ui-components/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine finally resolving never-ending discussions about UI decisions for good. Here are some practical examples of decision trees for UI components and how to use them effectively. An upcoming part of [Smart Interface Design Patterns](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust Tutorial – Learn Advanced Iterators & Pattern Matching by Building a JSON Parser]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rust-tutorial-build-a-json-parser/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rust-tutorial-build-a-json-parser/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T10:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Iterators and match patterns are two of the most used language features in Rust. If you have written any real world application, big or small, chances are that you've already used these, whether knowingly or unknowingly. In this tutorial, I aim to help you understand how they actually work, the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshul Sanghi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linear Algebra Crash Course - Mathematics for Machine Learning and Generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linear-algebra-crash-course-mathematics-for-machine-learning-and-generative-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linear-algebra-crash-course-mathematics-for-machine-learning-and-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T20:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linear algebra is a useful skill for professionals in data science, machine learning, and AI. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you linear algebra. This crash course spans just over 6 hours and is a great...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an EKS Cluster Across AWS Local Zones using the AWS CDK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-eks-cluster-using-aws-local-zones-with-aws-cdk/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-eks-cluster-using-aws-local-zones-with-aws-cdk/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T14:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Local Zones are a new type of infrastructure that enables you to build and run applications closer to end-users, providing low latency and improved performance.  They are designed to provide the same high availability and reliability as an AWS Region, but with the added benefit of low-latency connections]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gursimar Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linear vs Logistic Regression:  How to Choose the Right Regression Model for Your Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linear-regression-vs-logistic-regression/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linear-regression-vs-logistic-regression/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T13:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regression models identify trends in a dataset and predict outcomes based on the trends they have analyzed and identified.  Linear and Logistic Regression are two types of regression models that are similar but carry out their functions in distinct ways. They're also two fundamental techniques in machine learning that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwadamisi Samuel Praise</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React 19 – New Hooks Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-19-new-hooks-explained-with-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-19-new-hooks-explained-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T12:56:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi fellow readers! Web Development is a constantly evolving landscape. The whole ecosystem consists of different libraries and technologies. React is one of the most widely used libraries in web development.  There are small releases every now and then. However, this year, the React team has made a significant]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Era Of Platform Primitives Is Finally Here]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/netlify-platform-primitives/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/netlify-platform-primitives/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Application frameworks have built whole ecosystems on top of them. Let’s take a closer look at serverless platforms such as Netlify’s [Platform Primitives](https://www.netlify.com/platform/primitives) and explore how they can increase our productivity with a serverless fullstack experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide to the Node.js Event Loop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-guide-to-the-node-js-event-loop/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-guide-to-the-node-js-event-loop/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T07:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js is an open-source JavaScript runtime environment that allows you to run JavaScript outside the browser. Although Node.js is single-threaded, it has an event loop that makes it multi-threaded. The Node.js event loop is a crucial mechanism in Node.js that makes Node.js programs run concurrently and asynchronously. Mastering the Node.js]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Musab Habeeb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manipulate Strings in JavaScript – With Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manipulate-strings-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manipulate-strings-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T21:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[String manipulation is a common task for programmers, whether it is extracting information from the string, converting letter cases, joining strings, or trimming extra white spaces. This tutorial covers various methods and techniques for manipulating strings using JavaScript, offering you a comprehensive guide on how to work with strings in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Hu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build CRUD Operations with .NET Core – A Todo API Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-crud-operations-with-dotnet-core-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-crud-operations-with-dotnet-core-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T14:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to this comprehensive guide on building CRUD operations with .NET Core. We'll use a Todo API as our practical example so you can get hands-on experience as you learn. Throughout this tutorial, you'll learn how to create, read, update, and delete Todo items, and how to leverage Entity Framework]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaiah Cliford  Opoku</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source is Changing. The Changelog Host Jerod Santo on How to Keep Up [Podcast #125]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/open-source-is-changing-the-changelog-host-jerod-santo-on-how-to-keep-up-podcast-125/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/open-source-is-changing-the-changelog-host-jerod-santo-on-how-to-keep-up-podcast-125/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T14:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Jerod Santo, host of The Changelog, a podcast about open source software development that has been going strong for 15 years. Jerod is plugged in to the world of Open Source, going to all the big con...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an MVP for Your Project – and Why You Should Do It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/minimum-viable-product-between-an-idea-and-the-product/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/minimum-viable-product-between-an-idea-and-the-product/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proof of concept, prototypes, wireframes, mockups… what actually constitutes a Minimum Viable Product (MVP)? Well, it's a product with just enough features to gather comprehensive qualitative feedback. In practice, it's as easy to understand the concept of an MVP as it is to ride a bicycle. Let's do it then.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oleg Romanyuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching It Up With HTML’s Latest Control]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/switching-it-up-html-latest-control/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/switching-it-up-html-latest-control/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of relying on checkbox hacks to create a “switch” control for forms that toggle between two states, HTML may be gaining a native way to go about it by adding a `switch` attribute to checkbox inputs. Daniel Yuschick walks us through a first impression of switch controls and discusses current and ongoing considerations that need to be explored further before it is ready for prime time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Daniel Yuschick)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose a Tech Stack for Your SaaS Product – Lessons from a Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/choose-a-tech-stack-for-your-saas-product/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/choose-a-tech-stack-for-your-saas-product/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T08:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a developer, I've seen how choosing the "right" tech stack can be a double-edged sword. I often fell into the trap of chasing shiny new technologies, thinking they were the key to building the next great product. But experience has taught me that prioritizing speed to market trends often]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Cruz Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Partition Queues for Distributed Workloads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-partition-queues-for-distributed-workloads/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-partition-queues-for-distributed-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T20:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technology, like human lives, evolves, and with this evolution comes the use of better solutions to existing problems. You might wonder: does this complicate systems or make them more efficient?  In this article, we will discuss some measures you can take to make systems much more efficient and reliable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoye Victor Chukwuebuka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pass the AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate Certification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pass-the-aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-certification/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pass-the-aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-certification/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T20:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you trying to earn the AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate certification? We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is is designed to help you pass the certification exam and showcase your expertise in AWS t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Practices For Naming Design Tokens, Components, Variables, And More]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/naming-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/naming-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can we get better at naming? This post is dedicated to naming conventions, tips, and real-world examples that help you name things in a robust and flexible way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Your Django App – Best Practices and Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-secure-your-django-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-secure-your-django-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T15:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a software developer or engineer, it's not enough to know how to build useful solutions – you must also ensure that they are secure. Prioritizing your users is crucial when developing and deploying your software because if users can't use your app, it becomes useless. In this guide, we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Iroegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern CSS Layouts: You Might Not Need A Framework For That]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/modern-css-layouts-no-framework-needed/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/modern-css-layouts-no-framework-needed/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easy to get lost in a sea of CSS frameworks and libraries, each promising easier styling and smoother layouts. Brecht De Ruyte demonstrates four CSS utility classes (plus a bonus) using techniques that allow them to be used practically anywhere you need a particular layout — be it Grid or Flexbox — with configurable options.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript Interview Prep Handbook – Essential Topics to Know + Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/js-interview-prep-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/js-interview-prep-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T09:58:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a widely used language in web development and powers interactive features of virtually every website out there. JavaScript makes it possible to create dynamic web pages and is very versatile. JavaScript remains one of the most in-demand programming languages in 2024. Many companies are looking for proficiency in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Style React Components]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-style-react-components/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-style-react-components/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T09:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can only make your React app visually appealing to users with styling. That makes styling a fundamental aspect of building captivating user interfaces. With React's component-based architecture, there are a ton of options for styling. These include traditional CSS, utility-first approach, CSS-in-JS solutions, and more. In this article, we'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[APIs with Node.js and Express – Course in Spanish for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/apis-with-nodejs-and-express-course-in-spanish-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/apis-with-nodejs-and-express-course-in-spanish-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T08:11:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An application programming interface (API) is software that acts as an intermediary, allowing two applications to communicate. This project will teach you how to develop an API step by step and connect it to a database. We just published a course on ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-Tuning LLM Models Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fine-tuning-llm-models-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fine-tuning-llm-models-course/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T16:22:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-tuning is a process in machine learning that allows you to adapt pre-trained models to specific tasks or datasets, enhancing their performance and usability. We just posted a comprehensive course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Real Time Chat App with Supabase and Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-real-time-chat-app-with-supabase-and-angular/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-real-time-chat-app-with-supabase-and-angular/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T14:32:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you improve your skills with Supabase and Angular. In this course, you will learn how to build a real-time chat application. The course is perfect for anyone lookin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Collaborate with Web Development Teams Using Productivity Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-collaborate-with-web-development-teams-using-productivity-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-collaborate-with-web-development-teams-using-productivity-tools/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T12:52:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a web developer, designer, or project manager, you're likely quite busy these days and have a lot on your plate.  This is partly because the number of websites is growing rapidly, with 71% of all businesses [https://www.forbes.com/advisor/business/software/website-statistics/] in the world having one. In fact, every three seconds]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarif Kahn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Resilient Microservice Systems – SOLID Principles for Microservices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/solid-principles-for-microservices/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/solid-principles-for-microservices/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:56:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are in the era of transformative technology with several innovations springing up to improve service delivery and enhance customers’ satisfaction. More so is the introduction of microservices and other distributed systems into the software industry to revolutionize enterprise application development. Its introduction has helped to solve problems associated with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oluwatobi Joshua</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hidden vs. Disabled In UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/hidden-vs-disabled-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/hidden-vs-disabled-ux/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Should you hide or disable a feature? You’ve probably been there before. Here are some considerations for hiding versus disabling, along with possible alternatives to improve UX. An upcoming part of [Smart Interface Design Patterns](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript Class Handbook – Complete Guide to Class Fields and the Super Keyword]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-class-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-class-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T20:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Classes let you privatize your data while providing users indirect access to it. It is an excellent way to prevent direct access to your constructor’s data. This handbook aims to show you exactly how classes work in JavaScript. We will also discuss class fields and the super keyword. Table of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi Sofela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become an Open Source Project Maintainer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-an-open-source-maintainer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-an-open-source-maintainer/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T17:21:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might be wondering why you would want to become an open source maintainer.  Well, I can tell you from my own experience that you'll learn a lot, grow your network, and meet and collaborate with people you wouldn’t have the opportunity to otherwise.  It also helps you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BekahHW</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Online Safety – A Guide to Protecting Yourself]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/online-safety-a-guide-to-protecting-yourself/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/online-safety-a-guide-to-protecting-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T15:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating digital accounts safely is a concern for many in the modern age.  Digital accounts have become an integral part of our daily lives. From email and online banking to accounts on ride-sharing platforms like Uber and e-commerce platforms like Amazon, protecting our digital lives online is becoming imperative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohit Jacob Mathew</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a REST API Without a Server]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-rest-api-without-a-server/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-rest-api-without-a-server/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T10:13:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a Front-End developer and want to showcase your skills, it may be a problem if you use GitHub pages or Netlify to show your apps.  Instead, you can create a REST API directly in the browser without the need of any server. With this, you can showcase]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakub T. Jankiewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Your Flutter Package Privacy Manifest Compatible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-your-flutter-package-privacy-manifest-compatible/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-your-flutter-package-privacy-manifest-compatible/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T08:10:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beginning May 1st, Apple will enforce all new applications or updated versions of applications that will be uploaded to the Apple Store, to include a Privacy Manifest file.  If you are unfamiliar with what a Privacy Manifest is, I suggest reading my  other article [/news/what-the-ios-privacy-manifest-means-for-developers/]. There has been]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Ben Rachel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI is Overrated – Why ThePrimeagen Ripped Out GitHub Copilot From His Code Editor [Podcast #124]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-is-overrated-why-theprimeagen-ripped-out-github-copilot-from-his-code-editor-podcast-124/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-is-overrated-why-theprimeagen-ripped-out-github-copilot-from-his-code-editor-podcast-124/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T23:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp I interview The Primeagean. He's a software engineer who streams himself programming. He recently left his job at Netflix to stream full-time. We talk about: Prime's journey from his teacher tellin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn College Precalculus with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-college-precalculus-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-college-precalculus-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T19:07:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Precalculus is an important mathematical course that lays the groundwork for calculus and other higher-level math subjects. We just released a college precalculus course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This course is unique in that you will ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A User Segmentation Matrix To Foster Cross-Org Alignment]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/building-user-segmentation-matrix-foster-cross-org-alignment/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/building-user-segmentation-matrix-foster-cross-org-alignment/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there such a thing as harmony between designers and developers in the workplace, and if so, how can it be achieved? In this article, Chris Day explores the challenges of effective collaboration, outlines the key factors at play, and (hopefully!) empowers you to find the right solutions to help you and your team deliver to their full potential.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Talke Hoppmann-Walton)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deal with Traffic Surges in Distributed Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deal-with-traffic-surges-in-distributed-systems/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deal-with-traffic-surges-in-distributed-systems/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web and Distributed Systems can often get overwhelmed with traffic.  What leads to systems being overwhelmed, why does it happen, and what are some common strategies we can use to deal with this? We'll answer these questions in this article. Table of Contents  1. What is traffic in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anant Chowdhary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why am I not getting Quincy Larson's email anymore?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-am-i-not-getting-quincy-larsons-email-anymore/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-am-i-not-getting-quincy-larsons-email-anymore/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T23:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're not getting Quincy Larson's email each week, and you want to get them again, do the following: Fill out this form. It takes less than a minute. Search your spam folder for "Quincy Larson" and if you find any of my emails in there, mark th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Join the freeCodeCamp Discord Server and Chat with Fellow Campers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-join-the-freecodecamp-discord-server-and-chat-with-fellow-campers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-join-the-freecodecamp-discord-server-and-chat-with-fellow-campers/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T21:13:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp runs a popular Discord community where we hang out and chat about technology. You can join in the fun and learn from fellow campers who are going through freeCodeCamp's core curriculum. You can use this link: https://discord.com/invite/f...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond CSS Media Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/beyond-css-media-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/beyond-css-media-queries/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Juan Diego Rodriguez explains why media queries still occupy a vital role in responsive layouts; only they are now one tool in a larger toolbox with modern techniques that are best when used together.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Pop-up Image in Your Spreadsheet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-image-lightbox/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-image-lightbox/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T10:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll show you two ways to create a lightbox effect in a spreadsheet. The first will trigger the image to be displayed in a large area in the sheet. The second will be an actual HTML popup on top of the sheet. If you want to follow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the Algorithms Behind Quantum Computing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-algorithms-behind-quantum-computing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-algorithms-behind-quantum-computing/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T15:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum computing leverages the principles of quantum mechanics to process information at incredible speeds. We just posted a Quantum Computing course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This course, created by Michael from Quantum Soar, is desi...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transforming The Relationship Between Designers And Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/transforming-relationship-between-designers-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/transforming-relationship-between-designers-developers/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there such a thing as harmony between designers and developers in the workplace, and if so, how can it be achieved? In this article, Chris Day explores the challenges of effective collaboration, outlines the key factors at play, and (hopefully!) empowers you to find the right solutions to help you and your team deliver to their full potential.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Chris Day)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zustand vs useState – How to Manage State in React Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/zustand-vs-usestate-how-to-manage-state-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/zustand-vs-usestate-how-to-manage-state-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T09:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State management in React applications has evolved a lot in recent years, especially with the advancement of functional state and the introduction of hooks.  Developers have more flexibility and state management has generally become simpler. But as applications grow, they become more complex to manage – and you may]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use WordPress with AI Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-wordpress-with-ai-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-wordpress-with-ai-tools/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T17:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress is the most popular way to make websites. I just created a new course for the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use WordPress. Plus, you'll learn how to use AI tools from Hostinger to create blog content more quick...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Designers Aren’t Understood]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/designers-business-ux-language/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/designers-business-ux-language/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do we conduct UX research when there is no or only limited access to users? Here are some workarounds to run UX research or make a strong case for it. An upcoming part of [Smart Interface Design Patterns](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microservices vs Monoliths: Benefits, Tradeoffs, and How to Choose Your App's Architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/microservices-vs-monoliths-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/microservices-vs-monoliths-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T00:18:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're tasked with designing an application, one of the first questions that probably comes to your mind is whether to design a microservice or a monolith. The consequences of this seemingly simple and innocuous decision are potentially significant, and they're often not fully thought through. A wrong decision can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn JavaScript with Clear Explanations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-with-clear-explanations/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-with-clear-explanations/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T19:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a versatile and powerful programming language primarily used to create interactive and dynamic content on websites. It is one of the core technologies of the World Wide Web, alongside HTML and CSS. While HTML provides the structure of w...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Store Data Locally in React Native Expo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-store-data-locally-in-react-native-expo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-store-data-locally-in-react-native-expo/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T11:42:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React Native has grown in popularity as a mobile application development tool because of its ability to create cross-platform applications using familiar JavaScript and React principles.  When building mobile applications, one common requirement is the ability to save data locally on the device. This is when local storage comes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Caleb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Handle Events in React – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-events-in-react-19/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-events-in-react-19/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T09:26:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Event handling is fundamental to understanding how React processes browser events and updates the DOM. As a React developer, it's a critical skill to have, as it enables efficient management of user interactions within web apps. This article covers how to set up event handlers and proceeds to more elegant]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Times You Need A Custom @property Instead Of A CSS Variable]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/times-need-custom-property-instead-css-variable/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/times-need-custom-property-instead-css-variable/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Preethi Sam walks through an example that demonstrates where custom properties are more suitable than variables while showcasing the greater freedom and flexibility that custom properties provide for designing complex, refined animations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Sam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a React Chatbot – a Step by Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-react-chatbot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-react-chatbot/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T22:27:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving realm of web technologies, the integration of AI-powered chatbots has become a defining trend in 2024.  With rapid advancements in Large Language Models (LLMs), chatbots have grown to become pivotal tools adopted across many websites and services. From FAQ bots to live chat support, they can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tan Jin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Pro Designer in 2024 [Interview with Gary Simon Podcast #123]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-pro-designer-in-2024-interview-with-gary-simon-podcast-123/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-pro-designer-in-2024-interview-with-gary-simon-podcast-123/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T18:05:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Gary Simon, a developer and designer who started DesignCourse and has published several courses on freeCodeCamp.org over the years. We talk about: Growing up in rural Ohio, marrying young, and stayi...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Gary Simon Rebuilt his Developer Agency after a Massive Loss [Podcast #123]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-gary-simon-rebuilt-his-developer-agency-after-a-massive-loss-podcast-123/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-gary-simon-rebuilt-his-developer-agency-after-a-massive-loss-podcast-123/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T18:05:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Gary Simon, a developer and designer who started DesignCourse and has published several courses on freeCodeCamp.org over the years. We talk about: Growing up in rural Ohio, marrying young, and stayi...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a QR Code Generator for URLs with Node.js, Next.js, and Azure Blob Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-qr-code-generator-using-nodejs-nextjs-azure-blob-storage/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-qr-code-generator-using-nodejs-nextjs-azure-blob-storage/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T15:41:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A while ago, a client asked me to help them create a special app for generating QR codes so users could receive payments.  What set this app apart was that instead of users entering a URL to generate a QR code, they would initiate a request through the app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayomide Wilfred</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize Your Database – Optimization Principles and Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/database-optimization-principles/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/database-optimization-principles/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T15:21:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Databases are an integral component of building applications, whether web, desktop or mobile. They symbolically serve as the mitochondria of the application, as their primary function is to manage data. Database management is a critical skill a developer must possess in building scalable applications that have a high level of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oluwatobi Joshua</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Handle Concurrency with Goroutines and Channels in Go]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-concurrency-in-go/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-concurrency-in-go/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T15:07:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concurrency is the ability of a program to perform multiple tasks simultaneously. It is a crucial aspect of building scalable and responsive systems.  Go's concurrency model is based on the concept of goroutines, lightweight threads that can run multiple functions concurrently, and channels, a built-in communication mechanism for safe]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Destiny Erhabor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should You Learn TypeScript? Pros and Cons of TS Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/should-you-learn-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/should-you-learn-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T14:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll explore the question: is TypeScript worth learning? Before we try finding the answer together, let me tell you why I'm suddenly asking this. I come from a Java background where writing code demands that you be type-aware. This means that if you are declaring a string,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Modern Guide For Making CSS Shapes]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/modern-guide-making-css-shapes/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/modern-guide-making-css-shapes/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this comprehensive guide, Temani Afif explores different techniques for creating common shapes with the smallest and most flexible code possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Objects in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-objects-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-objects-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T06:22:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In programming, objects are fundamental building blocks used to represent real-world entities or concepts. JavaScript, a versatile and popular language, offers various ways to create these objects.  This article dives deep into these methods, equipping you with the knowledge to craft objects tailored to your programming needs. We'll begin]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JS Remove Char from String – How to Trim a Character from a String in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-remove-char-from-string/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-remove-char-from-string/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T19:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manipulating strings is a fundamental skill in programming. A common task you might encounter when coding in JavaScript is trimming characters from a string. Trimming involves removing specific characters from the beginning and/or end of a string. Th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tezos Blockchain Development Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tezos-blockchain-development-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tezos-blockchain-development-course/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T14:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tezos is a blockchain network that distinguishes itself through a unique self-amending ledger, allowing it to upgrade without the need for hard forks—an approach that promotes continuity and reduces division within the community. Tezos aims to addres...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Forensics Of React Server Components (RSCs)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/forensics-react-server-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/forensics-react-server-components/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React Server Components (RSCs) combine the best of client-side rendering, and author Lazar Nikolov thoroughly examines how we got here with a deep look at the impact that RSCs have on the page load timeline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lazar Nikolov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Python on a Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-python-on-a-mac/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-python-on-a-mac/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T06:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python is the most popular first language for programmers on a Mac. Until recently, the language's lack of standard development tooling, plus competing optional-but-essential development tools, meant a rocky start for Python beginners.  To cut through the confusion, I'll show you an up-to-date approach to install Python and set]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kehoe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Array Handbook – How to Create, Work with, and Loop Through Arrays]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/php-array-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/php-array-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T22:25:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In every programming language, arrays provide a flexible option to store more than one data type in a single variable. They are one of the most versatile data structures in the programming world, which is one reason a lot of external data and many APIs come as arrays. When you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run a Postgres Database in Azure Kubernetes Service and Integrate it with a Node.js Express Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-run-postgres-in-kubernetes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-run-postgres-in-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T20:43:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone! Today, you're going to learn about deploying a Postgres container in Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) and connecting it to a Node.js application. In this fast-paced development landscape, deploying via containers, particularly with Kubernetes, is becoming increasingly popular. Some companies perform numerous deployments daily, so it's crucial for you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayomide Wilfred</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a React Native Splash Screen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-native-splash-screen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-native-splash-screen/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T19:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll get a hands-on practical guide for creating a native splash screen for React Native CLI applications.  Note that this tutorial is not applicable for apps created with Expo. SVG Icon Image and Background The first thing you need is an image. It can be in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucas Garcez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Analysis with Python – How I Analyzed My Empire State Building Run-Up Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/empire-state-building-run-up-analysis-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/empire-state-building-run-up-analysis-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T16:56:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A tower running race [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tower_running] is a race that you run up the stairs of a building. These happen around the world. I got the chance to participate in the Empire State Run Up in NYC, 2023 edition.  > The Empire State Building Run-Up (ESBRU)—the world’s first and most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement an OAuth2 Resource Server with Spring Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/oauth2-resourceserver-with-spring-security/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/oauth2-resourceserver-with-spring-security/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T15:39:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone! Imagine you are building an awesome application, with lots of cool features. Picture a backend server at its core that hosts a majority of the business logic and exposes functionality through APIs. Once you have planned out your APIs, there's one crucial step you need to take care]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Git in Detail to Manage Your Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-git-in-detail-to-manage-your-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-git-in-detail-to-manage-your-code/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:42:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version control is an essential skill for anyone involved in software development, from solo hobbyists to professional developers working in large teams. Understanding how to effectively manage changes and collaborate on code is critical, and Git is ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pass the GitHub Actions Certification Exam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pass-the-github-actions-certification-exam/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pass-the-github-actions-certification-exam/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:29:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub recently launched a GitHub Actions certification exam. And we just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will prepare you to pass this exam. This course is ideal for developers, DevOps professionals, and anyone interes...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep Learning Course – Math and Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deep-learning-course-math-and-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deep-learning-course-math-and-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:17:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the math behind deep learning is important if you want to become proficient in machine learning techniques. We just published a 14-hour deep learning course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This course is specifically tailored t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML for Beginners – HTML Basics With Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-html-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-html-basics/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T19:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the exciting world of web development! In this beginner's guide, you will learn the fundamentals of HTML, the backbone of every web page.  Imagine a tree: its roots anchor and nourish the entire plant. Similarly, HTML, the root of web development, provides the foundation for every webpage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casmir Onyekani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Git Submodules – Explained With Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-git-submodules/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-git-submodules/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:40:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is undeniably a very important tool for developers, as it helps us collaborate seamlessly, track changes efficiently, and maintain project integrity across distributed environments. However, as projects grow in complexity and scope, so does their dependencies. For this reason, there is a need for a mechanism to properly manage]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jima Victor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Concatenate Strings – How JS String Concatenation Works]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-js-string-concatenation-works/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-js-string-concatenation-works/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When coding in JavaScript, you may need to combine multiple strings to create a new, longer string. This operation is known as concatenation. In this article, you will learn five ways to concatenate strings in JavaScript. How to Concatenate Strings i...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Run UX Research Without Access To Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/how-run-ux-research-without-access-users/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/how-run-ux-research-without-access-users/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do we conduct UX research when there is no or only limited access to users? Here are some workarounds to run UX research or make a strong case for it. An upcoming part of Smart Interface Design Patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How is Flutter Platform-Agnostic?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-is-flutter-platform-agnostic/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-is-flutter-platform-agnostic/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T07:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter builds applications for multiple platforms (desktop, mobile, and web) from the same codebase. Flutter does this in a pixel-perfect and platform-agnostic manner.  In this article, we will explore how Flutter is platform-agnostic through how it renders user interfaces and through platform channels. Table of Contents  * What]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Obum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do Closures Work in JavaScript? Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understand-javascript-closures/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understand-javascript-closures/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T07:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sally and Joe are two love birds. They shared everything with each other and soon enough it was almost impossible to think that anything could come between them. One day, they had a quarrel which built up to a break up.  It was hard for Joe and he wanted]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asoluka Tochukwu Austin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React Developer Tools – Explained With Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-devtools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-devtools/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T20:12:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traditional browser developer tools are designed to inspect and debug web pages by interacting with your HTML, CSS, and JavaScript code. However, you can't use them to inspect and debug React applications efficiently due to the nature of React. This is where the React Developer Tools, AKA React DevTools comes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-amazon-ec2-auto-scaling/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-amazon-ec2-auto-scaling/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T16:32:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Auto scaling is like having a smart system that keeps an eye on how many people are visiting your website. When you have a lot of people, it quickly adds more servers to handle the extra traffic. And when things quiet down, it scales back to save you money. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Destiny Erhabor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decoding Chaos: How True Randomness Works in Software Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/true-randomness-in-software-engineering/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/true-randomness-in-software-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T16:27:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Randomness When you hear the word "randomness," what usually comes to mind? You may think of  something intangible, an abstract concept without a specific shape or form  – it's random.  But randomness is much more than an abstract idea – it's a fundamental aspect of our daily decisions]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gor Grigoryan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Harness Mouse Interaction Data For Practical Machine Learning Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/harness-mouse-interaction-data-machine-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/05/harness-mouse-interaction-data-machine-learning/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Eduard Kuric discusses mouse interaction data, what kind of magic can be done with it, and some of the hidden pitfalls to watch out for so you get a head start incorporating them in your solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eduard Kuric)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the useReducer Hook in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-usereducer-hook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-usereducer-hook/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T17:48:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll take a deep look at the useReducer hook in React. It can look confusing, especially if you are coming across the hook for the first time. This article breaks down the useReducer hook concept into understandable bits with both code and real-world examples to enable you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Olanrewaju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Construction Worker to Teaching Millions of Developers with John Smilga [Podcast #122]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-construction-worker-to-teaching-millions-of-developers-with-john-smilga-podcast-122/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-construction-worker-to-teaching-millions-of-developers-with-john-smilga-podcast-122/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T16:07:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview prolific programming teacher John Smilga. John grew up in the Soviet Union. He worked construction for 5 years before becoming a developer. Today he has taught millions of fellow devs through his man...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>