<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-02-02T01:13:09.723Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Al Assistants That Help Your Productivity (Besides ChatGPT)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-assistants-for-productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-assistants-for-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T22:10:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT may be the talk of the town these days, but there are other AI assistants that can help you increase your productivity.  AI assistants are specialized artificial intelligence software programs designed to imitate human behavior and thinking. They are able to recognize objects, solve problems, and perform tasks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create and Publish an NPM Package – a Step-by-Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-and-publish-your-first-npm-package/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-and-publish-your-first-npm-package/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T21:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NPM is the largest software registry on the internet. There are over a million packages in the NPM Library.  Developers publish packages on NPM to share their code with others. And organisations also use NPM to share code internally. In this article, you will learn how to create a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Serialize Your Data in Kotlin and Jetpack Compose]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serializing-your-data-in-kotlin/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serializing-your-data-in-kotlin/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T21:19:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serialization is the process of transforming data that's in one format into another format that can be stored.  If you have ever worked with a database or fetching data from a server, this should all be familiar to you. If not, you have come to the right place.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Ben Rachel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caching Data in SvelteKit]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376634</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/caching-data-in-sveltekit/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T15:04:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My previous post was a broad overview of SvelteKit where we saw what a great tool it is for web development. This post will fork off what we did there and dive into every developer’s favorite topic: caching. So, …
Caching Data in SvelteKit originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding App Directory Architecture In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/understanding-app-directory-architecture-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/understanding-app-directory-architecture-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new App Directory architecture has been the main character of the recent Next.js release, which keeps bringing up many questions. In this article, Atila Fassina explores the advantages and pitfalls of this new strategy and reflects on whether you should use it in production now or not.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React.js vs React Native – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-js-vs-react-native-whats-the-difference/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-js-vs-react-native-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T00:41:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are React.js and React Native the same? If you're new to the world of web and mobile development, you might be wondering the same thing.  As a newbie, it's easy to assume that React.js are React Native are the same. After all, they both have "React" as part of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kingsley Ubah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the "this" Keyword in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-this-keyword-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-this-keyword-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T23:40:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone! In this article we're going to talk about the THIS keyword in Javascript.  This used to be a concept that confused me a little bit, so I'll try to break it down for you so you can understand its uses and in what situations can it be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asynchronous Programming in JavaScript – Guide for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/asynchronous-programming-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/asynchronous-programming-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T23:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To understand what asynchronous programming means, think about multiple people working on a project simultaneously, each on a different task. In traditional (synchronous) programming, each person would have to wait for the person before them to finish their task before starting their own.  But with asynchronous programming, everyone can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dickson Boateng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio vs Visual Studio Code – What's The Difference Between These IDE Code Editors?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/visual-studio-vs-visual-studio-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/visual-studio-vs-visual-studio-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T19:17:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first time I heard about “Visual Studio”, I thought it was the same as “Visual Studio Code”. I don’t know why Microsoft decided to confuse everyone with the names of those two development tools. But that’s a story for another day. “Visual Studio” and “Visual Studio Code” are not]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chart.js Tutorial – How to Make Pie and Doughnut Charts in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-pie-and-doughnut-charts-using-chartjs-in-angular/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-pie-and-doughnut-charts-using-chartjs-in-angular/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T17:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial we will learn how to create a simple pie and doughnut chart using the Chart.js library in an Angular application. What is Chart.js? Chart.js is a JavaScript library for building charts. It's designed to be intuitive and simple, but it's powerful enough to build complex visualizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Swatej Patil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Length of List – How to Find the Size of a List]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-length-of-list-how-to-find-the-size-of-a-list/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-length-of-list-how-to-find-the-size-of-a-list/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T16:56:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A list is a data structure in Python that contains multiple elements in a particular order. And sometimes you might need to get the size of a list. I'll show you how to do that in this article. How to Create a List in Python You can create lists in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Magic Of February (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-february-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-february-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new batch of desktop wallpapers is for you. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for February 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Scraping in JavaScript – How to Use Puppeteer to Scrape Web Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-scraping-in-javascript-with-puppeteer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-scraping-in-javascript-with-puppeteer/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T15:26:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the world of web scraping! Have you ever needed data from a website but found it hard to access it in a structured format? This is where web scraping comes in. Using scripts, we can extract the data we need from a website for various purposes, such as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaël Thomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How B2B Sales Help Us Understand Our Role As UX Designers Better]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/b2b-sales-understand-role-ux-designers-better/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/b2b-sales-understand-role-ux-designers-better/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout a customer journey (particularly in B2B), there will be interactions that are primarily between two people rather than a human and an interface. In this article, Paul Boag explains why you cannot improve the user experience without considering the entirety of the UX journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Unit Tests for Instance Methods in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-unit-tests-for-instance-methods-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-unit-tests-for-instance-methods-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T00:13:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tutorial will teach you how to write unit tests for instance methods in Python. In a previous tutorial [/news/how-to-write-unit-tests-for-python-functions/], we covered how to write unit tests for Python functions. While unit testing for instance methods works similarly, you may have some challenges creating and managing objects (instances of a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bala Priya C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Require – How to Use the require() Function in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-javascript-require-function/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-javascript-require-function/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T00:07:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, modules refer to a file that holds JavaScript code which performs a specific purpose. Modules are self-contained, making it easy to add, remove, and update functionalities without affecting your entire code because they are decoupled from other pieces of code. When you have these modules in separate JavaScript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Dockerize an AdonisJS Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-dockerize-an-adonisjs-application/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-dockerize-an-adonisjs-application/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T00:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating software is hard. So you want to build it once and run it everywhere without adjusting configurations for different operating systems and machines every time. Well, this is one problem that dockerizing your application can help solve. Here's what we'll cover in this tutorial:  * What is Docker?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Solomon Eseme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Hooks Tutorial – How to Use the useReducer Hook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/usereducer-hook-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/usereducer-hook-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T23:15:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State is an important part of a React application. Most functionalities involve making state updates in your component.  But as your application grows, state updates become more and more complex. These complex state updates might get overwhelming when you revisit your code. There is a different way of handling]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find a Remote Developer Job in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-a-remote-developer-job/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-a-remote-developer-job/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T22:09:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the world continues to adapt to the new normal of remote work, the demand for remote developers has never been higher.  Companies are now realizing the benefits of hiring remote workers, including cost savings and access to a wider pool of talent.  If you're looking for a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Field</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java List – Example Lists in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-lists-work-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-lists-work-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T18:09:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use the Java List interface to store objects/elements in a an ordered collection. It extends the Collection interface.  TheList interface provides us with various methods for inserting, accessing, and deleting elements in a collection. In this article, you'll learn how to extend and implement the List interface]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Sheets Tutorial – How to Enable Multiple Selection Data Validation Using Apps Script]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-sheets-multiple-data-validation-selections/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-sheets-multiple-data-validation-selections/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T17:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I will show you how to allow for multiple items to be selected using the drop-down data validation feature in Google Sheets. Here's the Google Sheet [https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1yxc4k1x5idcS_moQ1Bq8LnHGZF2nm9dpARglY7Rv0UI/edit#gid=390071620]  we'll use for the example. You can make a copy of this to edit yourself by clicking File ->]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where Hot Trends Go to Die – What We Can Learn from Failed Tech Products]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/where-hot-tech-trends-go-to-die/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/where-hot-tech-trends-go-to-die/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T17:17:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're interested in technology, you may also have an active interest in learning about hot technology trends.  But you don't want to take every last one of these gadgets and business fads too seriously: some are bound to disappoint.  (Although don't think you can hold me personally]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TypeScript in React Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/using-typescript-in-react-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/using-typescript-in-react-apps/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T16:59:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! A while ago I wrote an article about TypeScript [/news/an-introduction-to-typescript/], explaining its main features and why it's a good idea to use it in large projects.  Today we're going to take a quick look at how we can use TypeScript in a React app, so you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master the HTTP Networking Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/http-networking-protocol-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/http-networking-protocol-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T16:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP (Hypertext Transfer Protocol) is the foundation of data communication on the World Wide Web. It is used to transfer data from the client (web browser) to the server (web host) and vice versa. Understanding the basics of HTTP networking is crucial for anyone who wants to pursue a career]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Vim – Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vim-beginners-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vim-beginners-guide/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T16:08:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vim is one of the most popular text editors among Linux users. Linux System Administrators especially often prefer it to other editors.  In this article, you'll learn a lot about Vim and see how you can quickly start using Vim as a developer. What is Vim?  Vim is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easy SVG Customization And Animation: A Practical Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/svg-customization-animation-practical-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/svg-customization-animation-practical-guide/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers often feel discouraged from editing SVG markup and experimenting with SVG animations, thinking it’s a significant time investment or they need to use a complex animation library to do so. In this article, Adrian showcases his favorite tricks, which make the process streamlined and fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AR, VR, and a Model for 3D in HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376674</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/ar-vr-and-a-model-for-3d-in-html/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-27T14:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tucked down somewhere in the Safari Technology Preview 161 release notes is a seemingly innocous line about support for a new HTML element and attribute:
Added support for <model src> and honor <source type> attributes (257518@main)
Anytime I …
AR, VR, and a Model for 3D in HTML originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Strong Customer Relationships For User Research]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/build-strong-customer-relationships-user-research/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/build-strong-customer-relationships-user-research/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-27T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Rachel walks you through various ways that product teams can utilize to build relationships with customers. She will share some tips and tricks from her experience that have helped her nurture customer relationships and build better products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Renaissance Rachel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perform Database Migrations using Go Migrate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/database-migration-golang-migrate/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/database-migration-golang-migrate/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T23:17:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its introduction, the programming language Go (also known as Golang) has become increasingly popular. It is known for its simplicity and efficient performance, similar to that of a lower-level language such as C++.  While working with a database, schema migration is one of the most important tasks that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rwitesh Bera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Switch Blockchains on MetaMask with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-switch-blockchains-on-metamask-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-switch-blockchains-on-metamask-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T23:15:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With over 10,000 blockchains currently operating, there are endless possibilities for deploying your smart contracts.  For anybody to be able to use your Decentralized Application (DApp), they need to be connected to the blockchain where you've deployed your smart contract. This article will show you how to prompt your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Omobola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Polymorphic Associations in Ruby on Rails]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/polymorphic-association-ruby-on-rails/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/polymorphic-association-ruby-on-rails/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T18:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polymorphic association in Ruby on Rails refers to the type of active record association. From the Rails Guide [https://guides.rubyonrails.org/association_basics.html#polymorphic-associations] , it allows a single model to belong to more than one other model on a single association. This tutorial assumes that you have some knowledge of a few associations in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sampurna Chapagain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A High-Contrast Design System With CSS Custom Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/creating-high-contrast-design-system-css-custom-properties/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/creating-high-contrast-design-system-css-custom-properties/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing our colors can truly help people to access our content. In this article, Brecht de Ruyte takes a deep dive into how we can create a high-contrast system while maintaining a balance between designing something accessible and respecting the look and feel of a brand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better ROI For Your Digital Products: Why Continuous Research Is Key]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/better-roi-digital-products-continous-research/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/better-roi-digital-products-continous-research/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[57% of product professionals say that product research has a positive effect on customer satisfaction. 42% agree that it affects profitability. Imagine how much more successful your product would be if you did research continuously?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Suzanne Scacca)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here are 850+ Ivy League Courses You Can Take Right Now for Free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ivy-league-free-online-courses-a0d7ae675869/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ivy-league-free-online-courses-a0d7ae675869/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T03:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 8 Ivy League schools [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ivy_League] are among the most prestigious universities in the world. They consist of Harvard, Yale, Princeton, Columbia, Cornell, Dartmouth, Brown, and the University of Pennsylvania. In 2023, all 8 Ivy League schools are ranked in the top-20 of the U.S. News & World Report national]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhawal Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Pandas DataFrame Groupby Method]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pandas-dataframe-groupby-method/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pandas-dataframe-groupby-method/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T21:32:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pandas is a fast and approachable open-source library in Python built for analyzing and manipulating data.  This library has a lot of functions and methods to expedite the data analysis process. One of my favorites is the groupby method, mainly because it lets you get quick insights into your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Faith Oyama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Comparison Operators – How to Compare Objects for Equality in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-comparison-operators-how-to-compare-objects-for-equality-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-comparison-operators-how-to-compare-objects-for-equality-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T18:47:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While coding in JavaScript, there may be times when you need to compare objects for equality. The thing is, comparing objects in JavaScript is not that straightforward. In this article, you learn three ways to compare objects for equality in JavaScript. Let's get into it! What's the Difference Between Comparing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Integrate PayPal into Your HTML, CSS, and JS Product Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/integrate-paypal-into-html-css-js-product-pages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/integrate-paypal-into-html-css-js-product-pages/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T17:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine if you had an amazing product landing page, with customers lined up to make a purchase. But your manual JavaScript payment processing with server-side scripts, Authorize.net, or 2Checkout failed you. Frustrated by being unable to make the purchase, your customer leaves to go to your competitors. I imagine that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Duggan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MySQL Date Functions – Explained with Example Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mysql-date-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mysql-date-functions/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T17:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SQL is a programming language we use to interact with relational databases. SQL databases contain tables, which contain rows of data. These tables can contain a wide range of data types. In this article, you'll learn how MySQL functions help make date management very easy.  These functions help perform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zubair Idris Aweda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animating CSS Grid (How To + Examples)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376528</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/animating-css-grid-how-to-examples/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T16:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m pleased to shine a light on the fact that the CSS grid-template-rows and grid-template-columns properties are now animatable in all major web browsers! Well, CSS Grid has technically supported animations for a long time, as it’s baked right …
Animating CSS Grid (How To + Examples) originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code a Reddit Clone with React and Firebase]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-reddit-clone-with-react-and-firebase/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-reddit-clone-with-react-and-firebase/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T15:18:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coding a Reddit clone is a great project to help you learn a bunch of different programming skills and technologies. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to code a Reddit clone using React, Firebase, Next.js, Chakra UI, and TypeScript. Shadee Merhi]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KNN Algorithm – K-Nearest Neighbors Classifiers and Model Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/k-nearest-neighbors-algorithm-classifiers-and-model-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/k-nearest-neighbors-algorithm-classifiers-and-model-example/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T15:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The K-Nearest Neighbors (K-NN) algorithm is a popular Machine Learning algorithm used mostly for solving classification problems.  In this article, you'll learn how the K-NN algorithm works with practical examples. We'll use diagrams, as well sample data to show how you can classify data using the K-NN algorithm. We'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Product Reviews And Ratings UX: A Designer’s Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/product-reviews-ratings-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/product-reviews-ratings-ux/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do we design effective reviews and ratings? With a distribution chart, decimal scores, tags, recommendation score and unedited product photos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Better Policy with Open Policy Agent and the Apache APISIX OPA Plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-open-policy-agent-and-apache-apisix-opa-plugin/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-open-policy-agent-and-apache-apisix-opa-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T19:28:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One common thing in every organisation is policy [https://www.openpolicyagent.org/docs/latest/philosophy/#policy]. Policies define how an organisation operates.  They are essential to the long-term success of an organisation. They preserve significant knowledge about how to comply with matters such as legal requirements, work within technical constraints, and avoid repeating mistakes.  Softwares]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Njoku Samson Ebere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Sort a List in Java – Java List Sorting Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-sort-a-list-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-sort-a-list-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T19:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes data needs to be arranged in a specific order so it's easier to understand, search, and process.  We call this process sorting. Sorting refers to arranging data in a specific order using certain criteria. You can sort different types of data, including numbers, strings, and objects. Java provides]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Smart Goals You Can Actually Achieve]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-smart-goals-you-can-achieve/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-smart-goals-you-can-achieve/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T17:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we start the new year, it is a good time to reflect back on how the past 12 months went, and gear up for the next 12.  I like to spend a few hours in the beginning of the year doing a reflection of the past year, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shruti Kapoor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Connectivity – How We Connect to the Internet and IoT Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/digital-connectivity-internet-and-iot-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/digital-connectivity-internet-and-iot-explained/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T17:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telephones changed the way we all talked to each other and went about our work (well, the way our great-grandparents did, at any rate). Information could now be communicated instantly, rather than being sent over slow, overland routes.  But that's hardly news to anyone these days. The modern network]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copying Designs Doesn’t Work, And Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/copying-designs-doesnt-work/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/copying-designs-doesnt-work/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Striking the right balance between inspiration and innovation might be hard. Let’s explore how to effectively get inspiration from others without losing that magic spark, including some do’s and don’ts along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Peter Ramsey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 55 With Tejas Kumar: Is Technology Making Us Redundant?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/smashing-podcast-episode-55/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/smashing-podcast-episode-55/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we ask whether technology is making us redundant; will we all soon be replaced with AI? Vitaly Friedman talks to Tejas Kumar to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does a VPN Work? Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-does-a-vpn-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-does-a-vpn-work/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T00:08:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you worry about online security while using public Wi-Fi? Or has someone told you that you might get hacked when using an insecure connection and someone will steal all your details? Well, you might have also heard that you should use a VPN to protect your online privacy. But]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tejan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Wireshark – Computer Networking Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-wireshark-computer-networking/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-wireshark-computer-networking/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T23:35:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, you will learn about the single most important and useful tool in Computer Networks – Wireshark. This post relies on basic knowledge of computer networks. Be sure to check my  previous post about the five layers model [/news/the-five-layers-model-explained/] if you need a refresher. What is Wireshark?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free College Algebra Course (with Python Code!)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/college-algebra-course-with-python-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/college-algebra-course-with-python-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T17:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[College Algebra is an important course for a wide variety of professions and University programs. It is especially important for computer science students. We just published a full and comprehensive college Algebra course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This course is designed as a full one-semester college course. This course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Unit Tests in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-unit-tests-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-unit-tests-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T15:35:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building a website and coding all the cool features you had planned, you'll want to test if everything works as expected. Now, you can’t do that just by going through the website yourself – you need to check if each unit of your code is working as you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Visualize Confusing Git Commands with Git-Sim]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-sim/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-sim/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T14:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is an essential tool for developers to learn in order to effectively collaborate on source code. But certain Git concepts and commands are notoriously difficult for devs to learn. Not only that, but Git commands often have nuances that lead to varying results on the state of your local]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Stopak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are CSS Pseudo-Classes?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-pseudo-classes-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-pseudo-classes-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To make sense of CSS pseudo-classes, we need to understand state. In this context, the word state means a situation or condition that something is in at a particular point in time. Take the state of a stoplight, for example. At any point in time it has one of three]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Kurata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With SvelteKit]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376610</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/getting-started-with-sveltekit/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T13:48:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SvelteKit is the latest of what I’d call next-gen application frameworks. It, of course, scaffolds an application for you, with the file-based routing, deployment, and server-side rendering that Next has done forever. But SvelteKit also supports nested layouts, server mutations …
Getting Started With SvelteKit originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Level Up Your CSS Skills With The :has() Selector]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/level-up-css-skills-has-selector/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/level-up-css-skills-has-selector/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS relational selector :has() offers what was previously impossible without JavaScript. Let’s explore some magical powers that :has brings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Submit a Form with JavaScript – JS Submit Button Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-submit-a-form-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-submit-a-form-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T22:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When building applications and websites on the internet, you’ll sometimes need your users to supply information by filling out a form. But then you might wonder – how do you get this data from the form? Well, you can do this with JavaScript. In this article, you will learn how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write And Run C and C++ Code in Visual Studio Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-and-run-c-cpp-code-on-visual-studio-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-and-run-c-cpp-code-on-visual-studio-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T21:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code (or VS Code for short) is a very common and widely used text editor and IDE (Integrated Development Environment). You can make VS Code very powerful like an IDE using a lot of extensions. Before approaching the process of running your first C or C++ code on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remove From String in Python – How to Remove Characters from a String]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/remove-from-string-in-python-how-to-remove-characters-from-a-string/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/remove-from-string-in-python-how-to-remove-characters-from-a-string/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T20:20:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, there are times when you might want to remove unnecessary characters from a string. Python provides two built-in methods you can use for that purpose – replace() and translate(). So, in this article, you will learn how to remove a character from a string with those two methods]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Native Networking – How To Perform API Requests In React Native using the FetchAPI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-native-networking-api-requests-using-fetchapi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-native-networking-api-requests-using-fetchapi/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T19:35:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[APIs, or application program interfaces, are essential mechanisms for businesses in all industries. They allow for a secure exchange of data between two different systems, such as a web application and a database. Think of when you are using a mobile app to order food from a restaurant. The restaurant's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kingsley Ubah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Functions Work in JavaScript – JS Function Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-functions-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-functions-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T17:52:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a widely-used programming language that is essential for web development. Its ability to run on both client-side and server-side makes it a versatile tool that has become an essential tool for web developers. JavaScript is a high-level, interpreted language used on the client side, meaning it runs in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Excel Tutorial – How to Clean Data with the TRIM() and CLEAN() Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/excel-tutorial-clean-data-with-the-trim-and-clean-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/excel-tutorial-clean-data-with-the-trim-and-clean-functions/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T17:42:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Without clean data, your spreadsheet is knocking on death's door. In this tutorial I will show you two fast ways to clean up the data in your Excel or Google Sheets spreadsheet. When dealing with data sets, especially large ones and/or those that you didn't create, it is likely that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Key To Good Component Design Is Selfishness]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/key-good-component-design-selfishness/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/key-good-component-design-selfishness/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Daniel Yuschick demonstrates that building selfish components is the key approach to avoiding different pitfalls on the way to good component design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Daniel Yuschick)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Spell Check on your Linux Terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/spell-check-on-your-linux-terminal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/spell-check-on-your-linux-terminal/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T16:17:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know you can use the terminal to check the spelling of a passage you've written?  The terminal has a lot of utility commands, but most people are unaware of many of them.  I've seen people using Microsoft Word or Google to check the spelling of a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Real-World Uses for :has()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376331</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/more-real-world-uses-for-has/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T15:34:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The :has() pseudo-class is, hands-down, my favorite new CSS feature. I know it is for many of you as well, at least those of you who took the State of CSS survey. The ability to write selectors upside down …
More Real-World Uses for :has() originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose a WordPress Host]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hosting-a-wordpress-website/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hosting-a-wordpress-website/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T20:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking for a reliable and secure WordPress hosting provider? With so many options available, it can be hard to know which host is right for your needs. When selecting a hosting provider, several factors need to be taken into consideration. From the size of your website to the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Campbell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Pre-Caching? How to Increase Website Speed and Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-detailed-guide-to-pre-caching/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-detailed-guide-to-pre-caching/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T18:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speed and performance are two of the key ingredients that make a website stand out from its peers. Imagine visiting a bestseller list on the Amazon website and finding that the product pages take forever to show up. What about a blog publishing some great stories that readers aren’t able]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saurabh Dashora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add to a List in Python – List Addition Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-to-a-list-in-python-list-addition-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-to-a-list-in-python-list-addition-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T17:51:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A list is a mutable sequence of elements surrounded by square brackets. If you’re familiar with JavaScript, a Python list is like a JavaScript array. It's one of the built-in data structures in Python. The others are tuple, dictionary, and set. A list can contain any data type such as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Organize Your Code with Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/organizing-code-with-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/organizing-code-with-functions/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T17:29:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Functions are a fundamental building block of programming. They help us organize our code into manageable and reusable pieces.  Let's explore the basics of functions by way of a burger joint. A burger joint may seem like an odd place to learn about code organization...but let's see where this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Kurata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Stack Development with MongoDB, Java, and React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-development-with-mongodb-java-and-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-development-with-mongodb-java-and-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T17:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Full stack web developers must be familiar with a wide variety of technologies and programming languages.  We just published a video course in the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is designed to introduce students to building full stack applications using MongoDB, Java, Spring Boot, and React. The course will guide]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a ChatCPT Clone with React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-chatcpt-clone-with-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-chatcpt-clone-with-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T16:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The OpenAI API is a powerful tool that allows developers to harness the power of advanced machine learning algorithms to create intelligent applications. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use the OpenAI API with React to create a powerful application]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Tailwind CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-tailwind-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-tailwind-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T16:50:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tailwind CSS is a powerful tool for creating beautiful and functional designs. We just published a video course on the freeCodeCamp.org channel that is designed to introduce you to the basics of using Tailwind CSS, and to help you understand how to use it to create effective and efficient designs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Document Object Model Works in JavaScript – DOM Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-dom/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-dom/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T15:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Document Object Model (DOM) is an essential part of web development. It provides a way for programmers to interact with and manipulate the structure of a website.  With the help of the DOM, developers can access and change the different parts of a webpage. This allows them to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dickson Boateng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introverted Design: Building Better UX Experiences]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/introverted-design-building-better-ux-experiences/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/introverted-design-building-better-ux-experiences/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Pratik Joglekar explores the typical traits of introverts and uses them to make parallels and categorize digital experiences that can stand out without being loud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Pratik Joglekar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Designing For Introverts]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/guide-designing-for-introverts/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/guide-designing-for-introverts/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Pratik Joglekar explores the typical traits of introverts and uses them to make parallels and categorize digital experiences that can stand out without being loud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Pratik Joglekar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fuzz Hidden Directories and Files with Ffuf]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fuzz-hidden-directories-files-with-ffuf/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fuzz-hidden-directories-files-with-ffuf/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T14:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fuzzing is a technique used to test the security of a web application. It helps you find vulnerabilities you may not have discovered through other testing methods. Fuzzing also improves the overall quality and stability of a web application. In this article, we will look at what Fuzzing is in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Transition to Manifest V3 for Chrome Extensions]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376454</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-transition-to-manifest-v3-for-chrome-extensions/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T13:54:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While I am not a regular Chrome extension programmer, I have certainly coded enough extensions and have a wide enough web development portfolio to know my way around the task. However, just recently, I had a client reject one of …
How to Transition to Manifest V3 for Chrome Extensions originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Duggan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Job Description Generator with NextJS and ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-job-description-generator-with-nextjs-and-chatgpt/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-job-description-generator-with-nextjs-and-chatgpt/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T23:50:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we will discuss how to build a Job Description Generator with  Next.js [https://nextjs.org/], and ChatGPT [https://openai.com/blog/chatgpt/], a powerful language generation model developed by OpenAI. We will also use TailwindCSS [https://tailwindcss.com/], a utility-first CSS framework, to style our Next.js app. Check out the GitHub Repo here [https://github.com/lelouchB/ai-job-description]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ASHUTOSH K SINGH</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Julia Programming Applications – What is Julia Used For?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/applications-of-julia/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/applications-of-julia/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T21:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Julia [https://julialang.org/] is a high-level, high-performance dynamic programming language. It combines the ease of use of scripting languages like Python with the speed and efficiency of compiled languages like C/C++.  Julia has been gaining traction due to its speed, intuitive syntax, and ability to quickly and efficiently solve complex]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ifihanagbara Olusheye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Style Your React Apps with CSS Like a Pro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/style-react-apps-with-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/style-react-apps-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T20:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is a JavaScript library for building user interfaces. And it's gained a lot of popularity in the front-end development community.  One of the benefits of using React is its integration with CSS, which allows developers to apply styles to their components in a modular and reusable way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1000+ Free Developer Certifications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-certificates/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-certificates/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T18:01:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that organizations such as freeCodeCamp, Google, and Harvard offer online courses to help you learn software development? And that many of these include free certificates and badges?  To help you choose one that's right for you, I've created a full list. As avid online learners, my]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhawal Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For Loops in Python – For Loop Syntax Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/for-loops-in-python-with-example-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/for-loops-in-python-with-example-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T17:25:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While coding in Python, you may need to repeat the same code several times. Writing the same lines of code again and again repeatedly throughout your program is considered a bad practice in programming – this is where loops come in handy. With loops, you can execute a sequence of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Handle Errors in Computer Networks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-errors-in-computer-networks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-errors-in-computer-networks/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T16:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are some magical things about the Internet, and one thing in particular is that it works. In spite of so many obstacles, we can deliver our packets over the globe, and do so fast. Even more specifically, one amazing thing about the Internet is its ability to handle errors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Figma Auto Layout Masterclass: An Online Workshop To Support Ukraine 🇺🇦]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/figma-auto-layout-masterclass/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/figma-auto-layout-masterclass/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get better at your craft and support the people in Ukraine — that’s the idea behind our Figma Auto Layout Masterclass with Christine Vallaure. **We are donating all proceeds** from the online workshop to humanitarian aid in Ukraine. Monday, March 27, 09:00AM – 12:00PM PT / 18:00 – 21:00 CET. Donate and join!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solved With :has(): Vertical Spacing in Long-Form Text]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376435</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/solved-with-has-vertical-spacing-in-long-form-text/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T13:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever worked on sites with lots of long-form text — especially CMS sites where people can enter screeds of text in a WYSIWYG editor — you’ve likely had to write CSS to manage the vertical spacing between different …
Solved With :has(): Vertical Spacing in Long-Form Text originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grep Command in Linux – Usage, Options, and Syntax Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/grep-command-in-linux-usage-options-and-syntax-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/grep-command-in-linux-usage-options-and-syntax-examples/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T22:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grep is a useful command to search for matching patterns in a file. grep is short for "global regular expression print".  If you are a system admin who needs to scrape through log files or a developer trying to find certain occurrences in the code file, then grep is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use JavaScript for Data Analysis – A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/basics-of-data-analysis-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/basics-of-data-analysis-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T21:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data analysis involves taking data you have and extracting useful information from them. During the process, you need to clean the data, present them in a useful way, and draw conclusions that can help companies make important decisions. Data analysis is commonly done with languages like Python and R. Very]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zubair Idris Aweda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Use rem to Set Font Size in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-use-rem-to-set-font-size-in-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-use-rem-to-set-font-size-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T21:33:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Setting font sizes is something you'll do often as a web developer. But sometimes, especially for beginners, this can get a bit tricky.  In this article, I'll explain why I think you should always use rem over em for setting the font-size of an element. What are Relative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vinod Mathew Sebastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure User Authentication Methods – 2FA, Biometric, and Passwordless Login Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/user-authentication-methods-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/user-authentication-methods-explained/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T18:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital world, user authentication is essential in ensuring secure access to online accounts and resources. With the rise of cyber-threats, companies need to ensure that their users are authenticated before accessing any sensitive information. This helps protect the online safety of both parties. In the past, the most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hillary Nyakundi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why a Ternary Operator is not a Conditional Operator in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-a-ternary-operator-is-not-a-conditional-operator-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-a-ternary-operator-is-not-a-conditional-operator-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T17:17:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Until recently, I called a ternary operator a conditional operator in JavaScript. But I just learned that this isn't correct. In this tutorial, I will explain how I learned this, and hopefully it teaches you something new. I have a video version on this topic [https://youtu.be/vcNlFKzZTq4] you can watch as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unary, Binary, and Ternary Operators in JavaScript – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/unary-binary-ternary-operators-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/unary-binary-ternary-operators-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T16:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many operators in JavaScript that let you carry out different operations. These operators can be categorized based on the number of operands they require, and I'll be using examples to explain these categories in this tutorial. The three categories of operators based on the number of operands they]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript 2D Array – Two Dimensional Arrays in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-2d-arrays/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-2d-arrays/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T16:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript programming, we are all used to creating and working with one-dimensional arrays. These are arrays that contain elements (elements of similar data types or multiple data types). But it’s also good to know that two-dimensional arrays (2D arrays) exist in JS. In this article, you will learn what]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code Documentation, Streamlined]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/swimm-code-documentation-streamlined/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/swimm-code-documentation-streamlined/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing code documentation can be overwhelming when there’s no smooth process in place. Streamlining best practices and setting automation in your favor works a long way toward getting permanently up-to-date content that reflects the important pieces of your codebase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Burp Suite to Audit Web Applications – Pentesting and Bug Bounty Tool Overview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-audit-web-apps-with-burpsuite/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-audit-web-apps-with-burpsuite/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Burp Suite? Burp Suite is a powerful and widely-used web application testing platform. It helps security engineers identify potential risks in web applications. Burp Suite is also widely used by bug-bounty hunters. Since Burp Suite is a fully featured web-auditing platform, it comes with many tools to help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Common SVG Fails (and How to Fix Them)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376352</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/6-common-svg-fails-and-how-to-fix-them/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T13:51:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone recently asked me how I approach debugging inline SVGs. Because it is part of the DOM, we can inspect any inline SVG in any browser DevTools. And because of that, we have the ability to scope things out and …
6 Common SVG Fails (and How to Fix Them) originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mariana Beldi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React Hooks – Full Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-guide-to-react-hooks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-guide-to-react-hooks/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T01:04:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! Hooks are one of the main features of modern React code and one of the first concepts you should get comfortable with when learning about this library.  In this article I'm going to explain some of the most useful hooks React provides us with, how they work,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Format Output You Send to the Console]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/formatting-output-to-the-console/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/formatting-output-to-the-console/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T21:46:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have been a programmer for a while, then you have likely used a  console.log to display data.  You may want to see the value of data while your program is running, or you may be trying to troubleshoot a problem.  Sometimes the data displayed in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Hide Your API Keys in an Android Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hide-your-api-keys-in-android/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hide-your-api-keys-in-android/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T21:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's say that you are using a version control system and your project uses services that require API keys. Everything is all good when they're on your local machine, but you don’t want to share these API keys with the world. So how can you still preserve your API keys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Ben Rachel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Cloud Computing? Explained for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-cloud-computing-beginners-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-cloud-computing-beginners-guide/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T19:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may not always be aware of it, but you're enjoying the many fruits of the cloud just about every hour of every day. Many of the joys (and horrors) of modern life would be impossible without it.  Before we talk about what it does and where it's taking]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run Your Own Decentralized Authentication Service Using AuthN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-run-your-own-decentralized-authentication-service-using-authn/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-run-your-own-decentralized-authentication-service-using-authn/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T18:32:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The old authentication systems from monolithic applications don't work well in modern applications. When you build a web-application, you need a way to handle user authentication (the ability for a user to log in to your web-application). Traditionally, web-applications were built as monoliths and authentication systems were installed via a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Brown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing The Image Element LCP]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/optimizing-image-element-lcp/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/optimizing-image-element-lcp/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Largest Contentful Paint (or LCP) is a major web performance KPI which is still a new concept for many web developers since it became a ranking factor just recently. In this article, Eloïse Martin provides an overview of the best practices for the integration and optimization of an LCP image.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eloïse Martin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Grid to List Toggle using CSS Grid and JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/grid-to-list-toggle-using-css-grid/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/grid-to-list-toggle-using-css-grid/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T17:13:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will show you how to create a toggle to display items in a grid from a list. This will be using basic JavaScript skills with no external code or libraries. We will be using CSS Grid. What We Will Be Creating How to Create Our Starter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Real-time Chat App with ReactJS and Firebase]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/building-a-real-time-chat-app-with-reactjs-and-firebase/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/building-a-real-time-chat-app-with-reactjs-and-firebase/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T22:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'm going to show you how to build a real-time chat app using React.js and Firebase.  In the app, we will allow the user to log in with their Google account using Firebase's Google sign-in Authentication. We will also store and retrieve all the chatroom messages]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timonwa Akintokun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Search Functionality to a Ruby on Rails Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-search-to-ruby-on-rails-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-search-to-ruby-on-rails-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T18:22:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nowadays, most web applications have a search feature. Users can use the search feature in order to navigate websites more easily. Implementing a search feature in Ruby on Rails is very easy. By using only a few lines of code you can set it up. This tutorial assumes that you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sampurna Chapagain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Rename a Column in Pandas – Python Pandas Dataframe Renaming Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-rename-a-column-in-pandas/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-rename-a-column-in-pandas/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T18:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Pandas Dataframe is a 2-dimensional data structure that displays data in tables with rows and columns.  In this article, you'll learn how to rename columns in a Pandas Dataframe by using:   * The rename() function.  * A List.  * The set_axis() function. How to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coalesce SQL – Example PostgreSQL and SQL Server Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/coalesce-sql-example-postgresql-and-sql-server-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/coalesce-sql-example-postgresql-and-sql-server-functions/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T18:14:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In SQL, the COALESCE() function returns the first non-null value in an entry. It evaluates the values of the entries one by one, ignores the null values, then returns the first value that is not null. It works in PostgreSQL, SQL server, and MySQL. In this article, I will show]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C# Coding Best Practices – Coding Conventions with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/coding-best-practices-in-c-sharp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/coding-best-practices-in-c-sharp/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T16:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coding conventions ensure that your code is consistent, readable, understandable, and maintainable.  When it comes to writing clean and quality code, there are conventions developers should follow to make this possible.  There are a few things you should keep in mind while writing your code. In this article,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[File Permissions in Linux – How to Use the chown and chgrp Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/file-permissions-in-linux-how-to-use-the-chown-chgrp-command-s/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/file-permissions-in-linux-how-to-use-the-chown-chgrp-command-s/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T16:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to large organizations, Users and Groups in Linux play an important role in helping keep systems secure and properly functioning.  There can be different levels of users in an organization with different roles and permissions. And you'll need a good understanding Linux permissions to manage and/or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is SQL? Database Definition for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-sql-database-definition-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-sql-database-definition-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T18:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data is a powerful tool that drives everything you see and interact with on the internet. It facilitates research and powers today's technology. It is the driving force behind today's artificial intelligence and robotics. And so much more. Previously, these data were stored on paper, in physical files within cabinets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Grid-to-List Layout Toggle using Flexbox and JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flexbox-grid-to-list-toggle-using-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flexbox-grid-to-list-toggle-using-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T17:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will show you how to create a toggle to display items in a grid from a list. We'll do this using basic JavaScript skills with no external code or libraries. We will be using Flexbox to help us accomplish this. What We Will Be Creating Here's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software System Design for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/software-system-design-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/software-system-design-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T15:47:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building large-scale distributed systems like Google, Facebook, Amazon, and Twitter requires an in-depth understanding of computer science principles. This allows systems to handle millions of users concurrently despite hardware failures. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to design software systems. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matplotlib Figure Size – How to Change Plot Size in Python with plt.figsize()]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/matplotlib-figure-size-change-plot-size-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/matplotlib-figure-size-change-plot-size-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T15:29:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When creating plots using Matplotlib, you get a default figure size of 6.4 for the width and 4.8 for the height (in inches). In this article, you'll learn how to change the plot size using the following:   * The figsize() attribute.   * The set_figwidth() method.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Front-End Tools Of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/top-frontend-tools-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/top-frontend-tools-2022/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who doesn’t love a good front-end tool? In this roundup, you’ll find a nice list of useful front-end tools that were popular last year but are still bound to help you speed up and enhance your development workflow. Let’s dive in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[var, let, and const in JavaScript – the Differences Between These Keywords Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/differences-between-var-let-const-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/differences-between-var-let-const-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T22:48:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, you can declare variables with the var, let, and const keywords. But what are the differences between them? That's what I'll explain in this tutorial. I have a video version of this topic [https://youtu.be/Gd_JG3e1g4A] you can check out as well. 😇 If you're just starting out using JavaScript,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Accessibility – Common ARIA Mistakes to Avoid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-accessibility-common-aria-mistakes-to-avoid/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-accessibility-common-aria-mistakes-to-avoid/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T21:58:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible Rich Internet Applications – or ARIA – is a set of attributes and roles defined by the Web Accessibility Initiative [https://www.w3.org/WAI/]. These make the web more accessible to people with disabilities.  ARIA is extremely important for building accessible web applications. But it's very easy to misuse ARIA and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilknur Eren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS by Building the Google Logo in Pure CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-google-logo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-google-logo/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T19:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best ways to learn CSS is by creating something useful while you learn. I will show you how to use the following CSS items by creating the Google logo:  * position relative and absolute  * pseudo classes ::before and ::after  * positioning an element]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React Dev Tools – With Example Code and Videos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-dev-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-dev-tools/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T18:18:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working on a React project, one of the easiest ways to debug your code is using the React Dev Tools. React Dev Tools is an extension created by the React team. It enables developers to debug their code inside their Developer Tools. Once you add the extension, you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aman Kalra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accounting Number Format in Excel – How to Apply it to Selected Cells]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/accounting-number-format-in-excel-how-to-apply-it-to-selected-cells/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/accounting-number-format-in-excel-how-to-apply-it-to-selected-cells/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T18:11:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I will show you how to format cells in Microsoft Excel. We'll be looking particularly at the Accounting format for cells with numbers.  At the end of the article I'll give you two bonuses: a short video walkthrough of the methods we go over, as well]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developing Games Using Unreal Engine 5]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/developing-games-using-unreal-engine-5/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/developing-games-using-unreal-engine-5/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T15:27:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unreal Engine 5 is a powerful game engine that has been used to create some of the most popular and critically acclaimed games in recent years.  We just published an 11-hour Unreal Engine course for beginners on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Sourav created this coruse. He has 7 years]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[:has is an unforgiving selector]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376342</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/has-is-an-unforgiving-selector/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T14:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little thing happened on the way to publishing the CSS :has() selector to the ol’ Almanac. I had originally described :has() as a “forgiving” selector, the idea being that anything in its argument is evaluated, even if one or …
:has is an unforgiving selector originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Closed Captions And Subtitles UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/closed-captions-subtitles-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/closed-captions-subtitles-ux/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Captioning can be much more than text. Design patterns for better UX of subtitles, captions, video players, transcripts and on-screen text.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS by Building the Git Logo in Pure CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-git-logo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-git-logo/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T18:54:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best ways to learn CSS is by creating something useful while you learn. I will show you how to use the following CSS items by creating the Git logo:  * Transform to rotate an image  * position relative and absolute  * pseudo classes ::before]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL CONVERT – The DATE to String or DATETIME Function]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-convert-the-date-to-string-or-datetime-function-2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-convert-the-date-to-string-or-datetime-function-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T18:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with SQL, you'll need to learn how to format dates properly. This is because dates are an important aspect of any SQL and other software-related activities. You need to be able to work with dates to add timestamps to entries and keep track of when things happen,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Joins – LEFT Join, RIGHT Join, and INNER Join Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-sql-joins/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-sql-joins/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T18:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SQL is a programming language we use to interact with relational databases. SQL databases contain tables, which contain rows of data. These tables usually contain similar or related data. In an office management web application database, you would have tables for  employees, their departments, their managers, the projects they]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zubair Idris Aweda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Performance – How to Improve Page Speed with async and defer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-performance-async-defer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-performance-async-defer/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T18:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In web programming, JavaScript brings interactiveness and dynamic behaviour to your web pages. While HTML and CSS take care of the structure and aesthetics of the pages, they will be merely usable without JavaScript doing its job in the background. You can include JavaScript code in the HTML file in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Projects for Beginners in 2023 – Fun Ideas with Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-projects-for-beginners-easy-ideas-with-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-projects-for-beginners-easy-ideas-with-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T17:53:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You're ready to start making simple projects with React, but you don't know what to make. Where should you start? I have created seven unique and fun React projects for you to make, all of which will teach you essential React concepts that you need to know in 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Digital Privacy? A Beginner's Guide to Protecting Your Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/beginners-guide-to-digital-privacy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/beginners-guide-to-digital-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T17:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For all the many benefits we enjoy from technology – and particularly the technologies that make up the public internet – there are plenty of costs, too.  Figuring out how you want to balance the benefits against the costs can take some careful thinking. Here's a concise and effective]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Props in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/props-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/props-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T16:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're first learning React, props are often one of the most difficult topics to understand – especially when it comes to passing props across components. And when you need similar props in more than one component, things can get really tricky. In this guide, we will start by understanding]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tooba Jamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Faking Min Width on a Table Column]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376307</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/faking-min-width-on-a-table-column/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T15:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The good ol’ <table> tag is the most semantic HTML for showing tabular data. But I find it very hard to control how the table is presented, particularly column widths in a dynamic environment where you might not know how …
Faking Min Width on a Table Column originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anders Pedersen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Your Collaboration Problems Go Away By Sharing Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/sharing-components-designers-developers-collaboration-problems/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/sharing-components-designers-developers-collaboration-problems/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently UXPin has extended its powerful Merge technology by adding npm integration, allowing designers to sync React component libraries without requiring any developer input. This new step aims to improve collaboration between designers and developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shane Hudson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS by Building the Nextflix Logo in Pure CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-nextflix-logo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-nextflix-logo/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T01:37:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best ways to learn CSS is by creating something useful while you learn. I will show you how to use the following CSS concepts by creating the Netflix logo:  * border-left and border-right  * pseudo class ::before  * box-shadow  * transform: skewX What]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Better Web Developer in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-better-web-developer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-better-web-developer/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T23:05:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web development is a highly in-demand and popular skill these days. So if you’re at a crossroads in your life and thinking about becoming a web developer – or just want to further improve your skills – read on. To be a great web developer, you must learn many skills]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shahan Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Review of CS50 – Harvard's Introduction to Computer Science Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cs50-course-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cs50-course-review/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T22:20:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you considering taking the CS50 [/news/harvard-cs50/] Introduction to Computer Science course, but wondering if it's the right fit for you?  As someone who doesn’t have a computer science degree and was looking to learn the fundamentals of the field, I was in the same boat. That's why I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoebe Voong-Fadel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Setup React and Tailwind CSS with Vite in a Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-tailwindcss-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-tailwindcss-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T18:49:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tailwind CSS is a popular CSS framework, and React is one of the most popular JavaScript libraries. And Tailwind CSS and React are a great combo to use if you're building a frontend project. In this article, you will learn how to setup your coding environment with Vite, install React]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Segun Ajibola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Synthetic Identity Theft and How to Protect Yourself]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/synthetic-identity-theft/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/synthetic-identity-theft/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T18:42:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s digital age, cybercriminals have no shortage of methods to steal people's identities and sensitive data. One such method is synthetic identity theft, which is becoming one of the most dangerous and common forms.  In fact, according to a figures published by Federal Reserve Bank of Boston [https://www.bostonfed.org/news-and-events/news/2022/08/synthetic-identity-fraud-is-not-a-victimless-crime-costs-billions-damages-lives.aspx]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dmitry Dragilev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS by Building the React Logo in Pure CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-react-logo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-react-logo/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T18:21:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best ways to learn CSS is by creating something useful while you learn. I will show you how to use the following CSS concepts by creating the React logo:  * position: absolute  * vw (view width)  * transform: rotate()  * animation using keyframes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Email Verification in a Flask App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/setup-email-verification-in-flask-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/setup-email-verification-in-flask-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T17:56:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Email verification is a crucial aspect of creating a new user account or signing up for a service. It helps confirm that the email address provided is valid and belongs to the intended user. In this article, we will explore the process of handling email verification in Flask. The topic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Google Like a Pro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-google-like-a-pro/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-google-like-a-pro/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T15:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you tired of sifting through pages of irrelevant search results? Do you want to become more efficient at finding the information you need on the web? If so, this course is for you. We just published a video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Delete a File in Python – And Remove a Directory, Too]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-delete-a-file-in-python-and-remove-a-directory-too/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-delete-a-file-in-python-and-remove-a-directory-too/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T15:24:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python offers many standard utility modules which enable several functions in the applications we build. In this article, we'll learn about the modules for deleting files and directories. One of the most popular modules exposed in Python is the os module. This is one of the standard utility modules. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iferror Function in Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/iferror-function-in-excel-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/iferror-function-in-excel-example/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T15:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use the IFERROR function to catch errors in Excel. Using the function's parameters, you can return a custom value when specific errors occur.  In this article, you'll learn how to use the IFERROR function to evaluate and handle errors in Excel. You can use the IFERROR function]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Styling Buttons in WordPress Block Themes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376237</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/styling-buttons-in-wordpress-block-themes/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T13:56:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little while back, Ganesh Dahal penned a post here on CSS-Tricks responding to a tweet that asked about adding CSS box shadows on WordPress blocks and elements. There’s a lot of great stuff in there that leverages new features …
Styling Buttons in WordPress Block Themes originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fränk Klein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Authentication In Websites: A Banking Analogy]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/authentication-websites-banking-analogy/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/authentication-websites-banking-analogy/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is Eric Burel’s attempt at making the implementation of authentication less obscure. You’ll learn about tokens, authorization, CORS, credentials, HTTP headers, and such.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Burel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Post Request – How to Send an HTTP Post Request in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-post-request-how-to-send-an-http-post-request-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-post-request-how-to-send-an-http-post-request-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T23:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP requests allow your front-end application to interact successfully with a back-end server or database. One of the five popular HTTP methods for making requests and interacting with your servers is the POST method, which you can use to send data to a server. In this article, you will learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Ternary Operator – Syntax and Example Use Case]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-ternary-operator-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-ternary-operator-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T23:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many operators in JavaScript, one of which is the ternary operator. In this article, I'll explain what this operator is, and how it can be useful when building applications. I have a video version of this topic [https://youtu.be/MmwtZ0AwN9A] you can check out as well to supplement your learning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS by Building the Microsoft Logo 2 Different Ways in Pure CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-microsoft-logo-version-1/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-microsoft-logo-version-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T23:22:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best ways to learn CSS is by creating something useful while you learn. In this article I will show you two ways that you can create the Microsoft logo.  What We Will Be Creating We will create the Microsoft logo in pure CSS. It will look]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dictionary Iteration in Python – How to Iterate Over a Dict with a For Loop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dictionary-iteration-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dictionary-iteration-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T23:16:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, a dictionary is one of the built-in data structures (the others are tuples, lists, and sets). A dictionary is a collection of key:value pairs and you can use them to solve various programming problems. Dictionaries are very flexible to work with. You can get the keys and values]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Logging Works in Laravel Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/laravel-logging/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/laravel-logging/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T19:38:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Logs are records of the events happening with your application. Laravel, by default, writes log information into the laravel.log file that ships with a fresh Laravel installation. The file is housed within the storage > logs  directory.  In this tutorial, you'll learn the following:  * Introduction to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sule-Balogun Olanrewaju Ganiu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Hooks You Can Use in Every Project – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-hooks-every-project-should-use/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-hooks-every-project-should-use/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T19:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hooks are one of the most powerful features of React.  They enable us to easily reuse functionality across our application's components. What's best about hooks is their reusability – you can reuse your hooks both across components and your projects. Here are seven of the most important React hooks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS by Building the YouTube Logo in Pure CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-youtube-logo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-youtube-logo/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T18:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best ways to learn CSS is by creating something useful while you learn. I will show you how to use the following CSS concepts by creating the YouTube logo:  * Flexbox  * The border-radius property  * How to create a triangle in CSS What]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Solidity Modifiers? Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-solidity-modifiers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-solidity-modifiers/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T18:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will explore the various ways you can use modifiers in Solidity to modify the behavior of functions.  We will cover topics such as the syntax for defining and using modifiers, the _;  symbol, using multiple modifiers on a single function, modifiers with arguments, enum-based]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chigozie Oduah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Beginner's Guide to Digital Security – How to Keep Yourself Safe Online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-digital-security/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-digital-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T18:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whatever your connection to technology, security should play a prominent role in the way you think and act.  Technology, after all, amplifies the impact of everything we do with it. The things we say and write using communication technologies can be read and heard by many, many more people]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn to Code & Get a Developer Job in 2023 [Full Book]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-code-book/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-code-book/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T00:52:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to learn to code and get a job as a developer, you're in the right place. This book will show you how. And yes this is the full book – for free – right here on this webpage. A few years back, one of the Big 5]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a File in Linux from the Command Line – Create a File in the Terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-a-file-in-linux-from-the-command-line-create-a-file-in-terminal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-a-file-in-linux-from-the-command-line-create-a-file-in-terminal/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T18:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing files from the command line is one of the most common tasks for a Linux user.  Files are created, edited, deleted, and used by many of the background OS processes. Files are also used by regular users to accomplish daily tasks such as taking notes, writing code, or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Great HTML Form Controls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/perfect-html-input/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/perfect-html-input/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T17:43:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I'm going to show you all the things to consider when building the perfect HTML input. Despite its seemingly simple nature, there's actually a lot that goes into it. How to Make the Control  Well, we need to start somewhere. Might as well start with the control itself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Austin Gil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Check if a File Exists in Python with isFile() and exists()]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-check-if-a-file-exists-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-check-if-a-file-exists-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T17:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with files in Python, there may be times when you need to check whether a file exists or not. But why should you check if a file exists in the first place? Confirming the existence of a specific file comes in handy when you want to perform particular]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Int to String in Java – How to Convert an Integer into a String]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-integer-to-string-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-integer-to-string-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T15:57:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can convert variables from one data type to another in Java using different methods.  In this article, you'll learn how to convert integers to strings in Java in the following ways:  * Using the Integer.toString() method.   * Using the String.valueOf() method.   * Using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Set VS List – Sets and Lists in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-set-vs-list/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-set-vs-list/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T15:52:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, set and list are both data structures for storing and organizing any values. Those values could be numbers, strings, and booleans. In this article, we'll look at the differences between set and list. But before that, let's take a look at what both set and list are. What]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Produce Music with FL Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-produce-music-with-fl-studio/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-produce-music-with-fl-studio/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T15:44:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FL Studio is a powerful digital audio workstation (DAW) used by music producers all over the world. It has a wide range of features that allow users to create, produce, and mix music with ease. Whether you are a beginner or an experienced producer, this course is designed to help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Infinite Scroll in Next.js with Intersection Observer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-infinite-scroll-in-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-infinite-scroll-in-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T15:38:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creators and developers continually come up with new ways to enhance apps and provide value to users.  One feature that's useful for social media and ecommerce apps in particular is infinite scroll. It provides a seamless and intuitive browsing experience by reducing the time it takes to see new]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Divine Orji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Python for Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-python-for-web-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-python-for-web-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T15:33:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python is a popular programming language that is widely used in the development of web applications. It is easy to learn, has a large and active community, and is supported by a wealth of libraries and frameworks. We just published a crash course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Getting Data Visualization Right]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/guide-getting-data-visualization-right/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/guide-getting-data-visualization-right/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sara Dholakia presents a guide on how to choose just the right type of data visualization, with guidelines and things to keep in mind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sara Dholakia)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Clear Formatting in Excel – Remove Format From a Cell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-clear-formatting-in-excel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-clear-formatting-in-excel/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T01:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I will show you how to clear formatting from a cell in Excel. If you want the quick and dirty version, it's first up and will require you to simply click a couple times.  If you want to become a spreadsheet speedrunner, read this whole, brief]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 React Projects to Build in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-projects-to-improve-your-skills/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-projects-to-improve-your-skills/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T00:22:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to be good at React, building projects is one of the best ways to do it.  I have put together eight different projects that will not only show you what's possible to make with React, but give you some inspiration on what apps to make.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[860+ Free Online Programming & Computer Science Courses You Can Start This New Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-online-programming-cs-courses/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-online-programming-cs-courses/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twelve years ago, universities like Stanford and MIT opened up free online courses [https://www.classcentral.com/] to the public. Today, over 1,200 schools [https://www.classcentral.com/universities] around the world have created thousands of free online courses. To welcome the new year, I’ve compiled this list of 860+ such free online courses that you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhawal Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Format Compact Numbers with the JavaScript Internationalization API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/format-compact-numbers-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/format-compact-numbers-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T15:39:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes it can be difficult to fit large numbers into your site or app's layout, especially if you have to display several of them together.  As a result, a lot of modern sites and apps use the same format to display large numbers in a compact way. For example,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gerard Hynes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Custom Ghost CMS Theme]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-ghost-cms-theme/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-ghost-cms-theme/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T15:20:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ghost CMS is a platform specifically designed for bloggers and writers. Using Ghost, you can quickly get a blog website up and running.  Ghost targets primarily writers and all the features are specifically built for writing.  Ghost's new dashboard gives you a user-friendly interface, and beginners can easily]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Call Graph? And How to Generate them Automatically]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-automate-call-graph-creation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-automate-call-graph-creation/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T23:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever found yourself staring at lines of code, trying to wrap your head around how all the different functions fit together and interact with each other?  It can be a daunting task, especially in larger, more complex programs.  But fear not! There is a way to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel García Solla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Higher Order Functions in JavaScript – Explained with Practical Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/higher-order-functions-in-javascript-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/higher-order-functions-in-javascript-explained/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T22:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a web developer, you should always strive to learn new techniques and discover ways to work smarter with JavaScript.  One such technique is using higher order functions. Higher order functions are functions that take one or more functions as arguments, or return a function as their result. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sobit Prasad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Format Dates with Ordinal Number Suffixes (-st, -nd, -rd, -th) in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/format-dates-with-ordinal-number-suffixes-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/format-dates-with-ordinal-number-suffixes-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T21:57:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many online resources teach you how to format dates. But it's hard to find any that explain how to format dates with an ordinal number suffix (like 1st) in JavaScript – without using a library. In this short article, you will learn how to format dates in JavaScript with ordinal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python join() – How to Combine a List into a String in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-join-how-to-combine-a-list-into-a-string-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-join-how-to-combine-a-list-into-a-string-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T20:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[join() is one of the built-in string functions in Python that lets us create a new string from a list of string elements with a user-defined separator.  Today we'll explore join() and learn about:  * join() syntax  * how to use join() to combine a list into]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suchandra Datta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a React App With a .NET Core Backend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-react-app-with-a-dot-net-backend/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-react-app-with-a-dot-net-backend/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T19:57:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ASP.NET Core can work well as a backend for your React apps. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to to create a basic React application that leverages a .NET Web API Component written in C#. In order to integrate React with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is XSS? How to Protect Your Website from DOM Cross-Site Scripting Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-protect-against-dom-xss-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-protect-against-dom-xss-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T19:51:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Website security issues and vulnerabilities are a global problem as cyber security vulnerabilities are increasing. We have seen a major rise in the average number of these cases in the past few years, and 2021 saw an all-time high. So in this tutorial, we are going to talk about DOM]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrej Kovacevic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Basic User Authentication in a Flask App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-setup-user-authentication-in-flask/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-setup-user-authentication-in-flask/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T14:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[User authentication is important for protecting sensitive information and resources from unauthorized access. It helps ensure that only authorized users can access and make changes to data, and helps prevent unauthorized users from gaining access to sensitive information. There are different methods for implementing user authentication, including password-based authentication, token-based]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>