<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-08-07T01:05:44.622Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn About Operating Systems In-Depth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-about-operating-systems-in-depth/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-about-operating-systems-in-depth/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T14:29:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For many types of software engineers it is important to understand the fundamentals of operating systems. We just published a massive 25-hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you master the fundamentals of operating syste...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Rocket Control System: Basic Control Theory with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/basic-control-theory-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/basic-control-theory-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T14:26:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[$$\frac{\partial V}{\partial t} + \frac{1}{2}\sigma^2 S^2 \frac{\partial^2 V}{\partial S^2} = rV - rS \frac{\partial V}{\partial S}$$  Rocket transfer function]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Index Your Next.js Apps Faster Using IndexNow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-index-nextjs-pages-with-indexnow/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-index-nextjs-pages-with-indexnow/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T13:38:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js is a powerful framework for building lightning-fast applications. However, getting these applications indexed quickly by search engines is crucial for visibility and traffic, and sadly, this is not immediate. Even after uploading your sitemap, it can take up to weeks or even months before search engines crawl your pages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivek Sahu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Application With Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-event-app-with-node-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-event-app-with-node-js/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T17:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js it’s a runtime environment that allows you to run JavaScript code on the server side for building server-side applications. It works well for creating fast and scalable applications.  In this article, I will use a simple event management app as an example to show you how to build]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Send and Parse JSON Data in Golang – Data Encoding and Decoding Explained With Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/encoding-and-decoding-data-in-golang/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/encoding-and-decoding-data-in-golang/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T13:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When building web applications in Golang, working with JSON data is inevitable. Whether you're sending responses to clients or parsing requests, JSON encoding and decoding are essential skills to master.  In this article, we'll explore the different ways to encode and decode JSON in Golang. Table of Contents]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Destiny Erhabor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Time To Talk About “CSS5”]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/08/time-to-talk-about-css5/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/08/time-to-talk-about-css5/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered what happened after CSS3? It’s common knowledge that we never saw CSS4 come after it, yet we have a plethora of new features that have no similar way of defining when they were introduced. The W3C CSS-Next community group is actively searching for better approaches for how we describe the evolution of CSS over time and identify feature sets as effectively as we did with CSS3 way back in 2009 — and you can help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[(Hyper) Links About (Hyper) Links]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=379420</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/hyper-links-about-hyper-links/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T16:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heydon on the virtues of hyperlinking hypertext in an anchor element:
Sometimes, the <a> is referred to as a hyperlink, or simply a link. But it is not one of these and people who say it is one are 
…
(Hyper) Links About (Hyper) Links originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where Data Science meets Sports Analytics with Ken Jee [Podcast Interview #135]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/where-data-science-meets-sports-analytics-with-ken-jee-podcast-interview-135/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/where-data-science-meets-sports-analytics-with-ken-jee-podcast-interview-135/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T14:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Ken Jee. Ken's a Data Scientist. He's also a Sports Analytics practitioner who works with US Team Golf and USA Basketball. Ken hosts the excellent Ken's Nearest Neighbors podcast and the Exponential ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Grafana on EC2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-grafana-on-ec2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-grafana-on-ec2/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T13:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's data-driven world, it's important to monitor and visualize system metrics to make sure everything works consistently and performs well.  Grafana is an open-source analytics and monitoring platform. It has gained widespread recognition among developers and enterprises looking to extract more insights from the data produced by their]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Onwubiko Emmanuel Ebere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If I Was Starting My Career Today: Thoughts After 15 Years Spent In UX Design (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/08/thoughts-after-15-years-spent-ux-design-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/08/thoughts-after-15-years-spent-ux-design-part1/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this two-part series, Andrii Zhdan outlines common challenges faced at the start of a design career and offers advice to smooth your journey based on insights from his experience hiring designers. Learn why mastering design tools is crucial, how to build a strong portfolio, and tips for acing your first interviews.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andrii Zhdan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Invoice SaaS App with Next.js, Resend, Clerk and Neon Postgres]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-invoice-saas-app-with-next-js-and-neon-postgres/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-invoice-saas-app-with-next-js-and-neon-postgres/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T20:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn how to build an invoicing web app that allows users to add their bank information, manage a list of customers, and create and send invoices to customers. You'll also learn how to print and send React components as invoices and email templates directly from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankur Tyagi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Multilingual Website With Nuxt.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/08/how-build-multilingual-website-nuxt-i18n/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/08/how-build-multilingual-website-nuxt-i18n/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Handling translations for multilingual websites is famously difficult and, yet, crucial for many companies and organizations that serve a global audience. Thankfully, modern tooling abstracts away a great deal of the work, allowing for seamless translations that dynamically update the rendered content on a page, as demonstrated in this step-by-step tutorial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tim Benniks)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn RAG Fundamentals and Advanced Techniques]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-rag-fundamentals-and-advanced-techniques/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-rag-fundamentals-and-advanced-techniques/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T14:37:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding how to enhance the capabilities of AI and machine learning systems is a valuable skill. One method is Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG), a powerful technique that combines retrieval-based methods with generative models to create more...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Web Components Make Progressive Enhancement and CSS Encapsulation Easier!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=379335</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/html-web-components-make-progressive-enhancement-and-css-encapsulation-easier/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T13:21:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have to thank Jeremy Keith and his wonderfully insightful article from late last year that introduced me to the concept of HTML Web Components. This was the “a-ha!” moment for me:
When you wrap some existing markup in a 
…
HTML Web Components Make Progressive Enhancement and CSS Encapsulation Easier! originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kev Bonett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Functions and Mixins Module Notes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=378995</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-functions-and-mixins-module-notes/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T20:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most days, I’m writing vanilla CSS. Thanks to CSS variables and nesting, I have fewer reasons to reach for Sass or any other preprocessor. The times I reach for Sass tend to be when I need a @mixin to loop …
CSS Functions and Mixins Module Notes originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where You Can Still Get A Book Apart Titles]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=379392</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/where-you-can-still-get-a-book-apart-titles/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T14:52:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been a few months out since A Book Apart closed shop. I’m sad about it, of course. You probably are, too, if you have one of their many brightly-colored paperbacks sitting on a bookshelf strategically placed as a backdrop …
Where You Can Still Get A Book Apart Titles originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add JWT-Based Authentication in NestJS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-jwt-based-authentication-in-nest-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-jwt-based-authentication-in-nest-js/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T14:33:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authentication is a very important aspect of software development. It is the process of verifying a user’s identity. Authentication ensures that only authorized individuals access specific resources or perform certain actions within a system. It provides accountability by enabling the tracking of user actions and holding individuals responsible for their]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abimbola Adedotun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn C# for Unity in Spanish]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-c-sharp-for-unity-in-spanish/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-c-sharp-for-unity-in-spanish/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T12:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unity is a very popular and powerful game engine that relies on C# as its primary scripting language. Learn how to bring your games to life with Unity and C#. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org Spanish YouTube channel that will guide ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sweet Nostalgia In August (2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new batch of desktop wallpapers might be for you. Designed by the community for the community, they come in versions with and without a calendar for August 2024. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's New in macOS? How to Install the Sequoia Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/whats-new-in-macos-how-to-install-the-sequoia-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/whats-new-in-macos-how-to-install-the-sequoia-beta/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T14:55:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The macOS Sequoia public beta is now available. Though the final release of macOS Sequoia (macOS 15) won't be available until late September or early October 2024, I'll show you how to install the public beta for an advance look. It's actually stable enough for daily use. The macOS Sequoia]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kehoe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Hour With Dave Rupert]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=379381</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/smashing-hour-with-dave-rupert/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T14:16:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Magazine invited me to sit down for a one-on-one with “Uncle” Dave Rupert to discuss web components, yes, but also check in on Dave’s new Microsoft gig and what the ShopTalk co-host is working on these days.
I first …
Smashing Hour With Dave Rupert originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prompt Engineering Basics – How to Write Effective AI Prompts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prompt-engineering-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prompt-engineering-basics/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T19:22:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to the popularity of various Large-Language Models like ChatGPT, prompt engineering has become a key skill for developers (and non-developers) to have. It's important if you want to be able to tap into the full potential of these models. Whether you're a developer, researcher, or general user, knowing how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rethinking The Role Of Your UX Teams And Move Beyond Firefighting]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/07/rethinking-role-ux-teams-mov-beyond-firefighting/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/07/rethinking-role-ux-teams-mov-beyond-firefighting/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many UX professionals often find themselves working alone, and usually face more projects impacting user experience than they can handle. In this article, Paul Boag explains how UX teams can be transformed into a significant driver of customer-centric innovation within organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter Spacing is Broken and There’s Nothing We Can Do About It… Maybe]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=379318</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/letter-spacing-is-broken-and-theres-nothing-we-can-do-about-it-maybe/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T16:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post came up following a conversation I had with Emilio Cobos — a senior developer at Mozilla and member of the CSSWG — about the last CSSWG group meeting. I wanted to know what he thought were the …
Letter Spacing is Broken and There’s Nothing We Can Do About It… Maybe originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Diego Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Entity Framework Core with MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/using-entity-framework-core-with-mongodb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/using-entity-framework-core-with-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T14:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Entity Framework Core is a popular ORM (Object-Relational Mapper) for .NET applications, allowing developers to work with databases using .NET objects. It can be used with many types of databases, including MongoDB. In this article, you will learn ho...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Local Storage to Your Blazor Apps with Blazored.LocalStorage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-local-storage-in-blazor-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-local-storage-in-blazor-apps/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T13:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One critical feature of modern web applications is their ability to store and retrieve data on the client side [https://www.cloudflare.com/learning/serverless/glossary/client-side-vs-server-side/] . This is where local storage [https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/API/Window/localStorage] comes into play. In this article, we'll explore how to leverage the power of the Blazored LocalStorage NuGet package [https://www.nuget.org/packages/Blazored.LocalStorage] to seamlessly integrate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FADAHUNSI SEYI SAMUEL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Develop a CRUD App with Spring Boot, Neon Postgres, and Azure App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-crud-app-spring-boot-neon-postgres/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-crud-app-spring-boot-neon-postgres/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T19:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll explore how to develop a CRUD (Create, Read, Update, Delete) application using Spring Boot and Neon Postgres [https://neon.tech/]. We'll also deploy the application on Azure App Service [https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/products/app-service] and make it production-ready by setting up features like autoscaling and multiple environments. You'll learn how Neon Postgres]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhinav Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get a FAANG Dev Job in your 40s with Coding Interview University creator John Washam [#134]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-john-washam-crammed-for-8-months-got-a-job-at-amazon-then-taught-1000s-of-other-devs-134/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-john-washam-crammed-for-8-months-got-a-job-at-amazon-then-taught-1000s-of-other-devs-134/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T14:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview John Washam, a software engineer at Amazon. John's also creator of one of the most popular open source projects of all time, Coding Interview University. This is John's first-ever podcast interview, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Overcome Impostor Syndrome as a Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/overcome-impostor-syndrome-as-a-developer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/overcome-impostor-syndrome-as-a-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T14:23:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Impostor syndrome is a pervasive feeling of self-doubt and inadequacy that makes you believe you are a fraud despite your achievements and skills.  For new developers – and sometimes even seasoned professionals – this phenomenon can be particularly challenging as you navigate a fast-paced and ever-evolving industry.  But]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Venturi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Creational Design Patterns in Java? Explained With Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/creational-design-patterns-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/creational-design-patterns-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T13:04:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design Patterns provide you with an idea or a strategy for solving commonly occurring problems. They are proven solutions that follow the best practices and help you make your code flexible, reusable, and maintainable. The design patterns are classified into three categories based on their purpose:  * Creational]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anjan Baradwaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do Generative Models Work in Deep Learning? Generative Models For Data Augmentation Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/generative-models-for-data-augmentation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/generative-models-for-data-augmentation/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T12:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data is at the heart of model training in the world of deep learning. The quantity and quality of training data determine the effectiveness of machine learning algorithms.  On the other hand, obtaining massive amounts of precisely categorized data is a difficult and resource-intensive operation. This is where data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oyedele Tioluwani Taiwo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does Recursion Work? Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-recursion/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-recursion/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T15:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn about recursion and how it works. You need a good understanding of how functions work before learning recursion. I have used Python code for examples in this article because of its simple syntax, but the concept of recursion is the same for every programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Palistha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn System Design Principles and Prepare for an Job Interview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-system-design-principles/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-system-design-principles/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T14:44:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering system design is important for anyone who wants to build scalable and reliable applications. System design includes a range of topics from basic computer architecture to complex networking concepts, each playing an important role in creatin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pop(over) the Balloons]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=379281</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/popover-the-balloons/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T13:31:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve always been fascinated with how much we can do with just HTML and CSS. The new interactive features of the Popover API are yet another example of just how far we can get with those two languages alone.
You …
Pop(over) the Balloons originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Rhea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Sticky Notes App with React and Appwrite]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-sticky-notes-app-with-react-and-appwrite/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-sticky-notes-app-with-react-and-appwrite/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T01:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to dive into an exciting project that combines the latest in frontend and backend technologies? Imagine having a personalized notes application with dynamic features like draggable notes, autosave, and customizable colors. Not only will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating Image-To-Text And Text-To-Speech Models (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/07/integrating-image-to-text-and-text-to-speech-models-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/07/integrating-image-to-text-and-text-to-speech-models-part1/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joas Pambou built an app that integrates vision language models (VLMs) and text-to-speech (TTS) AI technologies to describe images audibly with speech. This audio description tool can be a big help for people with sight challenges to understand what’s in an image. But how this does it even work? Joas explains how these AI systems work and their potential uses, including how he built the app and ways to further improve it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Interpretable Artificial Intelligence Model – Simple Python Code Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-interpretable-ai-deep-learning-model/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-interpretable-ai-deep-learning-model/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T22:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence is being used everywhere these days. And many of the groundbreaking applications come from Machine Learning, a subfield of AI. Within Machine Learning, a field called Deep Learning represents one of the main areas of research. It is from Deep Learning that most new, truly effective AI systems]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Primitive Obsession?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-primitive-obsession/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-primitive-obsession/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T22:03:40.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Asaboro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Quantum Artificial Intelligence Model – With Python Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-quantum-ai-model/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-quantum-ai-model/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T18:28:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning (ML) is one of the most important subareas of AI used in building great AI systems. In ML, deep learning is a narrow area focused solely on neural networks. Through the field of deep learning, systems like ChatGPT and many other AI models can be created. In other]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comparable vs Comparator Interfaces in Java – Which Should You Use and When?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/comparable-vs-comparator-explained-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/comparable-vs-comparator-explained-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T13:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sorting is a fundamental operation in programming, essential for organizing data in a specific order. In Java, built-in sorting methods provide efficient ways to sort primitive data types and arrays, making it easy to manage and manipulate collections of data. For instance, you can quickly sort an array of integers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Simple Bitcoin-to-USD Calculator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-bitcoin-to-usd-calculator/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-bitcoin-to-usd-calculator/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T22:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to this fun and hands-on project where we'll build a calculator that converts Bitcoin to USD. You'll learn about API fetching, DOM manipulation, and localStorage, and you'll use some basic math along the way.  By the end of this tutorial, you'll have a functioning Bitcoin price calculator that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eesa Zahed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React's Context API – Tutorial with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-context-api-tutorial-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-context-api-tutorial-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T15:25:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In React, data is typically passed down from parent to child via props. But this can lead to "prop drilling" – where we have to pass props down through lots of components to get them where they're needed. Also, some props (for example, the current authenticated user, UI theme, or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alvaro Montoro: CSS One-Liners to Improve (Almost) Every Project]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=379278</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/alvaro-montoro-css-one-liners-to-improve-almost-every-project/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T14:38:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These sorts of roundups always get me. My wife will flip through Zillow photos of the insides of homes for hours because she likes seeing how different people decorate, Feng Shui, or what have you. That’s her little dip into …
Alvaro Montoro: CSS One-Liners to Improve (Almost) Every Project originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Enhanced Enums in Dart – Explained With Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-enhanced-enums-in-dart/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-enhanced-enums-in-dart/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T11:52:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enums are one of the most efficient ways to represent a fixed set of values. For example: days of the week, user online status, traffic light states, role hierarchy in an organization, and so on. What's interesting is that most typed languages such as Typescript, Java, C#, and Dart give]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Asaboro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Instant Search with Flask and HTMX]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-instant-search-with-flask-and-htmx/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-instant-search-with-flask-and-htmx/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T11:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instant search is a feature that shows search results as users type their query. Instead of waiting for a full page reload or submitting a form, results appear instantly, allowing users to find what they are looking for quickly. For example, when you start typing in a search box, suggestions]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Migrate a Flutter Application from GetIt to Bloc]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/migrate-a-flutter-application-from-getit-to-bloc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/migrate-a-flutter-application-from-getit-to-bloc/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T23:05:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I first built an application [https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tomerpacific.birthday_calendar&hl=en] using Flutter, I quickly ran into situations where I needed to pass state from widget to widget. These widgets weren’t directly related and all I knew back then was that there were only Stateless widgets or Stateful ones. I found it hard to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Ben Rachel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize Next.js App Performance With Lazy Loading]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/next-js-performance-optimization/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/next-js-performance-optimization/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T22:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People don't like using slow applications. And the initial load time matters a lot for web applications and websites.  An application that takes more than 3 seconds to load is considered slow and may cause users to leave the application or website. Next.js is a React-based framework you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Stuff I’m Excited After the Last CSSWG Meeting]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=379180</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-stuff-im-excited-after-the-last-csswg-meeting/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T17:16:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From June 11–13, the CSS Working Group (CSSWG) held its second face-to-face meeting of the year in Coruña, Spain, with a long agenda of new features and improvements coming to language. If 2023 brought us incredible advances like …
CSS Stuff I’m Excited After the Last CSSWG Meeting originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Diego Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get Machine Learning Skills without doing a PhD in Math [Podcast #133 with Daniel Bourke]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-machine-learning-skills-without-doing-a-phd-in-math-podcast-133-with-daniel-bourke/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-machine-learning-skills-without-doing-a-phd-in-math-podcast-133-with-daniel-bourke/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T14:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Daniel Bourke. He's a Machine Learning Engineer and creator of many popular tutorials on YouTube. He's also a frequent freeCodeCamp contributor. We talk about: How as a kid he hacked into his school...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting To The Bottom Of Minimum WCAG-Conformant Interactive Element Size]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/07/getting-bottom-minimum-wcag-conformant-interactive-element-size/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/07/getting-bottom-minimum-wcag-conformant-interactive-element-size/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WCAG provides guidance for making interactive elements more accessible by specifying minimum size requirements. In this article, Eric Bailey discusses the nuances of interactive element sizes and clarifies what it looks like to provide accessible interactive experiences using WCAG-compliant target sizes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn JavaScript Reactivity: How to Build Signals from Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-reactivity-build-signals-from-scratch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-reactivity-build-signals-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T21:17:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're learning JavaScript, you may have heard the terms reactivity or signals. But perhaps you haven't gotten to use them in practice yet. If so – or if you just want to learn more about these concepts – you're in the right place.  In this article, you'll learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React Router to Build Single Page Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-react-router-to-build-single-page-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-react-router-to-build-single-page-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T14:42:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Single Page Applications (SPAs) have revolutionized web development. They offer a more dynamic and fluid user experience compared to traditional multi-page applications. Traditional web apps require full-page reloads for almost every click the user makes. SPAs, on the other hand, load a single HTML page and update the page contents]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Olanrewaju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Move a Single Fly Machine and Volume to a New Region with flyctl]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-move-a-fly-application-to-a-new-region/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-move-a-fly-application-to-a-new-region/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T13:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fly.io allows users to deploy their applications to virtual machines in regions where their applications are mostly used. A Fly application can also be deployed to multiple regions. You may want to move your Fly application to a new region if you experience performance issues, high latency, or data residency]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clarence Bakosi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practice Your HTML, CSS, and JavaScript Skills in Spanish by Building 3 Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/practice-your-html-css-and-javascript-skills-in-spanish-by-building-3-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/practice-your-html-css-and-javascript-skills-in-spanish-by-building-3-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T11:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building projects is very important for learning how to code. When you create a project, you expand your portfolio and learn how to apply your skills to new situations. We just published a 2-hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org Spanish YouTube channel...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Design Systems With Penpot Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/07/build-design-systems-penpot-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/07/build-design-systems-penpot-components/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s turbulent landscape of design, Penpot stands out with its commitment to open-source, free unlimited access, and its unique, robust features. An example could be its new components system that takes another leap forward in aligning design with code. Let's dive into how it empowers both designers and developers to create more maintainable and scalable design systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pass the GitHub Advanced Security Certification Exam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pass-the-github-advanced-security-certification-exam/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pass-the-github-advanced-security-certification-exam/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T18:37:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ensuring the security of your code is important, and mastering GitHub Advanced Security (GHAS) can significantly enhance your ability to safeguard your projects. If you want to strengthen your security skills, obtaining the GitHub Advanced Security C...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sara Joy: Everybody’s Free (To Write Websites)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=379199</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/sara-joy-everybodys-free-to-write-websites/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T18:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sara Joy’s adaptation of the song “Everybody’s Free (To Wear Sunscreen)” (YouTube) originally by Baz Luhrman with lyrics pulled directly from Mary Schmich‘s classic essay, “Wear Sunscreen”. Anyone who has graduated high school since 1999 doesn’t even have …
Sara Joy: Everybody’s Free (To Write Websites) originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create 24 CSS Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-24-css-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-24-css-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T18:25:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS is an essential skill for web developers, and mastering it can greatly enhance the look and feel of your web projects. Whether you're a beginner looking to sharpen your skills or an experienced developer aiming to stay up-to-date with the latest ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Server-Side Rendering in Next.js Apps for Better SEO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/server-side-rendering-in-next-js-for-improved-seo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/server-side-rendering-in-next-js-for-improved-seo/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T18:02:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Server-side rendering (SSR) is a web development technique that can help improve your site's SEO. It does this by generating HTML content on the server in response to a user's request.  This approach contrasts with client-side rendering (CSR), where content is delivered as a basic HTML shell, and JavaScript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Your Node.js App on Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-node-js-app-on-azure/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-node-js-app-on-azure/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T11:56:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The advent of cloud computing marked a turning point in the field of technology. It provides easier access for users across the globe to web and mobile applications and services.  Modern-day computing services also provide a wide range of features which make web apps easier to use and more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oluwatobi Joshua</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Monte Carlo Methods? How to Predict the Future with Python Simulations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-monte-carlo-methods/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-monte-carlo-methods/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T21:42:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[-0.5 × (x2 + y2)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multithreading for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/multithreading-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/multithreading-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T20:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multithreading is a crucial concept in computer science that allows for the concurrent execution of two or more threads, enabling more efficient and optimized use of resources. It can significantly improve the performance of applications, particularl...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started With Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/getting-started-in-cybersecurity/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/getting-started-in-cybersecurity/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T11:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From design to coding to data science, there are many areas in the IT sector to explore. Because it's such a wealthy and alluring profession, you might be unsure of which one is ideal for you. This is where cybersecurity [https://iqmacodes.hashnode.dev/an-introduction-to-cybersecurity] comes in, one of the most fascinating fields of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hikmah Olawore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use LINQ in C# – With Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-linq/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-linq/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T20:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.Net (pronounced as "dot net") has many internal libraries and tools, but one that wields great power is LINQ (Language Integrated Query). It can be used in two ways: the language-level query syntax, or the LINQ API. In this article, we'll explore:  * What LINQ is.  * How]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Riordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's the Difference Between the useMemo and useCallback Hooks?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/difference-between-usememo-and-usecallback-hooks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/difference-between-usememo-and-usecallback-hooks/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T19:14:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React provides various hooks that make it easier to manage application state and other React features in functional components. Hooks provide class component features to functional components, and they don't need a lot of code compared to class components. Hooks also make your life easier by providing some convenient features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up a CI/CD Pipeline with Husky and GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-a-ci-cd-pipeline-with-husky-and-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-a-ci-cd-pipeline-with-husky-and-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T17:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CI/CD is a core practice in the modern software development ecosystem. It helps agile teams deliver high-quality software in short release cycles. In this tutorial, you'll learn what CI/CD is, and I'll help you set up a CI/CD pipeline using Husky and GitHub Actions in a Next.js application.  This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Viviana Yanez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Selectors]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=378745</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-selectors/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T16:13:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A complete guide covering all of the various methods we have to select elements in CSS and how to use them for applying styles.
CSS Selectors originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Design Effective Conversational AI Experiences: A Comprehensive Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/07/how-design-effective-conversational-ai-experiences-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/07/how-design-effective-conversational-ai-experiences-guide/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This in-depth guide takes you through the three crucial phases of conversational search, revealing how users express their needs, explore results, and refine their queries. Learn how AI agents can overcome communication barriers, personalize the search experience, and adapt to evolving user intent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yinjian Huang)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Generics in Java – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/generics-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/generics-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T18:57:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In your Java program, you might have encountered the dreaded ClassCastException  at runtime while working with different types of objects such as Integer, String, and so on. This error is mostly caused by casting an object to the wrong data type. In this article, you'll learn about generics and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anjan Baradwaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From doing data entry to becoming a developer with Jessica Chan AKA Coder Coder [Podcast #132]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-doing-data-entry-to-becoming-a-developer-with-jessica-chan-aka-coder-coder-podcast-132/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-doing-data-entry-to-becoming-a-developer-with-jessica-chan-aka-coder-coder-podcast-132/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T16:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Jessica Chan AKA Coder Coder. She's a software engineer has worked in the field for more than a decade. Interestingly, she studied photography in school and never took a programming class. We talk ab...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Linux for Beginners: From Basics to Advanced Techniques [Full Book]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-linux-for-beginners-book-basic-to-advanced/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-linux-for-beginners-book-basic-to-advanced/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T13:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Linux is one of the most valuable skills in the tech industry. It can help you get things done faster and more efficiently. Many of the world's powerful servers and supercomputers run on Linux. While empowering you in your current role, lear...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the tRPC Library? Explained with a Demo Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-trpc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-trpc/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T19:09:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a while now, I've been noticing a technology named tRPC [https://trpc.io/]  that's cited in many modern tech stacks, including T3 [https://create.t3.gg/]. But I didn't know what it was or why it had become so popular. So I began researching and learning about it. I didn't know what it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Afan Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Asynchronous JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-asynchronous-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-asynchronous-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T15:16:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asynchronous programming is a critical skill in modern JavaScript development, enabling developers to create more efficient and responsive applications. Whether you're a seasoned developer looking to brush up on your skills or a beginner eager to lea...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy a Web App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-a-web-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-a-web-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T13:54:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying a web application can seem daunting, but with the right tools and guidance, it becomes a manageable task. We are excited to share a comprehensive course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will explain this process. This course wil...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Secure Authentication: From Passwords to Passkeys]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/more-secure-authentication-from-passwords-to-passkeys/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/more-secure-authentication-from-passwords-to-passkeys/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T13:38:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving world of cybersecurity, authentication remains a cornerstone. Traditional methods, like passwords and social logins, are increasingly vulnerable to attacks. Enter passkeys—a revolutionary approach promising enhanced security and user convenience.  This guide will explore the current state of authentication, delve into what passkeys are, how they work,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Cruz Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Upgrade from Node 16 and Jest 26 While Staying on React Scripts 4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-upgrade-node-and-jest-while-on-react-scripts-v4/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-upgrade-node-and-jest-while-on-react-scripts-v4/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T19:35:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I was trying to upgrade some of my open source projects [https://github.com/classtranscribe/FrontEnd/]. They were made using  create-react-app [https://github.com/facebook/create-react-app] around 2019, and I wanted to upgrade to a newer version of NodeJS and Jest. This would let me take advantage of the security updates, bug fixes, speed improvements, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harsh Deep</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does a CPU Work Internally? From Transistors to Instruction Set Architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-does-cpu-work-internally/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-does-cpu-work-internally/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T19:14:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CPU (Central Process Unit) is the brain of a computer, and the main connection between software and hardware. It makes it possible to operate software on hardware. However, how does it work in deep detail? And how can it connect programs to certain computer hardware? This article aims to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Python Generators – Explained With Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-python-generators/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-python-generators/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T19:05:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python generators are a powerful feature that allow lazy iteration through a sequence of values. They produce items one at a time and only when needed, which makes them the best choice for working with large datasets or streams of data where it would be inefficient and impractical to load]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rochdi Khalid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Send HTTP Requests Using JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-send-http-requests-using-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-send-http-requests-using-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T17:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nowadays, the interaction between web applications relies on HTTP [/news/what-is-http/]. For instance, let's say you have an online shop application and you want to create a new product. You have to fill in all the necessary information and probably click on a button that says "Create". This action will send]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Hu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Stack Development with Next.js, Clerk, and Neon Postgres]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nextjs-clerk-neon-fullstack-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nextjs-clerk-neon-fullstack-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T15:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Full stack development is constantly evolving, with new developer tools and products being introduced that allow us to build secure and reliable applications more efficiently. In this tutorial, I’ll walk you through how to build highly performant web applications with Neon – a serverless PostgreSQL [https://neon.tech] database designed for the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankur Tyagi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Counter Button with React, TailwindCSS, and TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-counter-button-with-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-counter-button-with-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T14:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can you keep track of the number of times a user clicks a button? How are the hearts on Instagram or the likes on Facebook counted?  In this tutorial, we will build a button that tracks the number of times a button has been clicked. Along the way,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Devin Lane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Python SDK to Build Your Own Web Scraper]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-python-sdk-to-build-a-web-scraper/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-python-sdk-to-build-a-web-scraper/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T13:11:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Web scraping? Web scraping is a technique used to collect large amounts of data automatically using a programming script. This makes it useful for many professionals such as data analysts, market researchers, SEO specialists, business analysts, and academic researchers. What You'll Learn Here Python provides two libraries, Requests]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jess Wilk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Friction Is A Good Thing: Designing Sustainable E-Commerce Experiences]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/07/designing-sustainable-e-commerce-experiences/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/07/designing-sustainable-e-commerce-experiences/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, UX design contributes to the problem of excessive consumption through persuasive e-commerce practices and designing for companies with linear and exploitative business models. Anna Rátkai explores practical steps we can take to reduce material consumption and the massive environmental impact that comes along with it by designing mindful shopping experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Anna Rátkai)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve User Experience with Optimistic UI and SWR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-user-experience-with-optimistic-ui-swr/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-user-experience-with-optimistic-ui-swr/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T22:33:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever noticed how some apps feel like they can read your mind? You click a button, and before you can even blink, it's done – no loading screens, no waiting around. It's like magic, right? Well, let me tell you a little secret: that's the power of Optimistic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prepare to pass the AWS SysOps Administrator Associate (SOA-C02) Certification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-to-pass-the-aws-sysops-administrator-associate-soa-c02-certification/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-to-pass-the-aws-sysops-administrator-associate-soa-c02-certification/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T17:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you trying to earn the AWS SysOps Administrator Associate certification? We just released a MASSIVE course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is is designed to help you pass the certification exam and showcase your expertise in AWS tech...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn TypeScript with Interactive Lessons]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-typescript-with-interactive-lessons/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-typescript-with-interactive-lessons/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T16:26:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript can make your life easier as a programmer and make your code less error-prone. We just posted a TypeScript course for beginners on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Bob Ziroll from Scrimba teaches this course. Interactive code is avail...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Pandoc – An Open Source Tool for Technical Writers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-pandoc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-pandoc/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T15:33:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technical writers frequently navigate the complexities of various document formats and revisions. Pandoc [https://pandoc.org/], a free and open-source tool, offers a powerful solution to streamline these processes. In this tutorial, I'll explain the Pandoc's functionalities, specifically focusing on two key areas that can significantly enhance the workflow for technical writers:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikram Aruchamy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“If” CSS Gets Inline Conditionals]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=379002</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/if-css-gets-inline-conditionals/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T15:18:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few sirens went off a couple of weeks ago when the CSS Working Group (CSSWG) resolved to add an if() conditional to the CSS Values Module Level 5 specification. It was Lea Verou’s X post that same day that …
“If” CSS Gets Inline Conditionals originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does Knowledge Distillation Work in Deep Learning Models?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/knowledge-distillation-in-deep-learning-models/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/knowledge-distillation-in-deep-learning-models/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T13:35:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deep learning models have transformed several industries, including computer vision and natural language processing. However, the rising complexity and resource requirements of these models have motivated academics to look into ways to condense their knowledge into more compact and efficient forms. Knowledge distillation, a strategy for transferring knowledge from a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oyedele Tioluwani Taiwo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perform Load Testing in Spring Boot with Gatling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-integrate-spring-boot-with-gatling/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-integrate-spring-boot-with-gatling/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T19:46:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To evaluate the performance of a system, you need a tool that can simulate its behavior in production.  For this purpose, you can use a software tool based on Scala [https://www.scala-lang.org/] called Gatling [https://gatling.io/]. This article will teach you how to integrate it into a Spring Boot [https://spring.io/projects/spring-boot] application]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mario Casari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Vue E-commerce App Using MSW]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-vue-ecommerce-app-using-msw/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-vue-ecommerce-app-using-msw/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T18:49:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building an e-commerce app can be a time-consuming task, but with the right tools, it becomes much more manageable. In this guide, we'll explore how to create a robust Vue.js e-commerce application using Mock Service Worker (MSW) to simulate backend interactions.  Whether you're a seasoned developer or just starting]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhijeet Dave</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>