<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-02-08T00:54:25.928Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Destructuring Works in JavaScript – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/destructuring-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/destructuring-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T19:31:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Destructuring is a powerful JavaScript feature introduced in ES6 (ECMAScript 2015). It makes it easier to extract values from arrays or properties from objects and assign them to variables in a readable way.  Let's delve into how destructuring works and explore various use cases with examples. You can get]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work with useMemo in React – with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-usememo-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-usememo-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T18:13:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[useMemo is a valuable tool in the React framework, designed to optimize performance by memoizing expensive computations.  With useMemo, React can store the result of a function call and reuse it when the dependencies of that function haven't changed, rather than recalculating the value on every render.  useMemo]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Career Change to Code Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/career-change-to-code-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/career-change-to-code-guide/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T17:47:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many people who want to change careers to become a software developer but don't know what the optimal path is. There are many challenges and uncertainties that accompany such a significant change. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is a guide for those]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the JavaScript insertAdjacentHTML() method for Efficient DOM Manipulation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-insertadjacenthtml-method-efficient-dom-manipulation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-insertadjacenthtml-method-efficient-dom-manipulation/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T16:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, developers need to be able to dynamically update a page without replacing the entire content. A traditional method like innerHTML can cause performance issues, because these methods tend to replace the entire content of an element. The insertAdjacentHTML() method leads to better performance because you use it to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kamaldeen Lawal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Development Is Getting Too Complex, And It May Be Our Fault]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-development-getting-too-complex/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-development-getting-too-complex/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overwhelming number of frameworks and tooling available today gives the impression that web development has gotten perhaps too complex. Juan Diego Rodríguez explores if web development really is that complex and, most importantly, how we can prevent it from getting even more difficult than we already perceive it to be.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Master Boot Record Disk Partitioning Works in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-mbr-works-in-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-mbr-works-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T10:29:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Efficient storage management is a crucial aspect of maintaining a well-organized computing environment.  In this detailed guide, we'll explore the features of Master Boot Record (MBR) disk partitioning using the parted command on Linux.  Additionally, we'll cover the process of adding a new hard disk in VMware, as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Project – How to Build a Simple Parking Lot Management System]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-project-parking-lot-management-system/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-project-parking-lot-management-system/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T00:25:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! It's good to be back with another tutorial – this time on Java, one of the most popular programming languages out there today.  Java is used by developers and enterprises to build powerful applications that serve many different purposes. The object-oriented nature of Java makes writing clean,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Personal Branding for Developers – A Step by Step Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/personal-branding-for-devs-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/personal-branding-for-devs-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T23:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this handbook, you'll learn how to build your personal brand as a developer to help you make your mark in the tech industry.  With a focus on practicality and professionalism, this guide is designed for developers at all levels, from industry veterans to those just starting their coding]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Job Board Scraper with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-job-board-scraper-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-job-board-scraper-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T22:56:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to learn how to navigate the ever-evolving job market by scraping job posting sites like Indeed.com, then this guide is for you.  What is a Job Scraper? In the digital age, tools known as Job Board Scrapers (or just Job Scrapers) have become indispensable for people]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jess Wilk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the C# Programming Language – Full Book for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-csharp-book/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-csharp-book/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T22:35:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C# version 1 was released in January 2002. It is a modern, general purpose programming language designed and developed from the ground up by the renowned Danish software engineer, Anders Heijleberg and his team at Microsoft.  I’ve heard Anders Heijlsberg say in an interview that with C# the goal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gavin Lon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master React by Building 25 Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-react-by-building-25-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-react-by-building-25-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T17:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is one of the most popular frontend JavaScript frameworks.  We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build twenty-five different projects using React. Each project is designed to challenge and enhance your understanding of React's capabilities. Sangam Mukherjee developed this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Spring Boot and Spring Data JPA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-spring-boot-and-spring-data-jpa/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-spring-boot-and-spring-data-jpa/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T16:05:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By mastering Spring Boot and Spring Data JPA, you'll be equipped to build efficient, scalable, and secure applications with ease, making you a valuable asset in the job market and a more effective developer. We just published a comprehensive video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that teaches Spring Boot]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Strict Mode in JavaScript? Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-strict-mode-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-strict-mode-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T11:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a JavaScript developer, you may come across the string "use strict" at the top of your JavaScript code. This means that JavaScript's strict mode is in use. But what does this mean, and why does it matter? In this article, you'll learn what it means to write]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vim Key Bindings – Vim Keys List Reference]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vim-key-bindings-reference/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vim-key-bindings-reference/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T09:28:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Vim key bindings is crucial for navigating and editing text efficiently in Vim or Vim-based text editors like Neovim.  In this article, we'll explore the most common Vim key bindings that will help you navigate your text editor seamlessly. Table of Content  * Vim Modes  *]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Designing For Older Adults]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/guide-designing-older-adults/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/guide-designing-older-adults/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With one billion people aged 60 or older worldwide, inclusivity is more important than ever. Learn how to create digital experiences that empower independence and competence for older adults while enhancing usability for all. An upcoming part of Smart Interface Design Patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Databases Guarantee Isolation – Pessimistic vs Optimistic Concurrency Control Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-databases-guarantee-isolation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-databases-guarantee-isolation/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T22:41:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ACID (Atomicity, Consistency, Isolation, and Durability) is a set of guarantees when working with a DBMS. Pessimistic and optimistic concurrency control explains how databases achieve the “I” in ACID. Isolation is a guarantee that concurrently running transactions should not interfere with each other. This is arguably the most important ACID]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State Management in React – When and Where to use State]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-state-management/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-state-management/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T21:06:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State management is a crucial concept in React, which is one of the most popular JavaScript libraries in the world for building dynamic user interfaces.  Due to its importance in handling data, it is essential know how to manage state, when you need it, and where it can be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Olanrewaju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Filtering, Sorting, Limiting, and Pagination to Your Nest.js App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-filtering-sorting-limiting-pagination-to-nestjs-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-filtering-sorting-limiting-pagination-to-nestjs-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T19:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are reading this article, you are probably a developer who has used an API to call data for your application. You may have also used features such as filtering and pagination to limit the amount of data you want to receive.  These API features are important when]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okure U. Edet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is box-sizing: border-box in CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-box-sizing-border-box-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-box-sizing-border-box-css/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T18:26:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In CSS, there is a property called box-sizing that allows you to determine how the width and the height for an element is calculated.  A lot of CSS resets [/news/how-i-style-my-websites-with-my-favorite-css-resets-7ace41dbc43d/] will change the default box model from content-box to border-box to make the layouts easier to work with. But]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable JavaScript – How to Improve the Performance of Your JS Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/immutable-javascript-improve-application-performance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/immutable-javascript-improve-application-performance/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T15:09:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Javascript has become a very popular programming language thanks to its growing use in frontend and backend development.  And as devs build JavaScript applications for different companies and organizations, the size and complexity of these applications can pose interesting performance challenges. As developers, we seek to create applications that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clinton Joy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install React – A Step-by-Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-react-a-step-by-step-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-react-a-step-by-step-guide/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T12:43:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is an open-source JavaScript library that helps you build dynamic user interfaces (UIs). You can use it to build components that represent logically reusable parts of the UI. Because React is open source, anyone can access its source code, inspect it, modify it, and enhance it for their personal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoro Emmanuel Nzube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use OpenTelementry to Trace Node.js Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-opentelementry-to-trace-node-js-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-opentelementry-to-trace-node-js-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-03T00:21:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Observability refers to our ability to "see" and understand what's happening inside a system by looking at its external signals (like logs, metrics, and traces). Observability involves collecting and analyzing data from sources within a system to monitor its performance and address problems effectively. Why is Observability Useful?  1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abraham Dahunsi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Libraries to Use in Your Projects in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-libraries-to-use-in-your-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-libraries-to-use-in-your-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T18:42:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're building applications with React, you should learn how to use some helpful libraries that'll make it easier to add the features you need. For example, to add features like authentication or styling, you'll need to find a good third-party library to handle it. In this comprehensive guide, I'm]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Boot Process – What Happens when Booting RHEL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linux-boot-process-in-rhel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linux-boot-process-in-rhel/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T17:49:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The boot process is made up of a series of necessary actions that a computer goes through upon startup. These range from powering on to the complete loading of the operating system (OS) for optimal functionality.  It is vital to familiarize yourself with the boot process for various reasons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Mobile Swiping Component in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-mobile-swiping-component-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-mobile-swiping-component-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T17:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone wants to be able to access the web from their mobile phones these days. So it's important to consider the accessibility of your web app on Android and iPhones.  The most difficult part is building the navigation – and swiping in particular can cause a lot of headaches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Oh My Zsh creator and Dev Shop CEO Robby Russell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-oh-my-zsh-creator-and-ceo-robby-russell/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-oh-my-zsh-creator-and-ceo-robby-russell/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T17:11:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Robby Russell. Robby created the open-source project Oh My ZSH.  Oh My Zsh is a framework for managing your Zsh configuration for your command line terminal. It's been extremely popular among developers for more than a decade. Robby is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asynchronous Programming in JavaScript – Callbacks, Promises, & Async/Await Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/asynchronous-programming-in-javascript-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/asynchronous-programming-in-javascript-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T16:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All programming languages have runtime engines that execute their code. In JavaScript, the runtime engine is single-threaded, which means that it runs code line by line or sequentially. The JavaScript runtime engine makes it a synchronous programming language where programs run sequentially. Programming languages that are not synchronous are called]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Musab Habeeb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Words Cannot Describe: Designing For AI Beyond Conversational Interfaces]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-ai-beyond-conversational-interfaces/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-ai-beyond-conversational-interfaces/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Artificial Intelligence evolves the computing paradigm, designers have an opportunity to craft more intuitive user interfaces. Maximillian Piras examines how the latest AI capabilities can reshape the future of human-computer interaction beyond conversation alone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maximillian Piras)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Fast.ai – A Beginner-Friendly Gateway to Deep Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-fast-ai-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-fast-ai-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T00:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fast.ai is a user-friendly library that brings the power of deep learning to your fingertips, regardless of your skill level. Let’s learn how it works. Have you ever felt curious about deep learning but found the technical complexity overwhelming? Fast.ai [https://fast.ai/] is your answer. Fast.ai simplifies the journey into deep]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Your Web Sites Accessible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-your-web-sites-accessible/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-your-web-sites-accessible/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T16:16:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ensuring that web content is accessible to everyone, including people with disabilities, is not just a noble goal—it's a necessity. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you all about web accessibility. This course is designed to empower developers with the knowledge and skills]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Array Length – How to Find the Length of an Array in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-array-length-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-array-length-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T15:56:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript arrays are fundamental data structures that allow you to store and manipulate collections of elements efficiently. While working with arrays, you'll often need to know their length. The length of an array tells us how many elements are present in the array. You can use this to check if]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tantoluwa Heritage Alabi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Documentation Libraries to Help You Write Good Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/documentation-libraries-to-help-you-write-good-docs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/documentation-libraries-to-help-you-write-good-docs/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T15:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good project documentation is key to success for every company, startup, or individual project. Without documentation, it's much harder for new developers or others to use your project. In this article, I'll discuss some of my favourite libraries you can use for building your documentation site.  And don't worry]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Shadcn with Next.js 14]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/shadcn-with-next-js-14/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/shadcn-with-next-js-14/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T15:21:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shadcn is a collection of beautifully designed, accessible, and customizable React components that you can use to build modern web applications with Next.js. With Shadcn, you can quickly and easily create user interfaces that are both stylish and functional. If you are looking for a way to build modern, stylish,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Dynamic Segments with useParams in React Router]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-dynamic-segments-in-react-router/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-dynamic-segments-in-react-router/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T22:34:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a traditional website, when a user clicks on a URL, the browser makes a full-page request from the server and directs the user to a new page. This is referred to as static routing. This is very useful if you just need to navigate the user to a new]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Anie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pass the GitHub Foundations Certification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pass-the-github-foundations-certification-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pass-the-github-foundations-certification-course/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T21:54:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub Foundations Certification was released just a few weeks ago. And you can now watch a 9-hour exam prep course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel! Andrew Brown from ExamPro created this course. He has created a bunch of popular exam prep courses for the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This certification]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[nth-child() vs nth-of-type() Selectors in CSS – What’s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nth-child-vs-nth-of-type-selector-in-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nth-child-vs-nth-of-type-selector-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T18:33:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The :nth-child() and :nth-of-type() CSS selectors select items from a group of HTML elements. But they work in different ways. Here is the main distinction between them: nth-child() selects its items from any group of elements. nth-of-type() selects its items from a specified type of element. * :nth-child() selects items]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi Sofela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[29 Days Of Inspiration (February 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-february-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-february-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With February just around the corner, how about a little inspiration boost? We might have one for you: desktop wallpapers created with love by the community for the community. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the <input> Element to Access a Mobile Device's Camera]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-input-element-to-access-camera-on-mobile/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-input-element-to-access-camera-on-mobile/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T08:55:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a Selfie Take a Photo]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Hugging Face Transformer Library]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hugging-face-transformer-library-overview/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hugging-face-transformer-library-overview/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T00:36:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll talk about why I think the Hugging Face’s Transformer Library is a game-changer in NLP for developers and researchers alike. Have you ever wondered how modern AI achieves such remarkable feats, like understanding human language or generating text that sounds like it was written by a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ace Your Deep Learning Job Interview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ace-your-deep-learning-job-interview/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ace-your-deep-learning-job-interview/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T20:19:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you gearing up for a job interview in the deep learning field? Look no further!  We just published a video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is specifically designed to prepare candidates for deep learning job interviews, covering 50 common interview questions with detailed explanations. Tatev Aslanyan]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Admin Dashboard with React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-admin-dashboard-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-admin-dashboard-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T19:04:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you looked at interactive dashboards on websites like Stripe and thought, “How can I build something like this myself?” In this full-stack React and Next.js project, you’ll learn how to build a stunning admin dashboard from front to back. Our final admin dashboard will allow you to display and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Game Dev Tutorial – Build Gorillas with HTML Canvas + JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gorillas-game-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gorillas-game-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T18:18:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this JavaScript game tutorial, you'll learn how to create a modern version of the 1991 classic game Gorillas using plain JavaScript and the HTML canvas element. In this game, two gorillas throw explosive bananas at each other, and the first one to hit the other one wins the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hunor Márton Borbély</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Your Django Project on an EC2 Machine using GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-django-project-on-ec2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-django-project-on-ec2/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T15:40:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying a Django application can be streamlined and automated using GitHub Actions. This article provides a comprehensive guide on how to set up a continuous deployment pipeline for a Django project hosted on an AWS EC2 instance. By leveraging GitHub Actions, developers can automate their deployment process, making it more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muhammad Haseeb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Falsy Values in JavaScript? Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-falsey-values-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-falsey-values-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T15:27:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, every value has a boolean equivalent. This means it can either be evaluated as true (truthy value) or false (falsy value) when used in a boolean context.  But what is a boolean context? It's a situation where a boolean value is expected. Examples include if statements, logical]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Pandas for Data Cleaning and Preprocessing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-cleaning-and-preprocessing-with-pandasbdvhj/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-cleaning-and-preprocessing-with-pandasbdvhj/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steve Lohr of The New York Times said: "Data scientists, according to interviews and expert estimates, spend 50 percent to 80 percent of their time mired in the mundane labor of collecting and preparing unruly digital data, before it can be explored for useful nuggets."  This statement is 100%]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwadamisi Samuel Praise</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[200+ Universities Just Launched 1000+ Free Online Courses. Here’s the Full List.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/new-online-courses/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/new-online-courses/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you haven’t heard, universities around the world are offering their courses online for free (or at least, partially free). These online courses [https://www.classcentral.com/help/intro-to-online-learning] are collectively called MOOCs or Massive Open Online Courses. [https://www.classcentral.com/help/moocs] In the past ten years or so, over 1000 universities have created more than 20,000 such]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhawal Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Dapper in Your .NET Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-dapper-in-your-dotnet-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-dapper-in-your-dotnet-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T00:26:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with .NET, interacting with databases – particularly SQL databases – is inevitable. The common approaches involve ORM (Object Relational Mapping) tools like Entity Framework (EF Core) or Dapper. Dapper excels in speed and control for CRUD operations. This article explores Dapper's suitability for performance-critical .NET projects with simpler]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Riordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit on Ubuntu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-nvidia-cuda-toolkit-on-ubuntu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-nvidia-cuda-toolkit-on-ubuntu/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T21:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NVIDIA Compute Unified Device Architecture (CUDA) Toolkit is a software platform that allows developers to tap into the computing power of NVIDIA processing and GPU-accelerated applications. CUDA is also a programming model and an API that enables programmers to write code that can run on both the CPU and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abraham Dahunsi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beginner Web Dev Tutorial – Build a Weather App with Next.js & TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/beginner-web-dev-tutorial-build-a-weather-app-with-next-js-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/beginner-web-dev-tutorial-build-a-weather-app-with-next-js-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T18:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just published a great beginner's web dev tutorial on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. By the end of this tutorial, you'll have a solid understanding of several core technologies, including Next.js, Tailwind CSS, and TypeScript, all while creating a practical, real-world project. Core Technologies Used You will improve your skills]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter Tutorial – How to Migrate to V2 Embedding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flutter-migrating-to-v2-embedding/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flutter-migrating-to-v2-embedding/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T18:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you hopped on the Flutter bandwagon in it’s early days, most likely you have a project or two that were created prior to version 1.12 of Flutter. If that is the case, you may have seen this message whenever you run Pub get in one of your projects: >]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Ben Rachel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Homomorphic Encryption Works – Explained in Plain English]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/homomorphic-encryption-in-plain-english/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/homomorphic-encryption-in-plain-english/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T18:33:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the fields of cryptography and cybersecurity advance, homomorphic encryption [/news/introduction-to-homomorphic-encryption/] stands out as a groundbreaking technology.  It has the potential to reshape everything in data privacy and security. What really is homomorphic encryption? Why is it getting so much attention? How can it increase data privacy? Essentially, with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Feature Trap: Why Feature Centricity Is Harming Your Product]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/feature-centricity-harming-product/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/feature-centricity-harming-product/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most product teams commonly adopt a feature-centric mindset, finding them convenient for brainstorming, drafting requirement documents, and integrating into backlogs and ticketing systems. In this article, Andy Budd shows how fixation with features might be holding you back and how making a few small tweaks to your process could make an entire world of difference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andy Budd)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Sort an Array of Objects by Property Name in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-sort-array-of-objects-by-property-name-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-sort-array-of-objects-by-property-name-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T14:45:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn about one of the most common operations you'll perform while working with JavaScript: sorting an array of objects by property name. Basic Array Concepts Let's review some basic JavaScript concepts before delving deeper into the subject so that you have the background info you need.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kaushal Joshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Job Scheduling in RHEL – cron and at Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/job-scheduling-in-rhel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/job-scheduling-in-rhel/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T14:06:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Efficiently executing tasks at designated times or in response to certain events is essential in RHEL's job scheduling process. With the help of various tools and utilities, you can easily coordinate and automate job scheduling, eliminating the need for manual intervention. Some common tools for job scheduling in RHEL include:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Less Common HTML Tags You Should Know – With Example Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/less-common-html-tags/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/less-common-html-tags/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T14:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are only so many HTML tags [https://css-tricks.com/average-web-page-data-analyzing-8-million-websites/]  that people typically use when building websites. But as there are over 100+ HTML elements, I wondered if there were any more beginner-friendly tags that I didn't know about – and that others might find useful, too. After doing some research,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuzaali Surti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Authentication in Your Apps with Supabase Auth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-authentication-in-apps-with-supabase/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-authentication-in-apps-with-supabase/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T10:53:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll learn the basic key concepts that'll help you grasp how authentication and authorization work.  You'll start by learning what authentication and authorization are, and then learn how to implement authentication in your applications using Supabase auth. Table of Contents  *  Prerequisites]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fatuma Abdullahi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Python Decorator Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-python-decorator-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-python-decorator-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T17:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python decorators provide an easy yet powerful syntax for modifying and extending the behavior of functions in your code.  A decorator is essentially a function that takes another function, augments its functionality, and returns a new function – without permanently modifying the original function itself. This tutorial will walk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atharva Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Simple Guide To Retrieval Augmented Generation Language Models]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/guide-retrieval-augmented-generation-language-models/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/guide-retrieval-augmented-generation-language-models/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Language models have shown impressive capabilities. But that doesn’t mean they’re without faults, as anyone who has witnessed a ChatGPT “hallucination” can attest. In this article, Joas Pambou diagnoses the symptoms that cause hallucinations and explains not only what RAG is but also different approaches for using it to solve language model limitations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a React App in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-react-app-in-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-react-app-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T13:44:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2024, there are more ways than ever to get your React projects started. But which one should you choose? In this article, I'm going to break down all of the major ways you can use to create a React app and which one you should pick based off of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Simple Sentiment Analyzer Using Hugging Face Transformer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-simple-sentiment-analyzer-using-hugging-face-transformer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-simple-sentiment-analyzer-using-hugging-face-transformer/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T00:32:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will look at writing a sentiment analyzer using Hugging Face Transformer, a powerful tool in the world of NLP.  Imagine you’re running a business and you want to know what your customers think about your product. Or maybe you’re a movie director wanting to gauge]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React.js with Laravel to Build a Draggable Tasklist App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-react-with-laravel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-react-with-laravel/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T00:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have seen tutorials that help you build a simple React.js app that use some third-party API or a Node.js server as a backend. You could also use Laravel for this purpose and integrate it with React. As a backend framework, Laravel actually offers a tool to help you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>San B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize Your CSS Code for Faster Web Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-optimize-your-css-code-for-faster-web-pages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-optimize-your-css-code-for-faster-web-pages/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T00:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS is more than just a tool for styling. It also determines how web pages render in a browser. Well-optimized CSS means faster loading times and a smoother user experience. In today's digital landscape, the performance of a website is a key factor in its success. Writing efficient CSS code]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ophy Boamah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Running the Biggest Programming Channel on YouTube with freeCodeCamp's Beau Carnes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-biggest-youtube-programming-channel-beau-carnes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-biggest-youtube-programming-channel-beau-carnes/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T19:50:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beau Carnes has run the freeCodeCamp community YouTube channel for the past 5 years, taking it from 75,000 subscribers all the way up to 9 million. Beau started out working as a Special Education teacher at a Michigan high school. He taught himself how to code before working as a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Hash Map? Time Complexity and Two Sum Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-hash-map/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-hash-map/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T17:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hash table or hash map, is a data structure that helps with mapping keys to values for highly efficient operations like the lookup, insertion and deletion operations. In this tutorial, you'll learn the following:  * Constant and linear time complexity.  * Why use a hash map?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sule-Balogun Olanrewaju Ganiu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Natural Language Processing Techniques for Topic Identification – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/topic-identification-using-natural-language-processing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/topic-identification-using-natural-language-processing/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T16:16:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a lot of textual information available these days. It ranges from articles to social media posts and research papers. So our ability to distill meaningful insights is key. This helps us make informed decisions in a wide array of contexts.  For example, you can analyze a large volume]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ibrahim Abayomi Ogunbiyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn LangChain and Gen AI by Building 6 Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-langchain-and-gen-ai-by-building-6-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-langchain-and-gen-ai-by-building-6-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T16:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning LangChain empowers you to seamlessly integrate advanced language models like GPT-4 into diverse applications, unlocking capabilities in natural language processing and AI-driven applications. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build six end-to-end projects using LangChain and a variety]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Blurry Shimmer Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/css-blurry-shimmer-effect/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/css-blurry-shimmer-effect/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taking inspiration from shadows, author Yair Even Or creates the same sort of thing, only with a blurring effect in place of the shadow. Read along for a step-by-step explanation of how it comes together using a combination of masks, gradients, and the good ol’ `backdrop-filter` property.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yair Even Or)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Units – When to Use rem, em, px, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-units-when-to-use-each-one/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-units-when-to-use-each-one/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T00:58:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS units allow you to measure and specify different property values. You use them to modify CSS properties such as margins, padding, height, and width to make them compatible with devices of all screen sizes. CSS units have two basic types:  * Absolute units  * Relative units Absolute]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esther Christopher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get the First Line of a Multiline String in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-the-first-line-of-a-multiline-string-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-the-first-line-of-a-multiline-string-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T23:33:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, getting the first element of an array or string is pretty easy. But when it comes to getting the first line of a multiline string, some approaches can hurt your app's performance in certain cases. In this article, we will look at the three best ways you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Furkan Emin Can</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Next.js Apps to Github Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-next-js-app-to-github-pages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-next-js-app-to-github-pages/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T22:46:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will walk you through the process of publishing a Next.js application on GitHub Pages.  What makes this guide particularly helpful is that I'll teach you how to integrate with GitHub Actions, too. This means your application will be automatically deployed every time you push code]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code Extensions to Boost Your Productivity in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-vscode-extensions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-vscode-extensions/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T22:42:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the 2023 Stack Overflow Developer Survey [https://survey.stackoverflow.co/2023/#section-most-popular-technologies-integrated-development-environment] , Visual Studio Code (also known as VSCode) ranked as the most preferred integrated developer environment (IDE) tool.  Visual Studio Code has many great features out-of-the-box, and supports a large community of extensions to add enhanced functionality.  Stack Overflow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie Pina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Back Up and Restore Azure SQL Databases]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-back-up-and-restore-sql-azure-database/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-back-up-and-restore-sql-azure-database/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T22:34:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's Azure’s provides many services via a single cloud, which lets them offer one solution for multiple corporate infrastructures. Teams use Azure because they value the opportunity to run SQL databases in the cloud and complete simple operations via the Azure portal.  But you'll need to have a way]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Tray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyGame Tutorial – How to Build a Bouncing Ball Game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pygame-tutorial-build-a-bouncing-game/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pygame-tutorial-build-a-bouncing-game/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T22:46:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn how to create a simple yet funny bouncing ball game using the PyGame library.  Whether you're a beginner seeking to grasp the fundamentals of game development or an enthusiast eager to explore PyGame's capabilities, this article is your guide to crafting a simple yet]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan P. Romano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build AI Apps – A Frontend Developer's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/frontend-ai-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/frontend-ai-guide/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T22:05:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence: The New Frontier for Frontend Developers The demand for AI-powered applications is growing at a fast pace. As a front-end developer, you can take advantage of this trend and advance your career by integrating your skills in frontend development with AI technologies. This integration allows you to build]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahmud Adeleye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring with Event-Driven Architecture on AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deep-dive-into-event-driven-architecture-on-aws/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deep-dive-into-event-driven-architecture-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T15:03:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Event-driven architecture is a software design pattern where components or services perform actions in response to events, often asynchronously. This post serves as a companion to our video course, "Deep Dive into Event-Driven Architecture on AWS." In the course, we delve into some of the core fundamentals of event-driven architecture]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Dilemma In Graphic Design: Steering Towards Excellence In Typography And Beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/ai-dilemma-graphic-design-typography/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/ai-dilemma-graphic-design-typography/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI promises a major upheaval in typography, with designers finding themselves navigating both opportunities and challenges. How will it impact quality, design roles, and our use of type in the future? As we explore this new frontier, we realise that we are at a juncture as significant as Gutenberg’s press, set to redefine how we interact with text and visual communication.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Filip Paldia &amp; Jamie Clarke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage State in React Apps with APIs – Redux, Context API, and Recoil Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manage-state-in-react-apps-with-apis/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manage-state-in-react-apps-with-apis/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T00:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State management is a crucial aspect of building robust and scalable React applications, especially when dealing with APIs.  As your application grows in complexity, efficiently managing the state becomes essential for a smooth user experience.  In the React ecosystem, there are several options for state management, each with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a CRUD REST API with NestJS, Docker, Swagger, and Prisma]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-crud-rest-api-with-nestjs-docker-swagger-prisma/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-crud-rest-api-with-nestjs-docker-swagger-prisma/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T00:17:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to this in-depth guide on crafting a RESTful API with NestJS, Docker, Swagger, and Prisma. My goal here is to teach you how to build robust and efficient backends, regardless of whether you're a seasoned developer or a beginner just dipping your toes into the world of coding. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaiah Clifford Opoku</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Command Line Tricks You Can Learn Faster than Drinking Your Morning Coffee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/command-line-tricks-you-can-learn-quickly/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/command-line-tricks-you-can-learn-quickly/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T23:15:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this short tutorial, I want to share with you a few tricks and tips to help you deal with some common situations when you're working in the Linux command line. We will cover the following:  * find  * xargs and nproc  * taskset  * numactl]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Tools You Can Use in Visual Studio Code Besides GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-tools-to-use-in-vs-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-tools-to-use-in-vs-code/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T19:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI tools have become quite popular recently. Developers use these tools to help generate ideas, create simple code examples, and so on.  In 2023, ChatGPT and other Large Language Models found their way into many of our toolkits. And we can use them to be more productive and save]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create AI Assistants with OpenAI's Assistants API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-ai-assistants-with-openais-assistants-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-ai-assistants-with-openais-assistants-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T17:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI's Assistants API is a powerful tool that allows developers to build AI assistants within their apps efficiently. It simplifies managing conversation history and provides access to advanced features like Code Interpreter and Retrieval. The API also improves function-calling for third-party tools. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Data Analysis and Visualization with Python Using Astronomical Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-data-analysis-and-visualization-with-python-using-astrongomical-data/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-data-analysis-and-visualization-with-python-using-astrongomical-data/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T19:48:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you fascinated by both Python and the night sky? We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Python to analyze and visualize astronomical Data. This course was created by Spartificial, whose mission is to provide engineering education in the most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Your Web Server with Continuous Integration Using NGINX and CircleCI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/secure-web-server-with-continuous-integration-using-nginx-and-circleci/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/secure-web-server-with-continuous-integration-using-nginx-and-circleci/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T16:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web servers are responsible for delivering web pages and various resources to clients through the internet. They can exist either as software or hardware components. But unfortunately, they often become targets for hackers and malicious individuals seeking to exploit any vulnerabilities to compromise data and disrupt functionality. As a result,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abraham Dahunsi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with FPM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/getting-started-with-fpm/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/getting-started-with-fpm/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T16:42:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FPM [https://fpm.readthedocs.io/en/latest/getting-started.html] is a powerful wrapper that allows you to create packages for multiple programs in multiple operating systems.  In this tutorial I will show you how you can replace some of the tedious packaging of third party applications. What You Need to Complete this Tutorial  * A]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use SonarLint to Write Cleaner Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-sonarlint-to-write-cleaner-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-sonarlint-to-write-cleaner-code/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T23:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building a coding project, the better it is, the more fun it'll be to use. And the prouder you'll be of your hard work, right?  Also, writing quality and performant code helps your program or website work as expected – which should be every developer's goal. SonarLint]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okosa Leonard Onyekachukwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get a Developer Job]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-a-developer-job/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-a-developer-job/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T17:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The demand for skilled software developers continues to grow. However, for many self-taught developers, the path to securing a job in this competitive field can seem daunting. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is designed to guide aspiring software engineers through the job-hunting process. Lane]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perform CRUD Operations with Django Models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/models-in-django/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/models-in-django/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T16:10:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Django is a super useful tool for building web applications with Python. It follows the Model-View-Template (MVT) architecture, which is a popular design pattern for building web apps. In the MVT architecture, the Model refers to the internal representation of information stored, the View is responsible for processing user requests]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chepkirui dorothy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a High-Performance Tab Component in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-high-performance-tab-component/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-high-performance-tab-component/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T16:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tabs are more than mere UI elements – they're the backbone of user navigation and content organization in many applications. In React, crafting a tabbed component that's both efficient and responsive is not just an improvement, it's a necessity. This article takes a deep dive into constructing a React tab]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Progressive Web Apps? PWA Guide for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-progressive-web-apps-pwa-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-progressive-web-apps-pwa-guide/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T15:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Progressive Web Apps (PWAs) are simply installable web applications – websites that you can install on your device, much like you would install an app from an app store.  They bring together the best parts of using a website (easy to access, no need to install anything) with the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ophy Boamah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Design and Build Sustainable Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/design-and-build-sustainable-software/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/design-and-build-sustainable-software/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T01:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Electronic devices that run software are all around us. Your mobile phone, your car, your microwave, and virtually anything around you – there’s a very good chance that they have electronic components running some form of software. These devices inevitably use power and have batteries and circuits, which degrade over]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jayant Chowdhary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Validate Forms with Zod and React-Hook-Form]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-form-validation-zod-react-hook-form/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-form-validation-zod-react-hook-form/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T21:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forms allow you to collect user data on your websites and apps. And validation is essential to guarantee type safety and the proper format for collected data. You can perform validation on both the client and server side of the application.  This is where Zod and React-Hook-Form come in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gift Uhiene</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to create Python User Interfaces with PyQt5]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-python-user-interfaces-with-pyqt5/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-python-user-interfaces-with-pyqt5/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T21:21:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python can be used for everything from scripting, machine learning, web development, and graphical user interfaces. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that teaches them how to create visually appealing and functional user interfaces (UIs) using Python, with a specific focus on developing a Modern Music]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ACID Databases – Atomicity, Consistency, Isolation & Durability Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/acid-databases-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/acid-databases-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T17:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ACID stands for Atomicity, Consistency, Isolation and Durability. These are four key properties that most database management systems (DBMS) offer as guarantees when handling transactions. Most popular DBMS like MySQL [https://dev.mysql.com/doc/refman/8.0/en/mysql-acid.html], PostgresSQL [https://www.postgresql.org/about/] and Oracle [https://docs.oracle.com/cd/F51125_01/docs.85/SDS%20PI/acid-compliant-transactions.html#GUID-ECB79D66-46DE-4F48-93DC-8677E7BB44EF]  have ACID guarantees out of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TUI Applications with Click and Trogon – Linux Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tui-applications-with-click-and-trogon/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tui-applications-with-click-and-trogon/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T17:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux and terminal applications are almost synonymous. If you have used applications like grep, cat, sed, and AWK, those are command line interfaces ( CLI [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Command-line_interface]). And when they work together, they allow you to unleash the power of your computer by mixing and matching a few commands. Sometimes the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Custom Buttons to a Date Picker in Flatpickr]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-custom-buttons-to-flatpickr/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-custom-buttons-to-flatpickr/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T02:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever had to use a date picker in a web frontend project, chances are that you've used flatpickr. For the unacquainted, flatpickr [https://flatpickr.js.org/] is one of the most popular date picker libraries in the open source-verse. It's framework-agnostic, highly customizable, and lightweight. I recently had to use it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Idris Abdul-Lateef</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atomics and Concurrency in C++]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/atomics-and-concurrency-in-cpp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/atomics-and-concurrency-in-cpp/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T23:50:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concurrency is a programming term you'll need to be familiar with if you code in C++. It's especially relevant if you want to get more out of your available compute resources.  But concurrency comes with certain problems. Some of them can be solved using  mutexes [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mutual_exclusion], although mutexes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaid Humayun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Object-Oriented Programming in Java – Full Book]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-oriented-programming-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-oriented-programming-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T23:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Java is a go-to language for many programmers, and it's a critical skill for any software engineer. After learning Java, picking up other programming languages and advanced concepts becomes much easier.  In this book, I'll cover the practical knowledge you need to move from writing basic Java code to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Arrow Functions vs Regular Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/regular-vs-arrow-functions-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/regular-vs-arrow-functions-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T22:19:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, there are two main ways of writing functions. You can create functions using the regular function syntax. Or you can use the arrow function syntax.  In this article, you will learn how to use both options. You'll also learn about the differences between the two and when]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the Essentials of Data Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-essentials-of-data-engineering/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-essentials-of-data-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T21:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to freeCodeCamp's Data Engineering Video Course Data Engineering is a vital field in the tech industry focused on designing, building, and maintaining systems that collect, process, and analyze large volumes of data. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel all about data engineering, designed to cater]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize AWS Simple Storage Service for Better Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-optimize-aws-s3-for-performance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-optimize-aws-s3-for-performance/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T21:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[S3 is an Amazon Web Service that provides data storage and retrieval in the cloud. ‌‌ This article will discuss the common S3 performance bottlenecks and how they impact the service's overall performance. It will also share some best practices to serve as guidelines for optimising the performance of your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Feyijimi Erinle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How File Ownership and Permissions Work in RHEL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/file-ownership-permissions-rhel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/file-ownership-permissions-rhel/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T20:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux commands give you precise control over file ownership and permissions, ensuring data security and access control.  This guide will delve into several essential commands: chown, chgrp, chmod, and  umask. The examples will showcase their functionality, variations, and practical applications. Table Of Contents Here's what we'll cover in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Engine and Runtime Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-engine-and-runtime-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-engine-and-runtime-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T19:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A JavaScript engine is simply a computer program that executes JavaScript code. It's responsible for translating human-readable JavaScript code into machine-readable instructions that the computer's hardware can execute. When you write JavaScript code and run it in a browser, the code doesn't directly interact with your computer's hardware. Instead, it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Complex But Awesome CSS border-image Property]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/css-border-image-property/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/css-border-image-property/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS `border-image` property is one of those properties you undoubtedly know exists but may not have ever reached for. In this article, Temani Afif demonstrates different approaches for using `border-image` to create clever decorative accents and shapes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 React Projects to Build in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-projects-to-build-in-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-projects-to-build-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T12:07:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To be confident with using React, you need to build real-world projects. But what projects are worth building in 2024? I have put together a list of seven projects that I think are ideal for becoming a confident React developer, from simple to complex applications. This will give you some]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Immutability in JavaScript – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/immutability-in-javascript-with-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/immutability-in-javascript-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T23:21:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often hear the terms: immutable and immutability. But what do they mean, and, as developers, why should we care? Immutable basically means something that cannot be changed. In programming, immutable is used to describe a value that cannot be changed after it's been set. But, most programs require creating,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Kurata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Callbacks and Higher Order Functions in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/callbacks-higher-order-functions-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/callbacks-higher-order-functions-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T18:07:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way functions are treated and used in JavaScript is quite interesting. They are very flexible – we can assign a function as a value to a variable, return them as a value from another function, and pass them as an argument to another function. We can do all this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Franklin Okolie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Markdown in VSCode – Syntax and Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-markdown-in-vscode/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-markdown-in-vscode/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T17:46:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Markdown is a lightweight markup language for creating formatted text using a plain-text editor. It is widely used for creating README files, documentation, and other forms of text. Visual Studio Code (VSCode) is a popular source code editor that provides excellent support for Markdown, making it easy for developers, writers,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Poromon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Storage API – How to Store Data on the Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-storage-api-how-to-store-data-on-the-browser/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-storage-api-how-to-store-data-on-the-browser/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T17:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Web Storage API is a set of APIs exposed by the browser so that you can store data in the browser. The data stored in the Web Storage use the key/value pair format, and both data will be stored as strings. There are two types of storage introduced in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JS DOM Manipulation Best Practices – with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dom-manipulation-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dom-manipulation-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T17:41:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, you can manipulate the content of a web page using the Document Object Model (DOM). But how do you write code that is readable, easy to maintain, and not prone to performance issues?  That's what we'll cover in this article. I'll discuss some important best practices so]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Prepare for Data Analyst Job Interviews]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-for-data-analyst-job-interview/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-for-data-analyst-job-interview/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T17:31:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s digital world, every business and organization collects and uses data to build better products, target the right customers, improve efficiency, and even forecast future demand.  They say that data is the new oil – and now is the perfect time to enter the data analytics job market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jess Wilk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NGINX for Backend Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nginx/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nginx/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T16:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NGINX is a versatile and powerful open-source software used for web serving, reverse proxying, caching, load balancing, media streaming, and more. It's important to understand for backend developers. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you what you need to know about NGINX. Laith]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Magic Link Authentication with React, Flask, and Authsignal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-magic-link-authentication-with-react-flask-and-authsignal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-magic-link-authentication-with-react-flask-and-authsignal/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T18:40:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authentication is the process of verifying the identity of a user or system. It ensures that only authorized individuals or systems can access certain resources or perform specific actions. Magic Link Authentication offers a simple yet secure way for users to log in without passwords. This tutorial will walk you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Front-End Tools Of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/top-frontend-tools-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/top-frontend-tools-2023/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Useful front-end tools for CSS and JavaScript developers that were most popular last year and will help you speed up your development workflow. Let’s dive in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Sliding Window Technique – Algorithm Example and Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sliding-window-technique/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sliding-window-technique/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T15:11:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I was practicing coding problems that focused on Data Structures and Algorithms in preparation for a job change.  During this process, I came across the Sliding Window technique. I found this algorithm to be very interesting, so I wanted to share my learnings with the community.  This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize Search Queries in MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/optimize-search-queries-in-mongodb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/optimize-search-queries-in-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T21:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Searching through a database to extract relevant data can be quite cumbersome if you don't have – or know how to use – the right tools. MongoDB is a non-relational, no-SQL database that differs from relational SQL-based databases such as PostgresSQL, MySQL. These SQL-based databases use conventional rows and columns]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oluwatobi Joshua</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with Hugging Face – Open Source AI Models and Datasets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-started-with-hugging-face/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-started-with-hugging-face/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T21:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Hugging Face 🤗? If you are interested in Artificial Intelligence and Natural Language Processing, you have probably heard of Hugging Face – the company named after a cute emoji.  Hugging Face is not only a company, but also a platform that is transforming the fields of AI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ambreen Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding DOM Events and JavaScript Event Listeners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dom-events-and-javascript-event-listeners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dom-events-and-javascript-event-listeners/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T20:38:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript code in the browser uses an event-driven programming pattern. What this means is that when a specific DOM event happens in the browser, a piece of code will be executed as a response to that action. In this article, I will help you see and understand how to listen]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyTorch vs TensorFlow – Which is Better for Deep Learning Projects?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pytorch-vs-tensorflow-for-deep-learning-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pytorch-vs-tensorflow-for-deep-learning-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:46:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll look at two popular deep learning libraries — PyTorch and TensorFlow – and see how they compare. If you are getting started with deep learning, the available tools and frameworks will be overwhelming. Industry experts may recommend TensorFlow while hardcore ML engineers may prefer PyTorch. Both]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Stepper Component in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-stepper-component-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-stepper-component-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T15:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was working on a React project recently, and I realized that there were so many UI components that I had to build to get things done quickly. So I began to explore a lot of UI libraries like Material UI [https://mui.com] or Chakra UI [https://chakra-ui.com/]. Then I started wondering]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olabisi Olaoye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work with Third-Party APIs in React by Building a Crypto Exchange Rate Web App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/work-with-third-party-libraries-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/work-with-third-party-libraries-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T15:24:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working with APIs is crucial to any web application. And as a frontend developer, knowing how to connect your apps with third-party APIs is an important skill to have. In this article, you'll learn how to connect your app and fetch data from a third-party API by building a crypto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidera Humphrey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Document Object Model? DOM for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-the-dom/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-the-dom/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T15:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'm going to explain to you how the DOM works so that you have a clear picture of why JavaScript is needed to develop a web application. First, let's recap what we know about HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. How HTML, CSS, and JavaScript work When you want]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript DOM Manipulation Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-dom-manipulation-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-dom-manipulation-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T15:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOM Manipulation is one of the most exciting topics to learn about in JavaScript. This is because one of JavaScript's main uses is to make web pages interactive – and the Document Object Model (DOM) plays a major role in this.  The DOM is a powerful tool that allows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Custom CSS Animations with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-custom-css-animations/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-custom-css-animations/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T21:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animations are a crucial component of modern web design. They enable you to create dynamic and engaging web elements that attract more customers and drive more sales. In this article, we will discuss how to create cool custom animations using CSS. Prerequisites Before going forward with this article, make sure]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Hu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do Zsh Configuration Files Work?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-zsh-configuration-files-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-zsh-configuration-files-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T20:37:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beginners often get confused when configuring Zsh shell on a Mac. Zsh shell offers four configuration files with no discernible differences. Particularly, ~/.zshrc and ~/.zprofile appear to be identical, leaving us wondering which one to use.  In this article, you'll learn the difference and a simple guideline for your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kehoe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Work with RESTful APIs in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-work-with-restful-apis-in-react-simplified-steps-and-practical-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-work-with-restful-apis-in-react-simplified-steps-and-practical-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T19:09:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RESTful APIs are a crucial component in modern web development. They allow communication between different applications over the internet.  REST (which stands for Representational State Transfer) APIs operate on a stateless client-server architecture, providing a standardized way to create, read, update, and delete resources. Integrating RESTful APIs with React]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The React Roadmap for 2024 – How to Learn React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-react-roadmap-learn-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-react-roadmap-learn-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T18:57:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, I'll break down a complete roadmap that will cover all the concepts, libraries, and tools to help you become a React developer in 2024. My goal is to show you the happy path in React, navigating you away from pitfalls so you can spend your time on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a GitHub Template Repository for Scaffolding with React, Vite, and TailwindCSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-github-template-repository-with-react-vite-and-tailwindcss/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-github-template-repository-with-react-vite-and-tailwindcss/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T18:04:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers love productivity. When it comes to coding, we want to do things fast and we look out for opportunities to re-use things as much as possible. Say, you are getting started with a ReactJS project and want to use TailwindCSS  for the same. The first time, it would]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use New CSS Features to Build a Progress Indicator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-new-css-features-to-build-a-progress-indicator/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-new-css-features-to-build-a-progress-indicator/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T15:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the last 7 months, I’ve had my head down building Component Odyssey [https://component-odyssey.com/]. It’s been a richly fulfilling project and I’m eager for people to take the course and learn heaps about building component libraries using web components. I’ve seen some incredible demos over the past year, and wanted]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrico Karoulla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Data Analysis with Comprehensive 19-Hour Bootcamp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-data-analysis-with-comprehensive-19-hour-bootcamp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-data-analysis-with-comprehensive-19-hour-bootcamp/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T15:39:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of data analysis is vast and continually evolving, and staying ahead in this field requires a solid foundation in its core technologies and methodologies. We just published a 19-hour data analysis bootcamp on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This bootcamp, developed by Alex Freberg, provides an immersive learning experience]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use pnpm – Installation and Common Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-pnpm/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-pnpm/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T15:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[pnpm is like npm, but it's way faster and more efficient. After all, the starting p stands for performant. According to its creator, Zoltan Kochan, pnpm "allows you to save gigabytes of disk space." Many popular projects including Next.js, Vite, Svelte, and even freeCodeCamp use pnpm. So now is a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Biswas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make React Apps SEO-Friendly – A Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-seo-friendly-react-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-seo-friendly-react-apps/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T15:25:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing your web applications, you should always consider search engine optimization (SEO) techniques. Many things come into play when you're making sure your web application operates as intended and has an online presence. Search engines such as Google, Bing, and Yahoo serve as the primary medium for users seeking]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okosa Leonard Onyekachukwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>