<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-08-29T00:53:57.694Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Javascript Dates – How to Use the DayJS Library to work with Date and Time in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-date-time-dayjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-date-time-dayjs/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T22:09:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to handling dates and times in JavaScript, developers often find themselves grappling with the complexities of the built-in Date object. While vanilla JavaScript provides fundamental functionality, it can be quite cumbersome to work with, especially when dealing with parsing, formatting, and manipulating dates. This is where external]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Weatherston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Data Science and AI Handbook – How to Start a Career in Data Science]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-data-science-and-ai-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-data-science-and-ai-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T16:44:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this handbook, I'll show you how to use proven strategies and insights to get into the fields of AI and Data Science. I'll help you navigate the exciting world of Data Science and AI in 2023 so you can increase your chances of landing a job.  > Every]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tatev Karen Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Functions and Scope – a Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-functions-and-scope/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-functions-and-scope/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T14:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the exciting world of JavaScript Functions and Scope. Have you ever wondered how programs remember things and do tasks over and over again? Well, that's where functions and scope come into play. Whether you're a curious beginner or someone looking to strengthen your coding skills, get ready to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casmir Onyekani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Falling For Oklch: A Love Story Of Color Spaces, Gamuts, And CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/oklch-color-spaces-gamuts-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/oklch-color-spaces-gamuts-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Color Module Level 4 specification defined a slew of new color features when it became a candidate recommendation in 2022, including Oklab and Oklch, which have widened the field of color we have to work with. Explore the Oklch color space and how to start using it in CSS today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Earn a Free C# Certification from Microsoft and freeCodeCamp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-microsoft-c-sharp-certification/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-microsoft-c-sharp-certification/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T12:53:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm excited to announce that Microsoft and freeCodeCamp have teamed up to bring you a new free professional certification: the Foundational C# Certification. This professional certification includes 35 hours of training from Microsoft and an online certification exam by freeCodeCamp. By the end of this process, you'll have earned your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Real-Time Notification System with Go and Kafka]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-real-time-notification-system-with-go-and-kafka/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-real-time-notification-system-with-go-and-kafka/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T21:41:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, applications need to have instant data access and processing capabilities. Whether it's updating real-time stock trades for financial institutions or navigating through live traffic data, the ability to process and react to data in real time is crucial. In this tutorial, you’ll delve into the mechanics of Kafka]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hermann Rösch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How TypeScript Can Improve Your Web Development Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-typescript-can-improve-web-development-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-typescript-can-improve-web-development-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, everyone! In this article I'm going to talk about how TypeScript can help enhance and improve your web development projects.  If you're not familiar with TypeScript, you can read through this comprehensive beginner's guide [/news/learn-typescript-beginners-guide/] to get started. If you do know some TS, that's great – I'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adalbert Pungu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Large Language Model from Scratch Using Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-large-language-model-from-scratch-using-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-large-language-model-from-scratch-using-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T15:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever been fascinated by the capabilities of large language models like GPT-4 but wondered how they are actually work? If you want to uncover the mysteries behind these powerful models, our latest video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel is perfect for you. In this comprehensive course, you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Double Diamond Design Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/improving-double-diamond-design-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/improving-double-diamond-design-process/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The so-called “Double Diamond” is a great way of visualizing an ideal design process — but it’s just not the way most companies deliver new projects or services. Andy Budd proposes a new “Double Diamond” idea that better aligns with the way work actually gets done and highlights the place where design has the most leverage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andy Budd)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Routing in Next.js – How to Use App Router in your Next Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/routing-in-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/routing-in-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T15:13:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving world of web development, Next.js has consistently been a beacon of hope for developers seeking a balance between performance and ease of use.  With the introduction of the App Router in 2023, the framework has once again stirred the pot, leaving many of us scratching our]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering SQL for Web Developers – Full Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-for-web-devs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-for-web-devs/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T13:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's data-driven world, the ability to effectively manage and query databases is an essential skill for any programmer, data analyst, or software engineer. Whether you want to streamline business operations, uncover critical insights, or create dynamic applications, a solid understanding of Structured Query Language (SQL) is paramount. We just]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering SQL for Web Developers – Full Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/untitled-135/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/untitled-135/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T13:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's data-driven world, the ability to effectively manage and query databases is an essential skill for any programmer, data analyst, or software engineer. Whether you want to streamline business operations, uncover critical insights, or create dynamic applications, a solid understanding of Structured Query Language (SQL) is paramount. We just]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Photo Encryption App using Steganography]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-photo-encryption-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-photo-encryption-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T21:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this digital age, data flows freely across networks and devices. So protecting sensitive information from unauthorized access is crucial. That's where encryption comes in.  Encryption involves converting plain, readable data into an incomprehensible form. It's also essential to have a way to convert the data back into a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Houssein Badra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beginner's Python Tutorial: Pong]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/beginners-python-tutorial-pong/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/beginners-python-tutorial-pong/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T20:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pong was one of the first video games. And it also makes a good first (or early) Python project when you are learning to code. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you improve your Python and Pygame skills by teaching you how to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Perl Programming Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-perl-programming-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-perl-programming-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T17:56:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For decades, the Perl programming language has remained important in the realms of text processing, system administration, and even web development. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Perl. The course covers topics ranging from basic syntax to advanced]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Few Interesting Ways To Use CSS Shadows For More Than Depth]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/interesting-ways-use-css-shadows/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/interesting-ways-use-css-shadows/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often think of shadows in CSS as something to reach for when we want to add depth to a design. But shadows can be used for more than depth. Let’s experiment with different shadows — two CSS properties and a filter — to make interesting hover effects, different text styles, and even casting shadows on other shadows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Sam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Tampermonkey to Improve a Website's UI – Example Using freeCodeCamp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/customize-website-experience-with-tampermonkey/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/customize-website-experience-with-tampermonkey/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T22:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Tampermonkey? Tampermonkey is a browser extension that lets you add custom scripts to websites, making them work or look the way you want. It's like giving websites a makeover or adding new features. These scripts are called userscripts and you can make tampermonkey run those scripts when you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tasnim Ferdous</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Python Code Example Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-python-code-example-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-python-code-example-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T21:54:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Very few programming languages are as universally loved as Python. The brainchild of Dutch programmer Guido van Rossum [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Guido_van_Rossum], Python is easy to learn, powerful, and an utter joy to work with. Thanks to its popularity, video and written resources about Python are plentiful. This handbook, however, tries to be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farhan Hasin Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Bundle a Simple React Application Using esbuild]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/bundle-a-basic-react-application-using-esbuild/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/bundle-a-basic-react-application-using-esbuild/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T20:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bundling is an important phase in the web development process, particularly when dealing with JavaScript frameworks like React. It entails combining all the various JavaScript files and dependencies into a single file for faster browser loading and execution.  esbuild is a lightweight and efficient bundler for React apps. Here's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JS Date Validations – How To Validate a Date in JavaScript (With Examples)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-validate-a-date-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-validate-a-date-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T19:08:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are times when you need to validate a date input in your JavaScript applications. This article will show you how to perform the following date validations:  1. Check if a string is a valid date  2. Validate a string in the DD/MM/YYYY format  3. Check if]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy an Application to a Kubernetes Cluster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-docker-image-to-kubernetes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-docker-image-to-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T16:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's ever-changing technology landscape, companies are looking for reliable and scalable ways to run and manage software. And containers have transformed the way we deliver software. Container orchestration platforms have made it possible to deploy and manage containerised applications. Kubernetes is one such platform that has been a game-changer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Your Website Against SEO Poisoning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/protect-your-website-against-seo-poisoning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/protect-your-website-against-seo-poisoning/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T16:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital landscape, search engine optimization (SEO) is important for increasing online visibility and driving organic traffic to websites.  But cybersecurity threats, including SEO poisoning, pose a great risks to both website owners and SEO efforts.  To fight these risks and safeguard websites, cybersecurity experts and SEO]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isah Jacob</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Your Website Against SEO Poisoning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ensuring-website-security-collaborative-measures-for-cybersecurity-and-seo-experts-to-prevent-seo-poisoning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ensuring-website-security-collaborative-measures-for-cybersecurity-and-seo-experts-to-prevent-seo-poisoning/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T16:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital landscape, search engine optimization (SEO) is important for increasing online visibility and driving organic traffic to websites.  But cybersecurity threats, including SEO poisoning, pose a great risks to both website owners and SEO efforts.  To fight these risks and safeguard websites, cybersecurity experts and SEO]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isah Jacob</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Calculator App with Svelte]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-calculator-app-with-svelte/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-calculator-app-with-svelte/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T15:48:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Svelte is an open-source front-end JavaScript framework used for building web applications, designed to make developing interactive user interfaces more efficient and performant.  Compared to other front-end frameworks like React, Vue, or Angular, it focuses on a different approach by compiling components. In most traditional frameworks, you build components]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adejumo Ridwan Suleiman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stateful vs Stateless Architecture – Explained for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/stateful-vs-stateless-architectures-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/stateful-vs-stateless-architectures-explained/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T21:08:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In programming, "state" refers to the condition of a system, component, or application at a particular point in time.  As a simple example, if you are shopping on amazon.com, whether you are currently logged into the site or if you have anything stored in your cart are some examples]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing ScrapePark.org – Practice Web Scraping Without Hurting Anyone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/practice-web-scraping-safely/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/practice-web-scraping-safely/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T19:50:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I grew up in the 1990s, we skateboarded everywhere. If a parking lot had a ledge or a handrail, you'd better believe we waxed it and grinded our boards across it. Fast forward to the 2020s – many cities have built public skate parks. These are safe, legal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Development with Large Language Models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/development-with-large-language-models/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/development-with-large-language-models/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:13:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) open up a wide range of capabilities for developers We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will equip you with the skills to use LLMs effectively for your projects. Developed by Akshath from Luup.ai, this course will help you unlock the potential]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Google Drive Clone with Laravel, PHP, and Vue.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-google-drive-clone-with-laravel-php-vuejs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-google-drive-clone-with-laravel-php-vuejs/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T14:48:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building file manager application is a great way to learn many important programming concepts. We just posted a 14-hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build and deploy a feature-rich file manager application using Laravel (the PHP framework), Inertia, and Vue.js. This comprehensive course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the JavaScript at() Array Method]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-at-method/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-at-method/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T14:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of JavaScript's most exciting new features is the at() method. The at()  method is a new addition to the Array prototype in JavaScript. You can use this method to access elements in an array using a numeric index. The at() method takes an integer value and returns the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie Pina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use JSON Server for Front-end Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/json-server-for-frontend-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/json-server-for-frontend-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T13:54:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most common responsibilities for front-end developers is handling the data in their front-end applications. You’ll need to be able to retrieve data from an API, manipulate it, and then render it on the screen in a modern web application for user interactions.  Efficient communication between the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juliet Ofoegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Context Menus With Safe Triangles]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/better-context-menus-safe-triangles/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/better-context-menus-safe-triangles/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how to improve the user experience of nested menus and tackle a minor yet common issue with them when the user’s pointer leaves the menu item for a moment, and the nested menu goes away, requiring the user to re-hover and try again. A well-known concept called the “safe triangle” solves this problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Costa Alexoglou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is College Still Worth it? Tips from my 20 Years in Adult Education]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/is-college-worth-it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/is-college-worth-it/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T17:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So many people ask me each week: is college still worth it? In this 1-hour video I answer this question and other commonly asked questions about university. I've been in adult education for two decades at this point, and even though I'm not a labor market economist, I do feel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement a Blender Model in a React.js Application using Three.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/blender-three-js-react-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/blender-three-js-react-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T14:58:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this step-by-step guide, you'll learn how to build a basic Blender file with incorporated fundamental animations. After that, you'll learn how to integrate Three.js with your React apps using React Three Fiber.  Getting familiar with these concepts can help you make sure your upcoming React.js applications stand out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthes Bär</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn HTML and CSS – Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-css-handbook-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-css-handbook-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T14:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings, and welcome to this comprehensive HTML and CSS handbook. My goal is to teach you everything you need to know about building fast and beautiful websites that look great on any device. I'm assuming you have no knowledge of HTML or CSS and want to learn everything from scratch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karlgusta Annoh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform Associate Certification Study Course – Pass the Exam With This Free 7 Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hashicorp-terraform-associate-certification-study-course-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-12-hour-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hashicorp-terraform-associate-certification-study-course-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-12-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T14:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to pass the HashiCorp Terraform Associate Certification (003) with this free 7-hour course. What is the HashiCorp Terraform Associate? HashiCorp is a company specializing in open-source tools for multi-cloud workloads. HashiCorp's most popular tool is Terraform, which allows DevOps Engineers to write code to provision infrastructure for multiple]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Brown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use JavaScript Promises – Callbacks, Async/Await, and Promise Methods Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-promises-async-await-and-promise-methods/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-promises-async-await-and-promise-methods/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T16:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn everything you need to know about using promises and async/await in JavaScript. So let's get started. If you'd like to learn along with a video version of this tutorial, you can also check out my YouTube playlist [https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4jaiXP6vU2w&list=PLSJnlFr3D-mGIHFpo80ylsaBErtueSpYS&index=14] . Why Use Promises in JavaScript?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yogesh Chavan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ultimate Guide to High Performance WordPress]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-ultimate-guide-to-high-performance-wordpress/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-ultimate-guide-to-high-performance-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T14:35:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many strategies you can do to increase the performance of your WordPress websites and other websites. In this guide, we'll show you how to identify and fix performance issues for good. This guide combines over 20 years of experience of fine-tuning servers, CDNs, and website code to deliver]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Tips to Help You Build Better Web Development Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-tips-for-better-web-dev-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-tips-for-better-web-dev-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T14:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a widely used web programming language. If you're getting into software engineering or coding in particular and you want to focus on web development, learning JavaScript is probably the best thing to do. Learning JavaScript empowers you to create dynamic and interactive web experiences. And it lets you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Methods For Improving Drupal’s Largest Contentful Paint Core Web Vital]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/methods-improving-drupal-largest-contentful-paint-core-web-vital/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/methods-improving-drupal-largest-contentful-paint-core-web-vital/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The background image used in the hero component, which is slow to load, is a very common problem with any component that uses a large image file as a background image. In this article, Mike Herchel walks you through how to tackle this common performance issue using modern techniques.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mike Herchel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Web Scraping with Python and Beautiful Soup in Spanish – Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-web-scraping-with-python-and-beautiful-soup-in-spanish-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-web-scraping-with-python-and-beautiful-soup-in-spanish-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T04:50:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If your goal is to collect data from websites automatically, web scraping may be exactly what you need. In this course, you will learn all the basics with exercises and practical projects. We published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org Spanish YouTube channel [https://www.youtube.com/freecodecampespanol] that will teach you how to use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's the Difference Between Default and Named Exports in JavaScript?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/difference-between-default-and-named-exports-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/difference-between-default-and-named-exports-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:36:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is one of the most popular programming languages among web developers. And it offers multiple ways to organize and share code between different files.  When working with modules, you might come across two common ways of exporting: Default exports and Named exports.  Understanding the difference between these]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yazdun Fadali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Microsoft Learn Student Ambassador]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-microsoft-learn-student-ambassador/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-microsoft-learn-student-ambassador/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Microsoft Learn Student Ambassadors [https://mvp.microsoft.com/studentambassadors] program is a student-focused program designed to empower students to become advocates and leaders in the tech ecosystem.  Microsoft Learn Student Ambassadors are student leaders who collaborate with Microsoft to help fellow students learn about technology and engage with various Microsoft technologies and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salim Oyinlola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn JavaScript Operators – Logical, Comparison, Ternary, and More JS Operators With Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-operators/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-operators/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T15:44:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript has many operators that you can use to perform operations on values and variables (also called operands) Based on the types of operations these JS operators perform, we can divide them up into seven groups:  1. Arithmetic Operators  2. Assignment Operators  3. Comparison Operators  4.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make AI Art with Stable Diffusion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/stable-diffusion-crash-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/stable-diffusion-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T13:35:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to make AI Art with Stable Diffusion]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lynn Zheng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Knip: An Automated Tool For Finding Unused Files, Exports, And Dependencies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/knip-automated-tool-find-unused-files-exports-dependencies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/knip-automated-tool-find-unused-files-exports-dependencies/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of the projects have at least a few unused files, exports, and dependencies lying around, often because it’s difficult knowing when one thing relies on another and scary removing something you’re not sure is in use. Lars Kappert shares a tool he’s been working on that offers a solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lars Kappert)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the WordPress Command Line Interface – WP-CLI Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-wordpress-cli/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-wordpress-cli/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T21:37:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of website development and content management, efficiency and automation are key. The WordPress Command Line Interface – or WP-CLI – is a powerful tool that can help you streamlines tasks and manage WordPress websites more effectively.  This article provides an overview of WP-CLI, focusing on its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Venturi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Meteor Effect with React and TailwindCSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-meteor-effect-with-react-and-tailwindcss/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-meteor-effect-with-react-and-tailwindcss/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T16:14:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A while ago, I saw a post on Twitter that had some fancy beams of light emanating out from behind the main image. It looked like a meteor was blazing softly behind the card, and I thought it was a really cool UI component to have in a project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manu Arora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Accessible Text Over Images: Best Practices, Techniques, And Resources (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 2 of the series, Hannah Milan reviews in detail various accessible text over images techniques for designing your web and mobile app content, including framing the image, soft-colored gradients technique, text styles and text position, solid color shapes, and use of colored backgrounds. And finally, the emphasis will once again be placed on the accessibility aspect, which needs to be “baked in” right from the start rather than being an afterthought in your design process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Hannah Milan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TCP and UDP Protocols – Explained in Plain English]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tcp-and-udp-protocols/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tcp-and-udp-protocols/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T22:19:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that it's thanks to the TCP and UDP protocols that the internet works? But what do these acronyms mean? Well, TCP stands for Transmission Control Protocol and UDP stands for User Datagram Protocol Ok, but what are they? Why are they useful? Why is it thanks to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize Your WordPress Site for Search Engine Visibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/wordpress-seo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/wordpress-seo/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T14:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital landscape, where online presence is key to success, Search Engine Optimization (SEO) [/news/tag/seo/] plays a pivotal role in driving organic traffic to your website.  Among various content management systems, WordPress is a popular choice due to its user-friendly interface and flexibility.  But having a WordPress]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Campbell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard CS50's Introduction to Artificial Intelligence with Python – Free University Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/harvard-cs50s-ai-python-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/harvard-cs50s-ai-python-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T14:36:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard University's CS50 is one of the most popular beginner computer science courses in the world. And Harvard also has versions of CS50 with different focusses, all perfect for beginners. We just released Harvard CS50's Introduction to Artificial Intelligence with Python on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. If you are new]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deliver Powerful Tech Conference Talks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tips-for-speaking-at-tech-conferences/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tips-for-speaking-at-tech-conferences/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T14:24:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wanted to share your expertise at conferences, but something inside you is holding you back?  Perhaps it's the fear of speaking in front of a large audience, the worry of forgetting your words, or the challenge of finding the perfect topic to discuss. You're not alone]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shruti Kapoor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running A Page Speed Test: Monitoring vs. Measuring]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/running-page-speed-test-monitoring-versus-measuring/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/running-page-speed-test-monitoring-versus-measuring/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What does your performance “stack” look like? There are all kinds of tools available for measuring page speed, but what data and assumptions do they use to measure performance? And speaking of *measuring* performance, there’s quite a difference between that and *monitoring* performance. Let’s dig in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Minimum Stability In Composer?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-minimum-stability-in-composer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-minimum-stability-in-composer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T17:31:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Composer is a dependency management tool for projects running on PHP. PHP frameworks like Laravel, Symfony, and CodeIgniter use Composer to manage libraries and packages. In this tutorial, you’ll learn the following:  * Introduction to Composer.  * Minimum stability in Composer.  * Levels of stability, and the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sule-Balogun Olanrewaju Ganiu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn End-to-End Testing with Cypress for JavaScript Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-end-to-end-testing-with-cypress-for-javascript-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-end-to-end-testing-with-cypress-for-javascript-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T16:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ensuring the reliability and performance of your web applications is important. Testing is a key tool that will help with these things and more.  We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Cypress to create end-to-end tests for your JavaScript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering JavaScript Functions for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-javascript-functions-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-javascript-functions-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T16:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you new to the world of programming? Are you eager to unlock the potential of JavaScript to create more readable and maintainable code? If so, we have an excellent course for you. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you everything you need]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Your Websites and Apps – User-Friendly Deployment Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-websites-and-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-websites-and-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T14:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying your application is a key aspect of software development. Typically, having an app on your local system isn't enough – it needs to be accessible online. So choosing a suitable and user-friendly hosting and deployment plan is vital. The key to making the right decision lies in understanding the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy a Django App on Render]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploying-a-django-app-to-render/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploying-a-django-app-to-render/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T14:13:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Render is a hosting platform that helps you deploy your apps easily. Whether you're building web servers, static websites, cron jobs, or containers, this tool can help you streamline the process. If you're a developer early in your career and you need to build a compelling CV, résumé, or portfolio,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Iroegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find Good First Issues On GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-find-good-first-issues-on-github/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-find-good-first-issues-on-github/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T23:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So you may have been hearing about OpenSauced’s 100 Days of Open Source challenge [https://docs.opensauced.pizza/community/100-days-of-oss/] on X (Twitter) or from your friends in an online coding group. And maybe you want to join in but don’t know where to start.  Ooh, I know the feeling. When I first joined]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CHRISTINE T. BELZIE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a JavaScript Utility Library like Lodash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-javascript-utility-library-like-lodash/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-javascript-utility-library-like-lodash/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T21:15:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A utility library is a library that helps you streamline the implementation of common coding tasks. With it, you only need to focus on writing code that makes your project unique. One of the most popular JavaScript utility libraries is Lodash. Lodash is a JS library with over 40 million]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gideon Akinsanmi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add ESLint to Your React Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-eslint-to-your-react-project/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-eslint-to-your-react-project/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T16:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a React developer, maintaining code quality is essential for building robust and maintainable applications. Fortunately, there's a powerful tool called ESLint that can significantly improve the quality of your React projects. In this article, we will explore how ESLint works and create a sign-up button component to demonstrate its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isah Jacob</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Web APIs in Your Coding Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-apis-in-web-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-apis-in-web-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T16:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a developer, what comes to mind when you hear the word "API"? For me, I think of the word "connector", something that connects one thing to another.  So, what exactly is an API? API stands for Application Programming Interface [/news/how-apis-work/]. APIs connect different software applications, websites, and web]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juliet Ofoegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Application Performance Monitoring for Node.js Applications Using Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-monitoring-for-nodejs-applications-using-elastic/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-monitoring-for-nodejs-applications-using-elastic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T20:57:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building features is half the equation of creating a successful product.  The other half is making something scalable and maintainable. One aspect of that is the ability to monitor your services.  This is what we will learn today using the help of software provided by Elastic. This is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tamerlan Gudabayev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Friction As A Feature In Machine Learning Algorithms]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/friction-feature-machine-learning-algorithms/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/friction-feature-machine-learning-algorithms/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Friction often has a negative connotation in user experience design, but it actually has many benefits. Its best-known use case is mitigating unintended consequences in high-risk scenarios, yet it has a new place in the age of artificial intelligence. Adding strategic friction to interfaces can lead to profound efficiency gains in machine learning algorithms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maximillian Piras)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Accessible Text Over Images: Best Practices, Techniques, And Resources (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this two-part series of articles, Hannah Milan covers the best practices when using various accessible text over images techniques for designing your web and mobile app content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Hannah Milan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perform CRUD Operations – JavaScript and SQL Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-perform-crud-operations-js-and-sql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-perform-crud-operations-js-and-sql/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T20:41:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the most part, interactive website architectures will involve generating or dispensing data of one sort or another. You can certainly use HTML forms to collect user input. But the kind of web form that's described here [/news/creating-html-forms/] will only take you so far.  What we really need is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Dynamic Wordpress Site with Advanced Custom Fields and Custom Post Types]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-dynamic-wordpress-website/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-dynamic-wordpress-website/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T20:36:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, fellow WordPress enthusiasts! Today, I want to share with you an exciting journey I took while building Honeymoons.com [https://honeymoons.com]. It's a dynamic website that uses Advanced Custom Fields (ACF) [https://www.advancedcustomfields.com/] and Custom Post Types [https://developer.wordpress.org/plugins/post-types/registering-custom-post-types/] .  As a travel company specializing in dreamy honeymoon destinations, it was crucial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Campbell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETL vs ELT – Which Data Integration Technique Should You Choose?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/etl-vs-elt-which-data-integration-technique-should-you-choose/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/etl-vs-elt-which-data-integration-technique-should-you-choose/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T16:04:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, organizations are collecting large volumes of data from diverse sources. And their data teams need to harness the power of that data efficiently. Both ETL (Extract, Transform, Load) and ELT (Extract, Load, Transform) pipelines play pivotal roles in integrating data from various sources into a centralized data repository.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bala Priya C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Data Structure For Storing Non-Duplicate Items In Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-best-data-structure-for-storing-non-duplicate-items-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-best-data-structure-for-storing-non-duplicate-items-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T15:08:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're coding in Python and you need to store non-duplicate items while ensuring each item is unique, which data structure should you use?  I'd recommend the set data structure. It's an unordered collection of unique elements, meaning it cannot contain any duplicate items.  When you add elements]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Medical AI Models with TensorFlow – Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/medical-ai-models-with-tensorflow-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/medical-ai-models-with-tensorflow-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T13:20:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning is transforming many industries, including healthcare. Artificial intelligence is playing a pivotal role in saving lives and improving patient outcomes. And it is easier than you may think to start applying AI models to medical imaging. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Safe AI – Reducing Existential Risks in Machine Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/building-safe-ai-reducing-existential-risks-in-machine-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/building-safe-ai-reducing-existential-risks-in-machine-learning/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T12:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As technology advances at an unprecedented pace, so does the development of Machine Learning (ML) and Artificial Intelligence (AI) systems. These systems have grown exponentially in size, capability, and are now being deployed in critical and high-stakes environments. As with any powerful technology, safety becomes an important concern. We just]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Optimized Performance To Serve A Global Audience]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/optimize-performance-serve-global-audience/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/optimize-performance-serve-global-audience/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liran Cohen and the team at Bookaway, a travel booking service, dramatically improved their site’s performance by auditing Core Web Vitals. In this article, Liran shares his team’s process for auditing and monitoring Web Vitals and the effort it took to dramatically improve Bookaway’s performance — and the benefits that came with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Liran Cohen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a WhatsApp Dictionary Chatbot using Twilio, FastAPI, and MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-whatsapp-dictionary-chatbot-using-twilio-fast-api-and-mongodb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-whatsapp-dictionary-chatbot-using-twilio-fast-api-and-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T23:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you want to check what a word means while chatting with someone in WhatsApp. But you don't want to exit or minimize the app.  Well, how about building a WhatsApp bot that can give you the meaning of words you want to know? In this tutorial, you will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adejumo Ridwan Suleiman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp is Launching a Podcast in Chinese]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-podcast-in-chinese/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-podcast-in-chinese/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T09:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, everyone! I am Miya Liu. And I'm excited to announce the launch of the  freeCodeCamp Chinese Podcast [https://freecodecamp-in-chinese.transistor.fm/]. In this podcast, we'll bring you the inspiring learning and career development stories of developers, technical content creators, and other tech professionals We'll also share their insights into the world]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miya Liu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Got Accepted as an Author at freeCodeCamp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-i-got-accepted-as-an-author-at-freecodecamp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-i-got-accepted-as-an-author-at-freecodecamp/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T21:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Life is full of surprises. Certain actions may lead to a chain of events and you find yourself in a completely different state.  One of my biggest achievements in 2021 was to get accepted as an author at freeCodeCamp. I have been writing articles on freeCodeCamp's community publication since]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Practical Guide to Regular Expressions – Learn RegEx with Real Life Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/practical-regex-guide-with-real-life-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/practical-regex-guide-with-real-life-examples/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T20:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are Regular Expressions? Regular expressions, also known as regex, work by defining patterns that you can use to search for certain characters or words inside strings. Once you define the pattern you want to use, you can make edits, delete certain characters or words, substitute one thing for another,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tasnim Ferdous</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Two Numbers – The Machine Learning Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-two-numbers-using-machine-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-two-numbers-using-machine-learning/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T19:51:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of machine learning, we often encounter complex problems, from image recognition to natural language processing.  But let's take a step back and explore something more elementary yet equally intriguing: addition! Yes, you read that right – addition.  In this tutorial, we'll build a neural network]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 64 With Alvin Bryan: What Is A Headless CMS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/smashing-podcast-episode-64/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/smashing-podcast-episode-64/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re talking about headless content management systems. What are they, and how do they differ from more traditional systems? Drew McLellan talks to Alvin Bryan to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Server Components – How and Why You Should Use Them in Your Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-server-components/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-server-components/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T14:52:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In late 2020, the React team introduced the "Zero-Bundle-Size React Server Components" concept. Since then, the React developer community has been experimenting with and learning how to apply this forward-looking approach. React has changed how we think about building user interfaces. And the new model using React Server Components is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS And Accessibility: Inclusion Through User Choice]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/css-accessibility-inclusion-user-choice/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/css-accessibility-inclusion-user-choice/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Carie Fisher outlines which CSS media features are available for detecting user preferences and how they are used to design and build more inclusive user experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carie Fisher)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage State in Your Applications – useState() vs Redux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/usestate-vs-redux-state-management/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/usestate-vs-redux-state-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T21:35:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State management is crucial for handling an application's data, how users interact with it, and how different parts of the app behave.  And it's not something you'll use only in React.js [https://react.dev/], but also in other popular tools like Angular.js, [https://angularjs.org/] Vue.js, [https://vuejs.org/] and Next.j [https://nextjs.org/]s. There are two]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Calculate Definite and Indefinite Integrals in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/calculate-definite-indefinite-integrals-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/calculate-definite-indefinite-integrals-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T18:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python is a versatile programming language that offers libraries and tools for scientific computing and mathematical calculations.  Many essential mathematical operations frequently involve definite and indefinite integrals. In this article, we will explore how to perform these calculations using Python. How to Calculate Single Variable Definite Integrals Install SciPy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roy Chng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Bridge the Gap Between Development and Production with Valid HTTPS Certificates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/development-production-parity-with-valid-https-certs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/development-production-parity-with-valid-https-certs/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T17:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the core principles of software development involves maintaining development/production parity. But this is not always the case for developers working on localhost. To review, dev/prod parity refers to keeping development, staging, and production environments as similar as possible to avoid encountering undetected bugs. A lack of dev/prod parity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Linda Ikechukwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Living In The Moment (August 2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T09:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New month, new wallpapers! In this post, you’ll find unique and inspiring wallpapers for August 2023. Created with love by the community for the community, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>