<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-08-15T00:52:37.778Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's the Difference Between Default and Named Exports in JavaScript?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/difference-between-default-and-named-exports-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/difference-between-default-and-named-exports-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:36:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is one of the most popular programming languages among web developers. And it offers multiple ways to organize and share code between different files.  When working with modules, you might come across two common ways of exporting: Default exports and Named exports.  Understanding the difference between these]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yazdun Fadali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Microsoft Learn Student Ambassador]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-microsoft-learn-student-ambassador/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-microsoft-learn-student-ambassador/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Microsoft Learn Student Ambassadors [https://mvp.microsoft.com/studentambassadors] program is a student-focused program designed to empower students to become advocates and leaders in the tech ecosystem.  Microsoft Learn Student Ambassadors are student leaders who collaborate with Microsoft to help fellow students learn about technology and engage with various Microsoft technologies and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salim Oyinlola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn JavaScript Operators – Logical, Comparison, Ternary, and More JS Operators With Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-operators/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-operators/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T15:44:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript has many operators that you can use to perform operations on values and variables (also called operands) Based on the types of operations these JS operators perform, we can divide them up into seven groups:  1. Arithmetic Operators  2. Assignment Operators  3. Comparison Operators  4.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make AI Art with Stable Diffusion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/stable-diffusion-crash-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/stable-diffusion-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T13:35:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to make AI Art with Stable Diffusion]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lynn Zheng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Knip: An Automated Tool For Finding Unused Files, Exports, And Dependencies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/knip-automated-tool-find-unused-files-exports-dependencies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/knip-automated-tool-find-unused-files-exports-dependencies/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of the projects have at least a few unused files, exports, and dependencies lying around, often because it’s difficult knowing when one thing relies on another and scary removing something you’re not sure is in use. Lars Kappert shares a tool he’s been working on that offers a solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lars Kappert)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the WordPress Command Line Interface – WP-CLI Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-wordpress-cli/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-wordpress-cli/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T21:37:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of website development and content management, efficiency and automation are key. The WordPress Command Line Interface – or WP-CLI – is a powerful tool that can help you streamlines tasks and manage WordPress websites more effectively.  This article provides an overview of WP-CLI, focusing on its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Venturi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Meteor Effect with React and TailwindCSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-meteor-effect-with-react-and-tailwindcss/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-meteor-effect-with-react-and-tailwindcss/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T16:14:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A while ago, I saw a post on Twitter that had some fancy beams of light emanating out from behind the main image. It looked like a meteor was blazing softly behind the card, and I thought it was a really cool UI component to have in a project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manu Arora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Accessible Text Over Images: Best Practices, Techniques, And Resources (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 2 of the series, Hannah Milan reviews in detail various accessible text over images techniques for designing your web and mobile app content, including framing the image, soft-colored gradients technique, text styles and text position, solid color shapes, and use of colored backgrounds. And finally, the emphasis will once again be placed on the accessibility aspect, which needs to be “baked in” right from the start rather than being an afterthought in your design process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Hannah Milan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TCP and UDP Protocols – Explained in Plain English]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tcp-and-udp-protocols/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tcp-and-udp-protocols/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T22:19:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that it's thanks to the TCP and UDP protocols that the internet works? But what do these acronyms mean? Well, TCP stands for Transmission Control Protocol and UDP stands for User Datagram Protocol Ok, but what are they? Why are they useful? Why is it thanks to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize Your WordPress Site for Search Engine Visibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/wordpress-seo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/wordpress-seo/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T14:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital landscape, where online presence is key to success, Search Engine Optimization (SEO) [/news/tag/seo/] plays a pivotal role in driving organic traffic to your website.  Among various content management systems, WordPress is a popular choice due to its user-friendly interface and flexibility.  But having a WordPress]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Campbell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard CS50's Introduction to Artificial Intelligence with Python – Free University Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/harvard-cs50s-ai-python-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/harvard-cs50s-ai-python-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T14:36:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard University's CS50 is one of the most popular beginner computer science courses in the world. And Harvard also has versions of CS50 with different focusses, all perfect for beginners. We just released Harvard CS50's Introduction to Artificial Intelligence with Python on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. If you are new]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deliver Powerful Tech Conference Talks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tips-for-speaking-at-tech-conferences/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tips-for-speaking-at-tech-conferences/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T14:24:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wanted to share your expertise at conferences, but something inside you is holding you back?  Perhaps it's the fear of speaking in front of a large audience, the worry of forgetting your words, or the challenge of finding the perfect topic to discuss. You're not alone]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shruti Kapoor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running A Page Speed Test: Monitoring vs. Measuring]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/running-page-speed-test-monitoring-versus-measuring/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/running-page-speed-test-monitoring-versus-measuring/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What does your performance “stack” look like? There are all kinds of tools available for measuring page speed, but what data and assumptions do they use to measure performance? And speaking of *measuring* performance, there’s quite a difference between that and *monitoring* performance. Let’s dig in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Minimum Stability In Composer?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-minimum-stability-in-composer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-minimum-stability-in-composer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T17:31:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Composer is a dependency management tool for projects running on PHP. PHP frameworks like Laravel, Symfony, and CodeIgniter use Composer to manage libraries and packages. In this tutorial, you’ll learn the following:  * Introduction to Composer.  * Minimum stability in Composer.  * Levels of stability, and the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sule-Balogun Olanrewaju Ganiu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn End-to-End Testing with Cypress for JavaScript Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-end-to-end-testing-with-cypress-for-javascript-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-end-to-end-testing-with-cypress-for-javascript-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T16:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ensuring the reliability and performance of your web applications is important. Testing is a key tool that will help with these things and more.  We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Cypress to create end-to-end tests for your JavaScript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering JavaScript Functions for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-javascript-functions-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-javascript-functions-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T16:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you new to the world of programming? Are you eager to unlock the potential of JavaScript to create more readable and maintainable code? If so, we have an excellent course for you. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you everything you need]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Your Websites and Apps – User-Friendly Deployment Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-websites-and-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-websites-and-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T14:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying your application is a key aspect of software development. Typically, having an app on your local system isn't enough – it needs to be accessible online. So choosing a suitable and user-friendly hosting and deployment plan is vital. The key to making the right decision lies in understanding the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy a Django App on Render]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploying-a-django-app-to-render/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploying-a-django-app-to-render/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T14:13:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Render is a hosting platform that helps you deploy your apps easily. Whether you're building web servers, static websites, cron jobs, or containers, this tool can help you streamline the process. If you're a developer early in your career and you need to build a compelling CV, résumé, or portfolio,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Iroegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find Good First Issues On GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-find-good-first-issues-on-github/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-find-good-first-issues-on-github/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T23:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So you may have been hearing about OpenSauced’s 100 Days of Open Source challenge [https://docs.opensauced.pizza/community/100-days-of-oss/] on X (Twitter) or from your friends in an online coding group. And maybe you want to join in but don’t know where to start.  Ooh, I know the feeling. When I first joined]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CHRISTINE T. BELZIE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a JavaScript Utility Library like Lodash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-javascript-utility-library-like-lodash/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-javascript-utility-library-like-lodash/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T21:15:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A utility library is a library that helps you streamline the implementation of common coding tasks. With it, you only need to focus on writing code that makes your project unique. One of the most popular JavaScript utility libraries is Lodash. Lodash is a JS library with over 40 million]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gideon Akinsanmi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add ESLint to Your React Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-eslint-to-your-react-project/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-eslint-to-your-react-project/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T16:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a React developer, maintaining code quality is essential for building robust and maintainable applications. Fortunately, there's a powerful tool called ESLint that can significantly improve the quality of your React projects. In this article, we will explore how ESLint works and create a sign-up button component to demonstrate its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isah Jacob</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Web APIs in Your Coding Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-apis-in-web-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-apis-in-web-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T16:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a developer, what comes to mind when you hear the word "API"? For me, I think of the word "connector", something that connects one thing to another.  So, what exactly is an API? API stands for Application Programming Interface [/news/how-apis-work/]. APIs connect different software applications, websites, and web]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juliet Ofoegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Application Performance Monitoring for Node.js Applications Using Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-monitoring-for-nodejs-applications-using-elastic/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-monitoring-for-nodejs-applications-using-elastic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T20:57:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building features is half the equation of creating a successful product.  The other half is making something scalable and maintainable. One aspect of that is the ability to monitor your services.  This is what we will learn today using the help of software provided by Elastic. This is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tamerlan Gudabayev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Friction As A Feature In Machine Learning Algorithms]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/friction-feature-machine-learning-algorithms/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/friction-feature-machine-learning-algorithms/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Friction often has a negative connotation in user experience design, but it actually has many benefits. Its best-known use case is mitigating unintended consequences in high-risk scenarios, yet it has a new place in the age of artificial intelligence. Adding strategic friction to interfaces can lead to profound efficiency gains in machine learning algorithms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maximillian Piras)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Accessible Text Over Images: Best Practices, Techniques, And Resources (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this two-part series of articles, Hannah Milan covers the best practices when using various accessible text over images techniques for designing your web and mobile app content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Hannah Milan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perform CRUD Operations – JavaScript and SQL Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-perform-crud-operations-js-and-sql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-perform-crud-operations-js-and-sql/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T20:41:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the most part, interactive website architectures will involve generating or dispensing data of one sort or another. You can certainly use HTML forms to collect user input. But the kind of web form that's described here [/news/creating-html-forms/] will only take you so far.  What we really need is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Dynamic Wordpress Site with Advanced Custom Fields and Custom Post Types]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-dynamic-wordpress-website/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-dynamic-wordpress-website/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T20:36:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, fellow WordPress enthusiasts! Today, I want to share with you an exciting journey I took while building Honeymoons.com [https://honeymoons.com]. It's a dynamic website that uses Advanced Custom Fields (ACF) [https://www.advancedcustomfields.com/] and Custom Post Types [https://developer.wordpress.org/plugins/post-types/registering-custom-post-types/] .  As a travel company specializing in dreamy honeymoon destinations, it was crucial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Campbell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETL vs ELT – Which Data Integration Technique Should You Choose?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/etl-vs-elt-which-data-integration-technique-should-you-choose/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/etl-vs-elt-which-data-integration-technique-should-you-choose/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T16:04:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, organizations are collecting large volumes of data from diverse sources. And their data teams need to harness the power of that data efficiently. Both ETL (Extract, Transform, Load) and ELT (Extract, Load, Transform) pipelines play pivotal roles in integrating data from various sources into a centralized data repository.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bala Priya C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Data Structure For Storing Non-Duplicate Items In Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-best-data-structure-for-storing-non-duplicate-items-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-best-data-structure-for-storing-non-duplicate-items-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T15:08:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're coding in Python and you need to store non-duplicate items while ensuring each item is unique, which data structure should you use?  I'd recommend the set data structure. It's an unordered collection of unique elements, meaning it cannot contain any duplicate items.  When you add elements]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Medical AI Models with TensorFlow – Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/medical-ai-models-with-tensorflow-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/medical-ai-models-with-tensorflow-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T13:20:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning is transforming many industries, including healthcare. Artificial intelligence is playing a pivotal role in saving lives and improving patient outcomes. And it is easier than you may think to start applying AI models to medical imaging. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Safe AI – Reducing Existential Risks in Machine Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/building-safe-ai-reducing-existential-risks-in-machine-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/building-safe-ai-reducing-existential-risks-in-machine-learning/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T12:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As technology advances at an unprecedented pace, so does the development of Machine Learning (ML) and Artificial Intelligence (AI) systems. These systems have grown exponentially in size, capability, and are now being deployed in critical and high-stakes environments. As with any powerful technology, safety becomes an important concern. We just]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Optimized Performance To Serve A Global Audience]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/optimize-performance-serve-global-audience/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/optimize-performance-serve-global-audience/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liran Cohen and the team at Bookaway, a travel booking service, dramatically improved their site’s performance by auditing Core Web Vitals. In this article, Liran shares his team’s process for auditing and monitoring Web Vitals and the effort it took to dramatically improve Bookaway’s performance — and the benefits that came with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Liran Cohen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a WhatsApp Dictionary Chatbot using Twilio, FastAPI, and MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-whatsapp-dictionary-chatbot-using-twilio-fast-api-and-mongodb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-whatsapp-dictionary-chatbot-using-twilio-fast-api-and-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T23:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you want to check what a word means while chatting with someone in WhatsApp. But you don't want to exit or minimize the app.  Well, how about building a WhatsApp bot that can give you the meaning of words you want to know? In this tutorial, you will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adejumo Ridwan Suleiman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp is Launching a Podcast in Chinese]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-podcast-in-chinese/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-podcast-in-chinese/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T09:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, everyone! I am Miya Liu. And I'm excited to announce the launch of the  freeCodeCamp Chinese Podcast [https://freecodecamp-in-chinese.transistor.fm/]. In this podcast, we'll bring you the inspiring learning and career development stories of developers, technical content creators, and other tech professionals We'll also share their insights into the world]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miya Liu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Got Accepted as an Author at freeCodeCamp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-i-got-accepted-as-an-author-at-freecodecamp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-i-got-accepted-as-an-author-at-freecodecamp/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T21:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Life is full of surprises. Certain actions may lead to a chain of events and you find yourself in a completely different state.  One of my biggest achievements in 2021 was to get accepted as an author at freeCodeCamp. I have been writing articles on freeCodeCamp's community publication since]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Practical Guide to Regular Expressions – Learn RegEx with Real Life Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/practical-regex-guide-with-real-life-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/practical-regex-guide-with-real-life-examples/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T20:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are Regular Expressions? Regular expressions, also known as regex, work by defining patterns that you can use to search for certain characters or words inside strings. Once you define the pattern you want to use, you can make edits, delete certain characters or words, substitute one thing for another,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tasnim Ferdous</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Two Numbers – The Machine Learning Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-two-numbers-using-machine-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-two-numbers-using-machine-learning/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T19:51:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of machine learning, we often encounter complex problems, from image recognition to natural language processing.  But let's take a step back and explore something more elementary yet equally intriguing: addition! Yes, you read that right – addition.  In this tutorial, we'll build a neural network]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 64 With Alvin Bryan: What Is A Headless CMS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/smashing-podcast-episode-64/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/smashing-podcast-episode-64/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re talking about headless content management systems. What are they, and how do they differ from more traditional systems? Drew McLellan talks to Alvin Bryan to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Server Components – How and Why You Should Use Them in Your Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-server-components/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-server-components/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T14:52:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In late 2020, the React team introduced the "Zero-Bundle-Size React Server Components" concept. Since then, the React developer community has been experimenting with and learning how to apply this forward-looking approach. React has changed how we think about building user interfaces. And the new model using React Server Components is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS And Accessibility: Inclusion Through User Choice]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/css-accessibility-inclusion-user-choice/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/css-accessibility-inclusion-user-choice/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Carie Fisher outlines which CSS media features are available for detecting user preferences and how they are used to design and build more inclusive user experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carie Fisher)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage State in Your Applications – useState() vs Redux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/usestate-vs-redux-state-management/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/usestate-vs-redux-state-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T21:35:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State management is crucial for handling an application's data, how users interact with it, and how different parts of the app behave.  And it's not something you'll use only in React.js [https://react.dev/], but also in other popular tools like Angular.js, [https://angularjs.org/] Vue.js, [https://vuejs.org/] and Next.j [https://nextjs.org/]s. There are two]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Calculate Definite and Indefinite Integrals in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/calculate-definite-indefinite-integrals-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/calculate-definite-indefinite-integrals-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T18:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python is a versatile programming language that offers libraries and tools for scientific computing and mathematical calculations.  Many essential mathematical operations frequently involve definite and indefinite integrals. In this article, we will explore how to perform these calculations using Python. How to Calculate Single Variable Definite Integrals Install SciPy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roy Chng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Bridge the Gap Between Development and Production with Valid HTTPS Certificates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/development-production-parity-with-valid-https-certs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/development-production-parity-with-valid-https-certs/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T17:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the core principles of software development involves maintaining development/production parity. But this is not always the case for developers working on localhost. To review, dev/prod parity refers to keeping development, staging, and production environments as similar as possible to avoid encountering undetected bugs. A lack of dev/prod parity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Linda Ikechukwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Living In The Moment (August 2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T09:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New month, new wallpapers! In this post, you’ll find unique and inspiring wallpapers for August 2023. Created with love by the community for the community, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Higher-Order Components in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/higher-order-components-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/higher-order-components-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T17:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Higher-order components (HOCs) are a powerful feature of the React library. They allow you to reuse component logic across multiple components.  In React, a higher-order component is a function that takes a component as an argument and returns a new component that wraps the original component. HOCs allow you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Portfolio Site with Sanity and Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-portfolio-site-with-sanity-and-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-portfolio-site-with-sanity-and-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T16:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Knowing how to handle content is important when creating a personal website for yourself or a client.  This is because maintaining and updating a site can result in substantial expenses if you don't do it correctly. This is even more the case if you're building for someone with a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Eke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp is Launching a Podcast in Spanish]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-podcast-in-spanish/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-podcast-in-spanish/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T15:33:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! My name is Rafael Hernandez and I'm excited to announce the launch of our new podcast: El Podcast de freeCodeCamp en Español [https://freecodecamp-en-espanol.transistor.fm/].  ‌‌‌‌In this podcast, we'll dive into the stories of inspiring people in the world of technology and content creation. Our goal is to bring you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rafael D. Hernandez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Define An Array Of Colors With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/define-array-colors-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/define-array-colors-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join Temani Afif on experiment with modern CSS features to create an array of colors. The goal is to define a comma-separated list of colors and iterate through them using an index.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TypeScript Generics with Functional React Components]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typescript-generics-with-functional-react-components/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typescript-generics-with-functional-react-components/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T18:53:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will explore the powerful synergy between TypeScript generics and functional React components. Generics allow you to define flexible components that can adapt to different data structures and enforce type safety throughout your codebase. By leveraging Generics in functional components, you can create highly reusable and adaptable]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olasunkanmi Balogun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use Artificial Intelligence And Machine Learning To Summarize Chat Conversations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/artificial-intelligence-machine-learning-summarize-chat-conversations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/artificial-intelligence-machine-learning-summarize-chat-conversations/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll explore how to build a chat summarizer using the Cohere API and deploy it as a web application using Gradio.[ Cohere](https://cohere.com/) is an AI platform that provides state-of-the-art natural language processing models for a variety of tasks, including summarization. We’ll cover the steps involved in training the summarizer using sample chat conversations, interacting with the Cohere API to generate summaries, and creating a user-friendly interface using [Gradio](https://www.gradio.app/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Augmented Reality Course – Take Your First Steps into the World of AR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/take-your-first-steps-into-the-world-of-augmented-reality/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/take-your-first-steps-into-the-world-of-augmented-reality/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T13:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine transforming your surroundings with interactive digital overlays, creating new experiences, and changing the way you interact with the world around you. Welcome to the future – the future of Augmented Reality (AR). The freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel just launched a comprehensive new course that will teach you how to implement]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Next.js by Building a Custom API with MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-with-nextjs-and-appwrite-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-with-nextjs-and-appwrite-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T12:28:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're excited to announce the launch of a new course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will give you an in-depth understanding of how to build a custom API using Next.js and MongoDB. This course was created by Hitesh Choudhary. He is an an expert in the field and has]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Multiple Virtual Hosts on a Single RabbitMQ Instance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-multiple-virtual-hosts-on-one-rabbitmq-instance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-multiple-virtual-hosts-on-one-rabbitmq-instance/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T21:25:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, friends, and welcome to another tutorial. We'll be talking about RabbitMQ, a tool that is widely used as a message broker in distributed and Pub-Sub systems.  While multiple applications can share a single RabbitMQ instance, it's a great approach to configure it to have different virtual hosts for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ridwan Yusuf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Custom Animations in Flutter – A Step-by-Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/creating-custom-animations-in-flutter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/creating-custom-animations-in-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T17:44:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animations play a crucial role in enhancing user experience and making mobile apps more engaging.  Flutter, Google's UI toolkit for building natively compiled applications for mobile, web, and desktop, offers a powerful animation system that allows developers to create stunning custom animations.  In this step-by-step guide, we will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Storage Options – Block Storage vs File Storage vs Object Storage Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cloud-storage-options/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cloud-storage-options/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T17:10:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are three types of storage options offered by most cloud providers: block storage, file storage, and object storage (often referred to as BLOB or Binary Large Object).  This tutorial will explain these types of storage, their real-world use cases, and some trade-offs. What is Block Storage? Imagine you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Chatbot With the ChatGPT API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-chatbot-with-the-chatgpt-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-chatbot-with-the-chatgpt-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T15:48:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI's ChatGPT is a great tool for getting information as quickly as possible for your coding projects. Even better, you can now integrate the artificial intelligence-powered chat capability of OpenAI's models directly into your application. Recently, the OpenAI team expanded their API by giving developers access to their pretrained AI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kingsley Ubah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Regular Expressions Book – RegEx for JavaScript Developers [Full Book]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/regular-expressions-for-javascript-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/regular-expressions-for-javascript-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T15:27:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to master regular expressions and understand how they work in JavaScript, this book's for you. Regular expressions can be intimidating when you first encounter them. When I started learning to code, I gave up on regular expressions twice. While that was partly because I was intimidated by]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Faster HTML and CSS Code Using Emmet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-faster-html-and-css-using-emmet/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-faster-html-and-css-using-emmet/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T14:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emmet is an essential development tool that helps you quickly create repetitive structures like lists, tables, or ordered elements with minimal typing. It is more like a shorthand that translates to multiple lines of HTML or a CSS attribute. Emmet is built-in in many of the text editors like VS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Real-time Post Notifications to Your React Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-post-notifications-to-your-react-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-post-notifications-to-your-react-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T14:22:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I was working on an application.  That application was a Thread Clone, the newly launched social media platform. The tech stack I was using was React for the front end and Firebase for authentication, real-time database, and for file uploads. As I was building the app, I thought wouldn’t]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nishant Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Technology And The Future Of Language Translation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/modern-technology-future-language-translation/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/modern-technology-future-language-translation/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The field of language translation has never been more exciting. Explore the evolution of language translation platforms, how we got to where we are today, and what advancements we can look forward to in the coming years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adriano Raiano)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FastAPI Tutorial – How to Develop, Test, and Deploy APIs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fastapi-quickstart/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fastapi-quickstart/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T20:54:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the world of FastAPI, a sleek and high-performance web framework for constructing Python APIs. Don't worry if you're new to API programming – we'll start at the beginning.  An API (Application Programming Interface) connects several software programs allowing them to converse and exchange information. APIs are essential]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atharva Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Node.js? Server-Side JavaScript Development Basics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/node-js-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/node-js-basics/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T18:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js is a powerful runtime environment for executing JavaScript code outside  of a web browser. It brings the JavaScript language to the server-side, enabling developers to build scalable, high-performance, and event-driven applications. Let's discover how Node.js code works, and how that code can be integrated within your JavaScript and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is DNS? Basics for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-dns-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-dns-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T18:07:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you access a website like www.google.com [https://www.google.com/], would it surprise you to learn that the URL isn't really the website address?  There is some work "under the hood" to ensure that, when you type in a human friendly name like Google, it takes you to the website you're]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kealan Parr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Google Sheets – A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-sheets-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-sheets-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T17:53:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Sheets is an online spreadsheet app with real-time collaboration features. It's like Microsoft Excel for regular people. 🙌 gif of guy saying aren't ordinary people adorableAnd, these days, it's actually giving Excel a run for its money. It's picked up a lot of features and processing power over the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recreating YouTube’s Ambient Mode Glow Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/recreating-youtube-ambient-mode-glow-effect/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/recreating-youtube-ambient-mode-glow-effect/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adrian deconstructs YouTube’s “Ambient Mode” feature and how HTML `` and the `requestAnimationFrame` function are used to create the glowing effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy a Next.js App with Custom Domain on AWS Using SST]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-a-next-js-app-with-custom-domain-on-aws-using-sst/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-a-next-js-app-with-custom-domain-on-aws-using-sst/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T07:18:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless architectures have transformed the way we build and deploy applications in the cloud, bringing in more efficiency and scalability. In this article, we'll dive into the Serverless Stack Toolkit (SST), a framework for building serverless applications. We'll deploy a Next.js application and set up a custom domain, all without]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art Of Looking Back: A Critical Reflection For Individual Contributors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/critical-reflection-individual-contributors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/critical-reflection-individual-contributors/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the importance of critical reflective practice and challenge some beliefs about reflection and its role in our work and growth. Kristian Mikhel suggests a critical reflective routine for individual contributors and gives some practical recommendations that will make reflection meaningful and actionable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kristian Mikhel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Integrate ChatGPT with Google Sheets Using Google Apps Script]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-chat-gpt-formulas-in-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-chat-gpt-formulas-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to this tutorial on how to integrate ChatGPT with Google Spreadsheets using the GPT API and Google Apps Script. We will create two custom formulas, GPT_SUMMARY and GPT_SIMPLIFY. You can use GPT_SUMMARY to summarize a large passage or text into a few bullet points for easy reading. And you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nibesh Khadka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Full Stack Development with Next.js and Supabase by Building a Twitter Clone.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-full-stack-development-with-next-js-and-supabase-by-building-a-twitter-clone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-full-stack-development-with-next-js-and-supabase-by-building-a-twitter-clone/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T15:49:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Turn this: Into this: We just launched a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you master full stack development with Next.js 13 and Supabase by building a Twitter clone. The course also uses Tailwind CSS and TypeScript. This intensive course has been expertly developed by Pranjal Soni,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Join the #100daysofOSS Challenge and Embrace the Power of Open Source]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/100-days-of-oss-challenge/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/100-days-of-oss-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T20:25:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I made my first pull request (PR) to an open-source project six years ago. Technically, it was pre-work for a bootcamp that I would eventually complete, but it started my journey into open source.  It wasn’t until a couple of years later, after completing my bootcamp, that I saw]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BekahHW</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Project – How to Convert Multiple Images into a Single PDF File]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/convert-multiple-images-into-a-single-pdf-file-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/convert-multiple-images-into-a-single-pdf-file-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T20:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating projects is the best way to learn a programming language. It is fun and it's a creative way to learn new things.  Whenever I try to learn a new language or new technology, I try to create a project, whether it's a small byte-sized or big project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manipulate HTML and CSS Using JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manipulate-html-and-css-using-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manipulate-html-and-css-using-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T18:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, the HTML DOM (Document Object Model) represents the structure and content of an HTML document as a tree-like structure. In it, each element, attribute, and text node in the HTML document is represented as a node in the DOM tree.  In this article you're going to learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Information Architecture? How to Create Userflows and Sitemaps for UX Design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/information-architecture-userflow-sitemap/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/information-architecture-userflow-sitemap/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T20:40:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At some point in your design career, you may hear about Information Architecture (or IA). You might even have to create a userflow or sitemap. Now, this article aims to help you go back to the basics and remind you of the meaning and importance of IA. So if you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why are two similar objects not equal in JavaScript?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-are-two-similar-objects-not-equal-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-are-two-similar-objects-not-equal-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T18:53:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, two objects cannot be equal even though they are similar. Why is that the case? 🤔 Let's understand why. For example: const obj1 = {   name: "Dillion" } const obj2 = {   name: "Dillion" } console.log(obj1 === obj2) // false As you can see]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Python App Design with ttkbootstrap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/modern-python-app-design-with-ttkbootstrap/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/modern-python-app-design-with-ttkbootstrap/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T18:39:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking to add a touch of modernity to your Python apps? Do you want to master Tkinter and ttkbootstrap for a sleek, contemporary design? freeCodeCamp.org has just launched a brand new video course on YouTube that will teach you how to easily implement modern designs in your Tkinter-based]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLI Shells – A Brief History of Human-Computer Interfaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/shells-a-history-of-human-computer-interfaces/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/shells-a-history-of-human-computer-interfaces/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T16:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A computer is basically a piece of electronic circuitry that performs tasks as instructed by its users. But for a human to interact with this hardware, they must really know and understand how it works. The person must also know the order in which to give the computer various tasks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidiadi Anyanwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Measure Django Code Quality Using SonarQube, Pytest, and Coverage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-measure-django-code-quality-using-sonarqube-pytest-and-coverage/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-measure-django-code-quality-using-sonarqube-pytest-and-coverage/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T16:36:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings, fellow coding enthusiasts! We're going to dive deep into the realm of Django code quality assessment. In this comprehensive guide, I'll walk you through an in-depth approach to measuring the code quality of your Django-based application. By the end of this tutorial, you will be able to:  1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ridwan Yusuf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Dockerize a React Application – A Step by Step Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-dockerize-a-react-application/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-dockerize-a-react-application/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T14:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Picture this: you have developed an application that is ready to be deployed. You have worked really hard on it, so you want to make sure it gets deployed seamlessly and the final product is both fast and reliable. Enter images and containers. Images and containers help you package your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Age-Inclusive Products: Guidelines And Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/designing-age-inclusive-products-guidelines-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/designing-age-inclusive-products-guidelines-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With an estimated one in every eight individuals worldwide surpassing the age of 60, who are actively adopting online shopping, the need for user-friendly interfaces tailored to their needs becomes apparent. Explore the guidelines to help you design a more inclusive product for all, particularly for an older audience and your future self as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michal Halperin Ben Zvi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Stargazers and Forkers Cards to Your GitHub Repository]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-stargzers-and-forkers-to-your-github-repository/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-stargzers-and-forkers-to-your-github-repository/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T22:39:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a common practice for open source projects to welcome newcomers and help get them interested in contributing more. And there are various ways to do this. Two popular examples are using stargazers cards and forkers cards. Stargazers highlight the GitHub users' profiles who starred the repository. And forkers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Error-Free HTML Forms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-error-free-html-forms/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-error-free-html-forms/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T18:47:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After taking some coding courses, I decided that it was time to put my knowledge to good use and do a coding project.  Like most newbies, I went to Google to find some inspiration. As I scrolled through the internet, I stumbled upon Skillcrush’s list of HTML and CSS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CHRISTINE T. BELZIE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are BNF and EBNF in Programming?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-bnf-and-ebnf/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-bnf-and-ebnf/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T17:26:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As programmers, we communicate with computers through many languages: Python, JavaScript, SQL, C... you name it. But do you know how the creators of these languages precisely describe their syntax to us, leaving no room for doubt? They could've relied on plain English, but that would not be a good]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Biswas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Configure Visual Studio Code for Python Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-configure-visual-studio-code-for-python-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-configure-visual-studio-code-for-python-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T17:13:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code is one of the most versatile code editors out there. Even though it's a code editor, the sheer extensibility of the program makes it almost as capable as some of the JetBrains products out there. In this article, I'll walk you through the entire process of configuring]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farhan Hasin Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is NodeJS? The JavaScript Engine and Runtime Explained for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-node-js-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-node-js-explained/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T14:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every year another something JS enters the development sphere. With names such as VueJS, NextJS, and AngularJS, you may be under the impression that NodeJS is a JavaScript framework. Or you've heard that NodeJS is a language. But neither of those statements is accurate. To define NodeJS, we will take]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon &amp;quot;Woz&amp;quot; Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>