<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-11-03T00:55:47.810Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Helper Functions in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/helper-functions-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/helper-functions-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T20:11:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Helper functions in React.js are like your trusty assistants, and they play a crucial role in simplifying complex tasks. When these functions are well-structured, they make your code easier to read, maintain, and reuse.  In this article, we'll explore the significance of helper functions in React.js projects. We'll also]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adeeko Tobiloba Israel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Web Development with This Free 20-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-web-development-with-this-free-20-hour-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-web-development-with-this-free-20-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T17:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a complete beginner interested in learning web development? Look no further! We just published a comprehensive course about web development with HTML and CSS on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This course is thoughtfully designed and taught by Aakash N S, the CEO and co-founder of Jovian, a platform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Search Of The Ideal Privacy Icon]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/search-ideal-privacy-icon/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/search-ideal-privacy-icon/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Icons are capable of enhancing the content that surrounds them, but they have to be self-explanatory for that to happen. We have icons for things we like (a thumbs up), things we can share (a box topped with an up arrow), and even for protection against malicious online attacks (a shield), but what are the options we have for representing “privacy”?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Sam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Accessibility Tips for Developers – A11y Principles Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-accessibility-for-devs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-accessibility-for-devs/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T14:17:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Delete Check Send Add]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adeola Ajiboso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn to Code & Get a Developer Job [Full Book]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-code-book/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-code-book/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T23:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to learn to code and get a job as a developer, you're in the right place. This book will show you how. And yes this is the full book – for free – right here on this page of freeCodeCamp. Update October 20, 2023: I've recorded a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Cypress for End-to-End Testing Your React Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cypress-for-end-to-end-testing-react-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cypress-for-end-to-end-testing-react-apps/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T22:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is a popular framework for building web applications. It's is one of the best options for frontend engineering because of its declarative approach to user interface design and component-based architecture.  But it can be difficult to make sure your React application functions as intended in various different scenarios.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okosa Leonard Onyekachukwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create and Deploy IaC by Chatting with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-and-deploy-iac-by-chatting-with-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-and-deploy-iac-by-chatting-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T13:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infrastructure as Code (IaC) is a revolutionary approach to managing and provisioning computing infrastructure. With IaC, you can automate the process of provisioning, configuring, and managing infrastructure using code and software development techniques. This approach provides a more efficient, consistent, and reliable way of managing infrastructure compared to traditional manual]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Loop Through Arrays in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/loop-through-arrays-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/loop-through-arrays-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looping through arrays in JavaScript is a fundamental concept that every JavaScript developer should understand. Whether you're a beginner or an experienced developer, understanding how to loop through an array is crucial for many programming tasks.  In this article, we'll explore the different ways to loop through an array]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Answering Common Questions About Interpreting Page Speed Reports]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/answering-questions-interpreting-page-speed-reports/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/answering-questions-interpreting-page-speed-reports/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a closer look at how various performance tools audit and report on performance metrics, such as core web vitals. Geoff Graham answers a set of common questions that pop up during performance audits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tales Of November (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T09:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November is just around the corner, and with it, a new collection of desktop wallpapers to celebrate the beginning of the month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Let’s make this November colorful!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Scrape Amazon Product Reviews Behind a Login]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-scrape-amazon-product-reviews-behind-a-login/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-scrape-amazon-product-reviews-behind-a-login/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T16:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon is the most popular e-commerce website for web scrapers, with billions of product pages being scraped every month.  It is also home to a vast database of product reviews, which can be very useful for market research and competitor monitoring.  You can extract relevant data from the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Satyam Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin and Android Development – Build a Chat App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kotlin-and-android-development-build-a-chat-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kotlin-and-android-development-build-a-chat-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T16:24:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to dive into the world of Android development using Kotlin? We just posted a 10-hour Android course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Alexandru Cristian created this course. I will help you understand how to develop with Kotlin and Android. This course will take you on a journey]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automate Data Exports and Email Reports with Python – a Step-by-Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-data-exports-email-reports-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-data-exports-email-reports-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T16:08:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's data-driven world, automation is key to streamlining tasks and saving time. In this beginner-friendly tutorial, I'll walk you through the process of automating data exports from a PostgreSQL database and sending them as an email attachment using Python.  This step-by-step guide will help you grasp the fundamentals]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Frameworks vs Custom CSS – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-frameworks-vs-custom-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-frameworks-vs-custom-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T14:51:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to styling web pages, CSS or Cascading Style Sheets is the go-to tool for web developers. CSS is what gives your website that visually appealing look and feel, from colors and fonts to layout and positioning.  But there are two distinct approaches to applying CSS: using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys: A No-Frills Explainer On The Future Of Password-Less Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/passkeys-explainer-future-password-less-authentication/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/passkeys-explainer-future-password-less-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys are beginning to make their way into popular apps, from password managers to multi-factor authenticators, but what exactly are they? As this new technology promises to make passwords a thing of the past, Neal Fennimore explains the concepts behind passkeys, demonstrates how they work, and speculates what we might expect from them in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Neal Fennimore)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Overcoming 3 Layoffs with Senior Dev Kevin Miller]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-kevin-miller-coder-conversations/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-kevin-miller-coder-conversations/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T17:22:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's podcast, I interview Kevin Miller. He's a senior developer and host of the Coder Conversations YouTube channel. Kevin studied accounting in Texas and worked overnight for 7 years at hotels, making only $11 an hour. But his knowledge of spreadsheets lead to him learning more about]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I Wish I Knew About Working In Development Right Out Of School]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/beginner-web-development-working-career/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/beginner-web-development-working-career/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Victoria Johnson began a career in front-end development upon graduating from college. Now, roughly one year later, she reflects back on the decisions she made to crack into the field and find her first full-time job. This is her story, and she’s sharing it to provide those who are just starting out with another beginner’s perspective.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victoria Johnson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Good Documentation with Docsify]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-good-documentation-with-docsify/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-good-documentation-with-docsify/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T19:21:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Documentation is critical to a successful product. Without documentation, it's more difficult for people to use your product, and it's just as important if you're running an open-source project, too. Creating a documentation site can be challenging, especially if you're not familiar with front-end development.  I have been a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Created a SQL-like Language to Run Queries on Local Git Repositories]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gql-design-and-implementation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gql-design-and-implementation/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! I'm a Software engineer who's interested in low-level programming, compilers, and tool development.  Three months ago I decided to learn the Rust programming language and build a Git client that focuses on simplicity and productivity. ‌I started to think about how I could build the Git client]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amr Hesham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Algorithmic Trading Using Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-algorithmic-trading-using-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-algorithmic-trading-using-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T12:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the realm of financial markets, algorithmic trading has revolutionized the way trades are executed, providing a systematic approach to analyzing data and making investment decisions. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to implement algorithmic trading with Python using a variety]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Actionable And Reliable Usability Questionnaire With Only 7 Items: <span style="font-variant: small-caps">Inuit</span>]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/actionable-reliable-usability-questionnaire-inuit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/actionable-reliable-usability-questionnaire-inuit/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inuit (short for “**In**terface **U**sability **I**nstrumen**t**”) is a new questionnaire you can use to assess the usability of your user interface. It has been designed to be more diagnostic than existing usability instruments like, e.g., SUS and for use with machine learning, all the while asking fewer questions than other questionnaires. This article explores how and why Inuit has been developed and why we can be sure that it actually measures usability, and reliably so.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maximilian Speicher &amp; Johanna Jagow)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Structure JSON Responses in ChatGPT with Function Calling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-json-back-from-chatgpt-with-function-calling/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-json-back-from-chatgpt-with-function-calling/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T18:09:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT's Problem With JSON Open up the ChatGPT UI [https://chat.openai.com/] and ask it for some JSON. Chances are you will get a response like you can see in the cover photo above: a JSON object presented to you in markdown format, with some text to either side explaining what the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Charlesworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn MySQL – Beginner's Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-mysql-beginners-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-mysql-beginners-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T12:43:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Databases have become an integral part of storing and managing data efficiently. MySQL, a widely used open-source relational database management system, empowers users to handle data in a structured manner, facilitating easier retrieval and manipulation of information. Understanding MySQL is vital for developers, data analysts, and anyone aspiring to delve]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fight For The Main Thread]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/speedcurve-fight-main-thread/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/speedcurve-fight-main-thread/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having access to a free reporting tool like Lighthouse in DevTools is a great start for diagnosing performance issues by identifying bottlenecks on the main thread. Even better are paid tools like [SpeedCurve](https://www.speedcurve.com/?utm_source=smashingmag&utm_medium=magazine&utm_campaign=sm7_2023&utm_id=sm7_2023&utm_term=sm7_2023) to dig deeper into the data for more targeted insights and to produce visual reports to help make a case for performance improvements for your team and other stakeholders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Host and Deploy a React App with Firebase]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-a-react-app-with-firebase/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-a-react-app-with-firebase/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T15:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a front-end developer, you may have used a free hosting platform like Vercel, Netlify, or GitHub pages to deploy your front-end projects. Personally, I typically use Vercel and Netlify. But I also like trying out different web technologies, and I've used Firebase's authentication and storage features on different projects]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juliet Ofoegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning Fundamentals Handbook – Key Concepts, Algorithms, and Python Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T14:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're planning to become a Machine Learning Engineer, Data Scientist, or you want to refresh your memory before your interviews, this handbook is for you.  In it, we'll cover the key Machine Learning algorithms you'll need to know as a Data Scientist, Machine Learning Engineer, Machine Learning Researcher,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tatev Karen Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose the Right Build Tool for Your Java Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/choose-the-right-build-tool-for-your-java-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/choose-the-right-build-tool-for-your-java-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T14:57:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of Java development, selecting the right build tool is a crucial decision. Build tools automate various tasks, making the development process smoother and more efficient.  In this article, we'll explore three popular build tools used in Java development: Maven, Gradle, and Ant. We'll discuss their features,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Swap the Values of Two Variables Without a Temporary Variable in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/swapping-values-of-two-variables-without-a-temporary-variable-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/swapping-values-of-two-variables-without-a-temporary-variable-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T14:50:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swapping the values of two variables is a common task in programming. While the most straightforward approach involves using a temporary variable, Python provides several elegant techniques to achieve the same result without the need for that extra variable.  In this tutorial, we will take a look at some]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isah Jacob</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard CS50 – Free Computer Science Course (2023 Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/harvard-university-cs50-computer-science-course-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/harvard-university-cs50-computer-science-course-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T12:43:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard University's CS50 is one of the most popular beginner computer science courses in the world. We just released the entire 26-hour CS50 course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This is the updated 2023 edition of the course. Dr. David J. Malan is widely considered to be one of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Excel as a New Developer and Beat the Dunning-Kruger Trap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-dunning-kruger-effect/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-dunning-kruger-effect/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T21:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Dunning-Kruger Effect? Hey there, fellow developers! Imagine this. You've just landed your first tech job or maybe you're fresh out of a coding boot camp/university. You're pumped, excited, and ready to show the world with everything you've got.  But wait a minute—ever heard of the Dunning-Kruger]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Ren Jie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Center Text Vertically with CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-center-text-vertically-with-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-center-text-vertically-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T19:44:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have some text inside a div, and nothing else, the div's height will match the text height. Suppose, though, you have some text and an image. Your text will be aligned at the bottom of the div, which is usually not what you want. In this article, you'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Attardi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Writing for Developers – Why You Should Have a Blog and How to Start One]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/technical-writing-for-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/technical-writing-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T17:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having a blog is a useful asset for developers. It can be a lead magnet, as well as a place where you can sell digital products you create.  It can also simply be the place where you build a loyal audience within your niche, share your knowledge and ideas,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankur Tyagi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Docker Containers Work – Explained for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-docker-containers-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-docker-containers-work/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T16:45:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A container is a lightweight, standalone, and executable software package that includes everything needed to run a piece of software. And one of the most popular tools for working with containers is Docker. Docker is both the name of the company (Docker Inc) and the software they have created which]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Removing Object Properties Tells Us About JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/removing-object-properties-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/removing-object-properties-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Removing properties from an object in JavaScript might not be the most exciting job, but there are many ways to achieve it, each revealing a fundamental aspect of how JavaScript works. Juan Diego Rodríguez explores each technique in this article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing in Python with Pytest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/testing-in-python-with-pytest/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/testing-in-python-with-pytest/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T12:50:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ensuring the reliability and functionality of your code is crucial. This is where testing comes into play, serving as a safety net that helps catch bugs and verify that your application behaves as expected. We just published a pytest course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Pytest is one of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Roundup Of WCAG 2.2 Explainers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/roundup-wcag-explainers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/roundup-wcag-explainers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WCAG 2.2 officially became a “W3C Recommended” web standard on October 5, 2023, and with it, new success criteria and changes to existing guidelines for accessible user experiences. What are the changes, and how can you conform to them? This roundup provides links to WCAG 2.2 explainers that have been published or updated since the release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Node.js on Ubuntu – Node Linux Installation Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-node-js-on-ubuntu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-node-js-on-ubuntu/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T19:29:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a web developer working on the frontend or the backend, you'll want to have Node.js installed on your system.  But if you use the typical sudo apt install nodejs command, it may install a very old version of Node which can be troublesome for you. So]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Next.js, Tailwind CSS, and MongoDB to Build a Ticketing Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-next-js-tailwind-css-and-mongodb-to-build-a-ticketing-application/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-next-js-tailwind-css-and-mongodb-to-build-a-ticketing-application/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T15:54:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to improve your skills with Next.js, TailwindCSS, and MongoDB, we have a great project for you. We just released a video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build a modern ticketing app with Next.js, App Router, Tailwind CSS, MongoDB, and other]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Choose Typefaces For Fintech Products: Best Practices Guide (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/choose-typefaces-fintech-products-best-practices-guide-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/choose-typefaces-fintech-products-best-practices-guide-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finding the right typeface is tricky as a whole. Dividing the process into steps and having the right information at hand will make this journey a design adventure full of surprises. To avoid sinking into unnecessary details, use this guide as a map for your path. Review various font paraments and learn how to apply them to your designs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Daria Karpenko)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your First Web Component]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-your-first-web-component/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-your-first-web-component/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T20:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2023, browser support for web components (also known as custom elements) is really good. There's never been a better time to start building your own custom elements. Web components, also known as custom elements, are new HTML elements that you create. These elements encapsulate some markup, style, and interactivity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Attardi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Stack Project Tutorial – Create a Recipe App Using React, Node.js and PostgreSQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-project-create-a-recipe-app-using-react-node-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-project-create-a-recipe-app-using-react-node-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T20:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this in-depth tutorial, we'll build a full stack recipe app from scratch, using React, Node.js, Postgres and the Spoonacular API. We'll cover features such as:  * Building an API server in Node  * Integrating securely with a 3rd party API  * Interacting with a Postgres database]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Blakely</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Animation Techniques – CSS vs JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-animation-css-vs-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-animation-css-vs-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T14:54:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hover me]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Front End Developer Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/front-end-developer-roadmap/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/front-end-developer-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T14:23:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every week we publish a lot of great content on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. New people sometimes wonder where to start and what order to watch the courses. Well, if you want to become a front end developer, this is where to start. We just released our front end developer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Handle Breaking Changes for API and Event Schemas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-breaking-changes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-breaking-changes/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T14:18:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several years ago while designing APIs for an ecommerce company, I discovered the importance of API versioning. So I wrote about it in a freeCodeCamp [https://www.freecodecamp.org/news] article entitled How to Version a REST API [/news/how-to-version-a-rest-api/].  Now I find myself designing event schemas for sending messages across a distributed system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Kleier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Google Analytics to your Astro Website]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-google-analytics-to-your-astro-website/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-google-analytics-to-your-astro-website/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T18:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use data insights derived from your website or app to make important decisions that'll help grow your business. This information can help you improve user experience, create effective content strategies, and so on. Google Analytics is an effective tool for tracking and analyzing traffic and events on your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Flexbox Handbook – Complete Guide with Practical Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-css-flexbox-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-css-flexbox-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T17:25:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flexbox is a useful tool for creating beautiful and responsive layouts for web pages. In this guide, you will learn everything you need to know to start using CSS Flexbox like a pro. We'll also go through loads of practice examples. This is a perfect resource for you if you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build an AI Chatbot with the MERN Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-ai-chatbot-with-the-mern-stack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-ai-chatbot-with-the-mern-stack/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T13:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chatbots are being used everywhere. And an AI chatbot is a great project to help learn the MERN Stack. We just posted a new video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create an AI chatbot with the MERN Stack. This course was created by]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Animate Along A Path In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/animate-along-path-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/animate-along-path-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS loaders and progress indicators are some of the most widely used examples in tutorials and documentation. In this article, Preethi demonstrates an approach using animated custom properties, a conic gradient, CSS `offset`, and emoji to create the illusion of a scooter racing along a donut track.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Sam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Avoid Breaking Your React Application in Production]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-avoid-breaking-your-react-app-in-production/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-avoid-breaking-your-react-app-in-production/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T23:13:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that your React application that's deployed to production can crash any time because of unhandled errors? Thankfully, React Error Boundaries are here to save the day! Whenever any type of error happens during the rendering of a component or in lifecycle methods, React displays a blank page]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yogesh Chavan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Digital Products Store with Medusa and Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-digital-products-store-with-medusa-and-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-digital-products-store-with-medusa-and-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T22:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn how to build an e-book online store using Medusa and Next.js. Throughout the course of the article, we will:  1. Utilize the Medusa Next.js Starter Template     [https://medusajs.com/nextjs-commerce/] along with the Digital Products     Recipe [https://docs.medusajs.com/recipes/digital-products] build]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Event Bubbling and Event Capturing in JavaScript – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/event-bubbling-and-event-capturing-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/event-bubbling-and-event-capturing-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T21:26:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to improve your JavaScript code, you should understand how event bubbling and event capturing work. The ability to consistently run your code when certain events happen is crucial.  In this tutorial, you’ll learn about the following topics:  * What are Events in JavaScript?  *]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kamaldeen Lawal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 66 With Ethan Marcotte: What Is A Tech Union?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/smashing-podcast-episode-66/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/smashing-podcast-episode-66/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s Smashing Podcast episode, we’re talking about Tech Unions. What part can unions play in a modern tech workplace? Drew McLellan talks to Ethan Marcotte to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Routes in Next.js 13 – Client-Side, Server-Side, and Middleware-Based Protection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/secure-routes-in-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/secure-routes-in-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T14:42:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web applications often handle sensitive data and admin functionalities that should only be accessible to authenticated users. In such cases, route protection becomes crucial for safeguarding these routes from unauthorized access.  In this tutorial, we'll explore how to protect routes in Next.js 13 using three different methods. We'll learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use a Design System – a Case Study]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-a-design-system/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-a-design-system/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T14:37:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have heard of, studied, or used a design system at some point in your coding career. But what role do design systems actually play in our projects? Why should we even bother to create or use them? In this guide, you'll be learning what design systems are, why]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Fully Animated Sidebar in React.js using Framer Motion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-fully-animated-sidebar/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-fully-animated-sidebar/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T23:49:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding smooth and professional animations to your user interfaces can be a bit tricky. In this tutorial, I'll show you how to use Framer Motion in your React apps to create beautiful animations. This guide is perfect if you're new to Framer Motion or just want to make your animations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yazdun Fadali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Tabnabbing and How to Prevent it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-tabnabbing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-tabnabbing/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T22:56:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes when you're building a website, you may need a link to open in a new tab. What you might not realize, though, is that doing so could leave your users vulnerable to malicious attacks via a practice called "tabnabbing". And while nothing is foolproof, there is a way to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juanita Washington</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Overfitting in Machine Learning?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-overfitting-machine-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-overfitting-machine-learning/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T20:21:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever performed some task without really thinking about the process involved? For example, making coffee, tying your shoes, or walking through your neighborhood.  In these types of activities, you've done these things so many times that you've mastered the process. You can be thinking about something unrelated,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MENE-EJEGI OGBEMI</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Godot Game Development for Unity Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/godot-game-development-for-unity-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/godot-game-development-for-unity-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T15:36:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of the recent controversy surrounding Unity's pricing changes, many game developers have found themselves at a crossroads. The new pricing model proposed by Unity not only shook the indie developer community but led to a significant number of developers contemplating a switch to alternative game engines. If]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Headaches: Working With Media (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/gatsby-headaches-working-media-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/gatsby-headaches-working-media-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the final part of this two-part series on solving headaches when working with media files in Gatsby projects, Juan Rodriguez demonstrates strategies and techniques for handling various types of documents, including Markdown files, PDFs, and 3D models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PostgreSQL Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/posgresql-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/posgresql-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T14:02:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the realm of databases, making the right decision about which system to adopt can make or break the fluidity and efficiency of your applications. PostgreSQL, an open-source relational database, has increasingly become the go-to choice for developers worldwide.  We just posted a full PostgreSQL course on the freeCodeCamp.org]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Choose Typefaces For Fintech Products: Our Best Practices Guide (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/choose-typefaces-fintech-products-guide-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/choose-typefaces-fintech-products-guide-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fintech products are systems that are overloaded by many types of data like numerals, texts, spreadsheets, and so on. Working with these products requires the designer to pay a high level of attention and responsibility, as he becomes a provider between user and data. Daria shares her approach to digital product typography and reviews the key points to consider when choosing typefaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Daria Karpenko)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Numbers in Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/add-numbers-in-excel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/add-numbers-in-excel/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T21:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know you can write Python code in a spreadsheet? You'd be surprised how many different ways there are to do things in Excel. Below, I'll show you 9 ways to add two or more numbers. You can skip to a certain section if you'd like to see that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Project-Based Learning to Become a Better Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/project-based-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/project-based-learning/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T18:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article you’ll learn about project-based learning – how to get started, how to get ideas for a project, and more. Tutorial hell is real, and it's a terrible place to be in. Project-based learning is the best way to grow as a developer. You’ve probably heard that piece]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathanael Adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forms in HTML – How to Build Basic Forms with HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-basic-forms-with-html/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-basic-forms-with-html/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T14:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forms are a fundamental part of web development, allowing users to input and submit data efficiently. Creating forms in HTML is a relatively straightforward process. In this article, we'll explore how to build basic forms using HTML , , and   elements. We'll also cover various input types such]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Bun, a faster Node.js alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-bun-a-faster-node-js-alternative/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-bun-a-faster-node-js-alternative/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T14:39:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript has consistently evolved, always pushing the boundaries of what developers thought possible. Now, entering the spotlight is Bun, a groundbreaking runtime that promises to take JavaScript speeds to unprecedented levels. We just published a Bun crash course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Haider Malik developed this course. Haider has]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything I Know About UX Research I First Learned From Lt. Columbo]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/ux-research-learn-from-lt-columbo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/ux-research-learn-from-lt-columbo/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working in the area of UX sometimes feels like a crime drama. Can’t believe it? Then look at these fun parallels between modern UX practices and a classical TV detective.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Slava Shestopalov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Better Java Code using Pattern Matching and Sealed Classes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/write-better-java-code-pattern-matching-sealed-classes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/write-better-java-code-pattern-matching-sealed-classes/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T15:48:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explores how you can improve your Java code quality using Pattern Matching and Sealed Classes.  Java Pattern Matching allows you to write more concise and readable code when working with complex data structures. It simplifies extracting data from data structures and performing operations on them.  Let's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sameer Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build and Deploy a Full Stack Notion Clone with Next.js, DALL-E, Vercel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-deploy-a-full-stack-notion-clone-with-next-js-dall-e-vercel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-deploy-a-full-stack-notion-clone-with-next-js-dall-e-vercel/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T14:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web development has never been more exciting. The influx of new technologies and tools is reshaping the boundaries of what developers can create. At the epicenter of this transformation is the ability to integrate diverse systems seamlessly, creating powerful web applications. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prompt Engineering for Web Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prompt-engineering-for-web-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prompt-engineering-for-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T17:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking to supercharge your web development skills? Do you want to harness the power of AI to streamline your workflow? If so, freeCodeCamp.org's YouTube channel has just the course for you! We just posted a course that will teach you how to use prompt engineering to improve your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Stunning Animations with the Vue.js Transition API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/animations-with-vuejs-transition-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/animations-with-vuejs-transition-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T15:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m easily gripped by animations and purposeful motion on the Web – so much so that I wrote a whole article [https://favourfelix.com/stories/css-and-motion-build-animations-on-the-web/] on it.  I’m also a big fan of the Vue.js framework, and I’ve been building apps with it for three years. So it was a delightful surprise]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Favour C. Felix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A High-Level Overview Of Large Language Model Concepts, Use Cases, And Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/overview-large-language-model-concepts-use-cases-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/overview-large-language-model-concepts-use-cases-tools/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discuss the concept of large language models (LLMs) and how they are implemented with a set of data to develop an application. Joas compares a collection of no-code and low-code apps designed to help you get a feel for not only how the concept works but also to get a sense of what types of models are available to train AI on different skill sets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Storage Explained – How to Use localStorage and sessionStorage in JavaScript Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-storage-localstorage-vs-sessionstorage-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-storage-localstorage-vs-sessionstorage-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T16:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web Storage is what the JavaScript API [https://codesweetly.com/application-programming-interface-api-explained]  browsers provide for storing data locally and securely within a user’s browser. Session and local storage are the two main types of web storage. They are similar to regular properties objects [https://codesweetly.com/javascript-properties-object], but they persist (do not disappear) when the webpage]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi Sofela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work with Images in HTML – A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-images-in-html/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-images-in-html/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T15:33:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images are an essential part of web development, adding visual appeal and context to your web pages.  In HTML, you can easily incorporate images to enhance the user experience. This article will guide you through the basics of working with images in HTML and help you understand images in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API Integration Patterns – The Difference between REST, RPC, GraphQL, Polling, WebSockets and WebHooks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/api-integration-patterns/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/api-integration-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T15:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[API stands for Application Programming Interface. The “I” in API is the key part that explains its purpose. The interface is what the software presents to other humans or programs, allowing them to interact with it.  A good analogy for an interface is a remote control. Imagine you have]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Headaches: Working With Media (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/gatsby-headaches-working-media-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/gatsby-headaches-working-media-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how to incorporate a variety of media formats, such as images, videos, GIFs, SVGs, and so on, in a Gatsby website. Juan Rodriguez shares what he’s learned about optimizing files for improved performance after working with different plugins and techniques.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Migrate from create-react-app to Vite using Jest and Browserslist]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-migrate-from-create-react-app-to-vite/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-migrate-from-create-react-app-to-vite/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T18:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The React team no longer recommends using create-react-app (CRA) [https://github.com/facebook/create-react-app] as a bundler to create a new React application. The team and community realized that even though CRA was a jump-starter, it lacked the flexibility needed to configure or manage large and complex applications. Nowadays, the team recommends using production-grade]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saheed Oladele</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use URLs for State Management in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-urls-for-state-management-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-urls-for-state-management-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T17:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, URLs have been synonymous with web navigation. But the tide is turning, especially with the emergence of single-page applications. In the React universe, URLs are stepping up to play a pivotal role in state management. This article will guide you through the transformative journey of URLs as state]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethics of AI and ML]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-ethics-of-ai-and-ml/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-ethics-of-ai-and-ml/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T15:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rapid ascent of Artificial Intelligence (AI) and Machine Learning (ML) into mainstream technology and its influence on various sectors of our society raises a series of profound ethical questions. It's not just about the technical ability of these systems but the ethical implications that could shape our future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross-Browser Compatibility Testing – Best Practices for Web Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cross-browser-compatibility-testing-best-practices-for-web-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cross-browser-compatibility-testing-best-practices-for-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T23:40:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine putting in a ton of work to build a web application. And then it works in the Chrome browser, but misbehaves in Mozilla, Safari, or any other browser. As a web developer, you're likely eager to create amazing web applications that reach users across the globe. But one major]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casmir Onyekani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Request Location Permissions in Jetpack Compose]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/requesting-location-permissions-in-jetpack-compose/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/requesting-location-permissions-in-jetpack-compose/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T19:28:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting a user’s location can be a bit of hassle. Over the years, the permissions required to do this and the logic associated with it have changed quite drastically.  If your application depends on getting the user’s location, you want to ensure that the user has a good experience]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Ben Rachel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build and Deploy an Ecommerce Site with Next.js, Tailwind CSS, Prisma, Vercel, and daisyUI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ecommerce-site-with-next-js-tailwind-daisyui-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ecommerce-site-with-next-js-tailwind-daisyui-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T15:36:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When learning how to build a web app it can be helpful to see how everything works together, instead of learning a lot of technologies individually. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build and deploy a full-stack e-commerce website with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Arduino Handbook – Learn Microcontrollers for Embedded Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-arduino-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-arduino-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T13:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arduino is an open-source platform that combines hardware and software in designing and building electronic projects. Arduino can be applied in a variety of projects like:  * Home automation.  * Internet of Things (IoT).  * Audio and music.  * Automated and remote controlled systems.  *]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re-Creating The Pop-Out Hover Effect With Modern CSS (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/re-creating-pop-out-hover-effect-modern-css-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/re-creating-pop-out-hover-effect-modern-css-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Re-create a fancy hover effect where an avatar pops out of a starburst pattern for the frame on hover. The idea is to apply the concepts in a new context and gain another view of how trigonometric functions can influence the way we mask elements in CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Lists – Ordered, Unordered and Definition List Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-lists-with-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-lists-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T16:01:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you're creating an article with a list of recommendations or a web page with a menu of options. How do you structure this information to make it visually appealing and easy to navigate?  This is where HTML lists come to the rescue. In this article, we'll dive into]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Standardize Your Development Environment with devcontainer.json]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/standardize-development-environment-with-devcontainers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/standardize-development-environment-with-devcontainers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T14:45:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern software development workflows are complicated, involving many tools and dependencies.  When working in a team, it's not uncommon to use several different software programs, each with its own dependencies. This can quickly become confusing, with each software requiring different configurations and management.  One solution is to use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hrittik Roy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Increase Your VS Code Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/increase-your-vs-code-productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/increase-your-vs-code-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T14:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you watched a seasoned developer work in Visual Studio Code (VS Code) and wondered how they make it look so effortless? The freeCodeCamp YouTube channel is here to help you unlock your coding superpowers with a new course we just published about increasing your productivity in VS Code. Chris]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>