<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-06-10T01:21:51.681Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Higher Order Functions in JavaScript – Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/higher-order-functions-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/higher-order-functions-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T19:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, functions are treated as first-class citizens. We can treat functions as values and assign them to another variable, pass them as arguments to another function, or even return them from another function. This ability of functions to act as first-class functions is what powers higher order functions in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soham De Roy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In-Demand Tech Skills for 2022 –Lessons Learned from Candidate Data from 191 Countries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/in-demand-tech-skills-devskiller-report/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/in-demand-tech-skills-devskiller-report/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T19:47:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A popular Chinese proverb says: “The best time to plant a tree was 20 years ago. The second best time is now.”  The same applies to acquiring new tech skills. No matter if you’re a junior developer or a seasoned software engineer, there is always something you can work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakub Kubrynski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No-Code Tools to Use for Your Next Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/no-code-tools-for-building-your-next-project/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/no-code-tools-for-building-your-next-project/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T19:38:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have recently started being active in a couple of online maker communities, and I've met a lot of talented folks who are building amazing products.  One thing that has stood out to me while engaging with these makers is that many of them are not developers – in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shayan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Type the Vertical Line | Bar Character on a Keyboard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-type-the-vertical-line-bar-character-on-a-keyboard/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-type-the-vertical-line-bar-character-on-a-keyboard/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T16:06:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We use the vertical line character, |, in various scenarios and contexts. You'll use it in mathematics and programming, in Linux, and in computer science fields to represent different things. Programmers also call this character the pipe symbol. What is the Pipe Character Used For? In Mathematics, the double pipe]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Set – How to Create a Set in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-set-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-set-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sets are defined as a collection of objects. They are an important concept in math and programming.  Programming languages provide different ways to group objects. Lists, dictionaries, and arrays are some examples of grouping objects.  Python has its own methods of creating a collection of objects. In Python,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded Rust Programming on Raspberry Pi Zero W]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/embedded-rust-programming-on-raspberry-pi-zero-w/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/embedded-rust-programming-on-raspberry-pi-zero-w/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:37:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded programming in Rust requires a whole new knowledge base. Using a Raspberry Pi Zero W, you can quickly get up and running with embedded Rust. Starting with an embedded "Hello World" equivalent, and advancing to a text-to-morse-code translator, this article will walk you through the process.  * How]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaun Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Am I on the IndieWeb yet?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=366286</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/am-i-on-the-indieweb-yet/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:32:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can’t smash the Like button hard enough for what Miriam Suzanne has to say on the challenging technical hurdles of implementing Webmentions:
The first round required several online services along with HTML & JS changes to my static site, just to verify my 
…
Am I on the IndieWeb yet? originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use fnm – Fast Node Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fnm-fast-node-manager/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fnm-fast-node-manager/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've been working with Node for a while, you will most likely discover that your projects – or one you're working on – are written for an older version of Node. That means they won't work as expected with the latest version.  In that case, a Node version]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Biswas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Horizontal vs. Vertical Scaling – How to Scale a Database]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/horizontal-vs-vertical-scaling-in-database/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/horizontal-vs-vertical-scaling-in-database/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:26:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data Scalability Data scalability refers to the ability of a database to manipulate changing demands by adding and removing data. In this way, the database grows at the same pace as the software.  Via scaling, the database can expand or contract the capacity of the system's resources to support]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Iroegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Full Stack Amazon Clone with Flutter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-amazon-clone-with-flutter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-amazon-clone-with-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T14:11:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people complain about Amazon's UI but most people realize how complex Amazon's website truly is. If you want to improve your skills as a full stack developer, creating an Amazon clone will give you practice in many different areas. We just published a 12-hour course that will teach you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future Of Frontend Build Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/06/future-frontend-build-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/06/future-frontend-build-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explores the evolution and the future of frontend tooling, presenting a new set of tools featuring a change in paradigm, platform, or both.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alexander Joseph)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inline Style in HTML – CSS Inline Styles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/inline-style-in-html/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/inline-style-in-html/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T21:24:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) is a markup language that determines how your web pages will appear. It manages the colors, fonts, and layouts of your website elements, as well as allowing you to add effects or animations to your pages. We can style an HTML file/page in three ways: external]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Error 502 Bad Gateway Meaning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/error-502-bad-gateway-meaning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/error-502-bad-gateway-meaning/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T20:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you visit a website and you get a “502 Bad Gateway” error, it means there’s an issue with the servers powering the website. On many occasions, this error is an issue with the website itself, so on your end, there’s nothing you can do to solve it. But the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python enumerate() – What is the Enumerate Function in Python?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-enumerate-what-is-the-enumerate-function-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-enumerate-what-is-the-enumerate-function-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T19:56:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The enumerate() function in Python takes in a data collection as a parameter and returns an enumerate object.  The enumerate object is returned in a key-value pair format. The key is the corresponding index of each item and the value is the items.  In this article, we'll see]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove a Directory in Linux – Delete a Folder Command]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-a-directory-in-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-a-directory-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T17:11:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're using a user interface, you can right-click on a directory and select "Delete" or "Move to Bin". But how do you do this on the terminal? I'll explain that in this article. How to Remove a Directory in Linux There are two ways to remove directories in Linux:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Any UI in Flutter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-any-ui-in-flutter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-any-ui-in-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T15:22:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to convert any user interface image, piece, or screen into Flutter [https://flutter.dev] code. This is not a tutorial on building an app. It is rather a guide that will help you implement any UI you come across into an app you already have.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Obumuneme Nwabude</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Make a QR Code Generator With a Serverless Function!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=366147</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/lets-make-a-qr-code-generator-with-a-serverless-function/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T14:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[QR codes are funny, right? We love them, then hate them, then love them again. Anyways, they’ve lately been popping up again and it got me thinking about how they’re made. There are like a gazillion QR code generators out …
Let’s Make a QR Code Generator With a Serverless Function! originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Speech Recognition in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/speech-recognition-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/speech-recognition-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T14:10:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speech recognition allows software to recognize speech within audio and convert it into text. There are many interesting use-cases for speech recognition and it is easier than you may think to add it your own applications. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify Your Color Palette With CSS Color-Mix()]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/06/simplify-color-palette-css-color-mix/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/06/simplify-color-palette-css-color-mix/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS color-mix is an experimental function that blends two colors and can be used to simplify color palettes. You can define a color palette and theme without too much effort using CSS color-mix().]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Daniel Yuschick)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Components – How to Create a Search, Filter, and Pagination Component in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-react-components/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-react-components/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T23:37:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wrote the article "How to Search and Filter Components in React" exactly one year ago. > If you're building a React app, you want your users to be able to search & get exact results. And if you're getting data from an API, they need to be able to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spruce Emmanuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add JWT Authentication in FastAPI – A Practical Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-jwt-authentication-in-fastapi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-jwt-authentication-in-fastapi/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T23:28:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FastAPI [https://fastapi.tiangolo.com/] is a modern, fast, battle tested and light-weight web development framework written in Python. Other popular options in the space are Django [https://www.djangoproject.com/], Flask [https://flask.palletsprojects.com/en/2.1.x/]and Bottle [https://bottlepy.org/docs/dev/]. And since it's new, FastAPI comes with both advantages and disadvantages. On the positive side, FastAPI implements all the modern standards,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdullah Adeel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello World in Java – Example Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hello-world-in-java-example-program/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hello-world-in-java-example-program/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T17:13:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're learning a new programming language, you'll often see the first program called a "Hello World" program. It's used in most cases as a simple program for beginners.  I will assume that you're either reading this article as a beginner to the Java programming language or you're here]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change Font with HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-change-font-with-html/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-change-font-with-html/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T16:41:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in the days of HTML4, there was a  tag you could use to change the font size, font family, and the color of a text. But with HTML5, the  tag has been deprecated. So if you want to change anything related to the font, you have to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage PostgreSQL Databases from the Command Line with psql]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manage-postgresql-with-psql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manage-postgresql-with-psql/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T15:29:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now is a great time to learn relational databases and SQL. From web development to data science, they are used everywhere.  In the Stack Overflow 2021 Survey [https://insights.stackoverflow.com/survey/2021#most-popular-technologies-database-prof] , 4 out of the top 5 database technologies used by professional developers were relational database management systems. PostgreSQL is an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gerard Hynes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Interoperable Web Components That Even Work With React]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=366222</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/building-interoperable-web-components-react/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T13:57:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Those of us who’ve been web developers more than a few years have probably written code using more than one JavaScript framework. With all the choices out there — React, Svelte, Vue, Angular, Solid — it’s all but inevitable. One …
Building Interoperable Web Components That Even Work With React originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Museums For Digital History]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/06/digital-museums-digital-history/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/06/digital-museums-digital-history/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computer technologies have simplified the process of recording historical events, technological breakthroughs, contemporary art, and everyday life. However, the notion of digital archiving can be deceptive. Often our technical footprints are carved in sand rather than stone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alexey &amp; Alexander)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Prepare for Technical Interviews – Problem-Solving Tips + Mindset Tricks to Get You Ready]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/problem-solving-and-technical-interview-prep/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/problem-solving-and-technical-interview-prep/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T22:50:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we're going to talk a bit about technical interviews. I'll share a few tips that, based on my experience, might help you go through these interviews successfully. I originally wrote this article more than a year ago, before getting my first job offer as a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Foundational Mathematics on freeCodeCamp – Interactive Math Courses Open Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-foundational-math-curriculum/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-foundational-math-curriculum/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T21:58:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to use Python to solve math problems? Then freeCodeCamp's new Foundational Math course will guide you through the essential math you need to know to prepare you for the Data Science curriculum.  You will get a math refresher with a twist. Instead of using a pencil]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Pratowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Interview Questions – Interview Prep with Answers and Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-interview-questions-and-answers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-interview-questions-and-answers/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T21:55:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is a JavaScript library for creating user interfaces. It's used in over 30,000 live websites and has over 70,000 GitHub stars.  According to the 2021 Stack Overflow developer survey [https://insights.stackoverflow.com/survey/2021#section-most-popular-technologies-web-frameworks] , React has surpassed jQuery as the most popular web framework, and holds approximately 40.14% of the market]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does a Data Analyst Do? Data Analyst Job Description]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-a-data-analyst-do-data-analyst-job-description/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-a-data-analyst-do-data-analyst-job-description/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T20:44:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We live in a digital world, and with each passing day, we create 2.5 quintillion  bytes of data. That amount of data is generated by activities like browsing the web, using social media sites and streaming platforms, and communicating via instant messaging applications with friends and family. These are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does K8s Mean? How to Set Up Kubernetes and Manage Clusters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-k8s-mean-kubernetes-setup-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-k8s-mean-kubernetes-setup-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might've seen the term k8s in different sources, and wondered what it means. Well, it means Kubernetes. The abbreviation consists of:  * "k" which is the first letter of Kubernetes,  * "8" which is the number of letters between the first and the last in the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sigl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Checkout – How to Checkout a File from Another Branch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-checkout-file-from-another-branch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-checkout-file-from-another-branch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:36:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While you're working on a repository in Git, you might need to checkout a specific file from another branch. Luckily, Git offers many possible ways to do this task quickly. One of the easiest solutions is to use the git checkout command with the specified file as an argument. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Mouskhelichvili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux cp Command – How to Copy Files in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-linux-cp-command-how-to-copy-files-in-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-linux-cp-command-how-to-copy-files-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a couple different ways to copy and paste content when you're working on your computer. If you spend more time in the user interface of your device, you'll probably use your mouse to do this. You can copy files by right-clicking on the file and selecting "Copy", then]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Insert a Checkbox in Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-insert-a-checkbox-in-excel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-insert-a-checkbox-in-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T15:53:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Excel is a dynamic data analysis tool you can use to do virtually anything. From charting, graphing, and financial analysis to interactive forms and to-do lists, it's got you covered. If you want to use Excel to make a To-do list, an interactive form, or a printable form, then]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crow's Foot Notation – Relationship Symbols And How to Read Diagrams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crows-foot-notation-relationship-symbols-and-how-to-read-diagrams/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crows-foot-notation-relationship-symbols-and-how-to-read-diagrams/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T15:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Entity relationship diagrams (ERD) help us understand the connection between various "entities" that make up a system.  In software development, ERDs are mostly used in database design. This lets us create graphical representations of the entities that make up systems such as a database (you will understand this better]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Algorithms – with JavaScript Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-algorithms-with-javascript-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-algorithms-with-javascript-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T14:40:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we're going to take a look at algorithms, a key topic when it comes to computer science and software development. Algorithm is a fancy, sometimes intimidating, and often misunderstood word. It sounds like something really hard and complex, but actually it's nothing more than a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Case For Prisma In The Jamstack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/06/case-prisma-jamstack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/06/case-prisma-jamstack/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sam Poder explores how Prisma integrates with the Jamstack and why it’s a great solution for Serverless databases in JavaScript or TypeScript-based projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sam Poder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git List Remote Branches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-list-remote-branches/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-list-remote-branches/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T23:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are 4 different Git commands you can enter into your command line to list all of the remote branches of a repo. I will show you command line code examples of each of these. For all of these examples, I will use freeCodeCamp's open source repository [https://github.com/freeCodeCamp/freeCodeCamp/]. Command #1:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Please Give Me Some Space]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=366202</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/please-give-me-some-space/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T14:39:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s all kinds of ways to do that. Some more advisable and better-suited for certain situations than others, of course.
We could do it directly in HTML:
<pWe go from one line...<br<brdown a couple more.</p
But that’s …
Please Give Me Some Space originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Measuring The Performance Of Typefaces For Users (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/06/measuring-performance-typefaces-users-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/06/measuring-performance-typefaces-users-part1/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the first part of this article, written especially for typeface designers and typographers. See how typefaces work, how to test them, and other broader typographic issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Thomas Bohm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Tutorial – How to Setup PHP and XAMPP for Your Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-started-with-php/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-started-with-php/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello and welcome to this tutorial, everyone. Today, we'll look at how you can set up and use PHP in a project.  But before we get started, we'll need to understand what PHP is all about. What is PHP? PHP is an abbreviation or acronym for "Hypertext Preprocessor." It's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoro Emmanuel Nzube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Comments – How to Comment out CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-comments-how-to-comment-out-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-comments-how-to-comment-out-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T14:49:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Commenting is an integral part of any programming language, and CSS is no exception. If you have a very large project or you work in a team, then you'll need to help others understand your CSS stylesheet better by adding comments to it. Since stylesheets can get complicated and verbose]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Heroku Clone – Provision Infrastructure Programmatically]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-heroku-clone-provision-infrastructure-programmatically/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-heroku-clone-provision-infrastructure-programmatically/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T14:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heroku is a platform as a service that enables developers to build, run, and operate applications entirely in the cloud. Heroku makes it simple to do things like create virtual machines to host applications and to deploy websites. Some of the features that Heroku offers can actually be created easily]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Group Chat App With Vanilla JS, Twilio And Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/06/build-group-chat-app-vanillajs-twilio-nodejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/06/build-group-chat-app-vanillajs-twilio-nodejs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn how to create a group chat app. You will build a backend app using Node.js that will make group chats, authorize chat participants, and maintain sessions for them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is an SVG File?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-an-svg-file/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-an-svg-file/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T16:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SVG stands for scalable vector graphics. It's a web-friendly vector-based file format used to render two-dimensional images on the internet. You can identify SVG files by their extension – .svg. Unlike other popular image formats like PNG, JPEG, and JPG – which store image information in form of pixels because]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Indent HTML Code – And Why it's Important]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-indent-in-html-and-why-it-is-important/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-indent-in-html-and-why-it-is-important/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T15:40:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you are building out HTML files, it's really important to indent your code. But how do you do that in HTML and why is it important? In this article, I will show you how to properly indent your HTML files and explain why it is important to properly format]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Block Theme Patterns in WordPress 6.0]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365841</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-create-block-theme-patterns-in-wordpress-6-0/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T15:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Block patterns, also frequently referred to as sections, were introduced in WordPress 5.5 to allow users to build and share predefined block layouts in the pattern directory. The directory is the home of a wide range of …
How to Create Block Theme Patterns in WordPress 6.0 originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Dahal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy a Machine Learning Model as a Web App Using Gradio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-your-machine-learning-model-as-a-web-app-using-gradio/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-your-machine-learning-model-as-a-web-app-using-gradio/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T15:14:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You've built your Machine Learning model with 99% accuracy and now you are ecstatic. You are like yaaaaaaaaay! My model performed well.  Then you paused and you were like – now what?  Well first, you might have thought of uploading your code to GitHub and showing people your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ibrahim Abayomi Ogunbiyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code a Shopping Cart with JavaScript (no libraries)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-shopping-cart-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-shopping-cart-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T14:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are thousands of JavaScript libraries and frameworks. But when you are trying to improve your JavaScript skills, it can sometimes be helpful to create a project using no libraries and no frameworks. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to code]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPAs, Shared Element Transitions, and Re-Evaluating Technology]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=366175</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/spas-shared-element-transitions-and-re-evaluating-technology/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T14:12:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nolan Lawson sparked some discussion when he described a noticeable shift away from single-page applications (SPAs):
Hip new frameworks like Astro, Qwik, and Elder.js are touting their MPA [multi-page application] with “0kB JavaScript by default.” 
…
SPAs, Shared Element Transitions, and Re-Evaluating Technology originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Sink Your Website With Third Parties]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/06/dont-sink-website-third-parties/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/06/dont-sink-website-third-parties/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ken Harker explains what third-party resource requests really are and which common optimization strategies can help reduce the impact on the user experience. By carefully considering how third-party requests will fit into your website during the design stage, you’ll be able to avoid the most significant negative impacts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ken Harker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Apply to Google Summer of Code – GSoC Application Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-apply-to-google-summer-of-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-apply-to-google-summer-of-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T19:48:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have heard of Google Summer of Code [https://summerofcode.withgoogle.com]  but aren't sure how to apply, then read on. Whether you are a college student or a working professional, GSoC now is open to both. What is GSoC and How Does it Work? GSoC is a program that encourages]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jagruti Tiwari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Data Analysis?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-data-analysis/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-data-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T15:59:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data are everywhere nowadays. And with each passing year, the amount of data we are producing will only continue to increase. There is a large amount of data available, but what do we do with all that data? How is it all used? And what does all that data mean?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Square a Number in Python – Squaring Function]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-square-a-number-in-python-squaring-function/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-square-a-number-in-python-squaring-function/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T15:03:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To square a number, you multiply that number by itself. And there are multiple ways to do this in Python. You can directly multiple a number by itself (number * number) but in this article, I'll show you three ways you can do this without hardcoding both numbers. The three]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Open a Link in a New Tab – HTML target blank Attribute Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-open-a-link-in-a-new-tab/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-open-a-link-in-a-new-tab/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T14:53:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There will be times where you will want your user to click on a website link and have it open in a new browser tab. But how do you do that in HTML? In this article, I will show you how to use the target="_blank" attribute through code examples. I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Read File – How to Open, Read, and Write to Files in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-read-files-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-read-files-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T14:29:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reading and writing files is a common operation when working with any programming language. You can program your code to read data or instructions from a file and then write the data as well. This increases efficiency and reduces manual effort. Python has a well-defined methodology for opening, reading, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expand Your Horizons (June 2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What could be a better way to welcome June than with some colorful inspiration? Well, we might have something for you: wallpapers created with love by artists and designers from across the globe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 47 With Sara Soueidan: Why Does Accessibility Matter?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/smashing-podcast-episode-47/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/smashing-podcast-episode-47/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we ask why accessibility really matters and why it is so important to get it right. Smashing’s Vitaly Friedman talks in-depth to Sara Soueidan to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s That (Dev) Tool?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/whats-that-dev-tool/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/whats-that-dev-tool/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How many browser DevTools panels do you commonly use in your day-to-day web development? One? Three? Probably not that many more. In this article, Patrick Brosset shines the spotlight on a number of tools that people don’t use or even know about. Let’s dive in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Patrick Brosset)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python .split() – Splitting a String in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-split-string/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-split-string/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T20:27:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to turn a string into an array of strings using Python? One way to do this is with Python's built-in .split() method. Here's an example of how to do this in the Python command line: >>> string1 = "test your might" >>> string1.split(" "); # Output: ['test',]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lorem Ipsum Placeholder Text – Long Latin Filler Text and its History]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/lorem-ipsum-placeholder-text-latin-filler-history/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/lorem-ipsum-placeholder-text-latin-filler-history/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T13:24:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is the full Lorem Ipsum text from 55 BC: Sed ut perspiciatis, unde omnis iste natus error sit voluptatem accusantium doloremque laudantium, totam rem aperiam eaque ipsa, quae ab illo inventore veritatis et quasi architecto beatae vitae dicta sunt, explicabo.  Nemo enim ipsam voluptatem, quia voluptas sit, aspernatur]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Space – How to Add Spaces in HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-space-how-to-add-spaces/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-space-how-to-add-spaces/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T00:47:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding a space to your HTML can be deceptively difficult. And there are at least 5 of ways to go about doing this.  This tutorial will show you several examples. It will also show you how to use fancy versions of space, too. You can do all this in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ Vector – How to Initialize a Vector in a Constructor in C++]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cpp-vector-how-to-initialize-a-vector-in-a-constructor/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cpp-vector-how-to-initialize-a-vector-in-a-constructor/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T20:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with a collection of variables or data in programming, you usually store them in specific data types.  In C++, you can store them in arrays, structures, vectors, strings and so on. While these data structures have their distinctive features, we'll focus mainly on the various methods]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript For Loop – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-for-loops/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-for-loops/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T16:32:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Loops are a programming concept that we constantly encounter and implement as JavaScript developers.  And many developers are familiar with loops, but not everyone understands how they work and why or when they should use a specific type of loop. In this article, we will learn what for loops]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Chrome Extension]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-chrome-extension/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-chrome-extension/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T14:35:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A chrome extension is a software program that is designed to run within the Google Chrome web browser. Extensions can add a variety of functionality to the browser, including providing tools for web development, adding features to the browser interface, and changing the behavior of web pages. We just published]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just How Long Should Alt Text Be?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=366068</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/just-how-long-should-alt-text-be/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T14:25:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I teach a class over at the local college here in Long Beach and a majority of the content is hosted on the Canvas LMS so students can access it online. And, naturally, I want the content to be as …
Just How Long Should Alt Text Be? originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open-Source 3dicons Library: Case Study And Free Downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/3dicons-open-source-library-case-study-download/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/3dicons-open-source-library-case-study-download/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Vijay describes his learning experiences during the design stages of creating his 3dicons image library (a free library for product screens, social media posts and marketing campaigns), which you can download and use for free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vijay Verma)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Blockchain, Solidity, and Full Stack JavaScript Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-blockchain-solidity-full-stack-javascript-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-blockchain-solidity-full-stack-javascript-development/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T19:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are thousands of open jobs related to blockchain development companies like IBM, VMware, and Deloitte. We just published a 30-hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you learn skills related to blockchain, Solidity, and Web3 development. If you are interested in learning about blockchain development, this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript String.Split() Example with RegEx]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-split-example-with-regex/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-split-example-with-regex/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T18:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, you use RegEx to match patterns in characters. Combining this with the .split() string method gives you more splitting powers. The string constructor has many useful methods [https://dillionmegida.com/p/10-useful-string-methods-in-javascript/], one of which is the split() method. You use this method to split a string into an array of substrings]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beautify GitHub Profile]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=366107</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/beautify-github-profile/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T18:13:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It wasn’t long ago that Nick Sypteras showed us how to make custom badges for a GitHub repo. Well, Reza Shakeri put Beautify GitHub Profile together and it’s a huuuuuuge repo of different badges that pulls lots of examples …
Beautify GitHub Profile originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use PyScript – A Python Frontend Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pyscript-python-front-end-framework/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pyscript-python-front-end-framework/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T15:37:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python has grown in popularity immensely in recent years. It has a wide range of applications, from its most popular use in Artificial Intelligence, to Data Science, Robotics, and Scripting.  In the web development field, Python is used mainly on the backend with frameworks such as Django and Flask.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ifihanagbara Olusheye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lexical Scope in JavaScript – Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/lexical-scope-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/lexical-scope-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we are going to understand what lexical scope is by going through some helpful examples.  We will also have a brief discussion about how JavaScript compiles and executes programs.  Lastly, we will have a look at how you can use lexical scope to explain undeclared]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keyur Paralkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intermediate TypeScript and React Handbook – How to Build Strongly Typed Polymorphic Components]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-strongly-typed-polymorphic-components-with-react-and-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-strongly-typed-polymorphic-components-with-react-and-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T14:49:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone! 😎 In this detailed guide, I’ll show you how to build strongly typed Polymorphic React components with Typescript. If you prefer to read the entire guide in a single PDF document, you can download the accompanying free PDF [https://www.ohansemmanuel.com/books/how-to-build-strongly-typed-polymorphic-react-components] . You can download the eBook for free [https://www.ohansemmanuel.com/books/how-to-build-strongly-typed-polymorphic-react-components]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmanuel Ohans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cool CSS Hover Effects That Use Background Clipping, Masks, and 3D]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365946</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-hover-effects-background-masks-3d/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T14:13:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve walked through a series of posts now about interesting approaches to CSS hover effects. We started with a bunch of examples that use CSS background properties, then moved on to the text-shadow property where we technically didn’t use …
Cool CSS Hover Effects That Use Background Clipping, Masks, and 3D originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Accessible Design System Themes With CSS Color-Contrast()]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/accessible-design-system-themes-css-color-contrast/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/accessible-design-system-themes-css-color-contrast/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From working with design handoffs to supporting custom themes in a design system, the CSS `color-contrast()` function can become a cornerstone for developers by enforcing accessible UIs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Daniel Yuschik)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customizing Color Fonts on the Web]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=366077</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/customizing-color-fonts-on-the-web/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T00:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Myles C. Maxfield on the WebKit Blog published a nifty how-to for color fonts. It comes on the heels of what Ollie wrote up here on CSS-Tricks the other day, and while they cover a lot of common …
Customizing Color Fonts on the Web originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code a Framework – the  First Lines of Vue.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-a-framework-vuejs-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-a-framework-vuejs-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T21:38:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how frameworks are built? A couple of weeks ago I was writing an article and asked myself, what's the first line of code Evan You wrote to build Vue.js? Well, thanks to Git and Evan You pushing Vue's code to GitHub, I have been able to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fabio Pacific</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter Emoji – How to Use Twemoji on Your Website]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-twitter-emoji-on-your-website/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-twitter-emoji-on-your-website/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T21:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll explain what Twitter Emoji – or Twemoji – are and why you might want to use them. Why should you use Twitter Emojis? A couple of months ago, I started working on a project of mine, and I needed to allow users to select different icons]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shayan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Test React Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-test-react-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-test-react-applications/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T16:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is one of the most popular frontend JavaScript frameworks. If you want to make sure that your React apps work as intended, it is important to write comprehensive tests. We just published a React testing course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build, deploy,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use CSS Grid Layout – Grid Properties Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-css-grid-layout/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-css-grid-layout/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T15:32:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever had a problem positioning items on your web browser? Perhaps every time you try to think of a solution, you become tired and give up.  If so, stay tuned as I reveal a new method for resolving these kinds of problems with minimal or no stress.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoro Emmanuel Nzube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Promises for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-promises-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-promises-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T14:56:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, a promise is a placeholder (proxy) for the value of an ongoing operation. You typically use a promise to manage situations where you must wait for the outcome of an operation. For example, uploading files to the server and awaiting the response of an API call, or just]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spruce Emmanuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Perfect Table of Contents With HTML + CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365888</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-perfect-table-of-contents-with-html-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T14:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year, I self-published an ebook called Understanding JavaScript Promises (free for download). Even though I didn’t have any intention of turning it into a print book, enough people reached out inquiring about a print version that …
A Perfect Table of Contents With HTML + CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas C. Zakas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Weak Reference In JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/understanding-weak-reference-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/understanding-weak-reference-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Frank Joseph explains both weak and strong references in JavaScript, as well as the concept of reachability. Let’s dig in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frank Joseph)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeError: can't multiply sequence by non-int of type 'float' [SOLVED]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typeerror-cant-multiply-sequence-by-non-int-of-type-float-solved/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typeerror-cant-multiply-sequence-by-non-int-of-type-float-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T23:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When coding, you're likely to encounter errors. Error messages, in most cases, help you understand what the error is about. And understanding an error message is one of the steps in solving an error.  In this article, we'll talk about an error in Python – the "TypeError: can't multiply]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Caps in CSS - How to Uppercase Text with Style]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/all-caps-in-css-how-to-uppercase-text-with-style/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/all-caps-in-css-how-to-uppercase-text-with-style/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T21:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're designing a website or working on a project, you might want to use uppercase text for various reasons. Maybe you want to use an abbreviation or acronym, emphasize certain text, or use it for headings. There are multiple ways to uppercase text in HTML. The first way is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Code Editor with React that Compiles and Executes in 40+ Languages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-react-based-code-editor/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-react-based-code-editor/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T16:54:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An online code execution platform lets you write code in your favourite programming language and run that code on the same platform.  You can ideally see an output of the program that you've written (for example, a binary search program written in JavaScript). Today, we are going to build]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manu Arora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Round to Int – How to Round Up or Round Down to the Nearest Whole Number]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-round-numbers-up-or-down-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-round-numbers-up-or-down-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T16:52:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with float values (numbers with decimal values) in our Python program, we might want to round them up or down, or to the nearest whole number.  In this article, we'll see some built-in functionalities that let us round numbers in Python. And we'll see how to use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering SVG’s stroke-miterlimit Attribute]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365828</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/mastering-svgs-stroke-miterlimit-attribute/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T14:04:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, SVG has this stroke-miterlimit presentation attribute. You’ve probably seen it when exporting an SVG from a graphic editor program, or perhaps you find out you could remove it without noticing any change to the visual appearance.
After a good …
Mastering SVG’s stroke-miterlimit Attribute originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mariana Beldi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developing An Award-Winning Onboarding Process (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/developing-award-winning-onboarding-process-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/developing-award-winning-onboarding-process-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is a case study of how the platformOS team has researched, developed, and iteratively adjusted their onboarding processes over more than three years to eventually create the multiple award winning developer experience they provide today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kata Nagygyörgy &amp; Diana Lakatos)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Look At The CSS object-view-box Property]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365992</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/first-look-at-the-css-object-view-box-property/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T19:15:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahmad Shadeed — doing what he always does so well — provides an early look at the object-view-box property, something he describes as a native way to crop an image in the browser with CSS.
The use case? Well, …
First Look At The CSS object-view-box Property originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dialog Components: Go Native HTML or Roll Your Own?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365804</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/dialog-components-roll-your-own/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T14:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the author of a library called AgnosticUI, I’m always on the lookout for new components. And recently, I decided to dig in and start work on a new dialog (aka modal) component. That’s something many devs like to …
Dialog Components: Go Native HTML or Roll Your Own? originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rob Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Istio – How to Manage, Monitor, and Secure Microservices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-istio-manage-microservices/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-istio-manage-microservices/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T14:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three years ago, I wrote an article titled "Back to Microservices with Istio" [https://medium.com/google-cloud/back-to-microservices-with-istio-p1-827c872daa53]  for Google Cloud Community. I published it there to reach people interested in the latest technologies built on top of Kubernetes.  At that point, Istio was a niche technology. But fast-forward three years, and:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rinor Maloku</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lesser-Known And Underused CSS Features In 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/lesser-known-underused-css-features-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/lesser-known-underused-css-features-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS is constantly evolving, and some cool and useful properties either go completely unnoticed or are not talked about as much as others for some reason or another. In this article, we’ll cover a fraction of those CSS properties and selectors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Verevolf]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365971</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/verevolf/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T20:24:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zeldman:
You may not know his name, but he played a huge part in creating the web you take for granted today. And he’s back—kind of.
That would be Glenn Davis and the Verevolf site Zeldman’s talking about. The …
Verevolf originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find and Fix Security Vulnerabilities Using Snyk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-find-and-fix-security-vulnerabilities-using-snyk/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-find-and-fix-security-vulnerabilities-using-snyk/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T18:08:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will be covering an important topic, Security in Python.  We often download and install packages from PyPi but we're not sure about the vulnerabilities that might come with them.  So, in this tutorial, we will learn about an awesome tool called Snyk that helps]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Convert a Value to a Boolean in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-value-to-boolean-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-value-to-boolean-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T18:06:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A boolean is a primitive value [https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Glossary/Primitive] that represents either true or false. In Boolean contexts, JavaScript utilizes type casting [https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Glossary/Type_Conversion] to convert values to true/false. There are implicit and explicit methods to convert values into their boolean counterparts. This article provides an overview of truthy and falsy values and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie Pina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Coding Used For?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-coding-used-for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-coding-used-for/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T16:16:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you aware of the millions of lines of code behind the applications and devices you use every day? Coding is used for many different purposes - more than you may realize. In this article, I will first go over what the term 'coding' actually means. Then, I will briefly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ultimate Free Solo Blog Setup With Ghost And Gatsby]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/ultimate-free-solo-blog-setup-ghost-gatsby/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/ultimate-free-solo-blog-setup-ghost-gatsby/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will see step-by-step how you can get the best of customization with easy admin by using Ghost as a headless CMS for a Gatsby static site — everything for free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Greg Dickens)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Double VS Float in C++ – The Difference Between Floats and Doubles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/double-vs-float-in-cpp-the-difference-between-floats-and-doubles/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/double-vs-float-in-cpp-the-difference-between-floats-and-doubles/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T22:29:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In C++, there are various data types like string, int, char, bool, float, and  double. Each of these data types have specific values that can be stored in them. When working with integers, we usually store them in an int data type. But this is only useful for whole]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Symbols – HTML Icon and Entity Code List]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-symbols-html-icon-and-entity-code-list/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-symbols-html-icon-and-entity-code-list/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T15:32:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are some characters that are symbols which you don’t get access to on keyboards. In HTML, these characters are called entities and are reserved characters. For instance, there are cases when you might want to type the greater than (>) or lesser than (<) symbol while working on the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inline Image Previews with Sharp, BlurHash, and Lambda Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365784</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/inline-image-previews-with-sharp-blurhash-and-lambda-functions/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T14:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t you hate it when you load a website or web app, some content displays and then some images load — causing content to shift around? That’s called content reflow and can lead to an incredibly annoying user experience for …
Inline Image Previews with Sharp, BlurHash, and Lambda Functions originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Drum Machine with Python and Pygame]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-drum-machine-with-python-and-pygame/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-drum-machine-with-python-and-pygame/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T13:47:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A drum machine is a fun project to create to practice your Python skills. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create a drum machine project using Python and Pygame. Pete LeMaster created this course. Pete has created a bunch]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes For Front-End Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/kubernetes-front-end-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/kubernetes-front-end-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Benjamin Ajibade introduces Kubernetes to front-end engineers and explaines why Kubernetes is integral in a production-ready microservice architecture. Some key terms that are important for team collaboration will be discussed and conclude the post with a quick deployment to getting started as a beginner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Benjamin Ajibade)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Remote Work Companies for Developers in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/remote-work-companies-for-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/remote-work-companies-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T17:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finding a remote job as a developer can be tricky. You want to work for a company that recognizes the value of remote workers, and you want to be sure that the company will support and encourage your remote working style.  If you’re a developer looking for an opportunity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davis David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ Operator Example – &, or, + Operators in C++]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cpp-operator-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cpp-operator-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T15:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most programming languages have built-in functionalities that let us carry out certain operations like arithmetic, comparison, logical operations, and so on.  In this article, we'll talk about three operators in C++ – the bitwise AND (&) operator, the logical OR (||) operator, and the arithmetic + operator.  How]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minify CSS – CSS Minifying and Compression Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/minify-css-css-minifying-and-compression-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/minify-css-css-minifying-and-compression-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T15:20:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Minification is the process of reducing code size to reduce the size of your files. So how does this apply to CSS? Take a look at this code: h1 {   color: yellow; } p {   color: pink; } And the compressed version of it: h1 {]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Functions – How to Use calc(), max(), min(), and clamp()]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-functions-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-functions-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T15:11:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In CSS there are a lot of different units of measurement. You have px and percentages, vh, vw, em, rem, and others.  There will come a time when you want to get a value by combining two or more different units. CSS has a function that you can use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilenia Magoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interactive Starry Backdrop for Content]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365766</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/an-interactive-starry-backdrop-for-content/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T14:16:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was fortunate last year to get approached by Shawn Wang (swyx) about doing some work for Temporal. The idea was to cast my creative eye over what was on the site and come up with some …
An Interactive Starry Backdrop for Content originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jhey Tompkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve SQL Server Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-sql-server-performance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-sql-server-performance/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T17:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SQL server performance can be tricky. But there are a lot of things you can do to increase the speed of your queries. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to improve performance on SQL Server. Rajan Arora developed this course. Rajan]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Axios React – How to Make Get, Post, and Delete API Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/axios-react-how-to-make-get-post-and-delete-api-requests/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/axios-react-how-to-make-get-post-and-delete-api-requests/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T16:12:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Axios [https://axios-http.com/] is an HTTP client library based on promises. It makes sending asynchronous HTTP requests to REST endpoints easier and helps you perform CRUD operations. This REST endpoint/API could be an external API like the Google API, GitHub API, and so on – or it could be your own]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Break in Python – Nested For Loop Break if Condition Met Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/break-in-python-nested-for-loop-break-if-condition-met-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/break-in-python-nested-for-loop-break-if-condition-met-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T15:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Loops in programming let us execute a set of instructions/block of code continuously until a certain condition is met.  We can also use loops to iterate over a collection of data and perform a similar operation on each item in the data set. names = ["John", "Jane", "Doe"] for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving Icons for UI Elements with Typographic Alignment and Scale]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365531</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/improving-icons-for-ui-elements-with-typographic-alignment-and-scale/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T14:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Utilizing icons in user interface elements is helpful. In addition to element labeling, icons can help reinforce a user element’s intention to users. But I have to say, I notice a bit of icon misalignment while browsing the web. Even …
Improving Icons for UI Elements with Typographic Alignment and Scale originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcel Moreau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Modern Way To Create And Host A WordPress Site]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/elementor-modern-way-create-host-wordpress-site/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/elementor-modern-way-create-host-wordpress-site/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s take a closer look at how you can create your very own WordPress site up and running created and hosted with the Elementor Cloud Website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nick Babich)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 46 With Vitaly Friedman: Who Is Elliot Jay Stocks?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/smashing-podcast-episode-46/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/smashing-podcast-episode-46/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we ask how one man can go from designing websites for local bands to heading up Google Fonts Knowledge. Smashing’s Vitaly Friedman talks to Elliot Jay Stocks to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Promises – The promise.then, promise.catch and promise.finally Methods Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-promise-methods/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-promise-methods/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T18:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A promise is an object in JavaScript that will produce a value sometime in the future. This usually applies to asynchronous operations. In applications, asynchronous operations happen a lot. This can be API requests, delayed data processing, and much more. Instead of having to block code execution until the data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Arrays - How to Create an Array in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-array-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-array-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T18:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An array is a type of data structure where you can store an ordered list of elements.  In this article, I will show you 3 ways you can create an array using JavaScript.  I will also show you how to create an array from a string using the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Entry-Level Tech Jobs – Beginner IT Jobs with No Experience Required]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/entry-level-tech-job-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/entry-level-tech-job-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T17:51:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Entry-level jobs hire people with little or no experience in that job. There are plenty of entry-level tech jobs on the market these days because of the ever-growing demand for technology-savvy workers.  There are many reasons to join the tech industry such as competitive salaries, promising career paths, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Excel Absolute Reference – Cell Referencing Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/excel-absolute-reference-cell-referencing-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/excel-absolute-reference-cell-referencing-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T17:29:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Excel, you can use both absolute and relative cell referencing to make calculations. Relative referencing is the default. So, for example, whenever you extend a formula down some cells, the cells change based on the relationships of the rows and columns. What if you want each cell to lock]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Structures in JavaScript – With Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-structures-in-javascript-with-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-structures-in-javascript-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T17:16:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we're going to take a look at a key topic when it comes to computer science and software development: data structures. It's definitely a must know topic for anyone working in the software development world, but it can be hard to understand and even a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Quality Assurance Engineer – QA Engineer Career Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-quality-assurance-engineer-qa-engineer-career-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-quality-assurance-engineer-qa-engineer-career-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T15:33:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Quality Assurance (QA) Engineer is someone who tests software products throughout the whole development process. They ensure that the product meets high quality standards before releasing it to the public. But how do you become a QA Engineer? In this article, I will talk about the qualifications and process]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Backup Your Hashnode Articles to GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-backup-hashnode-articles-to-github/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-backup-hashnode-articles-to-github/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T15:21:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many developers have a personal blog on Hashnode [https://hashnode.com/], one of the most popular blogging communities for people exploring tech.  I also write on Hashnode, but recently I was thinking about whether there is any way to backup my published articles to GitHub. Fortunately, I have found an easy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should I Be A Developer? How to Pick a Career as a Programmer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/should-i-be-a-developer-programmer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/should-i-be-a-developer-programmer/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T15:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Few things are as important as picking your career path. And consequently, fewer decisions are harder to make.  It is, after all, hard to know whether or not you’ll like something that you’ve never done. If you choose a career path based on the wrong reasons, you might end]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Ciciliano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Style Variations in WordPress Block Themes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365377</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-style-variations-in-wordpress-block-themes/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T14:38:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Global styles, a feature of the block themes, is one of my favorite parts of creating block themes. The concept of global style variations in WordPress were introduced in Gutenberg 12.5 which would allow theme authors to create alternate …
Creating Style Variations in WordPress Block Themes originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Dahal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Full-Stack Single Page Application with Laravel 9, MySQL, Vue.js, Inertia, Jetstream and Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-full-stack-single-page-application-with-laravel-mysql-vue-and-docker/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-full-stack-single-page-application-with-laravel-mysql-vue-and-docker/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T13:55:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn how to build a single page application. I'll take you through the process step by step, using cutting edge technologies like Laravel 9, Jetstream, Vuejs, Inertiajs, MySQL, Tailwind CSS, and Docker. Let's get started. What you need to follow this guide: To follow along]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fabio Pacific</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rethinking Server-Timing As A Critical Monitoring Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/rethinking-server-timing-monitoring-tool/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/rethinking-server-timing-monitoring-tool/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What makes the underused `Server-Timing` header uniquely powerful among all other response headers? We’ll rethink the expectation for using it exclusively for timing and see fast solutions for hard-to-solve monitoring challenges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sean Roberts)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the JavaScript reduce and reduceRight Methods Work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-reduce-reduceright-works-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-reduce-reduceright-works-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T16:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[reduce and reduceRight are two built-in JavaScript array methods that have a bit of a steep learning curve.  But the very essence of these methods are as simple as the following arithmetic computations. Suppose we have an array of numbers: [1, 2, 3, 4] And we want to get]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Biswas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use GitHub Discussions as Your Blog's Chat System]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/github-discussions-as-chat-system/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/github-discussions-as-chat-system/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T15:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have a personal blog, you might be using a comment system to manage your blog's discussions and comments. If so, it's time to think about updating your comment system.  You can take your blog's comments to the next level with the help of GitHub Discussions. In this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rakesh Potnuru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Apache Airflow to Schedule and Manage Workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-apache-airflow-to-manage-workflows/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-apache-airflow-to-manage-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T15:11:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Airflow is an open-source workflow management system that makes it easy to write, schedule, and monitor workflows. A workflow as a sequence of operations, from start to finish. The workflows in Airflow are authored as Directed Acyclic Graphs (DAG) using standard Python programming.  You can configure when a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sameer Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cool Hover Effects That Use CSS Text Shadow]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365738</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/cool-hover-effects-that-use-css-text-shadow/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T14:43:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my last article we saw how CSS background properties allow us to create cool hover effects. This time, we will focus on the CSS text-shadow property to explore even more interesting hovers. You are probably wondering how adding shadow …
Cool Hover Effects That Use CSS Text Shadow originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Tasks: To Focus On What Matters You Must De-Focus On What Doesn’t]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/top-tasks-focus-what-matters-must-defocus-what-doesnt/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/top-tasks-focus-what-matters-must-defocus-what-doesnt/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We waste so much today. One way of focusing on what truly matters is by identifying Top Tasks for yourself. Learn how to make tough decisions by focusing on the real, quantifiable evidence that will help create a better experience for your users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Gerry McGovern)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Wordle Clone with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/building-a-wordle-game/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/building-a-wordle-game/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T21:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tantoluwa Heritage Alabi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Concatenate in Excel – How to Use the Concat Function]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/concatenate-in-excel-how-to-use-the-concat-function/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/concatenate-in-excel-how-to-use-the-concat-function/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T19:26:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Excel has many useful functions that you can use to work with your data. In this guide you will learn about the CONCAT function and how to use it. Concatenation just means to join two things together. And in Excel, you can use the CONCAT function to join data from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilenia Magoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Global Variables – How to Define a Global Variable Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-global-variables-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-global-variables-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T18:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn the basics of global variables. To begin with, you will learn how to declare variables in Python and what the term 'variable scope' actually means. Then, you will learn the differences between local and global variables and understand how to define global variables and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Neural Networks by Building a Self-Driving Car Sim Using JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/self-driving-car-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/self-driving-car-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T16:29:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Any application that can be written in JavaScript, will eventually be written in JavaScript." – Jeff Atwood It's time for you to create a self-driving car using JavaScript! We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you learn about neural networks by teaching you how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Excel Formulas – Basic Functions for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/excel-formulas-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/excel-formulas-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T15:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Excel lets you use formulas and functions to perform basic and advanced numerical calculations. You can do addition, subtraction, multiplication, division, mean, worke with strings, and many others. In Excel, the difference between a formula and a function is that a function is a predefined calculation while a formula]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A CSS Slinky in 3D? Challenge Accepted!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365706</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-css-slinky-in-3d/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:27:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Braydon Coyer recently launched a monthly CSS art challenge. He actually had reached out to me about donating a copy of my book Move Things with CSS to use as a prize for the winner of the challenge — …
A CSS Slinky in 3D? Challenge Accepted! originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jhey Tompkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use Google CrUX To Analyze And Compare The Performance Of JS Frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/google-crux-analysis-comparison-performance-javascript-frameworks/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/google-crux-analysis-comparison-performance-javascript-frameworks/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Dan Shappir analyzes the performance cost associated with various frameworks and explains the wide variety of framework and platform choices that are currently available to front-end and fullstack developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dan Shappir)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python split() – String Splitting Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-split-string-splitting-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-split-string-splitting-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T23:12:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The split() method in Python splits characters in a string into separate items in a list.  In this tutorial, we'll go over some examples to help you learn how to use the  split() method. We'll start from the syntax and then see how we can modify the list]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Modules – Complete Guide to ES Modules and Module Bundlers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-es-modules-and-module-bundlers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-es-modules-and-module-bundlers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T23:06:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modules and Module Bundlers are essential components of modern web development. But understanding how they work can quickly become overwhelming. This article will show you all you need to know about ES Modules and Module Bundlers in plain English. Table of Contents  1.  What Exactly Is a JavaScript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi Sofela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technology Trends in 2022 – Keeping Up [Full Book for Managers]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/technology-trends-in-2022-keeping-up-full-book-for-managers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/technology-trends-in-2022-keeping-up-full-book-for-managers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T23:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is based on my recently published book, Keeping Up, a quick and accessible guide to the current state of the tech industry and the big trends you can't afford to ignore.  In it, we'll cover everything from digital security, privacy, serverless platforms, the internet of things (IoT),]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting ANRs in Your Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/detect-application-not-responding-errors-in-your-application/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/detect-application-not-responding-errors-in-your-application/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T15:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there was a way to make my applications "Application not responding" error proof, I would do it.  ANRs always seem to sneak up on you when you're not expecting them. And the problem is that there's nothing you can do about them.  You might see them pop]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Ben Rachel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COLRv1 and CSS font-palette: Web Typography Gets Colorful]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365677</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/colrv1-and-css-font-palette-web-typography/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T14:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Toshi Omagari, the author of Arcade Game Typography, the world’s first multi-colored digital font was created in 1982 for a never-released video game called Insector. Multi-colored fonts, sometimes called chromatic type, are still relatively rare on the …
COLRv1 and CSS font-palette: Web Typography Gets Colorful originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Social Media App with Django]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-social-media-app-with-django/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-social-media-app-with-django/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T14:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Django is a high-level Python web framework that enables rapid development of secure and maintainable websites. We just published a 5-hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you improve your Django skills by building a social media application.  Tomi Tokko teaches this course. He has created]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>