<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-06-23T01:19:19.988Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a ChatGPT Plugin – Case Study using PodcastAPI.com and Serverless Cloudflare Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-chatgpt-plugin-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-chatgpt-plugin-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T23:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT [https://chat.openai.com/] is a highly intelligent auto-completion tool. It takes instructions or questions in natural language and provides good enough text-based outputs.  But there’s a catch — ChatGPT’s knowledge only goes up until September 2021. So, as of writing this blog post (June 2023), the model itself is not aware of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wenbin Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a Database Read-Only in MySQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-a-database-read-only-in-mysql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-a-database-read-only-in-mysql/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T22:49:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are learning MySQL, then you are likely enjoying executing different commands and checking the results afterward.  But you may be working on a project where you have modified your database to an acceptable state and you're worried about altering it by mistake. This could happen when you're]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intro to Generative AI – 10 Free Courses by Google]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/intro-to-generative-ai-10-free-courses-by-google/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/intro-to-generative-ai-10-free-courses-by-google/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T22:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you tired of all the AI talk yet? I am too, but I'm also intrigued by the technology behind it. If you'd like to dive into some of the details behind how AI actually works and take a break from the many creepy AI examples on the internet, check]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Computer Science Concepts Every Software Engineer Should Know – and How to Learn Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-every-software-engineer-should-know/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-every-software-engineer-should-know/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T22:06:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a software engineer, you may feel like you are in a bit of a rat race.  The rat race to learn the new technologies. A new frontend framework, a new database or even a new language which is a variation of another language. It's never ending and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tamerlan Gudabayev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Gnome Extensions For Developer Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-best-gnome-extensions-for-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-best-gnome-extensions-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T22:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a beginner who's using a Gnome-based distro like Ubuntu, Fedora, Arch Linux, and so on, there are tons of extensions available from the Gnome community. Gnome is an open-source Linux-based distro desktop environment (operating system) maintained by a large number of developers. Choosing the right Gnome extension(s) can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an AI Tweet Generator Using LangChain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-an-ai-tweet-generator-openai-langchain/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-an-ai-tweet-generator-openai-langchain/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T20:20:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've got a fun tutorial for you today. If you've read my previous article on building custom-knowledge chatbots using LangChain [/news/langchain-how-to-create-custom-knowledge-chatbots/], then you must be bursting with ideas of great projects you can create. Well, I want to encourage your creativity and give a concrete example of what you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Duggan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Pandas & Python for Data Analysis [Full Course]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-pandas-for-data-science/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-pandas-for-data-science/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T12:50:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pandas is an open source data analysis and manipulation tool. It is important to learn if you are interested in data science. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Pandas through interactive projects. You will develop 7 projects ranging from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Supabase, an Open-Source Firebase Alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-supabase-open-source-firebase-alternative/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-supabase-open-source-firebase-alternative/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T12:20:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supabase is an open-source Firebase alternative that is rapidly gaining popularity in the developer community. If you are looking to sharpen their backend skills, consider learning how to use Supabase. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org channel that is designed to help you master Supabase. This course was]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using AI To Detect Sentiment In Audio Files]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/ai-detect-sentiment-audio-files/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/ai-detect-sentiment-audio-files/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dive into an article where you will build an app that evaluates audio files for positive and negative sentiments. The idea is that you will create an interface for uploading an audio file, then transcribe the contents into text before analyzing the text and assigning it a positive or negative score for how the tone is perceived.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an API Proxy Gateway with AWS HTTP API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-an-api-proxy-gateway-with-aws-http-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-an-api-proxy-gateway-with-aws-http-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T16:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's fast-paced world, seamless integration between various services and systems has become ever more important. Security is also equally important while stitching these services together. So it's crucial to design applications meaningfully so that there's minimal friction between various systems.  This article focuses on the communication between a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prajwal Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a ChatBot using the GPT-4 API – Full Project-Based Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-gpt-4-api-chatbot-turorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-gpt-4-api-chatbot-turorial/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T14:07:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chatbots are transforming the way we interact online. Thanks to the OpenAI API, crafting intelligent, context-aware chatbots is now well within the reach of any budding web developer.  In this tutorial, I will teach you everything you need to know to build your own chatbot using the GPT-4 API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Offer Custom APIs to Your Users with AWS API Gateway]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-offer-custom-apis-to-your-users-aws-api-gateway/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-offer-custom-apis-to-your-users-aws-api-gateway/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T13:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of cloud computing and serverless architecture, AWS API Gateway is a powerful tool that helps you build robust, secure, and scalable APIs.  In this tutorial, I'll introduce you to API Gateway and explain the benefits of using this helpful tool. Then I'll show you how to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Simple HTML and PHP Form]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/creating-html-forms/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/creating-html-forms/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T22:17:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have a website, it's only a matter of time before you feel the irrepressible urge to gather information about your site's users.  The most direct way to do that is to ask them some questions. And, in the HTML world, the best tool for recording the answers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Hide Your Angular Properties – # vs private Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-vs-typescript-private-in-angular-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-vs-typescript-private-in-angular-explained/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T20:39:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you noticed a hash symbol showing up in Angular code samples? If not, you may see it soon. What is the purpose of the # and when should you use it? The # symbol was recently added to JavaScript to denote private class properties. Making a class variable private]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Kurata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Editing Comes To The Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/visual-editing-headless-cms/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/visual-editing-headless-cms/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visual editing is beginning to make its way into headless architecture and the early results look promising. We’ll look at a few headless CMSs that currently support visual editing in this article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Scott Gallant)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Transform Handbook – Complete Guide to CSS Transform Functions and Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-guide-to-css-transform-functions-and-properties/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-guide-to-css-transform-functions-and-properties/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T21:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS transform allows you to translate, rotate, skew, scale, or add perspective effects to HTML elements. This tutorial discusses everything you need to know to transform HTML elements like a pro. Table of Contents  1.  What is the CSS transform Property?  2.  What is the CSS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi Sofela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Headaches And How To Cure Them: i18n (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/gatsby-headaches-i18n-part-2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/gatsby-headaches-i18n-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 2 of the series concentrates on implementing internationalization (i18n) on a Gatsby website, an essential feature on any multilingual website that can be quite a bit of trouble if incorrectly implemented, creating more problems than it solves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn JavaScript for DOM Manipulation in Spanish – Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-for-dom-manipulation-in-spanish-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-for-dom-manipulation-in-spanish-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T15:12:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi! If you speak Spanish and you want to learn JavaScript for DOM manipulation, you are in the right place. In this article, you will find a brief introduction to JavaScript for DOM manipulation. You will learn why this is a very powerful tool for developing interactive web applications and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use GitHub Copilot to Become a Happier and More Productive Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/developer-productivity-with-github-copilot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/developer-productivity-with-github-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T17:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a number of AI tools for developers emerging on the market. But in my mind GitHub Copilot stands above the rest because of its usability, seamless IDE integration, and remarkable enhancements to developer productivity. Copilot offers a variety of AI tools that have radically streamlined my experience as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Kleier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Was SmashingConf In San Franciso Like?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/smashingconf-sanfrancisco2023-recap/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/smashingconf-sanfrancisco2023-recap/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One way of getting a more behind-the-scenes experience of any Smashing event is to apply as a volunteer, and Ren did just that! The SmashingConf team organized a conference in good ol’ San Francisco this year, and here’s pretty much how it went down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ren Chen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock the Mysteries of Pointers in C]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/finally-understand-pointers-in-c/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/finally-understand-pointers-in-c/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T15:14:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are few things in the programming universe that seem as daunting to beginners as pointers in C. Many new programmers shy away from tackling this essential component of the C programming language, which can leave a critical gap in their knowledge. We just posted a full course on the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Infrastructure as Code? Explained for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/infrastructure-as-code-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/infrastructure-as-code-basics/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T14:32:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infrastructure as Code (IaC) is a way of managing your infrastructure like it was code. This gives you all the benefits of using code to create your infrastructure, like version control, faster and safer infrastructure deployments across different environments, and having up to date documentation of your infrastructure. The article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Codux: The React Visual Editor That Improves Developer Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/codux-react-visual-editor-improves-developer-experience/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/codux-react-visual-editor-improves-developer-experience/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Codux](https://codux.hopp.to/smashing) is a new visual IDE brought to you by the fine folks over at[ Wix](https://www.wix.com/). It’s got a lot of low-code features that level the playing field for app development but is really designed for React developers. How so, you ask? That’s what we’re going to explore in this article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Server-Side Rendered (SSR) Svelte Apps With SvelteKit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/build-server-side-rendered-svelte-apps-sveltekit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/build-server-side-rendered-svelte-apps-sveltekit/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SvelteKit is a framework for building apps using Svelte. In this article, Sriram shows you how to build a server-side rendered (SSR) SvelteKit application and deploy it to Netlify by following this step-by-step guide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sriram Thiagarajan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Page Elements – Explained for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-page-elements/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-page-elements/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T21:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML, which stands for Hypertext Markup Language, is the standard markup language used for creating web pages and structuring their content on the World Wide Web.  HTML serves as the backbone of web development and acts as a fundamental building block for creating web-based documents. Let's take a quick]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Promises Work in JavaScript – A Comprehensive Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/guide-to-javascript-promises/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/guide-to-javascript-promises/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T16:35:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript has the ability to carry out asynchronous (or async) instructions. These instructions run in the background until they have finished processing.  Asynchronous instructions do not stop the JavaScript engine from actively accepting and processing more instructions. This is why JavaScript is non-blocking in nature. There are a few]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amazing Enyichi Agu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Power Platform Fundamentals Certification (PL-900) – Pass the Exam With This Free 4-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/microsoft-power-platform-fundamentals-certification-pl-900/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/microsoft-power-platform-fundamentals-certification-pl-900/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T14:28:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Certifications like the Microsoft Power Platform Fundamentals can help you advance in your career. You can learn everything you need to know to earn the Microsoft Power Platform Fundamentals Certification by completing this free 4-hour course that we just posted on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Andrew Brown created this course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 62 With Slava Shestopalov: What Is Design Management?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/smashing-podcast-episode-62/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/smashing-podcast-episode-62/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of The Smashing Podcast, we ask what is a design manager? What does it take and how does it relate to the role of Designer? Vitaly talks to Slava Shestopalov to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI in Google Sheets – How to Use GPT Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-in-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T22:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems to be the year of AI. And my favorite tool, Google Sheets, is not to be left out of the fun. 🎉 Coefficient [https://coefficient.io/gpt-google-sheets] produced a Google sheets extension with the ability to use OpenAI's GPT models from within a spreadsheet. It’s called GPT Copilot and it’s available]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use MySQL Stored Procedures to Simplify Database Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-simplify-database-operations-using-mysql-stored-procedures/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-simplify-database-operations-using-mysql-stored-procedures/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T22:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the realm of database management, MySQL has emerged as one of the most popular and reliable choices.  MySQL not only offers robust data storage capabilities but also provides a powerful feature called "procedures" that allows developers to streamline complex database operations.  In this tutorial, we will delve]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Upgrade Your React Skills with Three Helpful Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/upgrade-your-react-skills/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/upgrade-your-react-skills/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T21:12:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its announcement in 2013, React.js continues to be one of the most widely used JavaScript tools, thanks to its unmatched versatility and efficiency.  Backed by its component-based architecture and virtual DOM implementation, React.js excels in building modern and dynamic web applications. It enables developers to create reusable UI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moyosore J Olaojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Streamline Your File Upload Process in Express.js with Multer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/simplify-your-file-upload-process-in-express-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/simplify-your-file-upload-process-in-express-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T21:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[File uploading is a common requirement in web development projects. But handling file uploads in Node.js can be complex and time-consuming. That's where Multer comes in.  Multer is a powerful middleware for Node.js that simplifies the file upload process by handling multipart/form-data requests. In this tutorial, you will learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelvin Moses</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve Your Technical Writing Skills by Contributing to Open Source Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-tech-writing-skills-by-contributing-to-open-source/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-tech-writing-skills-by-contributing-to-open-source/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T18:15:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you been writing your tech blog posts on Hashnode [https://hashnode.com/about] or Dev.to [http://dev.to/], but you're itching to try something new? If so, there is something that can quench your thirst: contributing to open source.  I know, I know, you’ve probably heard “Contribute to open source!” countless times in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CHRISTINE T. BELZIE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Headaches And How To Cure Them: i18n (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/gatsby-headaches-i18n-part-1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/gatsby-headaches-i18n-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this first part of a two-part hands-on guide, Juan Rodriguez explains how to use several i18n plugins for Gatsby and reviews some others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Change Commit Message – How to Edit Commit Messages with Git Amend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-edit-git-commit-messages-with-git-amend/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-edit-git-commit-messages-with-git-amend/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T17:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Commit messages play a crucial role in Git version control. They provide a historical record of changes made to a repository.  Clear and descriptive commit messages help you collaborate better with team members, more easily maintain your code, and understand how the project works.  But there are times]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How CSS Spacing Works – A Guide for Web Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-spacing-guide-for-web-devs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-spacing-guide-for-web-devs/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T16:26:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we're going to talk about spacing in CSS spacing – sounds so basic, right? Well, it's not as basic as you might think.  Take, for instance, when you visit your favorite e-commerce site to scout for products. The first thing that welcomes you to the platform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clinton Joy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Ways You Can Use Linux on a Windows Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/5-ways-to-use-linux-on-a-windows-machine/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/5-ways-to-use-linux-on-a-windows-machine/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T15:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a developer, you might need to run both Linux and Windows side by side. Luckily, there are a number of ways you can get the best of both worlds without getting different computers for each operating system.  In this article, we'll explore a few ways to use Linux]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design Under Constraints: Challenges, Opportunities, And Practical Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/design-constraints-challenges-opportunities-practical-strategies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/design-constraints-challenges-opportunities-practical-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unleash the power of creative limitation! Learn how constraints aren’t barriers but instead stepping stones to innovative design. Find out how to challenge unproductive restrictions and leverage the rest to your advantage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Your Java Development Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-java-development-environment-a-comprehensive-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-java-development-environment-a-comprehensive-guide/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T20:14:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up an efficient Java development environment is key if you're a Java dev. It helps streamline your coding process and makes you more productive.  In this article, I will walk you through the important steps you need to set up a Java development environment. We'll cover how to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isah Jacob</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Front End JavaScript Development Handbook – React, Angular, and Vue Compared]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/front-end-javascript-development-react-angular-vue-compared/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/front-end-javascript-development-react-angular-vue-compared/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T13:57:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend frameworks are indispensable in web development. They provide structured approaches and pre-defined components to streamline the coding process.  These tools can also help boost productivity by offering reusable components and abstracting complex tasks like DOM manipulation and state management. This allows developers to focus on application logic rather]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adekola Olawale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Complete Rust Programming Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rust-programming-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rust-programming-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T12:43:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rust is a safe, concurrent, and practical language that guarantees memory safety and prevents runtime errors, making it increasingly popular among developers and big tech firms like Microsoft and Google. With its efficiency, growing industry demand, and robust features, learning Rust opens up exciting opportunities in systems programming and beyond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Tailwind CSS with NextJS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-tailwind-css-with-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-tailwind-css-with-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T21:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tailwind CSS is a popular utility-first CSS framework that offers a unique approach to building modern and responsive user interfaces. Unlike traditional CSS frameworks that provide pre-designed components, Tailwind CSS focuses on providing a comprehensive set of utility classes that you can directly apply to your HTML elements. When combined]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelvin Moses</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing Sites And Apps With Blind Users: A Cheat Sheet]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/testing-sites-apps-blind-users-cheat-sheet/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/testing-sites-apps-blind-users-cheat-sheet/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While compliance with accessibility checklists is essential, it doesn’t necessarily mean a pleasant experience. That’s why live sessions can give you lots of priceless insights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Slava Shestopalov &amp; Eugene Shykiriavyi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Decorators Explained For Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-decorators-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-decorators-explained/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T18:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of Python programming, decorators can be an elegant and powerful tool in the hands of experienced developers.  Decorators give you the ability to modify the behavior of functions without altering their source code, providing a concise and flexible way to enhance and extend their functionality. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roy Chng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Hackers Attack Social Media Media Accounts – And How to Defend Against Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-protect-social-media-accounts-from-attackers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-protect-social-media-accounts-from-attackers/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T16:42:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone, and welcome to the world of Social Media 📲. In this article, we will explore the famous (or infamous) sphere of social media, why it is critical to both you and hackers, and how you can avoid having your social media accounts attacked. Disclaimer: Hacking is a tool]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Iwugo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Universal And Cognitive-Friendly UX Design Through Pivot Tables And Grids]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/universal-cognitive-friendly-ux-design-tables-grids/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/universal-cognitive-friendly-ux-design-tables-grids/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article covers the best tips and recommendations on the elements to pay attention to, the rules to follow, and life hacks to get around certain difficulties in table design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yuliia Nikitina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Custom Widget in Flutter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-custom-widget-in-flutter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-custom-widget-in-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T15:12:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter has been getting more and more popular lately. You can use it to build complex applications that work smoothly on MacOS, Windows, and Linux.  But building these applications is not always a simple process. You often have to refactor your code to maintain the app’s performance.  One]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Computer Vision with Deep Learning and TensorFlow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-computer-vision-with-deep-learning-and-tensorflow/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-computer-vision-with-deep-learning-and-tensorflow/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T15:08:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computer vision is being used in more and more places. From enhancing security systems to improving healthcare diagnostics, computer vision techniques are revolutionizing multiple industries.  We just published a 37-hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you about deep learning for computer vision using TensorFlow. The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Shuffle an Array of Items Using JavaScript or TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-shuffle-an-array-of-items-using-javascript-or-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-shuffle-an-array-of-items-using-javascript-or-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T23:32:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article we'll be exploring how we can shuffle an array of items in multiple different ways using TypeScript, or JavaScript should you prefer. Pre-Requisites:  * An understanding of TypeScript or JavaScript  * A basic understanding of For Loops and Arrays The following examples are written in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Weatherston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Laravel APIs – Security, Features, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-laravel-apis/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-laravel-apis/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T23:27:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Laravel is the most popular PHP framework, with its elegant syntax, extensive feature set, and developer-friendly environment. And it's gained significant traction in recent years. The Laravel ecosystem is constantly being updated with new features. Laravel 10 [https://laravel.com/docs/10.x/releases] is exciting! Among its many strengths is the robust support for APIs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdulwahab Ashimi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the JSON Module in Python – A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-json-module-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-json-module-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T22:51:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JSON (JavaScript Object Notation) is a popular, lightweight data interchange standard. It represents data structures made up of key-value pairs that's quite straightforward and human-readable.  JSON has become the industry standard for data interchange between online services. And it's widely utilized in modern programming languages, including Python. JSON data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Style a React Application – Different Options Compared]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-style-a-react-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-style-a-react-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T21:52:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Styling plays a vital role in creating visually appealing and user-friendly web applications. When it comes to React applications, there are numerous ways to style components and UI elements.  In this article, we will explore several popular options, including pure CSS, CSS modules, CSS preprocessors, Tailwind CSS, CSS-in-JS libraries]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design Patterns for Distributed Systems – Key Concepts Every Developer Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/design-patterns-for-distributed-systems/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/design-patterns-for-distributed-systems/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T20:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I first started my career as a backend engineer, I always worked with monolithic systems. The work was good but I always had this thought in the back of my mind: > "Man, I want to work on big systems such as ones for Google, Netflix, etc..." I was]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tamerlan Gudabayev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Image Carousel Component with TypeScript and Styled-Components]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-image-carousel-component/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-image-carousel-component/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T17:28:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent years, OTT (over-the-top) video streaming platforms have become more innovative and convenient to use. In their user interfaces, movies and series titles are arranged so that the titles are clearly visible. In this tutorial, I’ll guide you through the process of creating an image carousel component that looks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keyur Paralkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Exit – How to Use an Exit Function in Python to Stop a Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-exit-how-to-use-an-exit-function-in-python-to-stop-a-program/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-exit-how-to-use-an-exit-function-in-python-to-stop-a-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T13:54:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exit() function in Python is used to exit or terminate the current running script or program. You can use it to stop the execution of the program at any point. When the exit() function is called, the program will immediately stop running and exit. The syntax of the exit()]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Primitive Objects In JavaScript: When To Use Them (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/primitive-objects-javascript-part-2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/primitive-objects-javascript-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the second part of the series, Kirill looks at the usefulness of primitive objects, exploring how reducing capabilities could be a benefit for your project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kirill Myshkin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Enable Collaboration In A Multiparty Setting]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/enable-collaboration-multiparty-setting/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/enable-collaboration-multiparty-setting/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Artificial Intelligence becomes more widespread, so too does the adoption of digital agents and voice interactions. Explore the power of mixed reality systems and multimodal communication to enhance collaboration between consultants and clients, transforming advisory services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Hannah Kühne &amp; Madlaina Kalunder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Sheets – How to Make a Dynamic Search Bar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dynamic-search-bar-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dynamic-search-bar-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T13:31:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tutorial is for when CTRL + F is not enough. 🔥 I bet I've used the CTRL + F shortcut more than any other keyboard shortcut in my life. CTRL + Z probably comes close, but I use CTRL + F to find things... 💥ALL 💥 💥💥THE 💥💥 💥💥💥TIME]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iA Presenter: A Case Study On Product Pricing Considerations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/ia-presenter-case-study-product-pricing-considerations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/ia-presenter-case-study-product-pricing-considerations/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pricing a product or service is one of the more challenging aspects of product development. Pricing is an inexact science, and chances are you will not get it right the first time. But where do you even begin? Let’s explore the important considerations that go into product pricing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose a CMS – Tips for Content Management Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-choose-a-cms/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-choose-a-cms/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T23:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're an entrepreneur or a developer, chances are you'll work with a content management systems (CMS) at some point. And knowing how to analyze the many features of the CMS options out there is important when choosing the right one for your use case. In this article, I'll explain]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build AI Apps with ChatGPT, Dall-E, and GPT-4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-ai-apps-with-chatgpt-dall-e-and-gpt-4/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-ai-apps-with-chatgpt-dall-e-and-gpt-4/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T17:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can level up your web development skills by harnessing the power of AI. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build AI apps with ChatGPT, Dall-E, and GPT-4. This course is designed to equip you with the knowledge and skills]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn to Build Graph Databases with Neo4j (Full Course)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-neo4j-database-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-neo4j-database-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T16:49:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neo4j is revolutionizing the way we handle complex relationships between data points. Its intuitive graph-based structure provides a flexible and efficient solution for various applications. We just published a Neo4j course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Whether you're a developer, a data scientist, or an aspiring technology enthusiast, this course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LangChain Tutorial – How to Build a Custom-Knowledge Chatbot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/langchain-how-to-create-custom-knowledge-chatbots/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/langchain-how-to-create-custom-knowledge-chatbots/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T15:41:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have read about the large number of AI apps that have been released over the last couple of months. You may have even started using some of them. AI tools such as ChatPDF [https://www.chatpdf.com/] and CustomGPT AI [https://customgpt.ai/use-cases/] have become very useful to people – and for good]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Duggan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Data Visualization is Important for UX Design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-data-visualization-is-important-for-ux-design/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-data-visualization-is-important-for-ux-design/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T15:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, we find ourselves consuming vast amounts of information, at an unprecedented rate. From online transactions, to social media interactions, to scientific research, the complexity of data grows exponentially. This reveals a challenge — how to transform this raw data to actionable insight.  This is where data visualization]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Form Control Styling With Selectmenu And Anchoring API]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/advanced-form-control-styling-selectmenu-anchoring-api/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/advanced-form-control-styling-selectmenu-anchoring-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to the Open UI working community group, there’s a new element on the horizon, <selectmenu>, that will make styling this type of form control a whole lot better. You’re going to walk through an early implementation of this new experimental element by creating a pattern that you would never have thought possible with CSS alone — a radial selection menu.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Format a Date with JavaScript – Date Formatting in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-format-a-date-with-javascript-date-formatting-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-format-a-date-with-javascript-date-formatting-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T17:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dates are a fundamental part of many JavaScript applications, whether it's displaying the current date on a webpage or handling user input for scheduling events. But displaying dates in a clear and consistent format is crucial for a positive user experience. In the past, I have written two articles on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Simple Deployment Pipeline with Reusable Github Actions and Heroku]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-simple-deployment-pipeline-with-reuable-github-actions-and-heroku/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-simple-deployment-pipeline-with-reuable-github-actions-and-heroku/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T17:25:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've been using GitHub for a while, you've probably heard of or used GitHub actions.  If you haven't heard of Github Actions or used them before, you can use them for automating your build, test, or deployment pipelines. You can create workflows that will be triggered upon certain]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Temp Table – How to Create a Temporary SQL Table]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-temp-table-how-to-create-a-temporary-sql-table/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-temp-table-how-to-create-a-temporary-sql-table/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T17:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SQL, which stands for Structured Query Language, is a programming language specifically designed for managing and manipulating relational databases.  It provides a standardized way to interact with databases and perform tasks such as querying data, inserting, updating, and deleting records, creating and modifying database structures, and more. SQL is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use AWS Cognito for User Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-aws-cognito-for-user-authentication/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-aws-cognito-for-user-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building complex applications, one seemingly simple feature can be difficult to implement: user authentication.  Though some apps don't need it depending on their use case, many do. You might spend a ton of time building an authentication module to provide a secure experience to your users and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Your Own Path In June (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new batch of desktop wallpapers might be for you. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, the wallpapers in this post come in versions with and without a calendar for June 2023. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Playbooks to Execute an Incident Recovery Plan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-playbooks-for-incident-recovery/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-playbooks-for-incident-recovery/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T01:28:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A playbook is the official, formal written record that describes policies and processes that will reliably produce a working deployment of an organization's resource stack. When it comes to generating predictable results, the playbook is  the plan. I'll describe all the key elements of a good playbook in just]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Cookies to Customize a Web Page's Content]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-cookies-to-customize-web-page-content/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-cookies-to-customize-web-page-content/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T22:04:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you develop websites or web apps, someday you’ll have to deal with cookies. That’s why I decided to write this tutorial on how to use cookies to customize a web page according to the previous web page the user comes from.  I wrote this tutorial using PHP, but]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Venturi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Full-Stack Application with Next.js – A Step-By-Step Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-full-stack-application-with-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-full-stack-application-with-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T21:54:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js can seem intimidating at first, with so many new concepts to grasp. But don't worry – in this step-by-step tutorial, I will provide you with all the essential information you need to create your first modern full-stack application with Next.js. In this tutorial, I will take you through the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yazdun Fadali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create and Publish a Vue Component Library – 2023 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-and-publish-a-vue-component-library-update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-and-publish-a-vue-component-library-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T20:11:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2020, I wrote a post [/news/how-to-create-and-publish-a-vue-component-library/] about building a Vue Component library. Since then the package I used has been deprecated, and the recommended way to build a library/package is to use Vite.  Getting Started I started off the project by running npm create vite@latest and naming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Barrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Responsive Websites – Best Practices for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/responsive-design-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/responsive-design-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T20:04:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way we interact with the web has changed dramatically, and it will keep changing. In the past, most people used desktop computers to access the internet. But today, people are using a wide variety of devices, including laptops, tablets, and smartphones. This has resulted in a growing demand for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fakorede Damilola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does JavaScript Work Behind the Scenes? JS Engine and Runtime Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-javascript-works-behind-the-scenes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-javascript-works-behind-the-scenes/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T18:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So you may know that your code somehow compiles and executes in your browser to display the beautiful web application you’ve built. But are you aware of all the components that come into play to enable the output?  Let’s dive a little into JavaScript behind the scenes. The abstract]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esther Christopher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GraphQL Tutorial – How to Query The Rick and Morty API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/graphql-queries-for-everyone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/graphql-queries-for-everyone/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T18:07:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I enjoy fictional books about greek gods, demigods, the oracle, and prophecies.  I am a huge fan of Rick Riordan's books. I recently came across Apollo's Trials, based on the greek god Apollo.  When I hear any mention of Apollo, my mind goes to the greek god who]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Velda Kiara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logical Operators in PHP – A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/logical-operators-in-php/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/logical-operators-in-php/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T17:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Logical operators play a key role in programming languages. They let you manipulate boolean values and evaluate logical conditions.  In PHP, there are four fundamental logical operators: AND, OR, NOT, and XOR. This guide will help you understand these operators, and I'll explain how they work using code examples]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Para</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Setup a Windows Machine for Machine Learning/Deep Learning Using an Nvidia Graphics Card (CUDA)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-setup-windows-machine-for-ml-dl-using-nvidia-graphics-card-cuda/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-setup-windows-machine-for-ml-dl-using-nvidia-graphics-card-cuda/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T14:58:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are learning machine learning / deep learning, you may be using the free  Google Colab [https://colab.research.google.com/]. But you might wonder if the free version is adequate.  If you can afford a good Nvidia Graphics Card (with a decent amount of CUDA cores) then you can easily]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Abort Merge – How to Cancel a Merge in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-abort-merge-how-to-cancel-a-merge-in-git/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-abort-merge-how-to-cancel-a-merge-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T14:18:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version control is a system that helps manage changes to files and directories over time. It allows multiple people to collaborate on a project, keep track of modifications, and revert to previous versions if needed.  One of the most popular version control systems is Git. Git [https://git-scm.com/] is a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What does the "Maximum call stack exceeded" error mean?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-the-maximum-call-stack-stack-exceeded-error-mean/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-the-maximum-call-stack-stack-exceeded-error-mean/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T07:56:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever gotten an error similar to this? This error occurs because the call stack has exceeded its limit. But what does this mean? First, let's understand what the call stack is. The Call Stack The call stack is a data structure in JavaScript that contains the function(s) being]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing A Better Design Handoff File In Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/designing-better-design-handoff-file-figma/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/designing-better-design-handoff-file-figma/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article provides practical tips for improving the handoff process between design and development in product development. The guidance covers effective communication, documentation, design details, version control, and plugin usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Shih)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strings in C# – What's New, Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/new-ish-things-about-c-strings/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/new-ish-things-about-c-strings/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T13:49:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Much of what we work with in our code are strings. Let's look at some of the newish things about C# strings ... including raw string literals and raw string interpolation that are new in C# 11. Raw string literals make it easy to build complex, multi-line strings, including JSON,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Kurata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Golang Environment – GOPATH vs go.mod]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/golang-environment-gopath-vs-go-mod/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/golang-environment-gopath-vs-go-mod/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T00:23:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll explore the differences between the traditional GOPATH  environment and the go.mod based environment for Go programming.  This distinction has significant implications for how Go developers structure and manage their project workspaces and dependencies. We'll start by understanding the GOPATH environment, its organization and its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Otavio Ehrenberger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Data Validation Rules in Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-data-validation-rules-excel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-data-validation-rules-excel/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T00:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data validation is a feature in Excel used in restricting data entry in specific cells. It can also prompt the user to enter valid data into the cells based on the rules and restrictions provided by the creator of the Excel worksheet.  When setting up a workbook, you might]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Faith Oyama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Sort Dictionary by Key – How to Sort a Dict with Keys]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-sort-dictionary-by-key/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-sort-dictionary-by-key/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T23:57:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sorting is a fundamental operation in computer programming that involves arranging elements in a specific order.  Whether you're working with numbers, strings, or complex data structures, sorting plays a crucial role in organizing and manipulating data efficiently.  From small arrays to large datasets, sorting algorithms allow programmers to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Exactly is Node.js? A Guide for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-exactly-is-node-guide-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-exactly-is-node-guide-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T23:08:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're thinking about doing back-end development using JavaScript, you will hear the term ‘Node.js’. Node is often associated with developing powerful web servers. But what exactly is Node.js? Is it a JavaScript framework just like Angular [https://angular.io/]? Is it a programming language? Is it a JavaScript Library? Is it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amazing Enyichi Agu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Success At Scale, A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/success-at-scale-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/success-at-scale-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Success At Scale”, our upcoming book with best-practice case studies from industry experts. Print and eBook shipping in fall 2023. Pre-order the book.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Golang Handbook – A Beginner's Guide to Learning Go]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-golang-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-golang-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T18:11:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Go programming languagehas been exploding in popularity. Tons of companies are using Go to build scalable, modern, backend infrastructure.  If you're looking to learn a new programming language, Go is a great choice. It's fast, lightweight, has an amazing open source community, and is actually quite easy to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Wagner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build and Deploy a LeetCode Clone with React, Next JS, TypeScript, Tailwind CSS, Firebase]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-deploy-a-leetcode-clone-with-react-next-js-typescript-tailwind-css-firebase/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-deploy-a-leetcode-clone-with-react-next-js-typescript-tailwind-css-firebase/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T15:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solving coding challenges on the LeetCode website is a great way to improve your developer skills. But an even better way to improve your skills is to develop your own LeetCode website. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Component Lifecycle Methods – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-component-lifecycle-methods/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-component-lifecycle-methods/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T14:28:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In React, components have a lifecycle that consists of different phases. Each phase has a set of lifecycle methods that are called at specific points in the component's lifecycle. These methods allow you to control the component's behavior and perform specific actions at different stages of its lifecycle. A component's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Basics for DevOps – How to Setup a Linux Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/aws-basics-for-devops/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/aws-basics-for-devops/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T14:26:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To create an application like WhatsApp or Facebook, you'd need many servers (30-40), operating system licenses, routers, cables, switches, gateways, air conditioning units, and employees for maintenance.  All this can be expensive and time-consuming, and there is no guarantee that the application will be successful in the market. But]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Satyam Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Socket Programming in Python?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/socket-programming-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/socket-programming-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T14:25:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to code a socket program in Python. But before that, let's understand what a socket is and where you might use it. We can define a socket as a quick connection which allows the transmission of data between two processes on the same]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>P S Mohammed Ali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Accessibility Matters in UI/UX Design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-accessibility-matters-in-ui-ux-design/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-accessibility-matters-in-ui-ux-design/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T14:18:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility is a word that is often thrown around in the design field. As a UI/UX/Web Designer, you might have heard this word a few times and you might wonder why it's important.  In this article, you will learn:  * What accessibility means  * Some myths surrounding]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Impact Of Agile Methodologies On Code Quality]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/impact-agile-methodologies-code-quality/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/impact-agile-methodologies-code-quality/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Say goodbye to traditional workflows and embrace Agile to unlock the power of high-quality code. Discover how Agile methodologies promote simplicity, modularization, readability, and continuous improvement, resulting in faster turnaround times, more responsive development processes, and ultimately, the creation of high-quality software that meets customer needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sarah Oke Okolo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Copy a Directory in Linux with the cp Command]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-copy-a-directory-in-linux-with-the-cp-command/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-copy-a-directory-in-linux-with-the-cp-command/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T22:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Copying directories is an essential task in Linux. It allows you to duplicate directories, create backups, or transfer data between different locations.  One of the most commonly used commands for copying files and directories in Linux is cp. In this tutorial, we will explore how to copy directories effectively]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Sheets – How to Automatically Post Events to Google Calendar with Apps Script]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-sheets-automatically-post-events-to-google-calendar-with-apps-script/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-sheets-automatically-post-events-to-google-calendar-with-apps-script/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T21:44:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article we'll link two Google services -> Google Sheets and Google Calendar. By using a very short custom function in Google Apps Script, we can add a list of events from a Google Sheet to a Google Calendar. 🤯 And we'll even have it email our guests as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Security Analysts Can Use Artificial Intelligence (AI) in Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-artificial-intelligence-in-cybersecurity/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-artificial-intelligence-in-cybersecurity/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T20:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) has been a game-changer in cybersecurity. It has revolutionized the approach to cybersecurity by providing advanced techniques to detect and mitigate cyber threats.  The use of AI in cybersecurity is increasing rapidly, with many companies adopting it as a key tool in their cybersecurity strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonya Moisset</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Responsive Navigation Bar with a Dropdown Menu using JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-responsive-navigation-bar-with-dropdown-menu-using-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-responsive-navigation-bar-with-dropdown-menu-using-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T20:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Navigation bars are essential components used a lot in websites and web apps. As a web developer, you will need to be able to customize them, either for a client project or a basic portfolio site. In this guide, you'll learn how to build a navigation bas for yourself from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Eke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Django to Code a ChatGPT Clone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-django-to-code-a-chatgpt-clone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-django-to-code-a-chatgpt-clone/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T18:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating an AI chatbot might seem like a daunting task, especially if you're not an experienced programmer. But we just launched a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will demystify the process and walk you through it step-by-step. This course focuses on using Django, a high-level Python web framework,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>