<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-04-29T01:17:43.211Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Blazor WebAssembly and Web API on .NET 6 by Building a Shopping Cart App]]></title>
        <id>626acd1fc1c601068f4e86be</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-blazor-webassembly-and/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T17:28:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blazor WebAssembly is a single-page app framework for building interactive client-side web apps with .NET. It uses open web standards without plugins or recompiling code into other languages. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Blazor WebAssembly and Web]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting Up CloudFront to Host Your Web App]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365413</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/setting-up-cloudfront-to-host-your-web-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T14:42:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my last article, we went over how to set up a web app that serves chunks and bundles of CSS and JavaScript from CloudFront. We integrated it into Vite so that when the app runs in a browser, …
Setting Up CloudFront to Host Your Web App originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CTA Modal: How To Build A Web Component]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/cta-modal-build-web-component/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/cta-modal-build-web-component/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Nathan Smith explains how to create modal dialog windows with rich interaction that will only require authoring HTML in order to be used. They are based on Web Components that are currently supported by every major browser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nathan Smith)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Habit System and Stay Motivated as a Developer]]></title>
        <id>6267958cc1c601068f4e758d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-habit-system-and-stay-motivated-as-a-developer/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T00:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you ever find it challenging to work on your project, side hustle, or even your hobby?  Have you ever had those moments where nothing feels exciting? You lay in bed thinking – is it me, or is my work that boring?  I have those days too. Some]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shruti Kapoor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Center a Div with CSS]]></title>
        <id>62458d52138a19064b069054</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-center-a-div-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T19:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a few common coding problems you might encounter when you start practicing what you've learned by building projects. One common problem you'll face as a web developer is how to place an element at the center of a page or within an element acting as its container. It's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Send Large Video Files – Share a Big File with Email]]></title>
        <id>626919edc1c601068f4e809e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-send-large-video-files-share-a-big-file-with-email/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T19:51:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sending large files through email can be quite challenging. This is because each email client has a size limit for file sharing. Gmail and Yahoo limit file size to 25MB, while outlook and iCloud limit files to 20MB. So, if you decide to send, for example, a video file larger]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix Google Chrome Black Screen on Linux OS (Wayland)]]></title>
        <id>6266b589ac55f60686c3c44f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fix-black-screen-on-google-chrome-on-linux-os/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T19:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a Linux user, then you've likely used the GNOME Desktop Environment at least once. The latest GNOME DE (Desktop Environment) uses Wayland nowadays. And while it's possible to remove Wayland and select Xorg if you want, most users are starting to use Wayland as their daily driver.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run Multiple Containers with Docker Compose]]></title>
        <id>6267fe2ec1c601068f4e77da</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/run-multiple-containers-with-docker-compose/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T19:31:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker has become increasingly popular over the last several years. One reason for this is that you can create portable containers which are fast and easy to deploy.  As described on Docker's website [https://www.docker.com/resources/what-container/], a container is something that packages your code along with any other dependencies so that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arjav Dave</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build and Push Docker Images to AWS ECR]]></title>
        <id>625fc3caac55f60686c38ce0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-push-docker-images-to-aws-ecr/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T16:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker is a platform that helps you build, run, and ship applications in a seamless and error-free way.  You've likely come across a scenario where the code is running on your machine, but is somehow throwing errors on someone else's machine.  Well, Docker was created to solve this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kaushal Joshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Assembly Language Programming with ARM]]></title>
        <id>6269557fc1c601068f4e8127</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-assembly-language-programming-with-arm/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T14:49:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Assembly language is a low-level programming language for a computer or other programmable device that is closest to the machine language. It is often specific to a particular computer architecture so there are multiple types of assembly languages. ARM is an increasingly popular assembly language.  We just published a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cool Hover Effects That Use Background Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365383</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/cool-hover-effects-using-background-properties/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T14:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A while ago, Geoff wrote an article about a cool hover effect. The effect relies on a combination of CSS pseudo-elements, transforms, and transitions. A lot of comments have shown that the same effect can be done using background …
Cool Hover Effects That Use Background Properties originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boosting UX With Design KPIs]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/boosting-ux-with-design-kpis/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/boosting-ux-with-design-kpis/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We should be able to measure how well a particular design solves a particular problem. Let’s explore design KPIs that capture user’s experience, how to measure them and how to keep both users and business stakeholders happy, over time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux chmod and chown – How to Change File Permissions and Ownership in Linux]]></title>
        <id>626074adac55f60686c397ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linux-chmod-chown-change-file-permissions/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T00:38:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux is a multi user OS which means that it supports multiple users at a time.  As many people can access the system simultaneously and some resources are shared, Linux controls access through ownership and permissions.  Linux file ownership In Linux, there are three types of owners: user,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Program to Print the Fibonacci Sequence]]></title>
        <id>6262b979ac55f60686c3aca1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-program-to-print-the-fibonacci-sequence/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T00:34:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Questions about the Fibonacci Series are some of the most commonly asked in Python interviews.  In this article, I'll explain a step-by-step approach on how to print the Fibonacci sequence using two different techniques, iteration and recursion.  Before we begin, let's first understand some basic terminology. What is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Resize Elements in Figma]]></title>
        <id>6253a5fcac55f60686c31c25</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-resize-elements-in-figma/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T23:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll learn a few different ways to resize elements and groups in Figma (in addition to the default method). We'll also learn how to resize frames without moving elements in the frames. In Figma, there are other ways to resize elements apart from the default method. So]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Homomorphic Encryption?]]></title>
        <id>6255a0d4ac55f60686c32eaa</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-homomorphic-encryption/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T23:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article we will discuss Homomorphic Encryption, the problem that it solves, and the different types that exist.  Then we will write code in Python to show some of its capabilities in action. Here's what we'll cover:  1. What is Homomorphic Encryption?  2. Advantages of Homomorphic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aris Zagakos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vite.js Tutorial – How to Install and Use Vite in Your Web Projects]]></title>
        <id>6265c16bac55f60686c3bf05</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-started-with-vite/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T21:41:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vite.js [/news/p/e534a679-ce3c-4cf1-842b-96087d30944d/Vite.js] is a rapid development tool for modern web projects. It focuses on speed and performance by improving the development experience. Vite uses native browser ES imports to enable support for modern browsers without a build process. Vite consists of two major parts:  * The dev server provides]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Popoola Temitope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Memoization? How and When to Memoize in JavaScript and React]]></title>
        <id>6259a28cac55f60686c35b31</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/memoization-in-javascript-and-react/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T21:16:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we will talk about memoization, an optimization technique that can help make heavy computation processes more efficient. We will start by talking about what memoization is and when it's best to implement it. Later on we will give practical examples for JavaScript and React. Table]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Wait – How to Sleep N Seconds in JS with .setTimeout()]]></title>
        <id>622864b663ded806bb9e6f8d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-wait-how-to-sleep-n-seconds-in-js-with-settimeout/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T19:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you might want to delay the execution of your code. You may need certain lines of code to execute at a point in the future, when you explicitly specify, rather than all the code executing synchronously. Something like that is possible with JavaScript. In this article, you will learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Text Align in CSS – How to Align Text in Center with HTML]]></title>
        <id>626595d9ac55f60686c3bcb6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/text-align-in-css-how-to-align-text-in-center-with-html/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T19:08:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There will be many times where you will need to center some text using HTML and CSS. But what is the best way to go about that? In this article, I will show you how to use the text-align property in CSS and show you how to vertically align text]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python For Loop Example – How to Write Loops in Python]]></title>
        <id>6267fd8cc1c601068f4e77d0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-for-loop-example-how-to-write-loops-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T19:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are just getting started in Python, for loops are one of the fundamentals you should learn how to use. In the Python programming language, for loops are also called “definite loops” because they perform the instruction a certain number of times. This is in contrast to while loops,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Reusable SVG Icon React Components]]></title>
        <id>6260a9fcac55f60686c399f9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-reusable-icon-react-components-for-colors-and-sizes-customization/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T18:22:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We use icons when building frontend applications all the time – for indications, pointers, and so on. Here's how to create a reusable React component for icons. When it comes to icons, you can use PNG or SVG images. PNGs come with a fixed color but allow dimension changes (like]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avoiding the Pitfalls of Nested Components in a Design System]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365359</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/nested-components-in-a-design-system/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T14:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When creating a component-based, front-end infrastructure, one of the biggest pain points I’ve personally encountered is making components that are both reusable and responsive when there are nested components within components.
Take the following “call to action” (<CTA />…
Avoiding the Pitfalls of Nested Components in a Design System originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Christofi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preventing Bad UX Through Integrated Design Workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/ux-integrated-design-workflows/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/ux-integrated-design-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When bad UX has lingered in a product for so long, it can feel like a mountain to overcome. In this article, Ceara Crawshaw shares her advice on how you can invoke joy and assure the quality in the work done on product teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ceara Crawshaw)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Debug Applications with Strace, Python, and Wireshark]]></title>
        <id>6262a8d5ac55f60686c3abd5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/debug-an-app-with-strace-python-wireshark/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T00:23:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I will show you a few techniques you can use to troubleshoot a program when is not behaving.  This list is not universal and, depending on what you are looking for, it may not be enough to solve your problem. But it should be a good]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Variables Definition – What are CSS Vars and How to Use Them?]]></title>
        <id>6265e8feac55f60686c3bf60</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-css-variables-and-how-to-use-them/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T22:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS variables are custom variables that you can create and reuse throughout your stylesheet.  In this article, I will show you how to create CSS variables on the :root pseudo selector and show you how to access them using the var() function.  How to Create a CSS Custom]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Sass with CSS]]></title>
        <id>6229cf6963ded806bb9e79c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-sass-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T22:32:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi there! If you are reading this article, you're probably trying to understand what Sass is and how it works.  Sass is a CSS preprocessor that helps you manage tasks in large projects where the style sheets get larger, you have a number of lines of CSS code, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adalbert Pungu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[module.exports – How to Export in Node.js and JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>6260ad0dac55f60686c39a04</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/module-exports-how-to-export-in-node-js-and-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T21:03:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In programming, modules are components of a program with one or more functions or values. These values can also be shared across the entire program and can be used in different ways. In this article, I will show you how to share functions and values by exporting and importing modules]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Analysis in Go – How to Use the Gota Package]]></title>
        <id>6255f46dac55f60686c332f7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/exploratory-data-analysis-in-go-with-gota/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T20:52:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data analysis is the process of filtering, manipulating, and processing raw data and datasets to get insights from them. Python and R are usually the go-to languages for data analysis. But these days Go is becoming more and more popular for this purpose.  In this tutorial, we will be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ukeje Chukwuemeriwo Goodness</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Speed Up Your Lambda Functions]]></title>
        <id>6262c8c9ac55f60686c3aec7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-speed-up-lambda-functions/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T19:43:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lambda has gained massive popularity over the past few years. It has various use cases, from running simple scripts to gluing flows and processes within a serverless architecture or when running microservices. Still, if you've just started working in a new environment or organisation, you might feel cautious about using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Haydar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Check if a Property Exists in a JavaScript Object]]></title>
        <id>62649b7dac55f60686c3b738</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-check-if-a-property-exists-in-a-javascript-object/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T17:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you are working with objects in JavaScript, you might need to check if a specific property exists or not.  In this article, I will show you three ways to check if a property exists in a JavaScript object.  How to Use the hasOwnProperty() Method in JavaScript The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Test Your Apps using Jest, Testing Library, Cypress, and Supertest]]></title>
        <id>62588c4bac55f60686c352c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/test-a-react-app-with-jest-testing-library-and-cypress/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T17:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we're going to talk about testing. I'll give you a good overview of what testing is and an introduction of how you can implement it on your JavaScript projects. We'll use four very popular tools – Jest, Testing library, Cypress and Supertest. First we're going]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Train an AI to Play a Snake Game Using Python]]></title>
        <id>6266ced1ac55f60686c3c620</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/train-an-ia-to-play-a-snake-game-using-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T16:48:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why waste time playing video games when you can train an AI to do it for you? Ok, maybe playing yourself is more fun but training an AI can be more educational. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you the basics of reinforcement]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage State in Flutter Apps]]></title>
        <id>6261bb97ac55f60686c3a424</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manage-state-in-flutter-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T14:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing state is something most developers need to deal with when working on applications.  You might be familiar with the model-view-viewmodel (MVVM) pattern, where the ViewModel is the one responsible for a view’s state. But in Flutter, things are a bit different.  If you are reading this, then]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Ben Rachel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skeleton Loader Example – How to Build a Skeleton Screen with CSS for Better UX]]></title>
        <id>625fb4c7ac55f60686c38c36</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-skeleton-screens-using-css-for-better-user-experience/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T13:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content loaders, skeleton screens, ghost elements, and content placeholders. These are the names given to the effect we'll be exploring today. Many companies, such as Linkedin, Facebook, Youtube and Slack, use this effect in their apps and websites, as you may have noticed. As much as we developers want our]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Mitolu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What If Our Sliders Actually Slid?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/what-if-sliders-actually-slid-html-element-input-range/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/what-if-sliders-actually-slid-html-element-input-range/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Jhey Tompkins explores one of GreenSocks’ newest plugins alongside React to create an impractical whimsical spin on a well-known native element: ``.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing Strong Front-end Test Element Locators]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364218</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/front-end-test-element-locators/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T18:45:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automated front-end tests are awesome. We can write a test with code to visit a page — or load up just a single component — and have that test code click on things or type text like a user would, …
Writing Strong Front-end Test Element Locators originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Noonan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing The CLI The Way People Use It]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/testing-cli-way-people-use-it/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/testing-cli-way-people-use-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered, why do people write CLI tools? When is a good time to think about yours? Today we’ll touch on these questions, along with some tips to remember when creating one. However, all of this serves as a prelude to the real topic: end-to-end testing of CLI tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Georgy Marchuk)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[502 Bad Gateway Error [Solved]]]></title>
        <id>62615f82ac55f60686c39ef9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/502-bad-gateway-error-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T00:45:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can get a 502 bad gateway error when there's a problem with the server of the website you are trying to connect to. In more technical terms, the “502” in the error is an HTTP status code which indicates that one server received an invalid response from another server.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Better Programmer – Use a Skill-Building Planner]]></title>
        <id>62616030ac55f60686c39f0f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-better-programmer-use-a-skill-building-planner/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T00:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many programmers are missing out on a simple way to improve their programming progress.  Just think of athletes, entrepreneurs, students, health-nuts, and travelers. They’re among the diverse groups of people who use a planner. Planners are often used to give productivity a boost in order to stay organized and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Haddad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How to Use JavaScript Arrays by Building an iPhone Product Page]]></title>
        <id>625e8cfaac55f60686c37f21</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-arrays-by-building-product-page/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T00:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had the idea for this tutorial while browsing the official iPhone website. Apple is known for its great products and impeccable design, and if you spend enough time checking out its website, you can learn a thing or two about branding and great design.  One of the things]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel A. Olubiyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Contribute to Open-Source Projects – A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>624e7b3eac55f60686c2f0b8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-contribute-to-open-source-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T23:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've been considering contributing to an open source project, you might be weighing the pros and cons of doing so. You might hear things like open-source projects won't help you grow. Or they can't change your career trajectory. And that your contributions definitely won’t add to your portfolio. If]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankita Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Should You Move to the Cloud? Advantages of Cloud Computing Explained]]></title>
        <id>623422f3cdcd57069ddfade9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advantages-of-cloud-computing/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T22:27:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term cloud computing refers to software and services that run on the internet instead of locally on your on-site server or computer. Adopting the cloud can help you and your team cut costs and ensure that your data and systems are available to your customers anywhere and at any]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davis David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Colaboratory – How to Run Python Code in Your Google Drive]]></title>
        <id>625df1a2ac55f60686c37b2d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-colaboratory-python-code-in-your-google-drive/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T19:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Google Colaboratory (“Colab”) is a notebook (like a Jupyter Notebook) where you can run Python code in your Google Drive.  You can write text, write code, run that code, and see the output – all in line in the same notebook.  Benefits of Google Colab Sharing notebooks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Pratowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Firmware? Definition and Examples]]></title>
        <id>6223b106c4d0d306772f4b41</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-firmware/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T18:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that firmware is literally everywhere? It might be strange to think about – but it's just as common as hardware and software. In fact, it is thanks to firmware that:  * Printers work  * Defibrillators work  * Car radios works  * and more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove a Property from a JavaScript Object]]></title>
        <id>6260bd7bac55f60686c39b14</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-a-property-from-a-javascript-object/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T17:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two ways to remove a property from a JavaScript object. There's the mutable way of doing it using the delete operator, and the immutable way of doing it using object restructuring.  Let's go through each of these methods in this tutorial. Remove a Property from a JS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saransh Kataria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Better Navigation With Navigation Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/designing-better-navigation-ux-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/designing-better-navigation-ux-queries/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In UX, we can use navigation queries, evaluation journeys, A-Z index and tap-ahead autocomplete to help users get where they want to be, faster. Let’s find out how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your Own Blog with Next.js and MDX]]></title>
        <id>625b6643ac55f60686c36806</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-your-own-blog-with-next-js-and-mdx/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T02:28:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I decided to build my blog, I found many tools out there that were readily available. I looked at Gastby [https://www.gatsbyjs.com/] along with content management systems like Ghost [https://ghost.org/], Contentful [https://www.contentful.com/], Sanity dot io [https://www.sanity.io/], and HUGO [https://gohugo.io/].  But I needed something that I could have total control]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caleb Olojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is FTP? File Transfer Protocol and FTP Server Meaning]]></title>
        <id>625eae40ac55f60686c381d2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-ftp-file-transfer-protocol-and-ftp-server-meaning/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T01:01:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTP stands for File Transfer Protocol. This is a network/communication protocol for transferring files between computers over a TCP/IP (Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol) network.  Examples of TCP/IP networks are:  * HTTP (Hypertext Transfer Protocol).  * HTTPS (Hypertext Transfer Protocol Secure).  * FTP (File Transfer Protocol). How]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Flush DNS on Mac – MacOS Clear DNS Cache]]></title>
        <id>624beda6ac55f60686c2e0f7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-flush-dns-on-mac-macos-clear-dns-cache/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T00:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn why flushing your DNS cache is important, and how you can clear the cache on your local system. Here is what we'll discuss in this guide:  1. What is DNS cache? 1. Why flushing DNS cache is important]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extern – C and C++ Extern Keyword Function Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>625d0d69ac55f60686c37241</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/extern-keyword-function-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T00:08:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The extern keyword in C and C++ extends the visibility of variables and functions across multiple source files.  In the case of functions, the extern keyword is used implicitly. But with variables, you have to use the keyword explicitly. I believe a simple code example can explain things better]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farhan Hasin Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How WebAuthn Authenticates Users Without a Password]]></title>
        <id>6255cce5ac55f60686c330c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/intro-to-webauthn/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T23:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of us are used to logging into different accounts using a password. For years this has been the norm, but passwords also face security issues:  * They are extremely annoying when we don’t remember them and even harder to    reset  * They can be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohit Jacob Mathew</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dns_probe_finished_nxdomain Error [Solved]]]></title>
        <id>625fe437ac55f60686c38f04</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dns_probe_finished_nxdomain-error-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T15:39:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a regular Google Chrome user, then you might have encountered the error “dns_probe_finished_nxdomain” before. It is usually accompanied by “This site can’t be reached”. This error is associated with the Domain Name System (DNS) server and can occur due to misconfiguration in the DNS server, an unresponsive]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Tailwind CSS to New and Existing WordPress Themes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364880</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/adding-tailwind-css-to-wordpress-themes/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T15:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the 15 or so years since I started making WordPress websites, nothing has had more of an impact on my productivity — and my ability to enjoy front-end development — than adding Tailwind CSS to my workflow (and it …
Adding Tailwind CSS to New and Existing WordPress Themes originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greg Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Redux Toolkit – The Recommended Way to Use Redux]]></title>
        <id>626007e4ac55f60686c3924f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-redux-toolkit-the-recommended-way-to-use-redux/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T13:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redux Toolkit is an opinionated toolset for efficient Redux development created by the Redux team. It is the the standard and recommended way to write Redux logic and manage state in your JavaScript applications. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Productivity Tips And Tools For A More Efficient Workflow]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/productivity-tips-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/productivity-tips-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who doesn’t love a good timesaver? In this post, we compiled useful productivity tips and tools that help you speed up routine tasks, enhance your development workflow, and stay organized.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Permissions – How to Find Permissions of a File]]></title>
        <id>625c8890ac55f60686c37088</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linux-permissions-how-to-find-permissions-of-a-file/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T21:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux is a multi-user Operating System which means it supports multiple users on a single system.  Each user has its own rights which might be limited as well to increase security. For example, users have a particular set of permissions to access a file – some users might be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Bypass ES Modules Errors in Next.js with Dynamic Imports]]></title>
        <id>6252e40fac55f60686c3142d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-bypass-es-modules-error-in-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T19:58:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you are building an application that can be accessed on the web, there are a lot of dependencies or packages that you will need for your application to function well. You'll need most of these packages when you're building JAMStack applications with frameworks or libraries like React, Vuejs, Next.js,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caleb Olojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Docker? Learn How to Use Containers – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>625d1728ac55f60686c3725e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-docker-learn-how-to-use-containers-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T19:50:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers are an essential tool for software development today. Running applications in any environment becomes easy when you leverage containers.  The most popular technology for running containers is Docker [https://www.docker.com/], which runs on any operating system. In this blog post, you will learn to use Docker for the top]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sigl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rubber Duck Debugging]]></title>
        <id>625e7b77ac55f60686c37edc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rubber-duck-debugging/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T17:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a software developer, you’ve probably been in a situation where your code is not working as expected. This could happen because you made a typo, you weren't paying enough attention, or you weren't sure how something worked. When your code doesn't work, it's frustrating – but the only thing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React + WebSockets Project – Build a Real-Time Order Book Application]]></title>
        <id>61372766d6679a07b7d43ded</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-websockets-project-build-real-time-order-book-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T17:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we will see how to build an Order Book web application, that we'll use to display real-time cryptocurrency info. We will use React with Typescript [https://create-react-app.dev/docs/adding-typescript/] for creating the UI,  Redux [https://redux.js.org/] for managing the application state, and  styled-components [https://styled-components.com/] for applying the styling. And]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mihail Gaberov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Host an Angular Application on GitHub Pages with Travis CI]]></title>
        <id>6259eec8ac55f60686c35fe1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/host-an-angular-application-on-github-pages-with-travis-ci/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll create an application using the latest version of Angular. Then we'll host it on the GitHub Pages static website service using the continuous integration tool Travis CI to deploy the application. Prerequisites Before you start, you need to install and configure the tools below to create]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rodrigo Kamada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jamstack Rendering Patterns: The Evolution]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/jamstack-rendering-patterns-evolution/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/jamstack-rendering-patterns-evolution/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ekene Eze shares his thoughts about the direction of the web in 2022, and what solutions we can expect to see come up in the ecosystem to significantly improve the Jamstack experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ekene Eze)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[strftime – Python DateTime Timestamp String]]></title>
        <id>62584ad7ac55f60686c34bd0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/strftime-python-datetime-timestamp-string/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T01:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The datetime object lets us work with dates and times in Python. But the value returned when we use this object is of the datatime data type rather than a  string. Here is an example that prints the current year, month, day and time to the console: from datetime]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS radial-gradient by Building Background Patterns]]></title>
        <id>625bf31cac55f60686c36991</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-radial-gradient/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T01:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are new to CSS gradients, you may have heard about something called  radial-gradient(). If you have never used it before, you are in the right place to learn about it. In this tutorial, I will focus on some real and practical examples to explain the secrets behind]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Network Security – How to Use Suricata, RaspberryPI4, and Python to Make Your Network Safe]]></title>
        <id>625c80fcac55f60686c37035</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/home-network-security-with-suricata-raspberrypi4-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T00:23:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous article [/news/wireless-security-using-raspberry-pi-4-kismet-and-python/], I showed you how to secure your wireless home network using Kismet [https://www.kismetwireless.net/]. Kismet is perfect for detecting anomalies and certain types of attack – but what if I want to analyze the traffic and look for abnormal patterns or patterns that could indicate an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Object-Oriented Programming in Java – A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>601e56cc0a2838549dcbf3d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-oriented-programming-concepts-java/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T22:03:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, folks! Today we are going to talk about object-oriented programming in Java. This article will help give you a thorough understanding of the underlying principles of object-oriented programming and its concepts.  Once you understand these concepts, you should have the confidence and ability to develop basic problem-solving applications]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Cyubahiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Object Oriented Programming with Python – Code a Minesweeper Game]]></title>
        <id>625dbd15ac55f60686c37860</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-oriented-programming-with-python-code-a-minesweeper-game/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T19:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improve your Python programming skills by coding everyone's favorite Windows 3.1 game: Minesweeper. We just published a Python course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to code Minesweeper using the tkinter library. Jim from JimShapedCoding developed this course. He has published many popular programming courses both]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Relational VS Nonrelational Databases – the Difference Between a SQL DB and a NoSQL DB]]></title>
        <id>624bed78ac55f60686c2e0eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/relational-vs-nonrelational-databases-difference-between-sql-db-and-nosql-db/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T17:56:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is an overview of relational and non-relational databases. Besides learning the fundamental differences between the two types of databases, you will also learn how to decide which one to use for your next project by going over their strengths and weaknesses. Here is what we'll cover:  1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js Image Tutorial – How to Upload, Crop, and Resize Images in the Browser in Next]]></title>
        <id>625aba3aac55f60686c36423</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-upload-crop-resize-images-in-the-browser-in-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T17:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two of the most fundamental image editing functions are resizing and cropping. But you should do these carefully because they have the potential to degrade image quality. Cropping always includes removing a portion of the original image, resulting in the loss of some pixels. This post will teach you how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Idris Olubisi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Mermaid Diagrams in Markdown]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364908</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/making-mermaid-diagrams-in-markdown/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T16:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mermaid diagrams and flowcharts have been gaining traction, especially with GitHub’s announcement that they are natively supported in Markdown. Let’s take a look at what they are, how to use them, and just as importantly: why.
Just like you …
Making Mermaid Diagrams in Markdown originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Esch-Laurent</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Systems Engineering? A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>622394b8c4d0d306772f4a08</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-systems-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T15:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was recently reading J. Martin's book Systems Engineering Guidebook – A Process for Developing Systems and Products. From it, I learned that systems engineering reduces manufacturing costs by 40% – did you know that? Neither did I. Even after taking a class where one of the topics was systems]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ultimate Guide To Push Notifications For Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/guide-push-notifications-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/guide-push-notifications-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are the benefits of using push notifications and what can you use them for? In this article, Lee Munroe explains how to implement them and which practices are best to follow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lee Munroe)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix the "Item Not Found" Windows Error When Deleting a File or Folder]]></title>
        <id>62585158ac55f60686c34d0a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-solve-item-not-found-windows-error-deleting-file-folder/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T18:32:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you use a Windows operating system, then you might have gotten this error before when trying to delete a file or folder.  It happens when, even though the file or folder is there, Windows says that it is failing to delete it because it can't find that file/folder]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use Storytelling In UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/use-storytelling-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/use-storytelling-ux/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Storytelling is a powerful tool for any UX designer. It helps create a product and understand the people who use it. In this article, Marli Mesibov takes a real-life example of an app she helped to build in 2017 and explains five steps you can use to help you build a story into your user experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marli Mesibov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy a Kotlin Microservice to AWS with App Runner]]></title>
        <id>624e81ffac55f60686c2f0bd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kotlin-aws-app-runner/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T06:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, everyone. In this step-by-step tutorial, I would like to show you how to deploy a Kotlin Microservice using Docker and AWS App Runner.  Together, we will learn:  * what exactly is AWS App Runner?   * how to configure AWS Command Line Interface on your local]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Wolak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Inspect an Element – Chrome Shortcut]]></title>
        <id>625807d4ac55f60686c348c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-inspect-an-element-chrome-shortcut/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T01:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Inspect Element feature of the Google Chrome browser is a powerful yet easy-to-use tool. It’s an important part of Chrome Developer Tools that you can use to check the source code of any website. But it doesn’t end there. You can take things further by changing the elements and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infinite Pagination in Flutter with Firebase, Riverpod, and Freeze]]></title>
        <id>6208aaaf56125b0677c64aaa</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/infinite-pagination-in-flutter-with-riverpod/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T23:46:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're developing an app, you'll have to decide how you want to load data. And this will typically bring up the issue of infinite pagination.  You likely won't be showing all of the available items in your DB to your users. You may fetch the first 10-20 items]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rutvik Tak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Azure Static Web Apps to Deploy an Angular App]]></title>
        <id>62549e60ac55f60686c32496</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-azure-static-web-apps-to-deploy-angular-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T23:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CI/CD has changed the way IT teams release new software versions.  In this tutorial I'll share my experience with Azure Static Web Apps – Azure's PaaS solution. I'll show you how you can take advantage of its flexibility to deploy an Angular App just by pushing your code to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Venturi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python List .append() – How to Add an Item to a List in Python]]></title>
        <id>6257f4fcac55f60686c34755</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-append-how-to-add-an-item-to-a-list-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T20:03:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lists are one of the most useful and versatile data types available in Python. Lists are a collection of arbitrary objects, just like arrays in other programming languages. In this tutorial you will learn:  * An overview of lists and how they are defined.  * Methods to insert]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write a Script to Change Your Zoom Background Every Day]]></title>
        <id>62563320ac55f60686c3361f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-a-script-to-change-zoom-background/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T18:05:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past few months, I've found a new use for the pictures that I've taken while hiking. I started using them as Zoom virtual backgrounds.  If you are anything like me and take a lot of pictures, it can be hard to decide which one looks good. And]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saransh Kataria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Docs Strikethrough – How to Cross Out Text in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>6256dd0eac55f60686c33b09</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-docs-strikethrough-how-to-cross-out-text-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T17:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're writing, sometimes you might want to strike through certain text. This means adding a horizontal line that runs through a piece of text.  Here is what it looks like: you are an awesome person.  These are various use cases for strikethroughs:  * To indicate that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Ready for a Job in Tech – Tips for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>62496868ac55f60686c2ccbc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-ready-for-a-job-in-tech/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T17:05:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few months back, I was invited to talk to a group of engineering students of a renowned college in India. I was supposed to interact with them, motivate them, and finally tell them, "What does the industry (the "job" world) look like?", "How can you get ready for it?"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When And How To Use Freelancers In Your Organization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/upwork-freelancers-organization/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/upwork-freelancers-organization/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you work in-house or run a digital agency, there are occasions when you will consider hiring freelancers to supplement your team. Today, we’ll take a look into a platform known as [Upwork](https://upwork.pxf.io/c/1221738/1245573/13634) and the best ways in finding the the right freelancers as well as integrating them into your team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modules in JavaScript – CommonJS and ESmodules Explained]]></title>
        <id>62560533ac55f60686c33336</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/modules-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T01:17:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we're going to take a look at modules in JavaScript. Modules are a technique heavily used in today's software design/architecture. First we're going to learn what they are and the different types of modules that exist. Then we're going to discuss why modules are useful.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Low-Code for Freelance Developers & Startups]]></title>
        <id>62577335ac55f60686c342d8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/low-code-for-freelance-developers-startups/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T01:17:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Low-code is a software development approach that requires little coding in order to build applications. It is made possible through a low-code platform. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use the Appsmith Low-Code platform.  Ania Kubów created this course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dot Symbol – Bullet Point in HTML Unicode]]></title>
        <id>6256c1d7ac55f60686c33a90</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dot-symbol-bullet-point-in-html-unicode/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T00:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In your HTML documents, you'll often need to make a list of items. And you can use bullet points for this purpose. You can show bullet points with the Unicode character (or entity) for bullet points. In this article, I will show you the Unicode and HTML entities for showing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React 18 New Features – Concurrent Rendering, Automatic Batching, and More]]></title>
        <id>6257472dac55f60686c341a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-18-new-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T21:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React 18 was released in March 2022. This release focuses on performance improvements and updating the rendering engine.  React 18 sets the foundation for concurrent rendering APIs that future React features will be built on top of.  In this tutorial, I will give a quick guide of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shruti Kapoor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with PysonDB]]></title>
        <id>62552369ac55f60686c329f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-started-with-pysondb/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T19:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often need to store some data while working on our personal projects. We can use a SQL or NoSQL database with a server, but that would require us to do a bit of setup.  In one of my previous articles, we saw a solution to this problem with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the slice() and splice() JavaScript Array Methods]]></title>
        <id>625664b6ac55f60686c33732</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-slice-and-splice-how-to-use-the-slice-and-splice-js-array-methods/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T19:17:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you are first learning JavaScript, it might be difficult to know the difference between the slice() and splice() array methods.  In this article, I will walk you through how to use the slice() and splice()  array methods using code examples.  How to use the slice() JavaScript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Closure in JavaScript – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>62527fd2ac55f60686c30fd4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-closures-explained-with-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T18:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we are going to talk about closures in JavaScript. I'll walk you through the definition of a closure, a simple day-to-day fetch utility closure example, and some of the advantages and disadvantages of using closures.  Table of Contents  * Prerequisites   * What are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keyur Paralkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python .zip() – Zip Function in Python]]></title>
        <id>624f2d28ac55f60686c2f644</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-zip-zip-function-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T18:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you use the zip() function in Python, it takes two or more data sets and "zips" them together. This returns an object containing pairs of items derived from the data sets. It groups these items in the order of their indexes.  Let me break it down a bit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CRUD Operations in JavaScript by Building TODO APP]]></title>
        <id>62508fa3ac55f60686c2feff</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-crud-operations-in-javascript-by-building-todo-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T17:57:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we're gonna learn how to do CRUD Operations in JavaScript by making a Todo App. Let's get started 🔥 This is the app we're making today:  * Live preview [https://crud-application-al9am9v2v-joyshaheb.vercel.app/]  * GitHub Repository [https://github.com/JoyShaheb/CRUD-Application] You can watch this tutorial on YouTube as well if you like 🎥]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joy Shaheb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing A Better Carousel UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/designing-better-carousel-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/designing-better-carousel-ux/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carousels don’t have a good reputation, and rightfully so. But we can make them more useful. **Best practices and guidelines** to improve the carousel design with honest scrolling direction, labels, thumbnails and grouped prev/next-buttons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TypeScript with GraphQL using TypeGraphQL]]></title>
        <id>624cb56dac55f60686c2e839</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-typescript-with-graphql/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T00:18:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is TypeScript? TypeScript is a superset of JavaScript that compiles to JavaScript for production. It's like JavaScript, but with powers – type powers. TypeScript helps you build typed applications that help you avoid static type errors in those apps and make predictable code. Without TypeScript, a function declared to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Glassmorphism? How to Create a Glass Card in Figma]]></title>
        <id>624640c4138a19064b06a073</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/glassmorphism-how-to-create-a-glass-card-in-figma/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T00:04:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Glassmorphism is a growing trend in user interface design. It makes your designs look modern and elegant. ‌‌‌‌In this article, we'll be learning about what glassmorphism means, how accessible it is, and how to design a simple glass card.‌‌ What is Glassmorphism? Glassmorphism is a style which, as the name]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Animated Landing Page with GSAP and TailwindCSS]]></title>
        <id>624fec14ac55f60686c2fa12</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-animated-landing-page-with-gsap-and-tailwindcss/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T23:56:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animations are a crucial part of any great website. Why? When done well, animations vastly improve the user experience of any site, as they help make sites fun and intuitive to use. This article will show you how to build an animated landing page with the help of a JavaScript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Akinyemi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started With React – A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>6250281aac55f60686c2fbcb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-started-with-react-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T23:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React (also known as React.js or ReactJS) is a free and open-source front-end JavaScript framework for creating UI components-based user interfaces.  React is maintained by Meta (previously Facebook) and a community of individual developers and organizations. According to the 2021 Stack Overflow’s developer’s survey [https://insights.stackoverflow.com/survey/2021#section-most-popular-technologies-web-frameworks] , React.js surpassed jQuery]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Update Node and NPM to the Latest Version]]></title>
        <id>622e87c6c3e3d106805daa1f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-update-node-and-npm-to-the-latest-version/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T20:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Node is a runtime environment that allows developers to execute JavaScript code outside the browser, on the server-side. NPM, on the other hand, is a package manager for publishing JavaScript packages (also known as Node modules) to the npm registry [https://www.npmjs.com/]. You can also use it to install packages to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP Error 504 – 504 Gateway Timeout Status Code Explained]]></title>
        <id>624eee4fac55f60686c2f457</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/http-error-504-gateway-timeout-status-code-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T20:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While surfing the internet, we are able to interact with web servers through HyperText Transfer Protocol (HTTP) requests. These requests are sent from the client (our browsers) to the server before we get a response.  HTTP status codes allows us know if our request to the server was successful]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows vs MacOS vs Linux – Operating System Handbook]]></title>
        <id>624aff1fac55f60686c2d22b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/an-introduction-to-operating-systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T20:14:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article I'm going to give a brief introduction to operating systems and compare the three main OSs that are out there nowadays. First we're going to review what an OS is and little history about them. Then, we'll review the main features and differences of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Terraform and AWS by Building a Dev Environment]]></title>
        <id>6255d209ac55f60686c33156</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-terraform-and-aws-by-building-a-dev-environment/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T19:32:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform is an open-source infrastructure as code software tool that makes it easy to programmatically to set up infrastructure on a variety of cloud service providers. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Terraform and AWS to setup a development]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python IDE – Best IDEs and Editors for Python]]></title>
        <id>62552a7eac55f60686c32a7f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-ide-best-ides-and-editors-for-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T19:28:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Much of your experience as a developer will depend on what program you've chosen to write your code in. A good integrated development environment (IDE) or Code Editor can really boost your productivity. The problem with popular languages like Python is that every IDE or code editor under the sun]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farhan Hasin Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Checkmark Symbol – HTML for Checkmark Unicode]]></title>
        <id>62557467ac55f60686c32c28</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/checkmark-symbol-html-for-checkmark-unicode/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T19:17:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you take a look at your keyboard, you'll see that there’s no key for typing a checkmark. You could decide to copy the checkmark symbol from the internet and paste it directly into your HTML code, but an easier way to do it is to use the appropriate Unicode]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Colorful VSCode Extensions – How to Personalize Your Editor]]></title>
        <id>623e2e30138a19064b065122</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-colorful-vscode-extensions-for-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T18:19:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Engineers spend a good portion of their day writing code in their integrated development environment, or IDE for short. And Visual Studio Code [https://code.visualstudio.com/] is one of the best free IDE's on the market.  I find that personalizing my IDE helps me enjoy the time I spend using it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie Pina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add a CSS Lens Flare to Photos for a Bright Touch]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364385</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/add-a-css-lens-flare-to-photos-for-a-bright-touch/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T17:10:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m a big fan of movies by J.J. Abrams. I enjoy their tight plots, quippy dialog, and of course: anamorphic lens flares. Filmmakers like Abrams use lens flare to add a dash of ‘homemade’ realism to their movies, …
Add a CSS Lens Flare to Photos for a Bright Touch originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shimin Zhang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Around The Artifacts Of Design Systems (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/artifacts-design-systems/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/artifacts-design-systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like many things, a design system isn’t ever a finished thing — it’s a journey. How we go about that journey can affect the things we produce along the way. Before diving in and starting to plan anything out, be clear about where the benefits and the risks might lie.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dan Donald)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Good API Documentation]]></title>
        <id>6248ec02ac55f60686c2c9f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-api-documentation-like-a-pro/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T02:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine that you just bought a new home theater system and you go to set it up. What do you do first? Thank goodness you have a handy device manual to help you out. You just need to follow the steps detailed in the manual, and voilà! Your home theater]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maybell Obadoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Attributes – Class and Instance Attribute Examples]]></title>
        <id>6252cd94ac55f60686c312e0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-attributes-class-and-instance-attribute-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T02:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When creating a class in Python, you'll usually create attributes that may be shared across every object of a class or attributes that will be unique to each object of the class. In this article, we'll see the difference between class attributes and instance attributes in Python with examples. Before]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is HTML? What Does HTML Stand For? [Solved]]]></title>
        <id>624bed98ac55f60686c2e0f3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-html-what-does-html-stand-for-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T01:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML is one of the fundamental technologies you can learn when starting out in web development. HTML code is present in every single webpage online. Once you have a good grasp of the fundamental concepts of the language, you will be well equipped to move on to the two other]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up a Virtual Environment in Python – And Why It's Useful]]></title>
        <id>6250c642ac55f60686c3023c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-setup-virtual-environments-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T20:46:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing software with Python, a basic approach is to install Python on your machine, install all your required libraries via the terminal, write all your code in a single .py file or notebook, and run your Python program in the terminal. This is a common approach for a lot]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Sanwo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Sandbox Tutorial – How to Enable Sandbox On Windows]]></title>
        <id>62515952ac55f60686c304b7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-enable-sandbox-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T20:13:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Sandbox is a temporary lightweight desktop environment that you can use to safely run Windows applications in an isolated space.  The software or applications that you install inside the Windows sandbox environment remain "sandboxed", and they all run separately from the host machine. So whatever happens in the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn the C++ Programming Language]]></title>
        <id>624447b2138a19064b0683f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-learn-the-c-programming-language/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T17:10:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the early days of computer programming, programmers had to write individual instructions in the Assembly language one by one.  Later on programming languages like FORTRAN and COBOL were created. The problem with these languages was that they were targeted at a certain group of people – FORTRAN for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farhan Hasin Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DNS Server Not Responding – Service Unavailable DNS Failure [Solved]]]></title>
        <id>624e9e37ac55f60686c2f16b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dns-server-not-responding-service-unavailable-dns-failure-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T15:59:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, you might suddenly discover that you can’t access the internet on your computer because of the error “DNS server not responding”. If you run a troubleshooter for the issue, you'll get a message like the below: In your Chrome browser, you might also get an error like the one]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create and Upload Your First Python Package to PyPI]]></title>
        <id>624da2d3ac55f60686c2eb3c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-and-upload-your-first-python-package-to-pypi/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T15:40:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few weeks ago, I wanted to learn how to build my first Python package, and I was trying to figure out where to start.  Well, I got confused and a bit stressed trying to find a simple and easy tutorial I could use to get started. For this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rochdi Khalid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Git Stash Command]]></title>
        <id>62459f78138a19064b069268</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-stash-commands/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T15:05:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's say you're working on a serious feature of a branch in Git – like revamping the hero section of your marketing page. You'll want to start doing experiments in your Revamp/Marketing-page-hero-section branch without screwing up master or main branch. Then suddenly you get call from your coworker to fix]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi⚡</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Resource Loading With fetchpriority, a New Priority Hint]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/boost-resource-loading-new-priority-hint-fetchpriority/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/boost-resource-loading-new-priority-hint-fetchpriority/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new attribute will enable us to fine-tune relative resource priority, improve LCP performance, deprioritize JavaScript fetch calls, and much more. Let’s check out fetchpriority and explore some potential use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python If-Else Statement Example]]></title>
        <id>62530365ac55f60686c316e5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-if-else-statement-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T17:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If-Else statements – AKA conditional logic – are the bedrock of programming. And Python has these in spades. Python offers several options for evaluating variables, their states, and whether specific conditions are met:  * Vanilla if-else statements  * if statements without the else part  * nested if-else]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PMP Certification Cost – 2022 Exam Fees, Degree Requirements, and Years of Experience]]></title>
        <id>6252eea7ac55f60686c315af</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pmp-certification-cost-degree-experience/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T15:44:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Project Management Professional (PMP) is widely seen by project managers as the "gold standard" credential. Many senior PM roles now require you to be PMP certified. So if you have been working as a PM for a few years, this guide will show you how you can take the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[List to String Python – join() Syntax Example]]></title>
        <id>625208b3ac55f60686c30de0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-to-string-join-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T23:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you want to convert your Python lists into strings. This tutorial will show you an example of how you can do this. But first, let's explore the difference between the Python list data structure and the Python string data structure. What is a List in Python? In Python, a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image File Types – The .jpeg, .svg, and .png Picture Format Extensions Explained]]></title>
        <id>62518273ac55f60686c30623</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/image-file-types-picture-format-extensions-jpeg-gif-png-svg-tiff/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T22:26:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you’re working with images, it’s important to understand the different file types. Which format is best for what application? In this tutorial, we’re going to explain the most common image file types, and when you should use them. Note that this is a short, non-technical article. If you want]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic Data-Fetching In An Authenticated Next.js App]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/dynamic-data-fetching-authenticated-nextjs-app/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/dynamic-data-fetching-authenticated-nextjs-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data is among the most important things that make up a web application or a conventional native app. We need data to be able to see and perhaps understand the purpose of an application. In this article, we’ll look at another approach to obtaining data in an application that requires authentication or authorization using Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Caleb Olojo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Force Delete a File – Windows Command Prompt cmd delete]]></title>
        <id>624c24d2ac55f60686c2e356</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-force-delete-a-file-windows-command-prompt-cmd-delete/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T07:11:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a Windows computer, you might want to delete files to free up disk space, or because you don't want the file(s) on your computer anymore. But sometimes, it seems impossible to delete a file for various reasons. These include the file being open in another program, lack of write]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Break The Code 2.0: A Browser Game Where You Solve Missions Using Coding Skills]]></title>
        <id>624f8558ac55f60686c2f79a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/break-the-code-2-game/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T03:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Break The Code 2.0 is a new browser game that sends you back in time to the year 1999. You complete codebreaking missions using your programming knowledge and your puzzle-solving intuition. The game is spread across 4 drives worth of missions:  * The /g1/ drive – "BoxOfChocolates"  *]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a DNS Server? DNS Servers Explained]]></title>
        <id>6251f9feac55f60686c30c4e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-dns-server/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T21:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The web would not work at all without DNS servers. They are responsible for translating domain names into IP addresses. Then computers use those IP addresses to locate and connect to web servers, and send users to the right websites. Many people first learned about the DNS system in October]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Margin VS Padding – What is the Difference? [Solved]]]></title>
        <id>6251f744ac55f60686c30bf9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-margin-vs-padding-what-is-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to CSS, there are a lot of properties that control the spacing of elements on a page. Two of the most common properties are margin and padding. Both margin and padding control the amount of space around an element, but they do it in different ways. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design a Scalable Mobile App With Figma Variants]]></title>
        <id>624ca9a4ac55f60686c2e7f9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/design-a-scalable-mobile-app-with-figma-variants/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T12:15:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Figma is a popular graphics editor and prototyping tool. Figma variants can streamline your frontend design process by allowing you to group and organize similar components into a single container. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you learn how to use Figma variants]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[flushdns – How to Flush DNS with the Windows ipconfig /flushdns Command]]></title>
        <id>624bfc9bac55f60686c2e0ff</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flushdns-how-to-flush-dns-with-the-windows-ipconfig-flushdns-command/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T03:41:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You've probably noticed that, after visiting a website for the first time, the website loads much quicker the next time you visit. This is because your operating system, or browser in the case of Google Chrome, cache IP addresses and DNS (Domain Name System) information of any website you visit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS IAM – Policy, Access Roles, Resources Explained, and Why They're Useful]]></title>
        <id>62435e6e138a19064b068027</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-introduction-to-iam-i-wish-i-had/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T02:50:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IAM, or Identity and Access Management, is one of the most common terms you'll hear in cloud-native environments. But what does it do? And if you're already familiar with IAM, how long did it take you to fully understand it? I will explain the main concepts behind this massive family]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Periklis Gkolias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to do a Hanging Indent in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>6250a2faac55f60686c2ff69</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-do-a-hanging-indent-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T21:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hanging indent is an easy way to make your documents look more professional. Google Docs has built in functionality to create this. What is a Hanging Indent? A hanging indent is a type of indentation where the first line of a paragraph is not indented, but subsequent lines in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Better Breadcrumbs]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/designing-better-breadcrumbs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/designing-better-breadcrumbs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this series of articles, we highlight design patterns and techniques to design better interfaces. You can also find more examples in [“Smart Interface Design Patterns”](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com/), a 6h-video course with 100s of hand-picked examples, curated by Vitaly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Devs For Ukraine, A Free Online Charity Conference 🇺🇦]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/devs-for-ukraine/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/devs-for-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Devs For Ukraine](https://www.devsforukraine.io/) is a free online charity conference organized by the lovely people at Remote. Two days filled with talks from engineering leaders around the globe, in support of Ukraine. April 25–26.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Command Line for Beginners – How to Use the Terminal Like a Pro]]></title>
        <id>6244f93a138a19064b068b9e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/command-line-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-05T16:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we'll take a good look at the command line (also known as the CLI, console, terminal or shell). The command line is one of the most useful and efficient tools we have as developers and as computer users in general. But using it can feel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Get Work Done: Wrangling Stakeholders And Overcoming Obstacles]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/stakeholders-overcoming-obstacles/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/stakeholders-overcoming-obstacles/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you work in-house or for an external agency, we all share one challenge — dealing with stakeholders, be they your boss, colleagues, or clients. In this post, veteran web designer Paul Boag shares his approach to getting things done in even the most challenging organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Package Manager – Complete Guide to NPM and Yarn]]></title>
        <id>624b0547ac55f60686c2d2e1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-package-manager-npm-and-yarn/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-05T00:08:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A package manager is a tool developers use to automate finding, downloading, installing, configuring, upgrading, and removing a system's packages. This article will show you all you need to get started with package managers like NPM and Yarn. But why exactly do we need a package manager in our development]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi Sofela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Beginner's Guide to Sass]]></title>
        <id>6233c160cdcd57069ddfadb8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-beginners-guide-to-sass/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T23:39:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered what SASS stands for? Or perhaps you already know what it is but haven't taken the time to study and use it. Whether you're learning about it for the first time, or want to brush up on your knowledge of the subject, this is the article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Mitolu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Types of Hard Drives – SATA, PATA, SCSI, and SSD]]></title>
        <id>624ad0f4ac55f60686c2d118</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/types-of-hard-drives-sata-pata-scsi-and-more-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T23:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hard drive is a non-volatile hardware component on a computer that acts as the storage for all digital content. It holds program files, documents, pictures, videos, music, and more. The non-volatile nature of hard drives means they don’t lose data, even if power is lost. Due to this, they]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make an Image Search App in React using the Unsplash API]]></title>
        <id>6249d59dac55f60686c2ce11</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-an-image-search-app-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T22:19:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unsplash is a site where you can download free and unlicensed images and use them as you see fit. In this tutorial, we will make an Image Search App using the Unsplash API to get access to its enormous collection of images and also download them. Before starting the development]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ateev Duggal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Project – How to Build a Wordle Clone using Python and Rich]]></title>
        <id>624a520eac55f60686c2cfa0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-wordle-clone-using-python-and-rich/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T20:21:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wordle is a popular game where you guess a five-letter word in six tries. After each guess, the color of the tiles will change to show how close your guess was to the word.  It is similar to the Hangman game [https://ireadblog.com/posts/124/hangman-game-using-python] which I've already shown you how to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docker Mount Volume – How To Mount a Local Directory]]></title>
        <id>62402130138a19064b0666c6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/docker-mount-volume-guide-how-to-mount-a-local-directory/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T20:08:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers make software engineering easier and more efficient, and Docker [https://www.docker.com/] containers are popular and easy to use.  Containers are essential for local development. They let you test-run your applications in local environments and start building out the required infrastructure. Docker containers are immutable by nature. This means that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sigl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thunder Client – An Alternative Way to Test Restful APIs]]></title>
        <id>623646bccdcd57069ddfb98f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/thunder-client-for-vscode/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T19:09:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article will teach you an alternative approach to testing client APIs using Thunder Client, an open-source extension available on VS Code marketplace [https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=rangav.vscode-thunder-client] .  You will not need to download any tools to do this, since you can get it done right within VS Code. The article covers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sule-Balogun Olanrewaju Ganiu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding CDN Caching to a Vite Build]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364166</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/adding-cdn-caching-to-a-vite-build/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T18:25:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content delivery networks, or CDNs, allow you to improve the delivery of your website’s static resources, most notably, with CDN caching. They do this by serving your content from edge locations, which are located all over the world. When a …
Adding CDN Caching to a Vite Build originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientific Computing in Golang with the Gonum Package]]></title>
        <id>624515df138a19064b068e7c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/scientific-computing-in-golang-using-gonum/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T15:49:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll introduce you to Gonum, a package you can use to perform scientific computations in the Go programming language. Here's what we'll cover in this intermediate tutorial:  * What is Gonum?  * Why use Gonum  * How to install and set up Gonum]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ukeje Chukwuemeriwo Goodness</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The freeCodeCamp World Translation Summit 2022 – Join the Translation Effort]]></title>
        <id>6244b25c138a19064b0686d0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-freecodecamp-world-translation-summit-2022-join-the-translation-effort/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T14:23:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Translation is a powerful tool that can change lives. Everyone should have access to free learning resources in their native language.  To achieve this, freeCodeCamp has started translating our curriculum into dozens of world languages, with the help of thousands of volunteers around the world. To honor our translators]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ExamPro Cloud Developer Environment Certification — Pass the Exam with This 12 Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>623f380c138a19064b06605b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/exampro-cloud-developer-environment-certification-gitpod-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T13:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a web-application developer looking to learn how to leverage the cloud or want to become a cloud developer, the ExamPro Cloud Development Environment (EXP-CDE-01) is the first step. What is a Cloud Developer Environment?  A Cloud Developer Environment (CDE) is a:  *  code editor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Brown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Progressively Enhanced, Accessible, Filterable And Paginated List]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/accessible-filterable-paginated-list-11ty-alpinejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/accessible-filterable-paginated-list-11ty-alpinejs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever wondered how to build a paginated list that works with and without JavaScript? In this article, Manuel explains how you can leverage the power of Progressive Enhancement and do just that with Eleventy and Alpine.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Manuel Matuzović)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Pass Callback Functions to String.replace() in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>6246e84d138a19064b06a1c9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-pass-callback-functions-to-string-replace-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T20:14:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that the string .replace() method accepts a callback function? I just discovered it today and thought I'd share. What do you need this function for? Why does it exist? I'll answer all these questions as you go through this article. The replace() Method The replace() string method]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Rate Limiter using Bucket4J and Redis]]></title>
        <id>6245914c138a19064b0690bb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rate-limiting-with-bucket4j-and-redis/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T19:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial we will learn how to implement rate limiting in a scaled service. We will use the Bucket4J [https://github.com/vladimir-bukhtoyarov/bucket4j]  library to implement it and we will use Redis [https://redis.io/] as a distributed cache. Why Use Rate Limiting? Let's get started with some basics to make sure we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhinav Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Full Stack Developer? 2022 Full Stack Engineer Guide]]></title>
        <id>6228642863ded806bb9e6f73</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-full-stack-developer-full-stack-engineer-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T18:42:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Full-stack developer roles are among the most highly sought after positions in the current job market. But what exactly is full-stack web development, and how do you become a full-stack developer? In this article, you will first learn what the term full-stack means. Then, you will see some suggested technologies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Inner Join – How to Join 3 Tables in SQL and MySQL]]></title>
        <id>6164065d804854468fda843b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-inner-join-how-to-join-3-tables-in-sql-and-mysql/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T18:19:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with your database, you might need to put together data from a few different tables. This article will show you how. I have already written about SQL joins here [/news/sql-join-types-inner-join-vs-outer-join-example/] and here [/news/sql-left-join-example-join-statement-syntax/], but let's take a moment to review how a join works first, and particularly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilenia Magoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NextJS and HarperDB Tutorial –Build a Full Stack Productivity Timer App]]></title>
        <id>6244a14e138a19064b0686c7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nextjs-and-harperdb-tutorial-build-a-full-stack-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T16:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building full stack applications can be tough. You have to think about frontend, APIs, databases, authentication - and how all of these things work together. So, in this article, I'll show you how to do all of those things using NextJS and HarperDB. We'll be building a full stack task]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The What, When, Why And How Of Next.js’ New Middleware Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/next-js-middleware-feature/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/next-js-middleware-feature/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js’ recent 12.0 release included a new beta feature: middleware. For a detailed explanation, you can read all about it in Sam’s previous article, “[Next.js Wildcard Subdomains](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/nextjs-wildcard-subdomains/)”. This article, on the other hand, dives into the overall concept of middleware and how handy it can be in building things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sam Poder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Apps with Firebase]]></title>
        <id>6245d985138a19064b069946</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-apps-with-firebase/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T00:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firebase is a platform developed by Google for creating mobile and web applications.  We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Firebase. This is the perfect course for beginners.  After learning the basics of Firebase, you will learn how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shell Scripting for Beginners – How to Write Bash Scripts in Linux]]></title>
        <id>623cc7e0138a19064b06474d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/shell-scripting-crash-course-how-to-write-bash-scripts-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T19:26:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shell scripting is an important part of process automation in Linux. Scripting helps you write a sequence of commands in a file and then execute them.  This saves you time because you don't have to write certain commands again and again. You can perform daily tasks efficiently and even]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shopify Email Automation – How to Automatically Send Emails]]></title>
        <id>62421c54138a19064b0672c6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/shopify-email-automation/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T17:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Email automation is not something new in the e-commerce space. And it's a pretty simple and straightforward concept. Email automation is all about sending emails to customers based on events that occur on your website, like abandoned cart emails, order confirmation emails, shipping confirmation emails, and so on. The result?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edan Ben-Atar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Augmented Reality Full Course]]></title>
        <id>6245d736138a19064b0698d9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/augmented-reality-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T16:40:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Augmented reality is a technology that lets people superimpose digital content, such as images, sounds & text, over a real-world environment. We just published a 12-hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you about augmented reality from a theoretical and practical perspective. Priyanshu Bhattaharjee developed this course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[charAt() in Java – How to Use the Java charAt() Method]]></title>
        <id>62445137138a19064b068407</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/charat-in-java-how-to-use-the-java-charat-method-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T16:10:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The charAt() method in Java returns the char value of a character in a string at a given or specified index. In this article, we'll see how to use the charAt() method starting with it's syntax and then through a few examples/use cases.  How to Use the Java charAt()]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Convert Video Files to a Gif in Python]]></title>
        <id>6245705d138a19064b068f59</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-video-files-to-gif-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T16:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I was able to convert some video files to a gif as I needed them in gif format for some of my articles. I decided to show you how I did it in 3 lines of code, so you can save yourself the extra effort of looking up a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Time For Reflection (April 2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s welcome the new month with some new wallpapers. Designed with love by artists and designers from across the globe, they are available in versions with and without a calendar for April 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Migrate a Database in PHP Using Phinx]]></title>
        <id>62418eca138a19064b066d98</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/easy-database-migrations-in-php-using-phinx/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T23:59:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building modern web applications usually involves a lot of data. Managing these data (databases) during development and production can be a lot.  This is especially tru if there's more than one developer, and multiple environments where changes have to be manually implemented. Database migrations help developers manage these changes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zubair Idris Aweda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Undo Merge – How to Revert the Last Merge Commit in Git]]></title>
        <id>62442bd2138a19064b06836a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-undo-merge-how-to-revert-the-last-merge-commit-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Branching is an integral part of Git because it lets you work without tampering with code that's already in production. When you finish working with a branch other than main, you'll want to merge it with the main so the feature or bug fix you just integrated will be reflected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Schedule a Task With Firebase Scheduled Cloud Functions]]></title>
        <id>62418f22138a19064b066da1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-schedule-a-task-with-firebase-cloud-functions/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T17:14:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I work on an app that removes the background of any image. The app will have a freemium plan, which means that I will offer a free number of credits to all users, and if they need more credits, they will need to buy more. My Android and iOS app]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dragos Ivanov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Benefits of a Student Email Address]]></title>
        <id>623d7224138a19064b06490a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/top-benefits-of-student-email-address/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T17:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent years, various tech companies and organizations have started supporting students who have an interest in and passion for tech. Many companies give their premium services to students for free, and others offer discounts on their products. If you're a student, basically all you need to take advantage of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hillary Nyakundi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tricks to Cut Corners Using CSS Mask and Clip-Path Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364279</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/cut-corners-using-css-mask-and-clip-path-properties/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T16:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently covered creating fancy borders with CSS mask properties, and now we are going to cut the corners with CSS mask and clip-path! A lot of techniques exist to cut different shapes from the corners of any element. …
Tricks to Cut Corners Using CSS Mask and Clip-Path Properties originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing A Better Infinite Scroll]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/designing-better-infinite-scroll/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/designing-better-infinite-scroll/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this series of articles, we highlight design patterns and techniques to design better interfaces. You can also find more examples in [“Smart Interface Design Patterns”](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com/), a 6h-video course with 100s of hand-picked examples, curated by Vitaly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>