<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-03-12T00:54:28.390Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Custom API Gateway with Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-custom-api-gateway-with-node-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-custom-api-gateway-with-node-js/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T23:16:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the era of microservices [https://www.brightsidecodes.com/blog/understanding-microservices-and-api-gateway] , where applications are divided into smaller, independently deployable services, managing and securing the communication between these services becomes crucial. This is where an API gateway comes into play.  An API gateway serves as a central entry point for all client requests. It]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Iroro Chadere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client-Side Form Handling with JavaScript – Explained with Example Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/form-validation-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/form-validation-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T21:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML forms are essential components of most websites and web apps. They enable interaction between users and those websites, and are a key concept for web developers to understand.  This comprehensive guide covers various aspects of HTML forms, from how to create and structure forms to JavaScript interaction and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samyak Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Success At Scale: Last Chance For Pre-Sale Price]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/success-at-scale-book-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/success-at-scale-book-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our next book, “Success at Scale” is finally at the printer, which means we’ll be shipping books soon. It’s also your last chance to get the book at the presale price. Get your copy and save now!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Having Fun in Tech with  CTO and Meme Queen Cassidy Williams (Cassidoo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-cassidy-williams-cassidoo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-cassidy-williams-cassidoo/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T15:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week's episode of The freeCodeCamp Podcast, I interview developer-turned-CTO Cassidy Williams, also known as Cassidoo on Twitter and TikTok. She's worked in tech for over a decade as a developer at several tech companies, including Amazon and Netlify. She has gradually progressed to senior developer and now CTO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Hooks – How to Use the useState & useEffect Hooks in Your Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-usestate-and-useeffect-hooks-in-your-project/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-usestate-and-useeffect-hooks-in-your-project/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T15:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hooks allow function components to have access to state and other React features, such as lifecycle methods. These Hook features were introduced to React version 16.8. One of the interesting things about the Hook features is that they let you use React without classes. This, in turn, helps simplify your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoro Emmanuel Nzube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Relationship Based Access Control (ReBAC)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/implement-relationship-based-access-control/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/implement-relationship-based-access-control/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital age, managing who can access what resources is more critical than ever. That's where ReBAC comes in. It's a fresh take on authorization, focusing on the relationships between different entities rather than just assigning static roles or attributes. Traditional access control methods, like Role-Based Access Control (RBAC),]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Imran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SVG Toggle Button Tutorial – How to Handle Dark Mode with CSS and JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-dark-mode-with-css-and-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-dark-mode-with-css-and-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T13:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can you detect dark mode in CSS and JavaScript? How can you manually override it with a toggle button? And how can you create a sun and moon icon with SVG? In this tutorial, you will learn how to detect dark mode in CSS and JavaScript, and you will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hunor Márton Borbély</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern CSS Tooltips And Speech Bubbles (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/modern-css-tooltips-speech-bubbles-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/modern-css-tooltips-speech-bubbles-part2/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1 of this series, Temani Afif explored different CSS techniques to create tooltip shapes. The main challenge was to rely on a single element and create optimized code that could easily be controlled using CSS variables to update the size, shape, and position of the tail. In this second part, you are going explore more shapes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a CRUD API – NodeJS and Express Project for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-crud-api-project/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-crud-api-project/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T11:04:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An API is a technology that powers communication between software applications on the internet. API stands for Application Programming Interface, and it is basically a set of rules and protocols that define how different software can interact with each other.  Imagine having two different programs: program A and program]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Yakubu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a 3D Art Gallery with Three.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-3d-art-gallery-with-threejs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-3d-art-gallery-with-threejs/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T16:21:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[3D web experiences can provide engaging and interactive user interfaces. And one of the best JavaScript libraries to create these experiences is Three.js. We just posed a comprehensive Three.js course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This course is designed to guide you through the process of building an interactive 3D]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up React Testing Library With Next.js – A Step-by-Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-setup-react-testing-library-with-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-setup-react-testing-library-with-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T15:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, you will learn how to set up React Testing Library in Next.js. We'll also talk about why you should always test your React applications. I'll discuss the features and benefits of using the React Testing Library to test your React applications and how to configure it with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an Inventory List with React useReducer, Axios, and JSON Server]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-an-inventory-list-with-react-usereducer-axios-and-json-server/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-an-inventory-list-with-react-usereducer-axios-and-json-server/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T15:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to web development, it's hard to ignore React.js. It has been one of the leading user interface libraries for a decade, and it supports a lot of popular frameworks like Next.js in the background. If you are a React developer, you likely appreciate its component-based architecture, uni-directional]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Tailwind CSS in Spanish – Full Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-tailwind-css-in-spanish-full-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-tailwind-css-in-spanish-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T15:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tailwind is a CSS framework with pre-defined classes that you can combine to build modern and responsive websites. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org Spanish YouTube channel [https://www.youtube.com/freecodecampespanol] that will teach you Tailwind CSS. You will go from the basics to actually building your own real-world projects. By]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an Interactive Button Component in Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-interactive-button-component-in-figma/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-interactive-button-component-in-figma/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:44:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Designers are always searching for tools that help ease their workflow and create innovative solutions for their users. This ranges from components, style guides, and design systems, to plugins and extensions. In this article, we're going to look at components as features which can help boost your efficiency as a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Cross-Browser Compatibility? How to Build Websites that Work Everywhere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-cross-browser-compatibility/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-cross-browser-compatibility/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:26:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When building for the web, it's easy to develop tunnel vision and only build for yourself. You may overlook the diverse needs of your audience and focus solely on your preferences and how things look on your preferred browser. This can cause you to miss out on crucial functionality aspects]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ophy Boamah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Basic CMS with Google Sheets and React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-basic-cms-with-google-sheets-and-reactjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-basic-cms-with-google-sheets-and-reactjs/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T17:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital landscape, creating a content management system (CMS) that is both cost-effective and easy to maintain can be difficult, especially if you're operating on a tight budget.  This tutorial will show you a solution that leverages Google Sheets as a makeshift database and React to build the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Venturi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use HTML Forms – HTML Form Basics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-html-forms/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-html-forms/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T10:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML forms are used to get information from users. They are widely used in webpages or apps for surveys or registration processes.  HTML form basics include the common HTML elements, tags, attributes, concepts, or best practices required for you to create good HTML forms. The collected data is sent]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelechukwu Isaac Awoke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End Of My Gatsby Journey]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/end-of-gatsby-journey/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/end-of-gatsby-journey/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[“Gatsby headaches”](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/gatsby-headaches-i18n-part-1/) are over. Juan Diego Rodríguez reflects on his decision to stop using Gatsby as his go-to framework. Through a detailed examination of its strengths and weaknesses, he provides valuable insights and alternative options for developers navigating their tooling choices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction to Mistral AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/an-introduction-to-mistral-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/an-introduction-to-mistral-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T07:22:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI is a new player in the field of artificial intelligence. It is promoted as a strong open-source competitor of ChatGPT (which is closed source). In this article, we’ll explore what Mistral AI is, its use cases, and how it compares to ChatGPT. Plus, I’ll show you a simple]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Prompt Engineering for Content Creators – Full Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-prompt-engineering-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-prompt-engineering-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T21:40:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a content creator in today's digital age, mastering prompt engineering is not just beneficial—it's essential. Prompt engineering refines your ability to communicate effectively with AI tools like ChatGPT, transforming them from mere tools into powerful allies in content creation. This guide is designed to help you unlock the potential]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Audio to Text using OpenAI Whisper]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-turn-audio-to-text-using-openai-whisper/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-turn-audio-to-text-using-openai-whisper/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T13:02:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you know what OpenAI Whisper is? It’s the latest AI model from OpenAI that helps you to automatically convert speech to text. Transforming audio into text is now simpler and more accurate, thanks to OpenAI’s Whisper. This article will guide you through using Whisper to convert spoken words into]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Ensure Open Source License Compliance in Your Business]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ensure-open-source-license-compliance-in-business/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ensure-open-source-license-compliance-in-business/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T11:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're using open source code in your operations, you'll want to manage things properly or potentially face legal issues, financial penalties, and damage to your reputation.  You don't need a law degree to avoid problems, but you should definitely familiarize yourself with some basic principles. This article comes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Microsoft Fabric? How to Build a Customer Segmentation Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-microsoft-fabric/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-microsoft-fabric/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T01:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Fabric is a data analytics tool that can help you streamline all your data needs and workflows, from data integration to analytics and engineering. In this guide, I'll explain what Microsoft Fabric is in more detail, how it works, and walk you through building a project with it. If]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benny Ifeanyi Iheagwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn C# Programming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-c-sharp-programming/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-c-sharp-programming/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T17:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C# is a popular programming language used for developing a wide array of applications, including web, mobile, desktop, and gaming applications, providing a robust platform for developers to build dynamic and scalable solutions across various industries. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Solve the Producer-Consumer Problem in Java using Multithreading]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-multithreading-producer-consumer-problem/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-multithreading-producer-consumer-problem/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T17:48:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concurrency is an important part of Java applications. Each application has multiple processes running at the same time. This helps utilize resources efficiently and improve performance. Multithreading is a method of achieving concurrency. It uses the concept of threads – lightweight processes – to execute multiple tasks in parallel. A]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practice Your Coding Skills by Building a Program in Different Ways]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/practice-coding-skills-by-building-a-program-different-ways/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/practice-coding-skills-by-building-a-program-different-ways/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T15:39:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While we have 365 days in other years, this year (2024) is special because it has one ‘extra’ day.  So in the spirit of Leap Day, let's practice some coding to understand various aspects of programming. We'll focus on the same program but from different perspectives.  Our example]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niladri S. Jyoti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up A Django Admin Site]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-a-django-admin-site/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-a-django-admin-site/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T14:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Django admin site provides developers with a simple yet effective way to manage their models and build sustainable projects. It allows you to create, view, update, and remove records from your applications.  In this article, you will learn how to register your models with your admin site, create]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Poromon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Sets in Python – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-sets-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-sets-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T12:54:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the vast landscape of Python programming, understanding data structures is akin to possessing a versatile toolkit. Among the essential tools in this arsenal is the Python set. Sets in Python offer a unique way to organize and manipulate data. Let's embark on a journey to unravel the mysteries of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BERT Explained – The Key to Advanced Language Models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/bert-explained-the-key-to-advanced-language-models/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/bert-explained-the-key-to-advanced-language-models/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T12:06:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how Google seems to understand exactly what you mean, even when your search terms are a bit off? Or how your favorite voice assistant can comprehend complex questions? The secret behind much of this smart technology is a powerful tool called BERT. In this article, I’ll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Lists in Python – Explained with Example Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-lists-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-lists-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T20:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, lists are a cornerstones of data organization and manipulation – so I think they deserve a thorough exploration.  This article delves into how to create and manipulate lists in Python, some advanced functionalities, and some practical applications of lists. You can get all the source code from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caching vs Content Delivery Networks – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/caching-vs-content-delivery-network/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/caching-vs-content-delivery-network/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T19:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of network optimization, Content Delivery Networks (CDNs) and caching play a vital role in improving website performance and user experience.  And while both aim to speed up website loading times, they have distinct purposes and mechanisms.  In this tutorial, we'll dive deep into the details]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anamika Ahmed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Compress Files to ".gz" on the Windows Operating System]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-files-to-gzip-on-windows/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-files-to-gzip-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T19:15:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may often need to compress files and folders for various reasons. And "Gzip" compression is a good choice for many scenarios.  Recently, I have faced an issue where I needed to compress a lot of files individually, and manual intervention to compress each file one by one using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast – AI and the Future of Education with Seth Goldin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-ai-and-the-future-of-education-with-seth-goldin/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-ai-and-the-future-of-education-with-seth-goldin/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T17:47:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson discusses AI and the future of education with Seth Goldin.  Among other things, Seth is co-founder of College Compendium, an education charity, and studies computer science at Yale. Also, the quote Quincy mentioned during the conversation about AI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern CSS Tooltips And Speech Bubbles (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/modern-css-tooltips-speech-bubbles-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/modern-css-tooltips-speech-bubbles-part1/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tooltips are a very common pattern used in CSS for years. There are a lot of ways to approach tooltips in CSS, though some evoke headaches with all the magic numbers they require. In this article, Temani Afif presents modern techniques to create tooltips with the smallest amount of markup and the greatest amount of flexibility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn React – A Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-for-beginners-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-for-beginners-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T00:34:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The goal of this handbook is to provide gentle step-by-step instructions that will help you learn the key concepts of React. Instead of covering all the theories and concepts of React in their entirety, I'll be teaching you important building blocks of the library. You'll learn about JSX, components, props,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Methods in Java – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-methods/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-methods/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T20:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Methods are essential for organizing Java projects, encouraging code reuse, and improving overall code structure.  In this article, we will look at what Java methods are and how they work, including their syntax, types, and examples. Here's what we'll cover:  1. What are Java Methods?  2. Types]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Syslog Handbook – How to Collect and Redirect Logs to a Remote Server]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-syslog-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-syslog-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T19:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're in information technology, you'll likely agree that logging is important. It helps you monitor a system, troubleshoot issues, and generally provides useful feedback about the system’s state. But it’s important to do logging right. In this handbook, I'll explain what the syslog protocol is and how it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Serhii Orlivskyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Gemini Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-gemini-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-gemini-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T18:47:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Gemini is a cutting edge AI model that is a competitor of GPT-4.  We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you harness the power of the advanced AI technology. Developed by the popular instructor Ania Kubów, this beginner's course offers a deep]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Machine Learning in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-machine-learning-in-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-machine-learning-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T17:38:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you curious about machine learning but don't know where to start? We just published a comprehensive Machine Learning course on the freeCodeCamp.org  that will teach you how to get started in 2024. Whether you're aspiring to become a Data Scientist, a Machine Learning Engineer (MLE), a Product Manager, or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Mobile Quiz App with React Native, ChatGPT and Supabase]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-mobile-quiz-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-mobile-quiz-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T17:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn how to build a mobile quiz application that authenticates users, allows them to take tests, and ranks them based on their scores.  The application leverages some of Supabase's features, such as authentication and database storage, to build a secured full-stack mobile application. Additionally, you'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Asaolu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build A House Price Prediction Model – Linear Regression Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-house-price-prediction-model/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-house-price-prediction-model/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T13:25:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever wondered how algorithms predict future house prices, stock market trends, or even your next movie preference? The answer lies in a fundamental yet powerful tool called linear regression.  Don't be fooled by its seemingly simple equation – this article will unveil its magic, empowering you to build and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwadamisi Samuel Praise</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Apply Math with Python – Numerical Analysis Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/numerical-analysis-explained-how-to-apply-math-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/numerical-analysis-explained-how-to-apply-math-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T11:41:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Numerical analysis is the bridge between math and computer science.  Essentially, it is the development of algorithms that approximate solutions that pure math would also solve, but using less computational resources and faster. This field is very important. Because for most solutions in the real world, we only need]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waiting For Spring (March 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new batch of desktop wallpapers is for you. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for March 2024. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Access Properties from an Array of Objects in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-access-properties-from-an-array-of-objects-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-access-properties-from-an-array-of-objects-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T00:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with JavaScript applications, it's common to work with arrays, nested arrays, and an array of objects. But a lot of beginners sometimes struggle with knowing how to access properties from these different data structures. In this article, we will discuss how to access properties from a variety]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Idempotence? Explained with Real-World Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/idempotence-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/idempotence-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T00:44:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Idempotence is a property of an operation that ensures that, if the operation is repeated once or more than once, you get the same result. Apply it once or more and the outcome's the same, idempotence is the name. All rhyming aside, idempotence is an important concept often used in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless Node.js Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serverless-node-js-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serverless-node-js-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T20:59:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The shift towards serverless architectures is rapidly becoming a pivotal aspect of application development. Even Node.js, which is traditionally used with servers, can be used to build a serverless application. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to develop serverless applications using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Reusable React Components]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-reusable-react-components/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-reusable-react-components/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T19:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are reusable React components? You can think of them as building blocks. They are independent pieces of code that can be reused throughout your website to save you time and effort. They can be anything from simple buttons to complex forms. Why Use Reusable Components? As your website grows,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shahan Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do Open Source Licenses Work? Permissive and Protective Software Licenses Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/permissive-and-protective-software-licenses/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/permissive-and-protective-software-licenses/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T17:07:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're going to use or work with open source resources, you'll need to understand the fine print on various classes of an open source license. Otherwise, how can you be sure you're not infringing on someone else's rights?  This article will introduce you to the big players and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Music Bot Using Discord.js – Step-by-Step Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-music-bot-using-discord-js-4436f5f3f0f8/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-music-bot-using-discord-js-4436f5f3f0f8/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Discord API provides you with an easy tool to create and use your own bots and tools.  In this tutorial, you'll learn how you can create a basic music bot and add it to your server. The bot will be able to play, skip, and stop the music,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabriel Tanner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build A Text Summarizer Using Huggingface Transformers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-text-summarizer-using-huggingface-transformers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-text-summarizer-using-huggingface-transformers/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T10:13:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s fast-paced world, we’re bombarded with information. It’s like trying to drink water from a fire hose. That's where a text summarizer comes in. Imagine it as a filter that separates the essential bits from the overwhelming flood of words. In this article, I'll walk you through what a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regular Expressions (RegEx) in JavaScript – A Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/regex-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/regex-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T20:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regular expressions, also known as regex, are powerful tools for pattern matching and text manipulation. Whether you're validating user input, extracting data from strings, or performing advanced text processing tasks, understanding regex is essential for developers. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the fundamentals of regular expressions in JavaScript,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samyak Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Render an Array of Components in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-render-array-of-components-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-render-array-of-components-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T19:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, I will show you how using indices to render an array of components in React can be problematic. I'll also teach you how to mitigate array rendering issues with unique ids. As always, we'll work on a real world example and solve problem I stumbled across while]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Generative AI in 30 Hours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-generative-ai-in/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-generative-ai-in/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T18:25:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving landscape of artificial intelligence, staying ahead of the curve is important for both enthusiasts and professionals alike. And one of the most popular elements of AI right now is Generative AI. We just posted a comprehensive course about Generative AI on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This course,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How TypeScript Generics Work – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-typescript-generics-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-typescript-generics-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T13:45:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript, with its powerful type system, offers a feature called Generics, which enables developers to write reusable and type-safe code. Generics allow you to create components that can work over a variety of types rather than a single one. This article delves into TypeScript Generics, providing thorough explanations and code]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Ternary Operator in JavaScript – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-ternary-operator-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-ternary-operator-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T13:04:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tired of bulky if-else statements? JavaScript's ternary operator offers a powerful solution. This handy tool lets you condense complex conditional logic into a single line, making your code cleaner, more elegant, and efficient. In this article, we'll take a deep dive into the ternary operator, understanding its syntax and showcasing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Franklin Okolie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reporting Core Web Vitals With The Performance API]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/reporting-core-web-vitals-performance-api/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/reporting-core-web-vitals-performance-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Performance API is a set of standards for measuring and evaluating performance metrics with JavaScript. This article demonstrates how to use the Performance API to generate performance metrics directly in the DOM to create your own reporting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Tailwind CSS to Your React Native Expo App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tailwindcss-in-react-native-expo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tailwindcss-in-react-native-expo/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T09:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tailwind CSS has been quite popular in the web development world due to its utility-first approach and seamless integration.  However, when developing mobile apps with React Native, integrating Tailwind CSS may be challenging. But guess what? Not anymore. With the development of tools such as NativeWind [https://www.nativewind.dev/], React Native]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Caleb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Essential SQL Concepts for Data Analysts – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-concepts-for-data-analysts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-concepts-for-data-analysts/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T00:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the vast and ever-growing realm of data analytics, Structured Query Language [/news/what-is-sql-database-definition-for-beginners/] (SQL) serves as a fundamental building block.  While SQL's roots lie in database management, it has expanded its reach, becoming the go-to tool for data extraction, manipulation, and analysis.  Whether you're just starting your journey]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Hereth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Publish Google Docs to WordPress in an SEO-Optimized Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/publish-google-docs-to-wordpress/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/publish-google-docs-to-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T23:21:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress is a popular content management system (CMS) known for its flexibility and user-friendly interface. But its built-in editor is not ideal for collaborative editing. Many publishers who work with writers need collaborative writing and editing features. This is where Google Docs comes into the picture. It’s a collaborative platform,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikram Aruchamy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Geolocation API in JavaScript – with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-javascript-geolocation-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-javascript-geolocation-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T22:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Geolocation API is a standard API implemented in browsers to retrieve the location of the people who are interacting with a web application. This API enable users to send their location to a web application to enable relevant services, such as seeking a restaurant or hotel near the user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn the Hard Parts of React – and Tips to Conquer Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hard-parts-of-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hard-parts-of-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T21:07:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you started learning React, only to face bugs that made you contemplate a career in goat herding? Don't worry – we've all been there.  In this guide, you'll join me on a quest through the quirky wonders of React. I'll help you navigate the perplexing moments, ensuring you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perform Performance Testing on Your Web Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/performance-testing-for-web-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/performance-testing-for-web-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T19:52:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Performance testing is an important yet underrated field of software development. And it’s a must-have skill that can help you prevent common software failures that occur in production applications.  Performance testing is a routine software practice which is carried out to determine the stability of a system in terms]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oluwatobi Joshua</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Web Designer’s Accessibility Advocacy Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-designer-accessibility-advocacy-toolkit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-designer-accessibility-advocacy-toolkit/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital designer Yichan Wang has put together this collection of strategies and selling points to help you encourage and advocate for accessibility in your place of work, including useful scripts you can use as starting points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yichan Wang)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced CSS Selectors – How and When to Use Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-css-selectors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-css-selectors/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T17:12:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing CSS is often painful for a lot of developers, because many of us lose our curiosity very early in the learning journey. For instance, as soon as we learn basic CSS selectors, we settle into a pattern of using only those, thinking they're all we need. But what if]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ophy Boamah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work with Redux-Thunk – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-redux-thunk/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-redux-thunk/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T02:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redux has become the go-to state management library for many JavaScript applications due to its predictable state container and unidirectional data flow. However, handling asynchronous actions in Redux can be a bit tricky. That's where Redux middleware like Redux-Thunk comes to the rescue. In essence, Redux-Thunk enhances the capabilities of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Configure Google Workspace Addon For Tier 2 CASA Security Assessment – Step by Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tier-casa-security-assessment/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tier-casa-security-assessment/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T16:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of the Google CASA process [https://appdefensealliance.dev/casa], developers can run static analysis on their application’s source code using an inline integration with OpenText’s Fortify Source Code Analyzer (SCA) via the CASA portal. Naturally, I had to prepare my source code as per instruction. In this article, I will share]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nibesh Khadka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: What it's like working at ChatGPT Creator Open AI. My Interview with Logan Kilpatrick]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-chatgpt-open-ai-logan-kilpatrick/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-chatgpt-open-ai-logan-kilpatrick/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T16:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Logan Kilpatric, a software engineer and ChatGPT creator Open AI's first-ever Developer Advocate hire. The week Logan started, ChatGPT hit 100 million users. During our conversation, Logan shares his journey from Illinois to Harvard, NASA, and now the world's most-watched tech]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Fetch API For Beginners – Explained With Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-fetch-api-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-fetch-api-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T12:14:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fetch API is a JavaScript function that you can use to send a request to any Web API URL and get a response. In this article, I'm going to show you how to make HTTP requests to external APIs using the JavaScript Fetch API. You're going to learn how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How TypeScript Interfaces Work – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-typescript-interfaces-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-typescript-interfaces-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T10:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript, a superset of JavaScript, has gained widespread adoption among developers due to its ability to provide static typing, enhancing code robustness and maintainability. One of TypeScript's key features is interfaces, which play a pivotal role in defining the shape of objects, enabling type checking and facilitating better code organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Camera App on the Web – No Plugins Required]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-camera-app-on-the-web/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-camera-app-on-the-web/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T00:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever had to make a video call right on your browser with Google Meet, Zoom, or any other video chat app? Well, here’s what you might have never thought to ask—how does it work? Well, there are a number of things that make a real-time video chat application fully functional]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Favour C. Felix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanilla JavaScript, Libraries, And The Quest For Stateful DOM Rendering]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/vanilla-javascript-libraries-quest-stateful-dom-rendering/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/vanilla-javascript-libraries-quest-stateful-dom-rendering/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s well-established that the web faces wide-ranging usability and performance issues, from user-hostile UI patterns and twisted search results to sluggish performance and battery-draining bloat. In this article, Frederik examines one small-but-significant aspect where developers take the reins: Painting pixels on the screen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederik Dohr)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the :has() Selector in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-has-selector-in-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-has-selector-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T14:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For most of the history of CSS, selectors have been limited to targeting elements based on their parents in the DOM tree. Consider this HTML structure: 
     
Paragraph 1
       
     	
Paragraph 2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Charlesworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use the Fullscreen API in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-use-full-screen-api-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-use-full-screen-api-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T14:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you run a game created for the web in fullscreen? In this quick tutorial, you'll see how to display a game or any other HTML element in fullscreen, how to exit fullscreen, and how to make a nice fullscreen toggle button in SVG. Recently I published a long]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hunor Márton Borbély</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the JavaScript Map and Set Objects – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-map-and-set-objects-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-map-and-set-objects-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T21:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Map and Set are two JavaScript data structures you can use to store a collection of values, similar to Objects and Arrays. They are specialized data structures that can help you store and manipulate related values.  In this tutorial, we will see how Map and Set work in detail]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure AI Fundamentals Certification (AI-900) 2024 UPDATE – Pass the Exam With This Free 4 Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/azure-data-fundamentals-certification-ai-900-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-4-hour-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/azure-data-fundamentals-certification-ai-900-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-4-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T15:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Azure AI Fundamentals Certification is for those seeking a Machine Learning role such as AI Engineer or Data Scientist. The certification has recently been updated for 2024 and I've released an updated course to teach you how to pass the exam. In the last decade companies have been collecting]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Brown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Type Aliases work in TypeScript – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-typescript-type-aliases-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-typescript-type-aliases-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T14:14:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of TypeScript's powerful features is type aliases, which allow developers to create custom names for types, enhancing code readability and maintainability. In this article, we'll explore TypeScript type aliases through examples. Table of Contents  * TypeScript Type Aliases  * Examples  * Conclusion What are Type Aliases]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use Node Version Manager In Your React Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-nvm-in-react-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-nvm-in-react-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T13:51:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide,  you'll learn how to effectively manage multiple Node versions for different projects using Node Version Manager (NVM). Whether you're developing React, Angular, Vue.js, or Node applications, you can always use NVM to set up the project and tailor it down to a specific Node version. Prerequisites Before]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Debug Coding Problems When Building Your Own Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/debug-coding-problems-in-your-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/debug-coding-problems-in-your-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T21:47:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ah, the joy of coding! There you are, cruising through your project, when suddenly – bam! – you hit a bug. It's like hitting a wall in a maze. But fear not, fellow coder, for I bring you the trusty map to navigate the treacherous bug-infested waters of programming. Whether]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Blakely</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use LocalStorage in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-local-storage-in-modern-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-local-storage-in-modern-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T21:37:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In modern web development, having a way to persist data helps developers improve performance and create a better user experience. And using local storage is an effective way of persisting data in an application. In this article, you will learn what local storage is and how to use it in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Types Work in TypeScript – Explained with JavaScript + TypeScript Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/basic-typescript-types/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/basic-typescript-types/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T21:05:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript is a superset of JavaScript that introduces static typing to JavaScript. TypeScript's enhanced type safety and code maintainability empower developers to write code more confidently. A fundamental aspect of TypeScript's static typing system is its support for basic types. These provide a foundation for defining the shape and behavior]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Python Basics – A Guide for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-python-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-python-basics/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T19:04:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you eager to dive into the world of programming but unsure where to begin? Look no further – Python is an excellent starting point for both newcomers and seasoned developers.  In this guide, I'll take you through the basics so you can get started on your Python journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chepkirui dorothy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Entering into the World of Concurrency with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/concurrency-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/concurrency-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T18:53:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we will explore concurrency in Python. We'll discuss Threads and Processes and how they're similar and different. You'll also learn about Multi-threading, Multi-processing, Asynchronous Programming, and Concurrency in general in Python.  Many tutorials discuss these concepts, but they can be challenging to grasp due to the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hemachandra Routhu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Data Structures and Algorithms in 48 Hours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-data-structures-and-algorithms-2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-data-structures-and-algorithms-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T18:20:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the realm of software development, mastering Data Structures and Algorithms could be a critical step towards securing your dream job.  We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will equip you with the knowledge to excel in coding interviews and problem-solving. You will learn the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Console Logging Tips – How to Debug and Understand Your Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/console-logging-tips/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/console-logging-tips/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T18:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Console logging is an essential tool for developers to use to debug and understand the behavior of their code.  While most developers are familiar with basic console logging using  console.log(), there are many other powerful methods provided by the console object that can make debugging more efficient and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS Flexbox in Spanish – Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-flexbox-in-spanish-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-flexbox-in-spanish-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T15:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With CSS Flexbox, you can easily create responsive websites that adapt to different screen sizes and devices. It's an essential skill for any modern web developer. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org Spanish YouTube channel [https://www.youtube.com/freecodecampespanol] that will teach you Flexbox from the fundamentals. By the end of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Practical Guide To Designing For Colorblind People]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-for-colorblindness/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-for-colorblindness/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Color accessibility is more than just ticking boxes. Even with good contrast, some color palettes can make interfaces challenging for users. Here are some practical guidelines to ensure more inclusive design for colorblind people. An upcoming part of Smart Interface Design Patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Connect a Domain Name to a Website Hosted on AWS EC2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-connect-a-domain-to-a-website-hosted-on-aws-ec2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-connect-a-domain-to-a-website-hosted-on-aws-ec2/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T23:51:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may want to host your website on a virtual private server or a virtual machine like AWS EC2. But it can be a challenge to connect a domain name that you purchased from providers like Namecheap or Godaddy. But if you know the steps to follow, this doesn't have]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Obed Ehoneah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How JavaScript's Reduce Method Works – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-reduce-method-code-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-reduce-method-code-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T18:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduced alongside other array methods in ECMAScript 5, reduce() offers a unique and powerful way to transform arrays into single values.  In this article, you'll learn about the reduce() method by understanding what it is, its syntax, and finally you'll see some use cases where you can use it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set up Swiper Element in a React Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-swiper-element-in-a-react-application/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-swiper-element-in-a-react-application/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T16:25:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carousels or image sliders are an integral part of many web applications. They help you group multiple elements in a single view. Using carousels, you can implement image slides, video slides, text slides, interactive image galleries, product catalogs, team profiles, and more. Swiper.js [https://swiperjs.com/] comes with powerful functionalities that make]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Anie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile Accessibility Barriers For Assistive Technology Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/mobile-accessibility-barriers-assistive-technology-users/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/mobile-accessibility-barriers-assistive-technology-users/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility goes beyond making products user-friendly. It can significantly impact the quality of life for people with disabilities. Kate Kalcevich shares lessons she learned from assistive technology users — challenges and barriers they encounter on mobile devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep Learning Fundamentals Handbook – What You Need to Know to Start Your Career in AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deep-learning-fundamentals-handbook-start-a-career-in-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deep-learning-fundamentals-handbook-start-a-career-in-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T23:47:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to get into the field of Artificial Intelligence (AI), one of the most in-demand career paths these days, you've come to the right place. Learning Deep Learning Fundamentals is your essential first step to learning about Computer Vision, Natural Language Processing (NLP), Large Language Models, the creative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tatev Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: How the Insane Pressure of Classical Music Prepared Jessica Wilkins for Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-jessica-wilkins-classical-music-learning-to-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-jessica-wilkins-classical-music-learning-to-code/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T18:47:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview orchestral musician-turned software engineer Jessica Wilkins. Jessica found success in the extremely competitive field of classical music, playing the Oboe in orchestras, recording sessions, and even at major events such as the NFL awards on national television. She started her own]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flexbox vs Grid in CSS – Which Should You Use?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flexbox-vs-grid-in-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flexbox-vs-grid-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T11:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever had issues with replicating a particular user interface from a Figma design? Do you find it difficult displaying elements in different sections of your browser screen? A major cause of rift between user interface (UI) designers and frontend developers is the issue of having an awesome UI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maybell Obadoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Optimization Techniques to Help You Write More Performant Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-performance-optimization-techniques/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-performance-optimization-techniques/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T00:57:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Performance optimization is a critical aspect of developing web applications. Users expect applications to load quickly and respond to their interactions smoothly.  In the React ecosystem, performance optimization techniques can significantly enhance the user experience by reducing load times and improving responsiveness. In this article, we will discuss eight]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temitope Oyedele</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get the Most of Video Coding Tutorials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-the-most-out-of-video-coding-tutorials/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-the-most-out-of-video-coding-tutorials/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T00:50:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever spent hours watching a coding tutorial, only to get to the end and feel like you haven't learned very much?  We've all been there, and it can be a frustrating experience when learning to code.  In this article, I will show you some of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Blakely</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Argo Workflows on Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-argo-workflows-on-kubernetes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-argo-workflows-on-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T23:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argo Workflows is an open source project that enables the orchestration of multiple Kubernetes jobs. Argo Workflows is implemented as a Kubernetes custom resource definition (CRD), which means it is native to the Kubernetes ecosystem and can run on any Kubernetes cluster. Workflows are set steps by which individual jobs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abraham Dahunsi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the JavaScript Filter Method Works – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-filter-method/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-filter-method/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T23:08:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript's filter method serves as a powerful tool for selectively extracting elements from arrays based on certain conditions.  Introduced alongside other array methods in ECMAScript 5, the filter method has since become a fundamental feature in JavaScript programming. In this article, we will delve into the JavaScript filter method,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript in the Browser – How the Document Object Model (DOM) and Events Work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-in-the-browser-dom-and-events/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-in-the-browser-dom-and-events/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T20:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this in-depth tutorial, you'll learn all about the Document Object Model, or DOM for short. As a web developer, understanding the DOM is fundamental for interacting with web browsers and creating dynamic web applications.  Throughout this guide, we will explore the DOM's hierarchical tree structure, essential properties, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samyak Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn SvelteKit in 2 hours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-sveltekit-full-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-sveltekit-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T18:47:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SvelteKit is the next evolution of Svelte, a modern JavaScript framework that compiles your code to highly efficient, vanilla JavaScript at build time. It's a great framework to learn for developers seeking to hone their skills or dive into modern web frameworks. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to Make Art with Code – p5.js Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/art-of-coding-with-p5js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/art-of-coding-with-p5js/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T18:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[p5.js is a JavaScript library that's transforming the way artists and designers approach make art with code. If you're intrigued by the intersection of art and programming, freeCodeCamp's YouTube course on p5.js is an ideal starting point.  Patt Vira created this course. She loves making art with code and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Draw with JavaScript on an HTML Canvas Element – Gorilla Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-draw-a-gorilla-with-javascript-on-html-canvas/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-draw-a-gorilla-with-javascript-on-html-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T16:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drawing from code can be fun for many reasons. You can generate art that follows a certain logic. You can create animations by moving only parts of an image. And you can even build up a whole game as I covered in this tutorial [/news/gorillas-game-in-javascript/]. In my last article, we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hunor Márton Borbély</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Chrome DevTools – Simple Strategies for Smarter Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chrome-devtools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chrome-devtools/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T16:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a web developer, there are many tools out there – in addition to your code editor – that can make you more efficient.  It doesn't matter if you're just starting out or have been coding for years. Knowing how to effectively use Developer Tools (DevTools for short) can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ophy Boamah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the App Directory in Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/app-directory-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/app-directory-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T00:52:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building a project using the latest version of Next.js, you'll be prompted to select between using the app/ directory or the pages/ directory. The  app/ directory is now the recommended way of building apps in Next.js. In this article, you'll learn how to maximize the potential of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Oghenetejiri Ukumakube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Map Method – Syntax and Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-map-method/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-map-method/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T00:50:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript's map method, introduced in ECMAScript 5, is a fundamental tool for array manipulation and transformation. This method is versatile and simple, and has become a staple in modern JavaScript programming.  In this article, we'll explore the map method's syntax and its wide array of applications, ranging from basic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Custom React Hook – a Hands-on Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-custom-react-hooks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-custom-react-hooks/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T17:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have been working with React, I bet you've had the opportunity to use hooks. But have you ever tried to create your own hook?  Today I will help you create your first custom hook and explain how they can improve your codebase. Why Create Custom Hooks? You]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dive into Backend Development by Building a CRUD API with Node and MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crud-api-with-node-js-express-mongodb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crud-api-with-node-js-express-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T15:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A key part of most backend development projects is CRUD.  We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will throw you into the world of backend development by guiding you through building a CRUD API from scratch. You will use Node.js, Express, and MongoDB. The course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Accessibility Standards Can Empower Better Chart Visual Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/accessibility-standards-empower-better-chart-visual-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/accessibility-standards-empower-better-chart-visual-design/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility for data visualization extends well beyond web standards, at least if you’re trying to create an experience that’s actually useful. This article focuses on techniques for creating useful and accessible visualizations that extend well beyond compliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kent Eisenhuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with Golang – a Developer Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/golang-developer-roadmap/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/golang-developer-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Go programming language – also known as Golang – is now almost 15 years old. And it's become a popular choice for web development and microservices thanks to its performance and efficient resource utilisation.  Go jobs are also quite well-paid. As per the Glassdoor report [https://www.glassdoor.com/Salaries/golang-developer-salary-SRCH_KO0,16.htm?countryPickerRedirect=true] , the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubham Chadokar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How JavaScript Promises Work – Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-promises-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-promises-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T23:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many operations, such as network requests, are asynchronous in nature. One of the most useful and powerful tools for working with asynchronous code is the Promise. In this handbook, you'll learn all about JavaScript Promises and how to use them. Table of Contents  1.  What is a Promise?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Attardi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optional Chaining in JavaScript – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/optional-chaining-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/optional-chaining-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T21:54:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript development often involves navigating through nested objects, which can be cumbersome and error-prone, especially when dealing with null or  undefined values. Enter optional chaining—a game-changer in modern JavaScript syntax. In this article, we'll explore optional chaining through practical examples, demonstrating how it streamlines code and makes development more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best CSS Frameworks to Use in Your Projects for 2024 and Beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-css-frameworks-for-frontend-devs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-css-frameworks-for-frontend-devs/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T21:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS has come a long way over the past few years. In the past, you'd use CSS to create simple-looking web applications that rely on HTML tables and CSS floats as their layout systems. And now you can architect complex interactive user interfaces that are appealing with elegant designs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Ikechukwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Custom HTML5 Video Player Using TailwindCSS and JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-custom-video-player-using-javascript-and-tailwind-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-custom-video-player-using-javascript-and-tailwind-css/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T15:14:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML5 comes equipped with a native video player. It's shipped with a simple user interface, functionality, and some basic controls in the browser. And while the functionality of the default video player via the browser works perfectly, the user interface isn't so beautiful and fancy, and it's just not generally]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Franklin Okolie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Practical Guide To Designing For Children]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/practical-guide-design-children/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/practical-guide-design-children/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to design for children aged 3–12, with insights into user behavior, considerations for parents, and practical UX guidelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Greater Than and Less Than Operators in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/greater-than-and-less-than-operators-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/greater-than-and-less-than-operators-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T11:02:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In your JavaScript programs, you'll often need to compare two values to see if one is greater than or less than the other. This is where the greater than and less than operators come in handy. In this article, we'll look at how to use these operators in greater detail]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debouncing in JavaScript – Explained by Building Auto-Complete Functionality in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deboucing-in-react-autocomplete-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deboucing-in-react-autocomplete-example/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T23:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi readers, I hope you are doing great! I am back with another tutorial on web development. If you are someone who enjoys developing web apps with JavaScript and React, then this post is for you. When you roll out a new app into production, you want to make sure]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the querySelector() Method and How Does it Work in JavaScript?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/queryselector-method-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/queryselector-method-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T23:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, there will be times when you need to access an HTML element. The  querySelector method is a web API that selects the first element that matches the specified CSS selector passed into it. But how does this work in more detail? In this article, we will look]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does Short-Circuiting Work in JavaScript?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/short-circuiting-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/short-circuiting-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T18:38:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, understanding truthy and falsy values is fundamental to writing efficient and concise code. Combined with the concept of short-circuiting, developers can write elegant solutions to common programming challenges.  In this hands-on guide, we'll explore truthy and falsy values, and understand the mechanics of short-circuiting in JavaScript. You]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Compare Two Dates in JavaScript – Techniques, Methods, and Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/compare-two-dates-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/compare-two-dates-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T17:57:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, you can use the date object to work effectively with dates, times, and time zones within an application.  Date objects help you efficiently manipulate data, handle various date-related tasks, and perform some calculations when creating real-world applications. In this article, we will learn about the following topics:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kamaldeen Lawal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve Your Communication Skills as a Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-communication-skills/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-communication-skills/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T13:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You built an application that solves a problem most business owners face. You registered yourself at a local event to speak about your product, but no one cares. You try selling it on social media groups, but don't receive more than "Wow, that's an interesting idea." Do these sound familiar?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tooba Jamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>