<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-10-10T00:54:46.469Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Storage Explained – How to Use localStorage and sessionStorage in JavaScript Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-storage-localstorage-vs-sessionstorage-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-storage-localstorage-vs-sessionstorage-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T16:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web Storage is what the JavaScript API [https://codesweetly.com/application-programming-interface-api-explained]  browsers provide for storing data locally and securely within a user’s browser. Session and local storage are the two main types of web storage. They are similar to regular properties objects [https://codesweetly.com/javascript-properties-object], but they persist (do not disappear) when the webpage]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi Sofela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work with Images in HTML – A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-images-in-html/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-images-in-html/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T15:33:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images are an essential part of web development, adding visual appeal and context to your web pages.  In HTML, you can easily incorporate images to enhance the user experience. This article will guide you through the basics of working with images in HTML and help you understand images in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API Integration Patterns – The Difference between REST, RPC, GraphQL, Polling, WebSockets and WebHooks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/api-integration-patterns/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/api-integration-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T15:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[API stands for Application Programming Interface. The “I” in API is the key part that explains its purpose. The interface is what the software presents to other humans or programs, allowing them to interact with it.  A good analogy for an interface is a remote control. Imagine you have]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Headaches: Working With Media (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/gatsby-headaches-working-media-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/gatsby-headaches-working-media-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how to incorporate a variety of media formats, such as images, videos, GIFs, SVGs, and so on, in a Gatsby website. Juan Rodriguez shares what he’s learned about optimizing files for improved performance after working with different plugins and techniques.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Migrate from create-react-app to Vite using Jest and Browserslist]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-migrate-from-create-react-app-to-vite/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-migrate-from-create-react-app-to-vite/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T18:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The React team no longer recommends using create-react-app (CRA) [https://github.com/facebook/create-react-app] as a bundler to create a new React application. The team and community realized that even though CRA was a jump-starter, it lacked the flexibility needed to configure or manage large and complex applications. Nowadays, the team recommends using production-grade]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saheed Oladele</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use URLs for State Management in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-urls-for-state-management-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-urls-for-state-management-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T17:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, URLs have been synonymous with web navigation. But the tide is turning, especially with the emergence of single-page applications. In the React universe, URLs are stepping up to play a pivotal role in state management. This article will guide you through the transformative journey of URLs as state]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethics of AI and ML]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-ethics-of-ai-and-ml/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-ethics-of-ai-and-ml/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T15:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rapid ascent of Artificial Intelligence (AI) and Machine Learning (ML) into mainstream technology and its influence on various sectors of our society raises a series of profound ethical questions. It's not just about the technical ability of these systems but the ethical implications that could shape our future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross-Browser Compatibility Testing – Best Practices for Web Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cross-browser-compatibility-testing-best-practices-for-web-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cross-browser-compatibility-testing-best-practices-for-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T23:40:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine putting in a ton of work to build a web application. And then it works in the Chrome browser, but misbehaves in Mozilla, Safari, or any other browser. As a web developer, you're likely eager to create amazing web applications that reach users across the globe. But one major]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casmir Onyekani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Request Location Permissions in Jetpack Compose]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/requesting-location-permissions-in-jetpack-compose/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/requesting-location-permissions-in-jetpack-compose/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T19:28:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting a user’s location can be a bit of hassle. Over the years, the permissions required to do this and the logic associated with it have changed quite drastically.  If your application depends on getting the user’s location, you want to ensure that the user has a good experience]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Ben Rachel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build and Deploy an Ecommerce Site with Next.js, Tailwind CSS, Prisma, Vercel, and daisyUI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ecommerce-site-with-next-js-tailwind-daisyui-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ecommerce-site-with-next-js-tailwind-daisyui-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T15:36:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When learning how to build a web app it can be helpful to see how everything works together, instead of learning a lot of technologies individually. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build and deploy a full-stack e-commerce website with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Arduino Handbook – Learn Microcontrollers for Embedded Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-arduino-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-arduino-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T13:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arduino is an open-source platform that combines hardware and software in designing and building electronic projects. Arduino can be applied in a variety of projects like:  * Home automation.  * Internet of Things (IoT).  * Audio and music.  * Automated and remote controlled systems.  *]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re-Creating The Pop-Out Hover Effect With Modern CSS (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/re-creating-pop-out-hover-effect-modern-css-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/re-creating-pop-out-hover-effect-modern-css-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Re-create a fancy hover effect where an avatar pops out of a starburst pattern for the frame on hover. The idea is to apply the concepts in a new context and gain another view of how trigonometric functions can influence the way we mask elements in CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Lists – Ordered, Unordered and Definition List Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-lists-with-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-lists-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T16:01:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you're creating an article with a list of recommendations or a web page with a menu of options. How do you structure this information to make it visually appealing and easy to navigate?  This is where HTML lists come to the rescue. In this article, we'll dive into]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Standardize Your Development Environment with devcontainer.json]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/standardize-development-environment-with-devcontainers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/standardize-development-environment-with-devcontainers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T14:45:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern software development workflows are complicated, involving many tools and dependencies.  When working in a team, it's not uncommon to use several different software programs, each with its own dependencies. This can quickly become confusing, with each software requiring different configurations and management.  One solution is to use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hrittik Roy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Increase Your VS Code Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/increase-your-vs-code-productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/increase-your-vs-code-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T14:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you watched a seasoned developer work in Visual Studio Code (VS Code) and wondered how they make it look so effortless? The freeCodeCamp YouTube channel is here to help you unlock your coding superpowers with a new course we just published about increasing your productivity in VS Code. Chris]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Firebase Remote Config?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/firebase-remote-config/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/firebase-remote-config/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T15:44:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remote configurations are useful because they allow you to alter the behavior in your application without having to release a new version of the app. One prominent example is using remote configurations to decide if a feature should be turned on or off. That way, you can gradually roll it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Ben Rachel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn SvelteKit and Tailwind CSS by Building a Web Portfolio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-sveltekit-and-tailwind-css-by-building-a-web-portfolio/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-sveltekit-and-tailwind-css-by-building-a-web-portfolio/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T15:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you're a seasoned developer or just starting your journey in the world of web development, keeping up with the latest tools and frameworks is essential. And you can learn about two popular web dev tools in the new course we just posted on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. In this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Portuguese freeCodeCamp Podcast]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-portuguese-podcast/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-portuguese-podcast/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T13:25:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! My name is Nielda Karla and I'm thrilled to announce the launch of our new podcast: freeCodeCamp Podcast em Português [https://www.freecodecamp.org/portuguese/news/freecodecamp-podcast-em-portugues/] . On this podcast, you'll hear the stories of those making a difference in the Portuguese-speaking developer community – each with their own unique journey.  Our]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nielda Karla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp is Launching a Podcast in Portuguese]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-is-launching-a-podcast-in-portuguese/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-is-launching-a-podcast-in-portuguese/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T13:25:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! My name is Nielda Karla and I'm thrilled to announce the launch of our new podcast: freeCodeCamp Podcast em Português [https://www.freecodecamp.org/portuguese/news/freecodecamp-podcast-em-portugues/] . On this podcast, you'll hear the stories of those making a difference in the Portuguese-speaking developer community – each with their own unique journey.  Our]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nielda Karla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Problem With WordPress Is Positioning, Not Plugins]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/problem-wordpress-positioning-not-plugins/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/problem-wordpress-positioning-not-plugins/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Geoff explores the often-overlooked divide between WordPress.org and WordPress.com, shedding light on the blurred lines between open-source ideals and commercial interests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LinkedIn Profile Optimization – A Web Developer's Guide to Attract Opportunity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linkedin-profile-optimization/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linkedin-profile-optimization/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T08:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a web developer, an optimized LinkedIn profile can bring numerous opportunities directly to you. After implementing invaluable optimization advice from industry experts who reviewed my profile, I now receive a steady flow of enticing prospects in my inbox! In this article, I'll share the insights I've gained to help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Larocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide to a Successful Open Source Journey – Lessons from Real-Life Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/guide-to-a-successful-open-source-journey/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/guide-to-a-successful-open-source-journey/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T20:07:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The journey to becoming a successful open-source contributor can be intimidating, frustrating, or confusing depending on your level of confidence, commitment, and expertise. I have had my fair share of all sides of the emotions that come with contributing to open source in the one and a half years (at]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kaxada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Integrate AI into Your Serverless App With Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-in-your-serverless-app-amazon-bedrock/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-in-your-serverless-app-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T19:23:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's tech landscape, integrating AI is no longer a luxury – it's a necessity.  AI-driven applications have the potential to transform user experiences, automate complex tasks, and unlock new realms of possibilities. Understanding and leveraging AI APIs is a pivotal skill for developers looking to stay at the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WaterBear: Building A Free Platform For Impactful Documentaries (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/waterbear-building-free-platform-documentaries-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/waterbear-building-free-platform-documentaries-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this second article of a two-part series, Adrian shares insights about building WaterBear — his first project as a lead developer — discussing the challenges his team encountered while building it and various accessibility and performance improvements they’ve made. You’ll get a peek at the inner workings of a team striving to find its groove to systematize the work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Lifecycle Methods and Hooks – a Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-lifecycle-methods-and-hooks-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-lifecycle-methods-and-hooks-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T17:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React [/news/react-beginner-handbook/#howmuchjavascriptyouneedtoknowtousereact]  is all about building user interfaces. And to do that effectively, React provides ways for components to manage their lifecycles.  This means that components can perform specific tasks at different stages of their existence, from the moment they are created to the point they are removed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casmir Onyekani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API Security for PCI Compliance (DSS 4.0)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/api-security-for-pci-compliance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/api-security-for-pci-compliance/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T14:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[API security is important for everyone, but especially if you are dealing with payment information. We just posted a crash course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you about API security and how to address the pivotal PCI DSS 4.0 requirements. PCI DSS stands for Payment Card Industry]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Context Managers in Python?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/context-managers-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/context-managers-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T13:49:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most common tasks that you'll have to perform in your programs is working with external resources. These resources can be files on your computer's storage or an open connection to third-party service on the internet. For the sake of simplicity, imagine a program that opens a file,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farhan Hasin Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Links in HTML – Tutorial with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-links-explained-with-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-links-explained-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T07:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Links are an essential part of the web because they connect web pages, documents, and resources across the internet.  In HTML (which is short for Hypertext Markup Language), links play a crucial role in creating a web of interconnected content, allowing users to navigate seamlessly between different web pages]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Text to Meaning: How Computers Understand Language]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-computers-understand-language/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-computers-understand-language/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T14:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Image Search App Using React – An In-Depth Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-image-search-app-using-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-image-search-app-using-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T11:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will build step-by-step a beautiful Unsplash Image Search App with pagination using React. By building this app, you will learn:  * How to build an application using Unsplash API in React  * How to make API Calls in different scenarios  * How to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yogesh Chavan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dancing Leaves And Spooky Fellows (October 2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How about a little inspiration boost? Well, we might have something for you: desktop wallpapers created with love by artists and designers from across the globe. They are available in versions with and without a calendar for October and can be downloaded for free. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Game Development and AI with Lynn Zheng]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-lynn-zheng-game-development-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-lynn-zheng-game-development-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T18:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[99 Game Development and AI with Lynn Zheng Today on the freeCodeCamp Podcast, I'm joined by Lynn Zheng. She's a software engineer at freeCodeCamp and at Salesforce. Lynn grew up in Shenzhen, China – the computer hardware capital of the world. Both of her parents were engineers. And from an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the Astro Web Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-astro-web-framework/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-astro-web-framework/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T16:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Astro is rapidly emerging as a go-to choice for developers looking to build fast, content-focused websites. Whether you're crafting landing pages, informative blogs, or intricate technical documentation, Astro offers a comprehensive suite of tools to make the process seamless. We just posted an Astro crash course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re-Creating The Pop-Out Hover Effect With Modern CSS (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/re-creating-pop-out-hover-effect-css-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/re-creating-pop-out-hover-effect-css-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is all about experimenting with modern CSS features. We will combine things like CSS masks, CSS variables, trigonometric functions, `@property`, and more to create a neat hover effect that would have been extremely difficult to do even a few years ago without the latest and greatest that CSS has to offer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Localization Handbook – How to Translate Your Website Into Different World Languages [Full Book]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/localization-book-how-to-translate-your-website/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/localization-book-how-to-translate-your-website/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T18:17:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome! In a global world where information is available to everyone in just a few clicks, adapting your website and resources to other languages and cultures is essential to succeed. This book will teach you the fundamentals of localization and how to translate your website to reach a global community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn LangChain for LLM Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-langchain-for-llm-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-langchain-for-llm-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T14:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Large language models have revolutionized the realm of Natural Language Processing (NLP) and have opened the doors for numerous applications in the tech world. But integrating and deploying these models to design powerful applications often demands a specialized set of tools and understanding. Enter LangChain: a game-changing framework tailored for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Stack Project Tutorial – Create A Notes App Using React and Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-project-tutorial-create-a-notes-app-using-react-and-node-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-project-tutorial-create-a-notes-app-using-react-and-node-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T14:10:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey there! Ready to build something cool? In this tutorial, we're going to create a full stack notes app using React, Node.js, and PostgreSQL.  We'll start from scratch and end up with a fully functioning app where you can create, edit, and delete notes. Plus, we're adding validation on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Blakely</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Enhanced Patterns In WordPress 6.3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/exploring-enhanced-patterns-system-wordpress/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/exploring-enhanced-patterns-system-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ganesh Dahal explains how the features have evolved since reusable blocks were officially released in WordPress 5.0 — and how the two have converged in WordPress 6.3 to form a powerful feature capable of allowing content creators to sync content and design patterns consistently in pages and posts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ganesh Dahal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Project Maintainer's Guide to Hacktoberfest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/project-maintainer-guide-to-hacktoberfest/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/project-maintainer-guide-to-hacktoberfest/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T07:02:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktoberfest is a month-long event that promotes open-source contributions, collaboration, and projects.  Participating in this event as either a project maintainer or a contributor gives new perspectives to either your project or your career. You also get to meet fun people. This article will walk you through how to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Iroegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Security Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/terraform-security-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/terraform-security-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T05:12:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform is a popular Infrastructure as Code (IaC) tool that allows users to define and manage cloud infrastructure in a declarative way.  However, like any tool, Terraform can introduce security risks if not used properly. In this article, we will explore the most common security risks when using Terraform, the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Katz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Self-Taught Developer's Fastest Path to a Developer Job]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/self-taught-developer-fastest-way-to-learn-to-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/self-taught-developer-fastest-way-to-learn-to-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T15:41:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This morning while I was eating breakfast, I opened YouTube and saw a video by self-taught developer Brian Cache: "The FASTEST Way to Learn to Code and ACTUALLY Get a Developer Job" (Capital letter emphasis is his own. The video is an 11 minute watch): I love watching these types]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the Basics of Java Programming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-basics-of-java-programming/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-basics-of-java-programming/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T14:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Java has been a popular programming language for over two decades. Learning Java is a good way to mastering the fundamentals of modern coding practices.  We just posted a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you the basics of Java programming. Alex Dobinca Cristian developed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Overview of Prismane  – An Open-Source React UI Library]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prismane-react-ui-library/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prismane-react-ui-library/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T12:52:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prismane is a free, comprehensive, have-it-all React UI library that provides a broad array of hooks, components, and form validators to help you build beautiful and functional user interfaces. Prismane was designed with performance in mind, ensuring lightning-fast loading times for a better user experience. In this article, you will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use HTML Elements – Headings, Paragraphs, and Text Formatting Elements Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-html-elements/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-html-elements/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T18:02:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML, which stands for HyperText Markup Language, is the standard markup language used to create webpages. HTML provides a structured way to organize content on a webpage, allowing web developers to present text and media in a clear and meaningful way.  In this article, we'll explore three fundamental HTML]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nuxt 3 Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nuxt-3-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nuxt-3-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T15:37:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nuxt.js has been making waves in the web development world, especially among Vue.js enthusiasts. With its unique capabilities for server-side rendering, static site generation, and single-page applications, Nuxt offers a robust set of features for developers looking to build modern web apps. We just posted a full course on Nuxt]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With Neon Branching]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/getting-started-with-neon-branching/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/getting-started-with-neon-branching/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Branches are a really nice (and safe) way to configure or reconfigure your database without fear of screwing up the production database. Let’s take a closer look at how branching works with [Neon](https://neon.tech/), and the good news is, you probably already know how it works!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 65 With Alex Older: How Do You Run A Grassroots Conference?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/smashing-podcast-episode-65/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/smashing-podcast-episode-65/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re talking about running grassroots conferences and meet-ups. What does it take to organize a small industry event for your community? Drew McLellan talks to WDC’s Alex Older to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Dynamic Programming to Solve the 0/1 Knapsack Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-dynamic-programming-to-solve-the-0-1-knapsack-problem/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-dynamic-programming-to-solve-the-0-1-knapsack-problem/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T16:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The art of computer science often revolves around solving problems that are seemingly simple at first glance, but dig a little deeper and you'll find intricate challenges that demand creativity, logic, and precision. One such iconic problem is the 0/1 Knapsack Problem. We just published a new course on the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WaterBear: Building A Free Platform For Impactful Documentaries (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/waterbear-building-free-platform-impactful-documentaries-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/waterbear-building-free-platform-impactful-documentaries-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adrian’s kicking off a two-part series, sharing his journey as a lead developer. In the process, you will learn about the lessons and insights Adrian gained at work, including the strategies that went into the technical stack of the project and what it looks like to collaborate with a team he is leading for the first time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python List Methods Explained in Plain English]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-methods-explained-in-plain-english/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-methods-explained-in-plain-english/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-24T14:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often make plans about the things we want, what we need to do, and places we want to visit. These lists could go on forever! However, there are times when we need to build a program that requires us to organize and manipulate information using lists.  In this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GOLD AGBONIFO_ISAAC</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Java Internals: Speed and Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-java-internals-speed-and-performance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-java-internals-speed-and-performance/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-24T13:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In most conversations about programming, speed, and efficiency in Java are reoccurring terms as it's a language native to these features. You might ask, what is Java? You may also wonder what it means for a programming language to be interpreted or compiled. Let's explore these concepts in the following]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoye Victor Chukwuebuka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Word Embeddings: The Building Blocks of NLP and GPTs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-word-embeddings-the-building-blocks-of-nlp-and-gpts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-word-embeddings-the-building-blocks-of-nlp-and-gpts/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-24T12:17:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Word embeddings serve as the foundation for many applications, from simple text classification to complex machine translation systems. But what exactly are word embeddings, and how do they work? Let's find out. What Are Word Embeddings? Word embeddings serve as the digital DNA for words in the world of natural]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction to HTML for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-html/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-html/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-24T11:57:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML, which stands for HyperText Markup Language, serves as the foundation of web development. It enables you to create interactive web pages, structure content, and effectively communicate your message.  In this guide, we'll explore HTML comprehensively, addressing essential questions to provide a strong foundation for budding web developers. The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: How to Run a Tech Conference with Ben Dunphy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-how-to-run-a-tech-event/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-how-to-run-a-tech-event/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T17:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today on the freeCodeCamp Podcast, I interview Benjamin Dunphy, founder of many San Francisco Tech Conferences including Reactathon. Ben studied international relations and had a short career in finance. Among other things, he co-authored a bill that eventually got passed in his state of New Hampshire. But Ben saw the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust Project – Create an Authentication Server]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rust-tutorial-authentication-server/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rust-tutorial-authentication-server/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T16:02:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rust programming language is often used for system-level programming, emphasizing safety, concurrency, and performance, making it a popular choice for building systems software, game engines, and web browsers. An authentication server is another good use case for Rust. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Contribute to Open-Source Projects – Git & GitHub Workflow for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-and-github-workflow-for-open-source/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-and-github-workflow-for-open-source/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T12:35:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first time I learned about open source was through a tweet that promoted Hacktoberfest in 2019. And my first-ever accepted pull request was to add a book title in emojis to a list. You might think, "You can't count that as an open source contribution. That's a joke!" I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayu Adiati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Path To Awesome CSS Easing With The linear() Function]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/path-css-easing-linear-function/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/path-css-easing-linear-function/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the new CSS `linear()` easing function on the horizon, the possibilities of what we can do to create natural-feeling animations and transitions in the future are greatly expanded. Jhey Tompkins looks at the current state of CSS easing in this article and demonstrates what we can expect from `linear()`, including handy tools to get your hands on it today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Hypothesis Testing? Types and Python Code Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-hypothesis-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-hypothesis-testing/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T00:41:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Curiosity has always been a part of human nature. Since the beginning of time, this has been one of the most important tools for birthing civilizations. Still, our curiosity grows — it tests and expands our limits. Humanity has explored the plains of land, water, and air. We've built underwater]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MENE-EJEGI OGBEMI</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binary Classification with TensorFlow Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/binary-classification-made-simple-with-tensorflow/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/binary-classification-made-simple-with-tensorflow/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T14:21:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binary classification is a fundamental task in machine learning, where the goal is to categorize data into one of two classes or categories.  Binary classification is used in a wide range of applications, such as spam email detection, medical diagnosis, sentiment analysis, fraud detection, and many more. In this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Mojo Programming Language for AI Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/new-mojo-programming-language-for-ai-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/new-mojo-programming-language-for-ai-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T14:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mojo combines the usability of Python with the performance of C, leading to greater programmability of AI hardware and extensibility of AI models. It's basically an enhanced version of Python specifically designed for Artificial Intelligence developers. We just posted a full Mojo course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Elliot Arledge]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Self-Playing AI Chess Engine from Scratch with Imitation Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-self-playing-ai-chess-engine-from-scratch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-self-playing-ai-chess-engine-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T08:11:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an article on how I created an AI chess engine, starting completely from scratch to building my very own AI chess engine.  Because creating an AI chess engine from scratch is a relatively complex task, this will be a long article, but stay tuned, as the product]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eivind Kjosbakken</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Design System in Next.js with Tailwind CSS and Class Variance Authority]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-a-design-system-in-next-js-with-tailwind-css-and-class-variance-authority/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-a-design-system-in-next-js-with-tailwind-css-and-class-variance-authority/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T07:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a web application and producing a smooth user experience in the always changing world of web development requires more than just good looks – you also need to make sure that your application's design is efficient and consistent throughout. If you have a design system in place, you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olasunkanmi Balogun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code Dark Mode for Google Sheets with Apps Script and JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-dark-mode-for-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-dark-mode-for-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T22:23:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Sheets is a great tool for working and collaborating on spreadsheets, but it doesn't have native support for dark mode.  In this article, we'll create our own dark mode. One way to do that would be by selecting all the cells and manually changing their background color and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Effects of AI in Cybersecurity Handbook – The Malicious Use of AI in Cyberattacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/effects-of-ai-in-cybersecurity-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/effects-of-ai-in-cybersecurity-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T20:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The field of cybersecurity is engaged in a relentless battle between those who defend systems and data, and those who seek to attack them. In this high-stakes arena, artificial intelligence (AI) has emerged as a new, game-changing ally for the defenders. To understand AI's profound impact, it is important to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonya Moisset</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build an SEO-Optimized Blog with Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-seo-optimized-blog-with-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-seo-optimized-blog-with-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T13:09:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a feature-rich blog is a great way to improve your web development skills.  We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create a blog that is not just visually appealing but also SEO-optimized for higher Google rankings. Codebucks created the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facilitating Inclusive Online Workshops (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/facilitating-inclusive-online-workshops-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/facilitating-inclusive-online-workshops-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To help ensure the success of a workshop, Ben Shih introduces the concept of an inclusive workshop. In Part 2 of the series, you will continue to delve deeper into several key principles and guidelines that you can follow during and after the workshop to encourage an inclusive atmosphere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Shih)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ultimate Beginner's Python Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ultimate-beginners-python-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ultimate-beginners-python-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T12:26:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever considered venturing into the world of Python programming or if you're just looking for a comprehensive guide to help reinforce your existing knowledge, you're in for a treat. I'm excited to announce that Dave Gray, one of our most popular instructors, has returned to the freCodeCamp.org YouTube]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Concepts to Know Before Learning Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-concepts-to-know-before-learning-node-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-concepts-to-know-before-learning-node-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T15:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before Node.js came into existence,  JavaScript could only be run on the browser. It could only be used as a scripting language for frontend web development.  Then, Node.js came to free JavaScript from this confinement. It made JavaScript ubiquitous (meaning it could now be run everywhere). Node.js is a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Musab Habeeb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy an AWS Lambda Function with Serverless Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-aws-lambda-with-serverless/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-aws-lambda-with-serverless/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T23:52:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless computing has revolutionized the way developers build and deploy applications in the cloud. It takes away the complexities of server management, allowing developers to focus solely on writing code and delivering value to their users. In the realm of serverless computing, AWS Lambda stands out as a leading platform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Destiny Erhabor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Smashing Magazine Uses TinaCMS To Manage An Editorial Workflow]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/smashing-magazine-tinacms-manage-editorial-workflow/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/smashing-magazine-tinacms-manage-editorial-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is a peek behind the curtain of how content is managed here at Smashing Magazine. In it, you’ll get a tour of an article’s full lifecycle, from a basic outline to the sort of thing you’re reading right this second.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build and Deploy an AI SaaS with Paid Subscriptions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-deploy-an-ai-saas-with-paid-subscriptions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-deploy-an-ai-saas-with-paid-subscriptions/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T17:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is easier than ever to launch your own Software as a Service (SaaS) company! (The hard part is getting people interested in it). We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will guide you through every step of building and deploying a full-stack AI SaaS application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network File System – How to Confirm Your Application is Using NFS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-confirm-your-application-is-using-nfs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-confirm-your-application-is-using-nfs/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T06:54:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was tasked recently to find which of our processes was accessing a NFS share [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Network_File_System]. During this process, I found that some tools are better adapted than others for the task. In this article, I want to share with you my findings. The whole process was fun and gave]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Disney Data Scientist Eric Leung on Math, Medicine, and Learning to Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-data-scientist-at-disney-eric-leung-on-math-medicine-and-learning-to-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-data-scientist-at-disney-eric-leung-on-math-medicine-and-learning-to-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T20:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I'm joined by Eric Leung, Data Scientist at Disney and long-time open source contributor to freeCodeCamp. Eric Leung grew up in Oklahoma and learned a lot of math in high school. His friends wanted to go to medical school and he originally planned to join them. But instead]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Solana Curriculum: Smart Contracts, dApps, and Command Line Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/solana-curriculum/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/solana-curriculum/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Solana Curriculum is live. You can now learn Solana's blockchain protocol and the Solana tool ecosystem interactively by building a series of projects. This curriculum is made possible by The Solana Foundation, who gave our charity a grant to 100% fund development of this curriculum. What will this curriculum]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Mondloch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Quick Look at Bun 1.0 – The Node.js Alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-quick-look-at-bun-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-quick-look-at-bun-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T07:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A wise man once told me, "When you start eating Bun, Node.js will feel bland". But why is that relevant? JavaScript got way faster with a new JavaScript runtime called Bun, which is now production-ready with its version 1.0 release. But how and why is it faster than Node.js? A]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nishant Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revealing Images With CSS Mask Animations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/revealing-images-css-mask-animations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/revealing-images-css-mask-animations/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s play with images and experiment with CSS masks. The idea is fairly simple: take a single `` tag and harness the power of CSS to accomplish complex hover transitions. Through different demos, you will see how CSS masks combined with gradients allow us to create fancy effects — with efficient, reusable code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Contribute to Open Source Projects – Non-Technical Things You Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-contribute-to-open-source/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-contribute-to-open-source/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T17:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've contributed to open-source projects for a few years and learned a lot from the process. These experiences allowed me to look closer at the open source flow, from the technical, such as Git and GitHub, to the non-technical aspects. Although they are as important as the technical sides, the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayu Adiati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Return Results from a Python Function to Your Program When a Library is Blocking the Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/return-results-from-a-python-function-when-library-is-blocking-the-way/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/return-results-from-a-python-function-when-library-is-blocking-the-way/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T10:46:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Usually a Python function passes its results back using a return statement. The problem is that sometimes it can't, so you need to figure out a different way to return those results.  This happens, most often, when someone else's library's interface is in the way, and you can't change]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David A. Kra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Vector Embeddings to Create an AI Assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vector-embeddings-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vector-embeddings-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T02:18:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vector embeddings are a key concept in the realm of machine learning and artificial intelligence. They bridge the gap between human language and machine understanding. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach out about vector embeddings and how to create an AI assistant. Ania]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Dynamic Programming Techniques in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-dynamic-programming-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-dynamic-programming-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T02:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic programming is a powerful technique that has been a cornerstone in the world of algorithms and computer science. It's a method that breaks down problems into smaller, more manageable sub-problems, solving each one only once and storing their solutions in case they're needed again. This approach is particularly useful]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Things to Consider When Picking Fonts for your Next Project – An In-Depth Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/things-to-consider-when-picking-fonts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/things-to-consider-when-picking-fonts/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T11:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the modern web, we've normalized fetching fonts from client-side, or embedding fonts in resources that are served to users. While this may be tempting, it actually makes very little sense for most use-cases. This isn't suggesting to never use external fonts. Just a reminder that fonts aren't free, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Falco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facilitating Inclusive Online Workshops (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/facilitating-inclusive-online-workshops-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/facilitating-inclusive-online-workshops-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Running a workshop can be an effective alternative to traditional, long-standing meetings. To help ensure its success, Ben Shih introduces the concept of an inclusive workshop. In Part 1 of the series, you discover the fundamentals of inclusivity and get some solid guidance on how to plan an inclusive remote workshop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Shih)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fine-Tune the Donut Model – With Example Use Case]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fine-tune-the-donut-model/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fine-tune-the-donut-model/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T17:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Donut model in Python is a model you can use to extract text from a given image. This can be useful in various scenarios, like scanning receipts, for example.  You can easily download the Donut model from GitHub [https://github.com/clovaai/donut]. But as is common with AI models, you should]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eivind Kjosbakken</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[13 Types of Cyber Attacks You Should Know in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/types-of-cyber-attacks-to-know/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/types-of-cyber-attacks-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T17:28:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2023, the digital landscape is filled with unprecedented cybersecurity risks. From phishing scams to ransomware attacks. This article outlines different types of cyber attacks that individuals and businesses should be vigilant about. Cyber-attacks are a prevalent threat in the online world. They have the potential to cause substantial difficulties]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Communication Design Patterns for Backend Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/communication-design-patterns-for-backend-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/communication-design-patterns-for-backend-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T16:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you’re building the backend of an application, you’ve got to figure out how all the different components are going to talk to each other.  It’s like setting up a communication network for your app’s brain, and the way you do it can seriously impact how well your app]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chinwendu Enyinna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fundamentals of Finance & Economics for Businesses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fundamentals-of-finance-economics-for-businesses/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fundamentals-of-finance-economics-for-businesses/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T14:58:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving landscape of business, understanding the intricacies of finance and economics is essential for success. Topics such as the principles of money and deciphering the impact of macroeconomic changes serve as the bedrock of strategic decision-making. We just posted a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Read a CSV File from S3 Bucket in AWS Lambda - A Definitive Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/read-csv-file-from-s3-bucket-in-aws-lambda/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/read-csv-file-from-s3-bucket-in-aws-lambda/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T10:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Simple Storage Service (S3) is a highly scalable, durable, and available object storage service. It is designed to store any amount of data, anytime, from anywhere on the web.  S3 is a key component of the Amazon Web Services (AWS) cloud platform. AWS Lambda is a serverless computing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikram Aruchamy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Transition vs Animation Handbook – How to Animate Elements in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-transition-vs-css-animation-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-transition-vs-css-animation-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T00:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS transitions and animations provide smooth, gradual ways to change an element's style. But they work in different ways. Here are the main distinctions between them: CSS Transition CSS Animation  * Creates smooth transitions from one CSS value to    another.   * You need triggers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi Sofela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve Your ReactJS Code – Tips for Code Readability and Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-reactjs-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-reactjs-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T20:34:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ReactJS is one of the most popular JavaScript libraries for building scalable and performant applications.  When you're working on ReactJS projects, whether they're large or small, you'll need to focus on code quality, readability, maintainable, and scalability.  Writing good code will also help you reduce PR comments from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neha sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Certified Associate (003) – How to Study for the Exam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/terraform-certified-associate-003-study-notes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/terraform-certified-associate-003-study-notes/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T19:17:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been meaning to get my Terraform associates certification for some time now, but something always got in the way.  Finally I was able to sit down and work my way through the study materials. Currently Andrew Brown and I are creating two Terraform Bootcamps: one for beginners [https://terraform.cloudprojectbootcamp.com/]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a no-code game with GDevelop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-no-code-game-with-gdevelop/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-no-code-game-with-gdevelop/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T19:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever dreamt of designing a video game but found yourself hesitant because of the coding aspect? Well, you can create your own came without code! We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org that will guide you through the creation of a wave defense game, all without having]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gradients, Blend Modes, And A Really Cool Hover Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/gradients-blend-modes-hover-effect/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/gradients-blend-modes-hover-effect/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gradients are a powerful CSS feature. We use them for texture, depth, and even to hide parts of elements with CSS masking. This article covers another interesting way to use gradients — as a hover effect that affects the appearance of other elements around the hovered element.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Samathanam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Requirements.txt – How to Create and Pip Install Requirements.txt in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-requirementstxt-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-requirementstxt-explained/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T14:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many Python packages we use to solve our coding problems daily. Take, for instance, the library "Beautiful Soup," – it doesn't come with Python by default and needs to be installed separately.  Many projects rely on libraries and other dependencies, and installing each one can be tedious]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tantoluwa Heritage Alabi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EternalBlue Explained – An In-Depth Analysis of the Notorious Windows Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/eternalblue-explained-an-analysis-of-the-windows-flaw/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/eternalblue-explained-an-analysis-of-the-windows-flaw/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T08:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>