<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-13T01:26:11.582Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Concatenate in Excel – How to Use the Concat Function]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/concatenate-in-excel-how-to-use-the-concat-function/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/concatenate-in-excel-how-to-use-the-concat-function/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T19:26:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Excel has many useful functions that you can use to work with your data. In this guide you will learn about the CONCAT function and how to use it. Concatenation just means to join two things together. And in Excel, you can use the CONCAT function to join data from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilenia Magoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Global Variables – How to Define a Global Variable Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-global-variables-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-global-variables-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T18:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn the basics of global variables. To begin with, you will learn how to declare variables in Python and what the term 'variable scope' actually means. Then, you will learn the differences between local and global variables and understand how to define global variables and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Neural Networks by Building a Self-Driving Car Sim Using JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/self-driving-car-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/self-driving-car-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T16:29:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Any application that can be written in JavaScript, will eventually be written in JavaScript." – Jeff Atwood It's time for you to create a self-driving car using JavaScript! We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you learn about neural networks by teaching you how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Excel Formulas – Basic Functions for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/excel-formulas-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/excel-formulas-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T15:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Excel lets you use formulas and functions to perform basic and advanced numerical calculations. You can do addition, subtraction, multiplication, division, mean, worke with strings, and many others. In Excel, the difference between a formula and a function is that a function is a predefined calculation while a formula]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A CSS Slinky in 3D? Challenge Accepted!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365706</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-css-slinky-in-3d/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:27:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Braydon Coyer recently launched a monthly CSS art challenge. He actually had reached out to me about donating a copy of my book Move Things with CSS to use as a prize for the winner of the challenge — …
A CSS Slinky in 3D? Challenge Accepted! originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jhey Tompkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use Google CrUX To Analyze And Compare The Performance Of JS Frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/google-crux-analysis-comparison-performance-javascript-frameworks/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/google-crux-analysis-comparison-performance-javascript-frameworks/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Dan Shappir analyzes the performance cost associated with various frameworks and explains the wide variety of framework and platform choices that are currently available to front-end and fullstack developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dan Shappir)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python split() – String Splitting Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-split-string-splitting-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-split-string-splitting-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T23:12:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The split() method in Python splits characters in a string into separate items in a list.  In this tutorial, we'll go over some examples to help you learn how to use the  split() method. We'll start from the syntax and then see how we can modify the list]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Modules – Complete Guide to ES Modules and Module Bundlers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-es-modules-and-module-bundlers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-es-modules-and-module-bundlers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T23:06:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modules and Module Bundlers are essential components of modern web development. But understanding how they work can quickly become overwhelming. This article will show you all you need to know about ES Modules and Module Bundlers in plain English. Table of Contents  1.  What Exactly Is a JavaScript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi Sofela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technology Trends in 2022 – Keeping Up [Full Book for Managers]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/technology-trends-in-2022-keeping-up-full-book-for-managers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/technology-trends-in-2022-keeping-up-full-book-for-managers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T23:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is based on my recently published book, Keeping Up, a quick and accessible guide to the current state of the tech industry and the big trends you can't afford to ignore.  In it, we'll cover everything from digital security, privacy, serverless platforms, the internet of things (IoT),]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting ANRs in Your Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/detect-application-not-responding-errors-in-your-application/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/detect-application-not-responding-errors-in-your-application/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T15:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there was a way to make my applications "Application not responding" error proof, I would do it.  ANRs always seem to sneak up on you when you're not expecting them. And the problem is that there's nothing you can do about them.  You might see them pop]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Ben Rachel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COLRv1 and CSS font-palette: Web Typography Gets Colorful]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365677</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/colrv1-and-css-font-palette-web-typography/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T14:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Toshi Omagari, the author of Arcade Game Typography, the world’s first multi-colored digital font was created in 1982 for a never-released video game called Insector. Multi-colored fonts, sometimes called chromatic type, are still relatively rare on the …
COLRv1 and CSS font-palette: Web Typography Gets Colorful originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Social Media App with Django]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-social-media-app-with-django/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-social-media-app-with-django/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T14:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Django is a high-level Python web framework that enables rapid development of secure and maintainable websites. We just published a 5-hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you improve your Django skills by building a social media application.  Tomi Tokko teaches this course. He has created]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Even Small UX Changes Can Result In An Increase In Conversion (A Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/sunuva-case-study-ux-changes-result-increase-conversion/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/sunuva-case-study-ux-changes-result-increase-conversion/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will be taking a closer look at a design case study and discuss possible reasons why its customers abandon their online shopping carts and what solutions are recommended in each particular case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Denis Studennikov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python List insert() – How to Add to a List in Python]]></title>
        <id>627a6d54ac30a306bbeac950</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-insert-how-to-add-to-a-list-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T21:22:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The list data type is one of the built-in data structures in Python along with sets, tuples, and dictionaries. You use a list to organize, group, and store data. But each of these data structures has distinctive features that differentiates them from each other. In this article, we'll see how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Print Without Newline [SOLVED]]]></title>
        <id>627a1dd3ac30a306bbeac53f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-print-without-newline-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T16:18:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're familiar with Python, you may have noticed that the built-in function  print() doesn't need an explicit \n character at the end of each line.  This means that the output from the following snippet of code print('freeCodeCamp Curriculum') print('freeCodeCamp News') print('freeCodeCamp YouTube Channel') will be: freeCodeCamp Curriculum]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farhan Hasin Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Lock Cells in Excel – Excel Locked Cell Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>627a40ceac30a306bbeac5da</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-lock-cells-in-excel-excel-locked-cell-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T15:57:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To keep your Excel data safe from unwanted editing and tampering, you might want to lock the cells and protect the worksheet. Fortunately, Excel is a highly customizable data analysis tool which lets you lock cells and protect your worksheets with a password at the same time. In this guide,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Server Infrastructure Clouds using Falco, Prometheus, Grafana and Docker]]></title>
        <id>627859645aeb5306e9ee725f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/secure-server-infrastructure-clouds-using-falco-prometheus-grafana-and-docker/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T14:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was recently looking for a way to keep tabs on our containers and applications at work. Specifically, I was interested in detecting anomalies in the configuration. After a little research, I stumbled on Falco [https://github.com/falcosecurity/falco]. What I found was a very complete Open Source platform with lots of features]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Path – How to Use the Pathlib Module with Examples]]></title>
        <id>6269555ac1c601068f4e811b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-pathlib-module-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T13:59:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Each operating system has different rules for constructing file paths. For example, Linux uses forward slashes for paths, while Windows uses backslashes.  This small difference can cause issues if you are working on a project and you want other developers who come from different operating systems to expand your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rochdi Khalid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Create a Tiny Programming Language]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365650</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/lets-create-a-tiny-programming-language/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T13:56:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, you are probably familiar with one or more programming languages. But have you ever wondered how you could create your own programming language? And by that, I mean:
A programming language is any set of rules that convert 
…
Let’s Create a Tiny Programming Language originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md Shuvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magical SVG Techniques]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/magical-svg-techniques/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/magical-svg-techniques/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s no secret that SVGs are super powerful, and yet, they still manage to surprise. Have you ever considered using SVG’s internal coordinate system to create a responsive image grid, for example, or adding texture to an SVG? In this post, we’ll look into some magical SVG techniques that open up new possibilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Resolve Merge Conflicts in Git – A Practical Guide with Examples]]></title>
        <id>6272b9cdc1c601068f4ec497</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/resolve-merge-conflicts-in-git-a-practical-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T23:09:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is an open-source distributed version control system. It helps you manage your project files easily using local branching, staging, and workflows.  Many developers use Git today. And they're usually familiar with basic Git concepts like:  * How to initiate a repository.  * How to create branches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Lowercase – How to Use the String lower() Function]]></title>
        <id>62725fadc1c601068f4ebf17</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-lowercase-how-to-use-the-string-lower-function/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T22:04:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strings are a fundamental part of working with Python. And the lower() method is one of the many integrated methods that you can use to work with strings. In this article, we'll see how to make strings lowercase with the lower() method in Python. What is a string? A string]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilenia Magoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Google Docs Clone with React, Material UI, & Firebase]]></title>
        <id>627601655aeb5306e9ee6ab2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-google-docs-clone-with-react-and-firebase/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T21:16:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll build a Google Docs clone using React, Material UI, and Firebase. The final app will look like this: If we click any document, it will open up and we can edit them however we need to. And the most amazing feature is that we can edit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nishant Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Object-Oriented Programming in JavaScript for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>6258683aac55f60686c35075</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-oriented-javascript-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T20:36:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we're going to review the main characteristics of object oriented programming (OOP) with practical JavaScript examples. We will talk about OOP main concepts, why and when it can be useful, and I'll give you plenty of examples using JS code.  If you're not familiar]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Excel Shortcuts – Keyboard Shortcuts for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>62727994c1c601068f4ec082</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/excel-shortcuts-keyboard-shortcuts-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T15:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many data analytics tools out there, but Microsoft Excel remains a popular go-to for storing and managing data. Since Excel has a lot of functionality built into it, getting familiar with the various keyboard shortcuts will help you work more efficiently. In this article, I’m going to show]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Tools for Creating AVIF Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365579</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/useful-tools-for-creating-avif-images/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T15:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AVIF (AV1 Image File Format) is a modern image file format specification for storing images that offer a much more significant file reduction when compared to other formats like JPG, JPEG, PNG, and WebP. Version 1.0.0 of the AVIF specification …
Useful Tools for Creating AVIF Images originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sunkanmi Fafowora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance Game Changer: Browser Back/Forward Cache]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/performance-game-changer-back-forward-cache/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/performance-game-changer-back-forward-cache/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the end of 2021, the Chrome team shipped some functionality that has the ability to make or break sites meeting the Core Web Vitals. So, let’s learn a little bit more about the Back/Forward Cache (aka bfcache), and what you can do to test if your website is compatible with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Center an Absolute Positioned Element Vertically and Horizontally with CSS]]></title>
        <id>62720d66c1c601068f4ebbdb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-center-an-absolute-positioned-element/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T19:56:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Absolute positioned elements are removed from the flow of a document. And sometimes, knowing how to correctly position such elements in the center of the page can be confusing. I mean, CSS is confusing already. 😅 In this article, I will show you how to center an absolute element either]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn Python in 2022]]></title>
        <id>627036b7c1c601068f4eb2b6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-learn-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T17:09:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With each passing year, the Python programming language becomes more and more popular. According to the Stack Overflow Developer Survey for 2021 [https://insights.stackoverflow.com/survey/2021#technology], Python was the 3rd most popular language, following JavaScript and HTML & CSS. And this growth doesn't seem to be slowing down anytime soon, so Python programmers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Serve a Subdomain as a Subdirectory]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365614</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-serve-a-subdomain-as-a-subdirectory/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T14:19:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s say you have a website built on a platform that excels at design and it’s available at example.com. But that platform falls short at blogging. So you think to yourself, “What if I could use a different blogging …
How to Serve a Subdomain as a Subdirectory originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Siciliano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Give Effective Feedback Remotely]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/give-effective-feedback-remotely/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/give-effective-feedback-remotely/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s explore how to give and receive better feedback when working remotely — feedback that is actionable, specific, kind, and that won’t set you on edge. We’ll start by explaining when feedback sessions don’t work and how to prevent it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joshua Mauldin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Visualization with D3.js]]></title>
        <id>62740998c1c601068f4ecc38</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-visualizatoin-with-d3/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T17:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[D3.js is a JavaScript library for manipulating documents based on data. D3 helps you bring data to life using HTML, SVG, and CSS. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that teaches how to implement various data visualization techniques with D3.js. Curran Kelleher teaches this course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Destructure an Array in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>62715143c1c601068f4eb5fe</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-destructure-an-array-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T14:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Array destructuring is an efficient way to extract multiple values from data that’s stored in an array. In this tutorial we’ll learn about array destructuring. We'll go over examples to learn the ins and outs of how array destructuring works.  I've also created a video of this tutorial: Let's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Madison Kanna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resilience, Flexibility And Immediacy: Working With Headless Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/resilience-flexibility-immediacy-headless-systems/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/resilience-flexibility-immediacy-headless-systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When deploying websites, there’s rarely a one-size-fits-all solution. Some websites benefit from server-rendered pages, some prefer statically generating content upfront. In this article, Stefan explains how a CMS such as [Storyblok](link) can help you make your site more resilient without losing the flexibility to deliver time-relevant content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stefan Baumgartner)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getline in C++ – cin getline() Function Example]]></title>
        <id>626fbddfc1c601068f4eaec5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/getline-in-cpp-cin-getline-function-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T20:06:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll talk about the getline() function in C++. This is an inbuilt function that accepts single and multiple character inputs. When working with user input in C++, the cin object allows us to get input information from the user. But when we try to log out the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage Browser Defaults with event.preventDefault() and event.stopPropagation()]]></title>
        <id>626b0796c1c601068f4e89b4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manage-default-behavior-in-browser/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T19:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Browsers have default interactions and behaviors for different events. For example, when a user clicks a "submit" button on a form, the form is submitted to a URL by default. When the child of an element is clicked, the click event also occurs on the element because it is the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Code Examples – Simple Python Program Example]]></title>
        <id>626d5ae3c1c601068f4ea1c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-code-examples-simple-python-program-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T17:20:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python is a high-level, general purpose, interpreted programming language. It's well-known for being very easy to learn yet powerful, and it has many uses in many different fields. If you're someone trying to get started with Python, it's easy to get lost among all the excellent learning resources on the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farhan Hasin Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How to Manipulate CSS with JavaScript by Coding a Dynamic Picture Frame]]></title>
        <id>626d47a4c1c601068f4e9f91</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-how-to-manipulate-css-with-javascript-by-coding-a-dynamic-picture-frame/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T15:27:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOM manipulation can simply be defined as manipulating HTML documents (or pages) with JavaScript.  The DOM stands for Document Object Model that you can visualize as a tree-like structure made up of different HTML elements.  Visualizing an HTML document like a tree makes it easy to access its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel A. Olubiyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REST API Design Best Practices – How to Build a REST API with JavaScript, Node.js, and Express.js]]></title>
        <id>625e8e8bac55f60686c37f27</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rest-api-design-best-practices-build-a-rest-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T15:10:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've created and consumed many API's over the past few years. During that time, I've come across good and bad practices and have experienced nasty situations when consuming and building API's. But there also have been great moments. There are helpful articles online which present many best practices, but many]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jean-Marc Möckel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn React Router 6]]></title>
        <id>62728f26c1c601068f4ec233</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-react-router-6/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T14:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React Router is a JavaScript library that helps developers create single-page applications that are responsive and have a dynamic user interface. It is a popular tool among React developers and is used to create routing and navigation for web applications. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Syntax Highlighting (and More!) With Prism on a Static Site]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365510</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/syntax-highlighting-prism-on-a-next-js-site/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T14:16:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, you’ve decided to build a blog with Next.js. Like any dev blogger, you’d like to have code snippets in your posts that are formatted nicely with syntax highlighting. Perhaps you also want to display line numbers in the …
Syntax Highlighting (and More!) With Prism on a Static Site originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing A Better Language Selector]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/designing-better-language-selector/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/designing-better-language-selector/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How difficult can it be to design a bulletproof language selector? It’s not as straightforward as one might think. We need to avoid redirects, decouple our language and country presets, allow for overrides, and use non-modal windows. Let’s dive in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Report a Bug to freeCodeCamp]]></title>
        <id>626fa644c1c601068f4ead26</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-report-a-bug-to-freecodecamp/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T21:07:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for taking the time to report an issue with freeCodeCamp. If you think you’ve found a bug on freeCodeCamp, please follow these steps to resolve your problem: Reset the Code in the Editor Try resetting the code in the editor using the reset button on the page. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove Duplicates in Excel – Delete Duplicate Rows Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>626fe2c2c1c601068f4eaf1d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-duplicates-in-excel-delete-duplicate-rows-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T19:58:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Excel worksheet can be difficult to work with if it contains duplicates – especially if you’re not the author of the worksheet. If you find them, you might want to highlight or remove such duplicates in the Excel sheet so you don’t run into errors. In this article, I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Prototypes and Inheritance – and Why They Say Everything in JS is an Object]]></title>
        <id>6259a2ffac55f60686c35b35</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prototypes-and-inheritance-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T16:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this short article we're going to talk about prototypal inheritance in JavaScript, and what are the implications of it. Table of Contents  * Intro  * How to access a prototype’s properties and methods in JavaScript  * The prototype chain  * A prototype-based language]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Join MySQL and Postgres in a Live Materialized View]]></title>
        <id>62612e2aac55f60686c39d58</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-join-mysql-and-postgres-in-a-live-materialized-view/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T15:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working on a project that consists of a lot of microservices, it'll likely also include multiple databases.  For example, you might have a MySQL database [https://www.mysql.com] and a  PostgreSQL database [https://www.postgresql.org], both running on separate servers. Usually, to join the data from the two databases, you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bobby Iliev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Google Dataproc – Example with PySpark and Jupyter Notebook]]></title>
        <id>626aebfac1c601068f4e8804</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-google-dataproc/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T15:14:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll explain what Dataproc is and how it works.  Dataproc is a Google Cloud Platform managed service for Spark and Hadoop which helps you with Big Data Processing, ETL, and Machine Learning. It provides a Hadoop cluster and supports Hadoop ecosystems tools like Flink, Hive, Presto,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sameer Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Custom GitHub Badges to Your Repo]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364932</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/adding-custom-github-badges-to-your-repo/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T14:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve spent time looking at open-source repos on GitHub, you’ve probably noticed that most of them use badges in their README files. Take the official React repository, for instance. There are GitHub badges all over the README file that communicate important dynamic info, like the latest released …
Adding Custom GitHub Badges to Your Repo originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Sypteras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Don’t Need A UI Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/you-dont-need-ui-framework/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/you-dont-need-ui-framework/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers often reach for UI frameworks like Bootstrap or Material UI, hoping that they’ll save a bunch of time and quickly build a professional-looking app. Unfortunately, things rarely work out this way. Let’s talk about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Josh Comeau)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design Principles – A List of the Principles of Design]]></title>
        <id>624bed87ac55f60686c2e0ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/design-principles-a-list-of-the-principles-of-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T22:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you start learning graphic design theory, you may be surprised to find out that there are specific rules you need to follow when designing. Those rules are known as design principles, and in this article, you will learn the basics of the 13 design principles. Knowing what design principles]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Convert a String to a Number in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>626e3d0bc1c601068f4ea71d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-a-string-to-a-number-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T22:25:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many ways to convert a string into a number using JavaScript. But what does that look like in code?  In this article, I will show you 11 ways to convert a string into a number.  How to convert a string to a number in JavaScript using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Int to String in C++ – How to Convert an Integer with to_string]]></title>
        <id>626c00bdc1c601068f4e918e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/int-to-string-in-cpp-how-to-convert-an-integer-with-tostring/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T21:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with strings in your code, you might want to perform certain operations like concatenating (or linking together) two strings.  But there are cases when you'd rather work with numerical values as though they were strings because concatenating a string and an integer will give you an error.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Index – How to Find the Index of an Element in a List]]></title>
        <id>62652501ac55f60686c3b91b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-index-find-index-of-element-in-list/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T20:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're learning to code, you eventually learn about lists and the different operations you can perform on them.  In this article, we'll go through how you can find the index of a particular element which is stored in a list in Python. What is a List in Python?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suchandra Datta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Collaborative Coding? Pair Programming, Mob Programming, and How it All Works]]></title>
        <id>626cee91c1c601068f4e995b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/collaborative-coding-tips/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T20:13:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coding is not supposed to be a steep mountain climb. And it can get a lot easier if you have the right strategies and tools.  After all, as noted software engineer and writer Joel Spolsky [http://blogs.perl.org/users/buddy_burden/2013/12/perl-and-me-part-4-a-worthy-program-exceedingly-well-read.html#note1]  says, "it is harder to read code than to write it." One]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrej Kovacevic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bash Command Line Tips to Help You Work Faster]]></title>
        <id>626c29dac1c601068f4e92e3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/bash-command-line-tips-to-help-you-work-faster/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T19:56:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning the command line is essential for any aspiring developer. And to execute commands on the command line, you need a shell. The Bash shell is popular in Unix-like operating systems like Mac and Linux. In fact in most Linux distros, Bash is the default shell. You can also use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vinod Mathew Sebastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sudo apt-get update VS upgrade – What is the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>6262bcd7ac55f60686c3acd4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sudo-apt-get-update-vs-upgrade-what-is-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T19:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[sudo apt-get update and sudo apt-get upgrade are two commands you can use to keep all of your packages up to date in Debian or a Debian-based Linux distribution. They're common commands for Linux admins and people doing DevOps, but are handy to know even if you don't use the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Koishigawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is ANAME? ANAME Record DNS Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>626b9e1cc1c601068f4e8d20</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-aname-aname-record-dns-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T18:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever had to make a domain name work with a website, you’ve probably seen ANAME as some record – just like the popular Canonical name record type or simply CNAME. CNAME and ANAME are both solutions for pointing a hostname to your website. For example, yourapp.netlify.com to yourwebsite.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming Paradigms – Paradigm Examples for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>6267194ac1c601068f4e72c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/an-introduction-to-programming-paradigms/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T16:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we're going to take a look at programming paradigms, a fancy title to describe popular ways or styles to organize your programming. I'll try to break it down in pieces and give a simple explanation of each paradigm. This way you can understand what people]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Realistic Reflections With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365491</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-realistic-reflections-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T14:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In design, reflections are stylized mirror images of objects. Even though they are not as popular as shadows, they have their moments — just think about the first time you explored the different font formats in MS Word or PowerPoint: …
Creating Realistic Reflections With CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud Associate Cloud Engineer Certification Study Course – Pass the Exam With This Free 20 Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>626c1b56c1c601068f4e9287</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-cloud-digital-leader-certification-study-course-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-20-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T13:32:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Google Cloud Associate Cloud Engineer? The Associate Cloud Engineer also commonly referred to as the ACE is the associate level certification by Google Cloud.  They key difference between the Associate Cloud Engineer and the Google Cloud Digital Cloud Leader is that the Associate Cloud Engineer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Brown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make A Wish (May 2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-30T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s welcome May with a new collection of wallpapers. Designed with love by artists and designers from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for May 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating the DigitalOcean Logo in 3D With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365447</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-the-digitalocean-logo-in-3d-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T14:37:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Howdy y’all! Unless you’ve been living under a rock (and maybe even then), you’ve undoubtedly heard the news that CSS-Tricks, was acquired by DigitalOcean. Congratulations to everyone! 🥳
As a little hurrah to commemorate the occasion, I wanted to …
Creating the DigitalOcean Logo in 3D With CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jhey Tompkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Partytown Eliminates Website Bloat From Third-Party Scripts]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/partytown-eliminates-website-bloat-third-party-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/partytown-eliminates-website-bloat-third-party-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Partytown, a lightweight open-source solution that reduces execution delays due to third-party JavaScript by offloading third-party scripts to web workers, which run in background threads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Steve Sewell)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Blazor WebAssembly and Web API on .NET 6 by Building a Shopping Cart App]]></title>
        <id>626acd1fc1c601068f4e86be</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-blazor-webassembly-and/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T17:28:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blazor WebAssembly is a single-page app framework for building interactive client-side web apps with .NET. It uses open web standards without plugins or recompiling code into other languages. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Blazor WebAssembly and Web]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting Up CloudFront to Host Your Web App]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365413</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/setting-up-cloudfront-to-host-your-web-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T14:42:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my last article, we went over how to set up a web app that serves chunks and bundles of CSS and JavaScript from CloudFront. We integrated it into Vite so that when the app runs in a browser, …
Setting Up CloudFront to Host Your Web App originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CTA Modal: How To Build A Web Component]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/cta-modal-build-web-component/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/cta-modal-build-web-component/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Nathan Smith explains how to create modal dialog windows with rich interaction that will only require authoring HTML in order to be used. They are based on Web Components that are currently supported by every major browser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nathan Smith)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Habit System and Stay Motivated as a Developer]]></title>
        <id>6267958cc1c601068f4e758d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-habit-system-and-stay-motivated-as-a-developer/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T00:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you ever find it challenging to work on your project, side hustle, or even your hobby?  Have you ever had those moments where nothing feels exciting? You lay in bed thinking – is it me, or is my work that boring?  I have those days too. Some]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shruti Kapoor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Center a Div with CSS]]></title>
        <id>62458d52138a19064b069054</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-center-a-div-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T19:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a few common coding problems you might encounter when you start practicing what you've learned by building projects. One common problem you'll face as a web developer is how to place an element at the center of a page or within an element acting as its container. It's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Send Large Video Files – Share a Big File with Email]]></title>
        <id>626919edc1c601068f4e809e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-send-large-video-files-share-a-big-file-with-email/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T19:51:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sending large files through email can be quite challenging. This is because each email client has a size limit for file sharing. Gmail and Yahoo limit file size to 25MB, while outlook and iCloud limit files to 20MB. So, if you decide to send, for example, a video file larger]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix Google Chrome Black Screen on Linux OS (Wayland)]]></title>
        <id>6266b589ac55f60686c3c44f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fix-black-screen-on-google-chrome-on-linux-os/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T19:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a Linux user, then you've likely used the GNOME Desktop Environment at least once. The latest GNOME DE (Desktop Environment) uses Wayland nowadays. And while it's possible to remove Wayland and select Xorg if you want, most users are starting to use Wayland as their daily driver.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run Multiple Containers with Docker Compose]]></title>
        <id>6267fe2ec1c601068f4e77da</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/run-multiple-containers-with-docker-compose/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T19:31:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker has become increasingly popular over the last several years. One reason for this is that you can create portable containers which are fast and easy to deploy.  As described on Docker's website [https://www.docker.com/resources/what-container/], a container is something that packages your code along with any other dependencies so that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arjav Dave</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build and Push Docker Images to AWS ECR]]></title>
        <id>625fc3caac55f60686c38ce0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-push-docker-images-to-aws-ecr/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T16:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker is a platform that helps you build, run, and ship applications in a seamless and error-free way.  You've likely come across a scenario where the code is running on your machine, but is somehow throwing errors on someone else's machine.  Well, Docker was created to solve this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kaushal Joshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Assembly Language Programming with ARM]]></title>
        <id>6269557fc1c601068f4e8127</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-assembly-language-programming-with-arm/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T14:49:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Assembly language is a low-level programming language for a computer or other programmable device that is closest to the machine language. It is often specific to a particular computer architecture so there are multiple types of assembly languages. ARM is an increasingly popular assembly language.  We just published a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cool Hover Effects That Use Background Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365383</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/cool-hover-effects-using-background-properties/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T14:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A while ago, Geoff wrote an article about a cool hover effect. The effect relies on a combination of CSS pseudo-elements, transforms, and transitions. A lot of comments have shown that the same effect can be done using background …
Cool Hover Effects That Use Background Properties originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boosting UX With Design KPIs]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/boosting-ux-with-design-kpis/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/boosting-ux-with-design-kpis/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We should be able to measure how well a particular design solves a particular problem. Let’s explore design KPIs that capture user’s experience, how to measure them and how to keep both users and business stakeholders happy, over time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux chmod and chown – How to Change File Permissions and Ownership in Linux]]></title>
        <id>626074adac55f60686c397ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linux-chmod-chown-change-file-permissions/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T00:38:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux is a multi user OS which means that it supports multiple users at a time.  As many people can access the system simultaneously and some resources are shared, Linux controls access through ownership and permissions.  Linux file ownership In Linux, there are three types of owners: user,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Program to Print the Fibonacci Sequence]]></title>
        <id>6262b979ac55f60686c3aca1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-program-to-print-the-fibonacci-sequence/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T00:34:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Questions about the Fibonacci Series are some of the most commonly asked in Python interviews.  In this article, I'll explain a step-by-step approach on how to print the Fibonacci sequence using two different techniques, iteration and recursion.  Before we begin, let's first understand some basic terminology. What is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Resize Elements in Figma]]></title>
        <id>6253a5fcac55f60686c31c25</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-resize-elements-in-figma/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T23:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll learn a few different ways to resize elements and groups in Figma (in addition to the default method). We'll also learn how to resize frames without moving elements in the frames. In Figma, there are other ways to resize elements apart from the default method. So]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Homomorphic Encryption?]]></title>
        <id>6255a0d4ac55f60686c32eaa</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-homomorphic-encryption/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T23:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article we will discuss Homomorphic Encryption, the problem that it solves, and the different types that exist.  Then we will write code in Python to show some of its capabilities in action. Here's what we'll cover:  1. What is Homomorphic Encryption?  2. Advantages of Homomorphic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aris Zagakos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vite.js Tutorial – How to Install and Use Vite in Your Web Projects]]></title>
        <id>6265c16bac55f60686c3bf05</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-started-with-vite/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T21:41:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vite.js [/news/p/e534a679-ce3c-4cf1-842b-96087d30944d/Vite.js] is a rapid development tool for modern web projects. It focuses on speed and performance by improving the development experience. Vite uses native browser ES imports to enable support for modern browsers without a build process. Vite consists of two major parts:  * The dev server provides]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Popoola Temitope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Memoization? How and When to Memoize in JavaScript and React]]></title>
        <id>6259a28cac55f60686c35b31</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/memoization-in-javascript-and-react/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T21:16:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we will talk about memoization, an optimization technique that can help make heavy computation processes more efficient. We will start by talking about what memoization is and when it's best to implement it. Later on we will give practical examples for JavaScript and React. Table]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Wait – How to Sleep N Seconds in JS with .setTimeout()]]></title>
        <id>622864b663ded806bb9e6f8d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-wait-how-to-sleep-n-seconds-in-js-with-settimeout/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T19:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you might want to delay the execution of your code. You may need certain lines of code to execute at a point in the future, when you explicitly specify, rather than all the code executing synchronously. Something like that is possible with JavaScript. In this article, you will learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Text Align in CSS – How to Align Text in Center with HTML]]></title>
        <id>626595d9ac55f60686c3bcb6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/text-align-in-css-how-to-align-text-in-center-with-html/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T19:08:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There will be many times where you will need to center some text using HTML and CSS. But what is the best way to go about that? In this article, I will show you how to use the text-align property in CSS and show you how to vertically align text]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python For Loop Example – How to Write Loops in Python]]></title>
        <id>6267fd8cc1c601068f4e77d0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-for-loop-example-how-to-write-loops-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T19:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are just getting started in Python, for loops are one of the fundamentals you should learn how to use. In the Python programming language, for loops are also called “definite loops” because they perform the instruction a certain number of times. This is in contrast to while loops,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Reusable SVG Icon React Components]]></title>
        <id>6260a9fcac55f60686c399f9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-reusable-icon-react-components-for-colors-and-sizes-customization/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T18:22:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We use icons when building frontend applications all the time – for indications, pointers, and so on. Here's how to create a reusable React component for icons. When it comes to icons, you can use PNG or SVG images. PNGs come with a fixed color but allow dimension changes (like]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avoiding the Pitfalls of Nested Components in a Design System]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365359</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/nested-components-in-a-design-system/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T14:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When creating a component-based, front-end infrastructure, one of the biggest pain points I’ve personally encountered is making components that are both reusable and responsive when there are nested components within components.
Take the following “call to action” (<CTA />…
Avoiding the Pitfalls of Nested Components in a Design System originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Christofi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preventing Bad UX Through Integrated Design Workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/ux-integrated-design-workflows/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/ux-integrated-design-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When bad UX has lingered in a product for so long, it can feel like a mountain to overcome. In this article, Ceara Crawshaw shares her advice on how you can invoke joy and assure the quality in the work done on product teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ceara Crawshaw)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Debug Applications with Strace, Python, and Wireshark]]></title>
        <id>6262a8d5ac55f60686c3abd5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/debug-an-app-with-strace-python-wireshark/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T00:23:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I will show you a few techniques you can use to troubleshoot a program when is not behaving.  This list is not universal and, depending on what you are looking for, it may not be enough to solve your problem. But it should be a good]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Variables Definition – What are CSS Vars and How to Use Them?]]></title>
        <id>6265e8feac55f60686c3bf60</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-css-variables-and-how-to-use-them/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T22:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS variables are custom variables that you can create and reuse throughout your stylesheet.  In this article, I will show you how to create CSS variables on the :root pseudo selector and show you how to access them using the var() function.  How to Create a CSS Custom]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Sass with CSS]]></title>
        <id>6229cf6963ded806bb9e79c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-sass-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T22:32:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi there! If you are reading this article, you're probably trying to understand what Sass is and how it works.  Sass is a CSS preprocessor that helps you manage tasks in large projects where the style sheets get larger, you have a number of lines of CSS code, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adalbert Pungu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[module.exports – How to Export in Node.js and JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>6260ad0dac55f60686c39a04</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/module-exports-how-to-export-in-node-js-and-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T21:03:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In programming, modules are components of a program with one or more functions or values. These values can also be shared across the entire program and can be used in different ways. In this article, I will show you how to share functions and values by exporting and importing modules]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Analysis in Go – How to Use the Gota Package]]></title>
        <id>6255f46dac55f60686c332f7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/exploratory-data-analysis-in-go-with-gota/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T20:52:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data analysis is the process of filtering, manipulating, and processing raw data and datasets to get insights from them. Python and R are usually the go-to languages for data analysis. But these days Go is becoming more and more popular for this purpose.  In this tutorial, we will be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ukeje Chukwuemeriwo Goodness</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Speed Up Your Lambda Functions]]></title>
        <id>6262c8c9ac55f60686c3aec7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-speed-up-lambda-functions/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T19:43:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lambda has gained massive popularity over the past few years. It has various use cases, from running simple scripts to gluing flows and processes within a serverless architecture or when running microservices. Still, if you've just started working in a new environment or organisation, you might feel cautious about using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Haydar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Check if a Property Exists in a JavaScript Object]]></title>
        <id>62649b7dac55f60686c3b738</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-check-if-a-property-exists-in-a-javascript-object/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T17:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you are working with objects in JavaScript, you might need to check if a specific property exists or not.  In this article, I will show you three ways to check if a property exists in a JavaScript object.  How to Use the hasOwnProperty() Method in JavaScript The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Test Your Apps using Jest, Testing Library, Cypress, and Supertest]]></title>
        <id>62588c4bac55f60686c352c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/test-a-react-app-with-jest-testing-library-and-cypress/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T17:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we're going to talk about testing. I'll give you a good overview of what testing is and an introduction of how you can implement it on your JavaScript projects. We'll use four very popular tools – Jest, Testing library, Cypress and Supertest. First we're going]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Train an AI to Play a Snake Game Using Python]]></title>
        <id>6266ced1ac55f60686c3c620</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/train-an-ia-to-play-a-snake-game-using-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T16:48:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why waste time playing video games when you can train an AI to do it for you? Ok, maybe playing yourself is more fun but training an AI can be more educational. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you the basics of reinforcement]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage State in Flutter Apps]]></title>
        <id>6261bb97ac55f60686c3a424</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manage-state-in-flutter-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T14:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing state is something most developers need to deal with when working on applications.  You might be familiar with the model-view-viewmodel (MVVM) pattern, where the ViewModel is the one responsible for a view’s state. But in Flutter, things are a bit different.  If you are reading this, then]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Ben Rachel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skeleton Loader Example – How to Build a Skeleton Screen with CSS for Better UX]]></title>
        <id>625fb4c7ac55f60686c38c36</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-skeleton-screens-using-css-for-better-user-experience/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T13:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content loaders, skeleton screens, ghost elements, and content placeholders. These are the names given to the effect we'll be exploring today. Many companies, such as Linkedin, Facebook, Youtube and Slack, use this effect in their apps and websites, as you may have noticed. As much as we developers want our]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Mitolu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What If Our Sliders Actually Slid?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/what-if-sliders-actually-slid-html-element-input-range/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/what-if-sliders-actually-slid-html-element-input-range/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Jhey Tompkins explores one of GreenSocks’ newest plugins alongside React to create an impractical whimsical spin on a well-known native element: ``.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing Strong Front-end Test Element Locators]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364218</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/front-end-test-element-locators/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T18:45:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automated front-end tests are awesome. We can write a test with code to visit a page — or load up just a single component — and have that test code click on things or type text like a user would, …
Writing Strong Front-end Test Element Locators originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Noonan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing The CLI The Way People Use It]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/testing-cli-way-people-use-it/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/testing-cli-way-people-use-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered, why do people write CLI tools? When is a good time to think about yours? Today we’ll touch on these questions, along with some tips to remember when creating one. However, all of this serves as a prelude to the real topic: end-to-end testing of CLI tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Georgy Marchuk)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[502 Bad Gateway Error [Solved]]]></title>
        <id>62615f82ac55f60686c39ef9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/502-bad-gateway-error-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T00:45:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can get a 502 bad gateway error when there's a problem with the server of the website you are trying to connect to. In more technical terms, the “502” in the error is an HTTP status code which indicates that one server received an invalid response from another server.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Better Programmer – Use a Skill-Building Planner]]></title>
        <id>62616030ac55f60686c39f0f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-better-programmer-use-a-skill-building-planner/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T00:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many programmers are missing out on a simple way to improve their programming progress.  Just think of athletes, entrepreneurs, students, health-nuts, and travelers. They’re among the diverse groups of people who use a planner. Planners are often used to give productivity a boost in order to stay organized and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Haddad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How to Use JavaScript Arrays by Building an iPhone Product Page]]></title>
        <id>625e8cfaac55f60686c37f21</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-arrays-by-building-product-page/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T00:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had the idea for this tutorial while browsing the official iPhone website. Apple is known for its great products and impeccable design, and if you spend enough time checking out its website, you can learn a thing or two about branding and great design.  One of the things]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel A. Olubiyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Contribute to Open-Source Projects – A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>624e7b3eac55f60686c2f0b8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-contribute-to-open-source-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T23:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've been considering contributing to an open source project, you might be weighing the pros and cons of doing so. You might hear things like open-source projects won't help you grow. Or they can't change your career trajectory. And that your contributions definitely won’t add to your portfolio. If]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankita Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Should You Move to the Cloud? Advantages of Cloud Computing Explained]]></title>
        <id>623422f3cdcd57069ddfade9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advantages-of-cloud-computing/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T22:27:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term cloud computing refers to software and services that run on the internet instead of locally on your on-site server or computer. Adopting the cloud can help you and your team cut costs and ensure that your data and systems are available to your customers anywhere and at any]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davis David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Colaboratory – How to Run Python Code in Your Google Drive]]></title>
        <id>625df1a2ac55f60686c37b2d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-colaboratory-python-code-in-your-google-drive/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T19:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Google Colaboratory (“Colab”) is a notebook (like a Jupyter Notebook) where you can run Python code in your Google Drive.  You can write text, write code, run that code, and see the output – all in line in the same notebook.  Benefits of Google Colab Sharing notebooks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Pratowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Firmware? Definition and Examples]]></title>
        <id>6223b106c4d0d306772f4b41</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-firmware/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T18:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that firmware is literally everywhere? It might be strange to think about – but it's just as common as hardware and software. In fact, it is thanks to firmware that:  * Printers work  * Defibrillators work  * Car radios works  * and more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove a Property from a JavaScript Object]]></title>
        <id>6260bd7bac55f60686c39b14</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-a-property-from-a-javascript-object/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T17:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two ways to remove a property from a JavaScript object. There's the mutable way of doing it using the delete operator, and the immutable way of doing it using object restructuring.  Let's go through each of these methods in this tutorial. Remove a Property from a JS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saransh Kataria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Better Navigation With Navigation Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/designing-better-navigation-ux-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/designing-better-navigation-ux-queries/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In UX, we can use navigation queries, evaluation journeys, A-Z index and tap-ahead autocomplete to help users get where they want to be, faster. Let’s find out how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your Own Blog with Next.js and MDX]]></title>
        <id>625b6643ac55f60686c36806</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-your-own-blog-with-next-js-and-mdx/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T02:28:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I decided to build my blog, I found many tools out there that were readily available. I looked at Gastby [https://www.gatsbyjs.com/] along with content management systems like Ghost [https://ghost.org/], Contentful [https://www.contentful.com/], Sanity dot io [https://www.sanity.io/], and HUGO [https://gohugo.io/].  But I needed something that I could have total control]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caleb Olojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is FTP? File Transfer Protocol and FTP Server Meaning]]></title>
        <id>625eae40ac55f60686c381d2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-ftp-file-transfer-protocol-and-ftp-server-meaning/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T01:01:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTP stands for File Transfer Protocol. This is a network/communication protocol for transferring files between computers over a TCP/IP (Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol) network.  Examples of TCP/IP networks are:  * HTTP (Hypertext Transfer Protocol).  * HTTPS (Hypertext Transfer Protocol Secure).  * FTP (File Transfer Protocol). How]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Flush DNS on Mac – MacOS Clear DNS Cache]]></title>
        <id>624beda6ac55f60686c2e0f7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-flush-dns-on-mac-macos-clear-dns-cache/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T00:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn why flushing your DNS cache is important, and how you can clear the cache on your local system. Here is what we'll discuss in this guide:  1. What is DNS cache? 1. Why flushing DNS cache is important]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extern – C and C++ Extern Keyword Function Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>625d0d69ac55f60686c37241</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/extern-keyword-function-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T00:08:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The extern keyword in C and C++ extends the visibility of variables and functions across multiple source files.  In the case of functions, the extern keyword is used implicitly. But with variables, you have to use the keyword explicitly. I believe a simple code example can explain things better]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farhan Hasin Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How WebAuthn Authenticates Users Without a Password]]></title>
        <id>6255cce5ac55f60686c330c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/intro-to-webauthn/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T23:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of us are used to logging into different accounts using a password. For years this has been the norm, but passwords also face security issues:  * They are extremely annoying when we don’t remember them and even harder to    reset  * They can be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohit Jacob Mathew</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dns_probe_finished_nxdomain Error [Solved]]]></title>
        <id>625fe437ac55f60686c38f04</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dns_probe_finished_nxdomain-error-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T15:39:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a regular Google Chrome user, then you might have encountered the error “dns_probe_finished_nxdomain” before. It is usually accompanied by “This site can’t be reached”. This error is associated with the Domain Name System (DNS) server and can occur due to misconfiguration in the DNS server, an unresponsive]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Tailwind CSS to New and Existing WordPress Themes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364880</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/adding-tailwind-css-to-wordpress-themes/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T15:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the 15 or so years since I started making WordPress websites, nothing has had more of an impact on my productivity — and my ability to enjoy front-end development — than adding Tailwind CSS to my workflow (and it …
Adding Tailwind CSS to New and Existing WordPress Themes originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greg Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Redux Toolkit – The Recommended Way to Use Redux]]></title>
        <id>626007e4ac55f60686c3924f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-redux-toolkit-the-recommended-way-to-use-redux/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T13:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redux Toolkit is an opinionated toolset for efficient Redux development created by the Redux team. It is the the standard and recommended way to write Redux logic and manage state in your JavaScript applications. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Productivity Tips And Tools For A More Efficient Workflow]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/productivity-tips-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/productivity-tips-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who doesn’t love a good timesaver? In this post, we compiled useful productivity tips and tools that help you speed up routine tasks, enhance your development workflow, and stay organized.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Permissions – How to Find Permissions of a File]]></title>
        <id>625c8890ac55f60686c37088</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linux-permissions-how-to-find-permissions-of-a-file/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T21:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux is a multi-user Operating System which means it supports multiple users on a single system.  Each user has its own rights which might be limited as well to increase security. For example, users have a particular set of permissions to access a file – some users might be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Bypass ES Modules Errors in Next.js with Dynamic Imports]]></title>
        <id>6252e40fac55f60686c3142d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-bypass-es-modules-error-in-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T19:58:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you are building an application that can be accessed on the web, there are a lot of dependencies or packages that you will need for your application to function well. You'll need most of these packages when you're building JAMStack applications with frameworks or libraries like React, Vuejs, Next.js,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caleb Olojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Docker? Learn How to Use Containers – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>625d1728ac55f60686c3725e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-docker-learn-how-to-use-containers-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T19:50:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers are an essential tool for software development today. Running applications in any environment becomes easy when you leverage containers.  The most popular technology for running containers is Docker [https://www.docker.com/], which runs on any operating system. In this blog post, you will learn to use Docker for the top]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sigl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rubber Duck Debugging]]></title>
        <id>625e7b77ac55f60686c37edc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rubber-duck-debugging/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T17:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a software developer, you’ve probably been in a situation where your code is not working as expected. This could happen because you made a typo, you weren't paying enough attention, or you weren't sure how something worked. When your code doesn't work, it's frustrating – but the only thing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React + WebSockets Project – Build a Real-Time Order Book Application]]></title>
        <id>61372766d6679a07b7d43ded</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-websockets-project-build-real-time-order-book-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T17:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we will see how to build an Order Book web application, that we'll use to display real-time cryptocurrency info. We will use React with Typescript [https://create-react-app.dev/docs/adding-typescript/] for creating the UI,  Redux [https://redux.js.org/] for managing the application state, and  styled-components [https://styled-components.com/] for applying the styling. And]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mihail Gaberov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Host an Angular Application on GitHub Pages with Travis CI]]></title>
        <id>6259eec8ac55f60686c35fe1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/host-an-angular-application-on-github-pages-with-travis-ci/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll create an application using the latest version of Angular. Then we'll host it on the GitHub Pages static website service using the continuous integration tool Travis CI to deploy the application. Prerequisites Before you start, you need to install and configure the tools below to create]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rodrigo Kamada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jamstack Rendering Patterns: The Evolution]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/jamstack-rendering-patterns-evolution/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/jamstack-rendering-patterns-evolution/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ekene Eze shares his thoughts about the direction of the web in 2022, and what solutions we can expect to see come up in the ecosystem to significantly improve the Jamstack experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ekene Eze)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[strftime – Python DateTime Timestamp String]]></title>
        <id>62584ad7ac55f60686c34bd0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/strftime-python-datetime-timestamp-string/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T01:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The datetime object lets us work with dates and times in Python. But the value returned when we use this object is of the datatime data type rather than a  string. Here is an example that prints the current year, month, day and time to the console: from datetime]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS radial-gradient by Building Background Patterns]]></title>
        <id>625bf31cac55f60686c36991</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-radial-gradient/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T01:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are new to CSS gradients, you may have heard about something called  radial-gradient(). If you have never used it before, you are in the right place to learn about it. In this tutorial, I will focus on some real and practical examples to explain the secrets behind]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Network Security – How to Use Suricata, RaspberryPI4, and Python to Make Your Network Safe]]></title>
        <id>625c80fcac55f60686c37035</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/home-network-security-with-suricata-raspberrypi4-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T00:23:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous article [/news/wireless-security-using-raspberry-pi-4-kismet-and-python/], I showed you how to secure your wireless home network using Kismet [https://www.kismetwireless.net/]. Kismet is perfect for detecting anomalies and certain types of attack – but what if I want to analyze the traffic and look for abnormal patterns or patterns that could indicate an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Object-Oriented Programming in Java – A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>601e56cc0a2838549dcbf3d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-oriented-programming-concepts-java/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T22:03:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, folks! Today we are going to talk about object-oriented programming in Java. This article will help give you a thorough understanding of the underlying principles of object-oriented programming and its concepts.  Once you understand these concepts, you should have the confidence and ability to develop basic problem-solving applications]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Cyubahiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Object Oriented Programming with Python – Code a Minesweeper Game]]></title>
        <id>625dbd15ac55f60686c37860</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-oriented-programming-with-python-code-a-minesweeper-game/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T19:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improve your Python programming skills by coding everyone's favorite Windows 3.1 game: Minesweeper. We just published a Python course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to code Minesweeper using the tkinter library. Jim from JimShapedCoding developed this course. He has published many popular programming courses both]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Relational VS Nonrelational Databases – the Difference Between a SQL DB and a NoSQL DB]]></title>
        <id>624bed78ac55f60686c2e0eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/relational-vs-nonrelational-databases-difference-between-sql-db-and-nosql-db/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T17:56:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is an overview of relational and non-relational databases. Besides learning the fundamental differences between the two types of databases, you will also learn how to decide which one to use for your next project by going over their strengths and weaknesses. Here is what we'll cover:  1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js Image Tutorial – How to Upload, Crop, and Resize Images in the Browser in Next]]></title>
        <id>625aba3aac55f60686c36423</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-upload-crop-resize-images-in-the-browser-in-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T17:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two of the most fundamental image editing functions are resizing and cropping. But you should do these carefully because they have the potential to degrade image quality. Cropping always includes removing a portion of the original image, resulting in the loss of some pixels. This post will teach you how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Idris Olubisi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Mermaid Diagrams in Markdown]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364908</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/making-mermaid-diagrams-in-markdown/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T16:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mermaid diagrams and flowcharts have been gaining traction, especially with GitHub’s announcement that they are natively supported in Markdown. Let’s take a look at what they are, how to use them, and just as importantly: why.
Just like you …
Making Mermaid Diagrams in Markdown originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Esch-Laurent</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Systems Engineering? A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>622394b8c4d0d306772f4a08</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-systems-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T15:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was recently reading J. Martin's book Systems Engineering Guidebook – A Process for Developing Systems and Products. From it, I learned that systems engineering reduces manufacturing costs by 40% – did you know that? Neither did I. Even after taking a class where one of the topics was systems]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ultimate Guide To Push Notifications For Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/guide-push-notifications-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/guide-push-notifications-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are the benefits of using push notifications and what can you use them for? In this article, Lee Munroe explains how to implement them and which practices are best to follow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lee Munroe)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix the "Item Not Found" Windows Error When Deleting a File or Folder]]></title>
        <id>62585158ac55f60686c34d0a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-solve-item-not-found-windows-error-deleting-file-folder/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T18:32:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you use a Windows operating system, then you might have gotten this error before when trying to delete a file or folder.  It happens when, even though the file or folder is there, Windows says that it is failing to delete it because it can't find that file/folder]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use Storytelling In UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/use-storytelling-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/use-storytelling-ux/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Storytelling is a powerful tool for any UX designer. It helps create a product and understand the people who use it. In this article, Marli Mesibov takes a real-life example of an app she helped to build in 2017 and explains five steps you can use to help you build a story into your user experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marli Mesibov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy a Kotlin Microservice to AWS with App Runner]]></title>
        <id>624e81ffac55f60686c2f0bd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kotlin-aws-app-runner/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T06:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, everyone. In this step-by-step tutorial, I would like to show you how to deploy a Kotlin Microservice using Docker and AWS App Runner.  Together, we will learn:  * what exactly is AWS App Runner?   * how to configure AWS Command Line Interface on your local]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Wolak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Inspect an Element – Chrome Shortcut]]></title>
        <id>625807d4ac55f60686c348c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-inspect-an-element-chrome-shortcut/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T01:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Inspect Element feature of the Google Chrome browser is a powerful yet easy-to-use tool. It’s an important part of Chrome Developer Tools that you can use to check the source code of any website. But it doesn’t end there. You can take things further by changing the elements and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infinite Pagination in Flutter with Firebase, Riverpod, and Freeze]]></title>
        <id>6208aaaf56125b0677c64aaa</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/infinite-pagination-in-flutter-with-riverpod/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T23:46:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're developing an app, you'll have to decide how you want to load data. And this will typically bring up the issue of infinite pagination.  You likely won't be showing all of the available items in your DB to your users. You may fetch the first 10-20 items]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rutvik Tak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Azure Static Web Apps to Deploy an Angular App]]></title>
        <id>62549e60ac55f60686c32496</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-azure-static-web-apps-to-deploy-angular-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T23:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CI/CD has changed the way IT teams release new software versions.  In this tutorial I'll share my experience with Azure Static Web Apps – Azure's PaaS solution. I'll show you how you can take advantage of its flexibility to deploy an Angular App just by pushing your code to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Venturi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python List .append() – How to Add an Item to a List in Python]]></title>
        <id>6257f4fcac55f60686c34755</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-append-how-to-add-an-item-to-a-list-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T20:03:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lists are one of the most useful and versatile data types available in Python. Lists are a collection of arbitrary objects, just like arrays in other programming languages. In this tutorial you will learn:  * An overview of lists and how they are defined.  * Methods to insert]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write a Script to Change Your Zoom Background Every Day]]></title>
        <id>62563320ac55f60686c3361f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-a-script-to-change-zoom-background/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T18:05:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past few months, I've found a new use for the pictures that I've taken while hiking. I started using them as Zoom virtual backgrounds.  If you are anything like me and take a lot of pictures, it can be hard to decide which one looks good. And]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saransh Kataria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Docs Strikethrough – How to Cross Out Text in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>6256dd0eac55f60686c33b09</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-docs-strikethrough-how-to-cross-out-text-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T17:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're writing, sometimes you might want to strike through certain text. This means adding a horizontal line that runs through a piece of text.  Here is what it looks like: you are an awesome person.  These are various use cases for strikethroughs:  * To indicate that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Ready for a Job in Tech – Tips for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>62496868ac55f60686c2ccbc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-ready-for-a-job-in-tech/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T17:05:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few months back, I was invited to talk to a group of engineering students of a renowned college in India. I was supposed to interact with them, motivate them, and finally tell them, "What does the industry (the "job" world) look like?", "How can you get ready for it?"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When And How To Use Freelancers In Your Organization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/upwork-freelancers-organization/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/upwork-freelancers-organization/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you work in-house or run a digital agency, there are occasions when you will consider hiring freelancers to supplement your team. Today, we’ll take a look into a platform known as [Upwork](https://upwork.pxf.io/c/1221738/1245573/13634) and the best ways in finding the the right freelancers as well as integrating them into your team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modules in JavaScript – CommonJS and ESmodules Explained]]></title>
        <id>62560533ac55f60686c33336</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/modules-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T01:17:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we're going to take a look at modules in JavaScript. Modules are a technique heavily used in today's software design/architecture. First we're going to learn what they are and the different types of modules that exist. Then we're going to discuss why modules are useful.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Low-Code for Freelance Developers & Startups]]></title>
        <id>62577335ac55f60686c342d8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/low-code-for-freelance-developers-startups/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T01:17:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Low-code is a software development approach that requires little coding in order to build applications. It is made possible through a low-code platform. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use the Appsmith Low-Code platform.  Ania Kubów created this course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dot Symbol – Bullet Point in HTML Unicode]]></title>
        <id>6256c1d7ac55f60686c33a90</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dot-symbol-bullet-point-in-html-unicode/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T00:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In your HTML documents, you'll often need to make a list of items. And you can use bullet points for this purpose. You can show bullet points with the Unicode character (or entity) for bullet points. In this article, I will show you the Unicode and HTML entities for showing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React 18 New Features – Concurrent Rendering, Automatic Batching, and More]]></title>
        <id>6257472dac55f60686c341a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-18-new-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T21:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React 18 was released in March 2022. This release focuses on performance improvements and updating the rendering engine.  React 18 sets the foundation for concurrent rendering APIs that future React features will be built on top of.  In this tutorial, I will give a quick guide of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shruti Kapoor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with PysonDB]]></title>
        <id>62552369ac55f60686c329f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-started-with-pysondb/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T19:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often need to store some data while working on our personal projects. We can use a SQL or NoSQL database with a server, but that would require us to do a bit of setup.  In one of my previous articles, we saw a solution to this problem with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the slice() and splice() JavaScript Array Methods]]></title>
        <id>625664b6ac55f60686c33732</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-slice-and-splice-how-to-use-the-slice-and-splice-js-array-methods/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T19:17:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you are first learning JavaScript, it might be difficult to know the difference between the slice() and splice() array methods.  In this article, I will walk you through how to use the slice() and splice()  array methods using code examples.  How to use the slice() JavaScript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Closure in JavaScript – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>62527fd2ac55f60686c30fd4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-closures-explained-with-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T18:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we are going to talk about closures in JavaScript. I'll walk you through the definition of a closure, a simple day-to-day fetch utility closure example, and some of the advantages and disadvantages of using closures.  Table of Contents  * Prerequisites   * What are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keyur Paralkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python .zip() – Zip Function in Python]]></title>
        <id>624f2d28ac55f60686c2f644</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-zip-zip-function-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T18:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you use the zip() function in Python, it takes two or more data sets and "zips" them together. This returns an object containing pairs of items derived from the data sets. It groups these items in the order of their indexes.  Let me break it down a bit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CRUD Operations in JavaScript by Building TODO APP]]></title>
        <id>62508fa3ac55f60686c2feff</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-crud-operations-in-javascript-by-building-todo-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T17:57:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we're gonna learn how to do CRUD Operations in JavaScript by making a Todo App. Let's get started 🔥 This is the app we're making today:  * Live preview [https://crud-application-al9am9v2v-joyshaheb.vercel.app/]  * GitHub Repository [https://github.com/JoyShaheb/CRUD-Application] You can watch this tutorial on YouTube as well if you like 🎥]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joy Shaheb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>