<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-04-21T01:02:06.797Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use APIs in Your Projects to Practice Your Coding Skills]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-apis-to-practice-coding-skills/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-apis-to-practice-coding-skills/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T22:28:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As web developers, we all know that practice makes perfect. But when it comes to practice, it's easy to get stuck in a programming rut. But how do you come up with new ideas to build? Sooner or later, you will find yourself running out of features to add or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Handle File Uploads on the Back End in Node.js and Nuxt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/handle-file-uploads-on-the-backend-in-node-js-nuxt/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/handle-file-uploads-on-the-backend-in-node-js-nuxt/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T22:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In some previous tutorials, I covered how to upload files using HTML [https://austingil.com/uploading-files-with-html/] and JavaScript [https://austingil.com/upload-files-with-javascript/]. It requires sending HTTP requests with the Content-Type [https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/HTTP/Headers/Content-Type] header set to multipart/form-data. Today, we are going to the back end to receive those multipart/form-data  requests and access the binary data from those]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Austin Gil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Communicate with ChatGPT – A Guide to Prompt Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-communicate-with-ai-tools-prompt-engineering/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-communicate-with-ai-tools-prompt-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T20:54:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI has become an integral part of our lives and businesses. Over the past few years, we’ve seen the rapid rise of AI tools, and their impact on our day-to-day activities can't be ignored. From virtual assistants to chatbots, AI just keeps getting smarter with more functionalities than before. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hillary Nyakundi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prepare for Your JavaScript Interview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-for-your-javascript-interview/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-for-your-javascript-interview/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T17:04:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you preparing for a JavaScript interview and want to ensure that you have a deep understanding of closures, functions, and currying? Then Roadside Coder's video course is just what you need. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help prepare you for a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does the Caret Mean in RegEx? Caret Metacharacter in Regular Expressions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-the-caret-mean-in-regex-how-to-match-the-start-of-a-line-in-regular-expressions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-the-caret-mean-in-regex-how-to-match-the-start-of-a-line-in-regular-expressions/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T16:47:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A caret (^) is one of the many symbols for creating patterns in regular expressions. A caret matches the start of a line or a particular string. But that’s not all there is to the caret (^) symbol. The caret symbol (^) is often referred to as an "anchor" because]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Copy File – Copying Files to Another Directory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-copy-file-copying-files-to-another-directory/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-copy-file-copying-files-to-another-directory/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T14:16:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with Python, there may be times when you need to copy a file. Copying files comes in handy when you need to create a backup. In this article, you will learn how to copy a file in Python using the shutil  module and its different methods. The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building And Dockerizing A Node.js App With Stateless Architecture With Help From Kinsta]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/building-dockerizing-nodejs-app-stateless-architecture-kinsta/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/building-dockerizing-nodejs-app-stateless-architecture-kinsta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dockerizing your Node.js apps can lead to smashing success—offering consistency, easy debugging, and hassle-free dependency management. When you host this container on Kinsta, you also benefit from high-speed performance, robust security, and top-notch scalability. By combining these two, you'll surely have a whale of a time as you sail smoothly through the development seas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tejas Kumar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Concepts to Know Before Learning React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-concepts-to-know-before-learning-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-concepts-to-know-before-learning-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of web developers use React as their go-to library for building UI components for their websites. React is one of the most popular frameworks for web development and it is written entirely in JavaScript. Since React was written in JavaScript, it uses a lot of the JavaScript concepts]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Musab Habeeb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Network Traffic is Routed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-network-traffic-is-routed/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-network-traffic-is-routed/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T22:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moving around the internet – or even over a private local network – requires all kinds of magic wand waving and sorcery.  Or, in sightly more accurate terms, it requires the combination of sophisticated engineering and the existence of key standards, including network ports, the domain Name System (DNS)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Interview Prep – How to Use a Collaborative Approach to Problem-Solving]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/collaborative-problem-solving-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/collaborative-problem-solving-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T21:14:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how experienced of a developer you are, being interviewed for a new job is always stressful. This is certainly true from my own experience.  In my case, I have been working professionally as a Software Developer for two and a half years, and I've had to face]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alberto Gonzalez Rosales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Box Shadow Generator With React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-box-shadow-generator-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-box-shadow-generator-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T20:21:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS is a powerful language for styling web pages. But when you're designing a website, things like box shadows can be particularly difficult to get right.  In this guide, you will learn how to create your own box shadow generator with React and Vite. Here is a preview [https://shadowgen.vercel.app/]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Uzondu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Mechanics In UI Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/color-mechanics-ui-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/color-mechanics-ui-kits/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adel Khamatov shares a model of color mechanics that he came up with during research on developing UI kits and illustrates an approach to solving related problems with best practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adel Khamatov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript in React – How to Manage State with Firebase Cloud Firestore]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manage-state-in-react-apps-with-firebase-cloud-firestore/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manage-state-in-react-apps-with-firebase-cloud-firestore/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T17:04:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State management is essential in today's world of web development. If you do it well, it helps you create apps that are reliable and effective. Firebase [https://firebase.google.com/] is a Backend-as-a-Service platform that has gained popularity along with the emergence of serverless architecture and cloud technologies. And Cloud Firestore [https://firebase.google.com/docs/firestore] is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olasunkanmi Balogun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT Course – Use the OpenAI API to Create Five Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chatgpt-course-use-the-openai-api-to-create-five-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chatgpt-course-use-the-openai-api-to-create-five-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T15:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of artificial intelligence is ever-evolving, and the OpenAI API is at the forefront of it. As the technology becomes more sophisticated, it's imperative for developers and enthusiasts to understand and utilize its potential in various applications. We just published an OpenAI API course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Godot for Game Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-godot-for-game-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-godot-for-game-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T15:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you interested in game development but don't know where to start? The Godot game engine is a popular open-source platform for game development, and our new video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel will teach you everything you need to know to create your own platformer game. The course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Print Methods in Java – How to Print to the Terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/print-methods-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/print-methods-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T14:28:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're learning Java, you probably started your coding journey by printing the "Hello World" program in the console. And that's a great way to begin – but after that, you need to learn how print methods and functions actually work. Well, this article will show you how those print]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does '$' Mean in RegEx?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-mean-in-regex/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-mean-in-regex/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T11:20:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The $ symbol is one of the most commonly used symbols in RegEx. It is used to match the end of a string. In this article, I’ll show you exactly what the dollar sign ($) does in RegEx and how to use it. What We'll Cover  * What is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python isEmpty() equivalent – How to Check if a List is Empty in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-check-if-a-list-is-empty-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-check-if-a-list-is-empty-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T04:52:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A list [/news/how-to-make-a-list-in-python-declare-lists-in-python-example/] is one of the data structures in Python that you can use to store a collection of variables.  In some cases, you have to iterate through and perform an operation on the elements of a list. But you can't loop/iterate through a list if it has]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy a NodeJS App with AWS CloudFormation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-nodejs-app-with-cloudformation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-nodejs-app-with-cloudformation/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T18:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you have built a great product and its user base is growing rapidly. You want to scale your product to be available to people around the world. To do this, you'll need good cloud infrastructure. But managing your cloud infrastructure manually can be exhausting. You might start wondering, "how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Common Causes of Invalid HTML Syntax – and How to Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/invalid-html-syntax-examples-and-fixes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/invalid-html-syntax-examples-and-fixes/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T16:51:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember those treehouses that we had as children and how the wood would wear, tear, and eventually collapse because we just would not stop jumping around inside it? Well that's kind of like HTML. This markup language is like the wood to your coding project. If it’s invalid, your solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CHRISTINE T. BELZIE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does $ Mean in Python? Operator Meaning + String Formatting Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-the-dollar-sign-mean-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-the-dollar-sign-mean-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T16:39:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Operators are special symbols you can use to perform different operations on variables (operands) in programming.  Python has different operators like arithmetic operators, assignment operators, logical operators, boolean operators, comparison operators, bitwise operators, and so on.  Although you'll not come across the dollar sign ($) operator when learning]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Primitive Values vs Reference Values – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-assigning-values-vs-assigning-references/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-assigning-values-vs-assigning-references/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T16:31:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In JavaScript, variables can hold two types of data: primitive values and reference values. Understanding the difference between these two types of data is crucial for writing efficient and bug-free code.  In this short article, we will explore the difference between values and references in JavaScript. Table]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 59 With Chiara Aliotta: What Is Design Storytelling?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/smashing-podcast-episode-59/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/smashing-podcast-episode-59/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of The Smashing Podcast, we take a look at design storytelling. What is it, and how can it help us shape digital experiences? Vitaly talks to Chiara Aliotta to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ModuleNotFoundError: no module named 'requests' [Solved in Python Django]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-module-not-found-error-solved/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-module-not-found-error-solved/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T23:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Errors are an inevitable part of programming, and every programmer will encounter them at some point in their career.  Errors in programming can take various forms, including syntax errors, logic errors, and runtime errors, and they can have a significant impact on the functioning of a program. Understanding the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is DevOps? How Development + Operations Helps Teams Work More Efficiently]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-devops-works/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-devops-works/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T23:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developers and operations teams work together, they can identify and solve problems more quickly. This helps them deliver software to users faster and with fewer errors.  This general practice is called DevOps. It involves using tools and techniques to automate tasks and make software development and deployment more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Satyam Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Git Rebase – Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-git-rebase/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-git-rebase/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T22:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The software engineering landscape is constantly changing. Staying up to date on new technologies is absolutely critical. But as developers, sometimes we forget how important it is to dig a bit deeper into the tried and true technologies that are the backbone of software development – such as version control]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Abbene</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Your PWA – Web App Security Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-protect-your-pwa/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-protect-your-pwa/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T21:28:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, everybody! I'm Rahul [https://fueler.io/rahoool]. In today's world, web apps have become more prevalent because they work seamlessly on multiple devices. But as with any application, PWAs can be vulnerable to security threats, which can compromise user data and damage the reputation. It's natural to get excited about launching something]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Machine Leaning without Libraries or Frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-machine-leaning-without-libraries-or-frameworks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-machine-leaning-without-libraries-or-frameworks/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T16:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to unravel the mysteries of machine learning algorithms and elevate your software development skills? Look no further!  We just published a machine learning course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This "No Black Box" Machine Learning Course in JavaScript offers a unique, hands-on approach to understanding machine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Design Thinking?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/what-is-design-thinking/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/what-is-design-thinking/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered if things could have been done differently? But not sure how? Well, then, do not fall in love with the solution, but fall in love with the problem! Here’s an article to dive deep into how design thinking could do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Krithika Subramanian)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conda Channel - What Is a Channel in Conda?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-channel-in-conda/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-channel-in-conda/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T16:36:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you install a package in Conda, it is downloaded and extracted from a remote directory using the directory's URL. The directory where these packages are stored is known as a channel. In this article, you'll learn what a channel is, how to use default channels, and how add new]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Pretty Print JSON in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-pretty-print-json-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-pretty-print-json-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JSON (JavaScript Object Notation) is a popular data interchange format that is widely used in web applications, APIs, and databases. It is a lightweight and human-readable format that is easy to parse and generate.  But when dealing with large and complex JSON data, it can be difficult to read]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does $ Mean in JavaScript? Dollar Sign Operator in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-the-dollar-sign-mean-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-the-dollar-sign-mean-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you dive into JavaScript code, you may come across the use of a dollar sign ($) in various contexts. In this article, we will explore what the dollar sign means in JavaScript, commonly known as the "dollar sign operator," and how it is used in JavaScript programming. Understanding the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JSONObject.toString() – How to Convert JSON to a String in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/jsonobject-tostring-how-to-convert-json-to-a-string-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/jsonobject-tostring-how-to-convert-json-to-a-string-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of web applications and services, JSON (JavaScript Object Notation) has become a widely used data format for data exchange between different systems.  In Java, it's common to work with JSON data, and an operation you'll frequently perform is converting a JSON object to a string representation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Refresh Page – How to Reload a Page in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-refresh-page-how-to-reload-a-page-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-refresh-page-how-to-reload-a-page-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a versatile programming language that allows developers to create dynamic and interactive web applications. One common task in web development is to refresh or reload a web page, either to update its content or to trigger certain actions. In this article, we will explore different ways to refresh]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is An ACL? Access Control Lists Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-deep-dive-into-access-control-lists/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-deep-dive-into-access-control-lists/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:43:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In computing, access control is the concept of limiting or regulating a person or machine's access to certain information or resources.  One of the major mechanisms you use to do that is an access control list (ACL). An ACL is a set of rules for allowing or denying access]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidiadi Anyanwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Initialize a Java List – List of String Initialization in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-initialize-a-java-list/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-initialize-a-java-list/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Java is a popular programming language widely used for developing robust and scalable applications. One of the essential data structures in Java is a list, which allows developers to store and manipulate a collection of elements. Initializing a list in Java is a crucial step in the development process as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Blog with the Ghost API and Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-blog-website-with-ghost-api-and-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-blog-website-with-ghost-api-and-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T21:14:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ghost CMS is a popular content management system that many devs and companies use to host their blogs.  It has many features and an editor that's highly optimized for writing. You can even build different themes using handlebars.js [https://handlebarsjs.com/]. But if you don't know Handlebars, learning it can be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The difference between Arrow functions and Normal functions in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-difference-between-arrow-functions-and-normal-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-difference-between-arrow-functions-and-normal-functions/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T21:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, there are two types of functions. You have normal functions and arrow functions. Let's explore the difference between them in this article. Arrow functions was introduced in ES6. And it introduced a simple and shorter way to create functions. Here's how to create a normal function, with arguments,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Live Football Scoreboard in React with Vite and Vitest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-project-with-vite-and-vitest/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-project-with-vite-and-vitest/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T20:41:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to yet another tutorial [https://www.mihailgaberov.com/] where you will learn how to build a ⚽ scoreboard app in React. This time we will use Vite as our next generation frontend tooling [https://vitejs.dev/] and Vitest [https://vitest.dev/] as a Vite-native unit testing framework.  You will also learn how to leverage React]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mihail Gaberov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Sheets – Learn Advanced Functions by Building a Zelda Dashboard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-sheets-advanced-functions-by-building-a-zelda-dashboard/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-sheets-advanced-functions-by-building-a-zelda-dashboard/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T17:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article we'll build a dashboard inspired by the recipes in Zelda: Breath of the Wild.  Our dashboard will have multiple data validation dropdown selections for us to choose ingredients. By using a =Query() function, we'll then display the recipes that contain any combination of the selected ingredients.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a LinkedIn Clone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-linkedin-clone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-linkedin-clone/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T17:24:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you interested in learning how to create a social networking site like LinkedIn using React and Firebase? We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you learn how to build a LinkedIn clone from start to finish, using the popular front-end library React and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Software Engineer – 2023 Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-software-engineer-2023-roadmap/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-software-engineer-2023-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T16:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software engineers are in high demand these days. They generally command comfortable salaries, and can have a good work-life balance. But what do software engineers do? And how can you become one yourself? In this article, I will explain the tasks and responsibilities of software engineers, and I will go]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Call vs Put vs Post – HTTP Request Methods Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/call-vs-put-vs-post-http-request-methods-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/call-vs-put-vs-post-http-request-methods-explained/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T14:59:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HTTP (Hypertext Transfer Protocol) is the foundation of communication between clients (such as web browsers) and servers (such as web servers) on the World Wide Web. One crucial aspect of HTTP is the request method, which indicates the type of operation the client wants to perform on a resource.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Delete File – How to Remove Files and Folders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-delete-file-how-to-remove-files-and-folders/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-delete-file-how-to-remove-files-and-folders/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T12:24:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many programming languages have built-in functionalities for working with files and folders. As a rich programming language with many exciting functionalities built into it, Python is not an exception to that. Python has the OS and Pathlib modules with which you can create files and folders, edit files and folders,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Bash Scripting to Enhance Your Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-bash-scripting-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-bash-scripting-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T20:52:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bash scripting is an essential skill for any developer, system administrator, or power user who wants to automate repetitive tasks and make their workflow more efficient. We just published a bash scripting for beginners course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Herbert from Herbertech created this course. In this course, you'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Mobile Apps with Firebase]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/firebase-course-html-css-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/firebase-course-html-css-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T20:46:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firebase is an app development platform from Google that offers tools and services for building and scaling applications. It includes real-time databases, authentication, analytics, and hosting features. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build a mobile app with HTML, CSS,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Apply Borders to Clip Paths with CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/apply-borders-to-clip-paths-with-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/apply-borders-to-clip-paths-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T17:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Applying borders to non-rectangular shapes in CSS can be challenging. In this article, we will explore ways to apply different border types to trapezoidal shapes in CSS.  The final shape we aim to achieve is a golden dashed parallelogram border, as you can see in the screenshot below: Parallelogram]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Frederick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys: What the Heck and Why?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377305</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/passkeys-what-the-heck-and-why/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T17:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These things called passkeys sure are making the rounds these days. They were a main attraction at W3C TPAC 2022, gained support in Safari 16, are finding their way into macOS and iOS, and are slated to …
Passkeys: What the Heck and Why? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neal Fennimore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conda Remove Package - How To Remove Matplotlib in Anaconda]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-a-package-in-anaconda/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-a-package-in-anaconda/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T12:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use Conda to create and manage different environments and their packages. It is mostly used for data science and machine learning projects.  In this article, you'll learn how to remove an environment's package using in built Conda commands.  You'll learn the following:   * How]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Convert a List to an Array and Back in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/convert-lists-to-arrays-and-back-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/convert-lists-to-arrays-and-back-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T00:04:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arrays and lists are two of the most commonly used data structures in Python.  You can use both arrays and lists to store collections of values, but they have some key differences.  For example, arrays are more efficient than lists for certain operations, such as mathematical operations on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Validate Forms in React – A Step-By-Step Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-validate-forms-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-validate-forms-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever worked with form validation in React, you know that it can quickly become messy and overwhelming. This is especially the case if you're just starting out with React.  In this tutorial, I will show you how to create reusable React components that allow you to build]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yazdun Fadali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network Architecture Basics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/network-architecture-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/network-architecture-basics/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T19:05:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Networking is engineering, magic, and skilled trade all rolled into one. Getting all the countless pieces to talk nicely – and reliably – to each other is complicated. Troubleshooting unexpected outages is worse.  But, once you've got it all running nicely, well that's when you should really be worried:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Design An Effective User Onboarding Flow]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/design-effective-user-onboarding-flow/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/design-effective-user-onboarding-flow/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to maximize conversions or collect necessary user information for other purposes, a user onboarding flow is necessary. In this article, you will learn how, with the help of Feathery, to design an effective user onboarding flow for your app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Suzanne Scacca)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn JavaScript Object-Oriented Programming by Building a Timer Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-object-oriented-programming/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-object-oriented-programming/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T17:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn JavaScript object-oriented programming by creating a simple timer application. Object-oriented programming is an important programming paradigm. It organizes code into objects which makes it easier to manage and maintain your applications. Many articles explain in detail the benefits of object-oriented programming and how you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miya Liu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Bytes to String – How to Convert a Bytestring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-bytes-to-string-how-to-convert-a-bytestring/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-bytes-to-string-how-to-convert-a-bytestring/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T22:52:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to convert a bytestring. I know the word bytestring might sound technical and difficult to understand. But trust me – we will break the process down and understand everything about bytestrings before writing the Python code that converts bytes to a string. So]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Linters and Code Formatters in Your Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/using-prettier-and-jslint/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/using-prettier-and-jslint/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T22:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we're going to take a look at two very useful tools we can use to make our lives easier when writing code: linting tools and code formatters. We're going to talk about what these tools are, how they work, why are they useful, and finally]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Render Lists in React using array.map()]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-render-lists-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-render-lists-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T21:39:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with React, you will often times need to render lists of items. With the map() method, you can create new results from your current lists or even showcase all the items in your lists. In this tutorial, you will learn how to use this method to access]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mwendwa Bundi Emma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The History of Artificial Intelligence from the 1950s to Today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-history-of-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-history-of-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T21:35:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humans have always been interested in making machines that display intelligence.  The Ancient Egyptians and Romans were awe-struck by religious statues that were manipulated by priests behind the scenes. Medieval lore is packed with tales of items which could move and talk like their human masters. And there have]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Gold</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Currency Converter GUI with Tkinter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-currency-converter-gui-with-tkinter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-currency-converter-gui-with-tkinter/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T16:44:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tkinter is a built-in Python library for creating graphical user interfaces (GUIs). It provides a set of tools for building windows, frames, buttons, textboxes, and other GUI elements.  It is easy to use and widely available, making it a popular choice for building GUI applications in Python. It is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unleash the Power of React Native to Build Mobile Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-native-full-course-android-ios-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-native-full-course-android-ios-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T15:37:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to dive into the world of React Native and create stunning mobile applications that work seamlessly on both Android and iOS platforms? We've got you covered! We just published a full React Native course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel.  Emma Williams created this course. She is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Reset Hard – How to Reset to Head in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-reset-hard-how-to-reset-to-head-in-git/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-reset-hard-how-to-reset-to-head-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T12:09:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a powerful version control system for tracking and managing changes and files in your source codes and other digital assets. One of the core functionalities of Git is "commits". Commits let you create a snapshot of your code. In other words, it’s like saving your work, but with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Data Analytics with New Advanced Certifications from Google]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/starting-and-excelling-in-data-analytics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/starting-and-excelling-in-data-analytics/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T20:47:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has been growing a list of certifications for the past few years. And they've just added some advanced coursework to the repertoire.  In this article, I'll introduce you to the Google Certifications and detail what's new. I'll focus on the Data Analytics pathway, but will include resources to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is CI/CD? Learn Continuous Integration/Continuous Deployment by Building a Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-ci-cd/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-ci-cd/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T19:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article you're going to learn about CI/CD (continuous integration and continuous deployment).  We're going to review what this practice is about, how it compares to the previous approach in the software development industry, and finally see a practical example of how we can implement it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Docker Compose? How to Use it with an Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-docker-compose-how-to-use-it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-docker-compose-how-to-use-it/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T19:29:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker helps you setup a development environment on your machine quickly. It only takes a couple of minutes to go through the entire process.  But let's assume you were assigned on a project which requires at least 10 different services in a running state to run your project. For]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conda Remove Environment – How to Delete an Env]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-delete-an-environment-in-conda/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-delete-an-environment-in-conda/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T05:11:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conda is an open-source package management and environment management system that can be used to create different, isolated coding environments.  With Conda, you can create separate environments for specific projects. You can have one environment for machine learning and another environment for data analytics. Each environment can have its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Upload Files with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/upload-files-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/upload-files-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T20:27:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently published a tutorial showing how to upload files with HTML [https://austingil.com/uploading-files-with-html/]. That's great, but it's a bit limited to using the native browser form behavior, which causes the page to refresh. In this tutorial, I want to show you how to do the same thing with JavaScript [https://austingil.com/category/javascript/]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Austin Gil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-Dimensional Arrays in Python – Matrices Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/multi-dimensional-arrays-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/multi-dimensional-arrays-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T17:28:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-dimensional arrays, also known as matrices, are a powerful data structure in Python. They allow you to store and manipulate data in multiple dimensions or axes.  You'll commonly use these types of arrays in fields such as mathematics, statistics, and computer science to represent and process structured data, such]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is HTTP? Protocol Overview for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-http/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-http/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T16:53:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Without HTTP (Hypertext Transfer Protocol), the World Wide Web as we know it today would not exist. HTTP is the protocol that enables the transfer of data over the internet, allowing users to access websites and other online resources. There are various ways to design web applications, including GraphQL, SOAP,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rufai Mustapha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java for Beginners – How to Create Your First "Hello World" Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hello-world-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hello-world-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T16:08:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are learning a programming language, the first thing you do is print something in the terminal/command prompt.  And that first thing is likely printing "Hello World" in the terminal. So that's what I'll show you how to do here if you are learning Java for the first]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering LINQ: Unlock the Power of Advanced C# Data Manipulation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linq-advanced-c-sharp-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linq-advanced-c-sharp-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a C# developer looking to enhance your skills in data manipulation and querying? Do you want to learn how to query and manipulate data from various sources using the power of Language Integrated Query (LINQ)? We are excited to introduce our latest video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Functions in C - Explained With Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-functions-in-c/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-functions-in-c/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T14:20:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Functions are an essential component of the C programming language. They help you divide bigger problems into smaller, more manageable chunks of code, making it simpler to create and run programs.  We'll look at functions in C, their syntax, and how to use them successfully in this article. What]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Know About GPT-4 for Non-AI Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-to-know-about-gpt-4/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-to-know-about-gpt-4/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T14:15:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are living through an AI revolution. The AI industry is constantly evolving, with new tools, products, and technologies emerging every day.  For those not familiar with the AI domain, keeping up with these developments can be challenging. The biggest news recently is undoubtedly GPT-4. Everyone from my barber]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kaushal Joshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indices of a List in Python – List IndexOf() Equivalent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/indices-of-a-list-in-python-list-indexof-equivalent/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/indices-of-a-list-in-python-list-indexof-equivalent/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T07:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python has several methods and hacks for getting the index of an item in iterable data like a list, tuple, and dictionary. In this article, we are looking at how you can get the index of a list item with the index() method. I’ll also show you a function that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bubble Sort Algorithm - Most Asked Questions About Bubble Sort]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/most-asked-questions-about-bubble-sort/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/most-asked-questions-about-bubble-sort/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T21:40:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bubble sort is a simple sorting algorithm that repeatedly loops through a list, compares adjacent elements, and swaps them if they are in the wrong order. The bubble sort algorithm is not the most efficient sorting algorithm when it comes to time complexity. But it is still often used as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Trie Data Structures Work – Validate User Input with Automated Trie Visualization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-validate-user-input-with-automated-trie-visualization/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-validate-user-input-with-automated-trie-visualization/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T21:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data structures play a vital role in computer science. They are essential for designing efficient software infrastructure.  Simply put, a data structure is a way of organizing and storing data in a computer so that it can be accessed and manipulated reliably. Also, it provides a set of operations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel García Solla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Symmetric and Asymmetric Key Encryption – Explained in Plain English]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/encryption-explained-in-plain-english/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/encryption-explained-in-plain-english/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T20:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Encryption is a way of scrambling data so that it can only be read by the intended recipient.  Encryption is an integral part of our daily lives – whether you are sending messages to friends on WhatsApp, visiting a website and your browser is making sure it's legitimate, or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build and Publish Python Packages With Poetry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-and-publish-python-packages-with-poetry/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-and-publish-python-packages-with-poetry/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T18:04:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Python package is a collection of Python modules that can be easily distributed and installed. It allows developers to reuse code across multiple projects and share it with others.  Python packages typically include a set of functions, classes, or other components that serve a specific purpose, such as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Personal Website with Next.js 13, Sanity.io, TailwindCSS, and TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-personal-website-with-next-js-13-sanity-io-tailwindcss-and-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-personal-website-with-next-js-13-sanity-io-tailwindcss-and-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T14:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a personal website can be an excellent way to practice various developer skills. And it can also help showcases your skills, projects, and accomplishments. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build a personal website using Next.js 13 for the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Protect Your App With A Threat Model Based On JSONDiff]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/protect-app-threat-model-jsondiff/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/protect-app-threat-model-jsondiff/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a developer who wants to concentrate on delivering a killer application rather than worrying about countless security issues, threat model documents can help you do that. With small architectural changes, we can make these threats manageable and prevent them in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zack Grossbart &amp; Terry Yao)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[850+ Online Courses with Real College Credit that You Can Access for Free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/370-online-courses-with-real-college-credit-that-you-can-access-for-free-4fec5a28646/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/370-online-courses-with-real-college-credit-that-you-can-access-for-free-4fec5a28646/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many universities offer online courses for credit. Class Central [https://www.classcentral.com/] has already compiled 70+ MOOC-based master’s degrees [https://www.classcentral.com/report/mooc-based-masters-degree/]. Many of the courses in these online degree programs are publicly available: anyone with an internet connection can take them. Some of these courses are “freebies” meant to give prospective students a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhawal Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Signals in Angular – How to Write More Reactive Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/angular-signals/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/angular-signals/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T00:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An exciting new feature is coming to Angular: signals! Signals provide a new way for our code to tell our templates (and other code) that our data has changed. This improves Angular's change detection, which also improves performance, and makes our code more reactive. You can try out this powerful]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Kurata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve User Experience  in React Apps – Animate Routes using Framer Motion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-user-experience-in-react-by-animating-routes-using-framer-motion/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-user-experience-in-react-by-animating-routes-using-framer-motion/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T22:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the modern digital landscape, user experience (UX) has become a central focus of web development. Providing a smooth, captivating, and aesthetically pleasing interface can really influence user satisfaction and retention.  Route animation is a frequently underestimated aspect of UX that can substantially improve a website's interactivity.  In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python vs Pandas - Difference Between Python and Pandas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/difference-between-python-and-pandas/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/difference-between-python-and-pandas/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T21:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The difference between Python and Pandas is a topic that often confuses some beginners in the Python ecosystem.  In this article, you'll learn about the differences between Python and Pandas, and what they are used for. You'll start by learning what each technology is used for, then you'll see]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Dorking for Penetration Testers — A Practical Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-dorking-for-pentesters-a-practical-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-dorking-for-pentesters-a-practical-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T21:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every day, Google processes over 8.5 billion searches. We know how much we use Google daily. With the crawling capabilities of Google, it can also be a powerful tool for pen testers. Google can help us find exposed files, scripts and other critical resources in web applications. To find this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Split String – How to Split a String into a List or Array in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-split-string-how-to-split-a-string-into-a-list-or-array-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-split-string-how-to-split-a-string-into-a-list-or-array-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T20:24:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will walk through a comprehensive guide on how to split a string in Python and convert it into a list or array.  We'll start by introducing the string data type in Python and explaining its properties. Then we'll discuss the various ways in which you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Upload Files with HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/upload-files-with-html/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/upload-files-with-html/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T20:17:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When building applications with HTML, you may eventually come to a point where you need to allow users to upload files. Surprisingly, it's not quite as straightforward as you might assume. In this post, we'll look at all things you need to support file uploads in HTML. How to Access]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Austin Gil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Minimal APIs in .NET 7]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-minimal-apis-in-net-7/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-minimal-apis-in-net-7/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T18:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Minimal APIs offer a streamlined approach to constructing HTTP APIs with minimal dependencies, making them perfect for microservices and applications that aim to incorporate only the essential files, features, and dependencies within ASP.NET Core. We just published a coruse on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you the power]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend Web Development: In-Depth Project Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/frontend-web-development-in-depth-project-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/frontend-web-development-in-depth-project-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T18:29:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking to improve your frontend web development skills with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, and React? If so, we have the perfect video course for you! We just published a 10-hour project-based, frontend web development course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Zach Gollwitzer published this course. Zach is a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Truncate Text with CSS and JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-truncate-text-with-css-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-truncate-text-with-css-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T18:06:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS [https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/CSS] is a powerful tool to have in your programming toolkit. It offers numerous features that allow you to create responsive and attractive websites.  Sometimes you might see an ellipsis (...) that appears to indicate that some content or text is hidden. Have you ever wondered how you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Fagbuyiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Weather Forecasting System in Python using Tkinter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-geolocation-based-weather-forecasting-system-using-tkinter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-geolocation-based-weather-forecasting-system-using-tkinter/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T16:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tkinter is a Python GUI (Graphical User Interface) toolkit that allows developers to create desktop applications with Python. It provides a set of tools and widgets for building graphical interfaces that are simple and intuitive to use.  Tkinter is included in the standard Python distribution and supports cross-platform development,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Encryption at Rest? Explained for Security Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/encryption-at-rest/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/encryption-at-rest/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T15:49:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Encryption is a technique for secure communication that converts plain text into a coded form that can only be deciphered with a secret key. Let's explore some of encryption's fun bits. Encryption works by using an algorithm to convert plaintext into ciphertext, which is unreadable without a corresponding decryption key.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python str() Function – How to Convert to a String]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-str-function-how-to-convert-to-a-string/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-str-function-how-to-convert-to-a-string/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T12:48:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python’s primitive data types include float, integer, Boolean, and string. The programming language provides several functions you can use to convert any of these data types to the other. One of those functions we’ll look at in this article is str(). It’s a built-in function you can use to convert]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage State in React and React Native with the PullState Library]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/state-management-in-react-and-react-native-with-pullstate/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/state-management-in-react-and-react-native-with-pullstate/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T21:47:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React and React Native are popular JavaScript libraries that allow developers to create complex user interfaces and mobile applications with ease.  One of the key benefits of both these libraries is that they each have the ability to manage their own state within components. But managing state, along with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Weatherston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create and Manage Virtual Machines with the Vagrant Command Line Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-and-manage-virtual-machines-with-vagrant/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-and-manage-virtual-machines-with-vagrant/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T20:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating and managing virtual machines used to be a tedious and time-consuming process. Replicating the VM on a different server can also be challenging, and it gets harder if you have to replicate multiple VMs. But then Vagrant came along, a command-line or shell tool that generally works with Type]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ijeoma Eti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Int Max in Python – Maximum Integer Size]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/maximum-integer-size-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/maximum-integer-size-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T18:20:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can check the maximum integer size in Python using the maxsize property of the sys module.  In this article, you'll learn about the maximum integer size in Python. You'll also see the differences in Python 2 and Python 3. The maximum value of an integer shouldn't bother you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the CSS Box Model and Style SVG Images]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-css-box-model-and-style-svg-images/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-css-box-model-and-style-svg-images/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T17:29:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every programmer who wants to write clean CSS and build great user interfaces should understand the CSS Box Model.  Before I understood the foundations of CSS, I would often write unnecessary styles for margins and padding.  CSS Box Model forms the basis for styling any element on a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Njoku Samson Ebere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Give Good Feedback for Effective Code Reviews]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-review-tips/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-review-tips/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T16:49:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, open sourcer! 😊 I’ve heard through the digital webs that you’ve become quite the wordsmith when it comes to giving feedback on pull requests and want to learn something new.  No worries, I’ve been there myself when I started getting more comfortable in the open source world. So,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CHRISTINE T. BELZIE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js vs React – What are the Differences?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/next-vs-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/next-vs-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T16:36:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone! Next.js 13 is trending these days, and it's a great time to learn it. But what even is Next.js? What is pre-rendering in Next.js, and why do we use it?  Well, let me explain. What is Next.js? Next.js is a backend framework which is based on React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nishant Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use part in Dart – Splitting Files for Scoped Access]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-part-in-dart/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-part-in-dart/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T16:17:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're coding in Dart, you may come across these  following situations:  1. A class/method is associated with a particular file of your codebase and you     want to keep it private only to that one file  2. You want to break your one big]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rutvik Tak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Unit Testing for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-unit-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-unit-testing/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T15:37:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's say you are developing an application. After long hours of coding, you manage to create some cool features. Now, you want to make sure the features are working as you want. This involves testing if each and every piece of code works as expected. This procedure is known as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Effectively Search Large Datasets in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-search-large-datasets-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-search-large-datasets-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T15:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you're trying to find a needle in a haystack, but the haystack is the size of a mountain. That's what it can feel like to search for specific items in a massive dataset using Python.  But fear not! With the right techniques, you can efficiently search and lookup]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Brief History of Open Source]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/brief-history-of-open-source/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/brief-history-of-open-source/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T14:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s difficult to imagine a world without open source. Open source is ubiquitous. In fact, open source is what powers the internet.  For example, 60% of the world’s websites run on Apache and Nginx, the most popular web servers [https://hbr.org/2021/09/the-digital-economy-runs-on-open-source-heres-how-to-protect-it#:~:text=Phones%2C%20cars%2C%20planes%2C%20and,Kubernetes%2C%20which%20powers%20cloud%20computing.] . And yes, even Fortune 500 companies use Nginx.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Agnes Nduta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Algorithms: Skills Of Designers That AI Can’t Replicate]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/skills-designers-ai-cant-replicate/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/skills-designers-ai-cant-replicate/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article highlights non-technical skills like curiosity, observation, empathy, advocacy, visual communication, and collaboration that designers routinely use in their process to make a difference through design. AI can be used to augment designers’ workflow instead of replacing people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lyndon Cerejo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin VS Java – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kotlin-vs-java-whats-the-difference/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kotlin-vs-java-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T20:21:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Java is a widely popular programming language that has been used for years in various domains, including web development, mobile app development, desktop applications, and game development.  On the other hand, Kotlin is a relatively new programming language that has been gaining popularity in recent years. Both languages are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insertion Sort Algorithm - Most Asked Questions About Insertion Sort]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/most-asked-questions-about-insertion-sort-algorithm/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/most-asked-questions-about-insertion-sort-algorithm/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T19:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sorting algorithms are an essential part of computer science. There are many sorting algorithms used to sort data. The insertion sort algorithm is one of the most basic and simple sorting algorithms. It is an efficient algorithm for small input sizes or for partially sorted data. The algorithm works by]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Paraphrasing Tool with ReactJs & ChatGPT Turbo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-paraphrasing-tool-with-reactjs-chatgpt-turbo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-paraphrasing-tool-with-reactjs-chatgpt-turbo/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T17:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a world where online content is growing exponentially, it's more important than ever to produce unique content that stands out. Paraphrasing tools can offer a quick solution to help you develop unique ideas and create original content. With the help of ReactJs and ChatGPT Turbo, developers can build a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Idris Olubisi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JS Sum of an Array – How to Add the Numbers in a JavaScript Array]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-numbers-in-javascript-arrays/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-numbers-in-javascript-arrays/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T17:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An array in JavaScript is an object that allows you to store an ordered collection of multiple values under a single variable name and manipulate those values in numerous ways. In this article, you will learn how to calculate the sum of all the numbers in a given array using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comments Inside JSON – Commenting in a JSON File]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/comments-in-json/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/comments-in-json/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T15:10:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JSON (JavaScript Object Notation) is a popular data interchange format used in web development and mobile applications due to its simplicity and flexibility. But JSON files do not officially support comments. This makes providing additional context or explanation for the data challenging. This article will show you how to include]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Include an Empty String in RegEx]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-include-empty-string-in-regex/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-include-empty-string-in-regex/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T11:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regular expressions (RegEx or RegExp for short) are a sequence of characters that define a search pattern. You can use them to search, replace, and validate the strings of a text in a wide variety of applications, such as text editors, developer tools, and command line tools. RegEx is also]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swing Into April (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With April just around the corner, we have a new collection of desktop and mobile wallpapers waiting for you to celebrate the beginning of the new month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, the wallpapers come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use an Email Validation Service for Flask User Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-email-validation-api-for-flask-user-authentication/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-email-validation-api-for-flask-user-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T22:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital world, online security is really important, and user authentication is a key aspect of it.  Email-based authentication [https://ashutoshkrris.hashnode.dev/how-to-set-up-email-verification-in-a-flask-app]  is one of the most popular and widely used methods for user registration and login. But it's not always reliable, as users can enter fake or invalid]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Integrate Chart.js in Angular Using Data from a REST API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-integrate-chart-js-in-angular-using-data-from-a-rest-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-integrate-chart-js-in-angular-using-data-from-a-rest-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T15:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Charts are a great way of visually displaying large sets of data in formats that are easy to understand and analyze. They are a great way of showing the relationship that exists between two or more data sets.  Different types of charts exist, some of which includes bar chart,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deji Adesoga</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Bubble Sort Algorithm With JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-bubble-sort-algorithm-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-bubble-sort-algorithm-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T15:34:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sorting is an essential task in programming, and the bubble sort algorithm is one of the simplest and most commonly used methods. As a beginner in solving algorithm questions or preparing for an interview, you might wonder how to implement this algorithm effectively. Don't worry; in this article, I will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use ChatGPT to Build a Low Code RegEx Generator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-chatgpt-to-build-a-regex-generator/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-chatgpt-to-build-a-regex-generator/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T13:33:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you tired of spending hours writing complex Regular Expressions (RegEx) to manipulate strings? Do you want to learn how to build a RegEx generator quickly and easily? Then this course is for you! We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you build a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Regular Expressions in CTRL F]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-you-use-regular-expression-in-ctrl-f/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-you-use-regular-expression-in-ctrl-f/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T13:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The conventional CTRL + F does not support Regex in many software tools we use in our day-to-day lives. But almost nothing is impossible in the tech world. Many of these software tools, such as VS Code, Chrome browser, Dreamweaver, Jetbrains, and others, have a built-in mechanism that supports RegEx]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Organizing Design Workshops: A Detailed Checklist]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/organizing-design-workshops-checklist/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/organizing-design-workshops-checklist/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workshops are all about people: they involve people, are conducted by people, and aim to close the gaps in people’s communication. Slava Shestopalov shares a checklist with everything you need to keep in mind when running a workshop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Slava Shestopalov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does :: Mean in Python? Operator Meaning for Double Colon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-mean-in-python-operator-meaning-for-double-colon/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-mean-in-python-operator-meaning-for-double-colon/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T07:21:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use the double colon (::) in Python to slice or extract elements in a collection such as a list or string. In this article, you'll learn the syntax and how to use :: to slice a list in Python. You'll also learn how to use the parameters associated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code a Simple Game and Host it on Your Website]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-a-simple-game/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-a-simple-game/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T23:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wanted to create your own game to share with others on your website? In this article, we'll be learning how to code a simple game using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, and then host it on your website.  The game we'll be coding is a classic word-guessing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Duggan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build and Push Dockerized Applications to the Azure Registry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-and-push-dockerized-applications-to-azure-registry/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-and-push-dockerized-applications-to-azure-registry/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T21:53:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A common issue on development teams is that an application might work on one developer’s computer but not on the others. Luckily, there's Docker, a popular containerization technology. It works by packing up all the components needed to run the application and then executing the application in an isolated environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Destiny Erhabor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the React Context API in Your Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/context-api-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/context-api-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T20:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing state is an essential part of developing applications in React. A common way to manage state is by passing props. Passing props means sending data from one component to another. It's a good way to make sure that data gets to the right place in a React application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dickson Boateng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Google Apps Script Code to Clear Data Ranges in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-apps-script-to-clear-data-in-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-apps-script-to-clear-data-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T19:55:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Apps Script allows you to write code in your spreadsheet. It functions like Visual Basic for Applications (VBA) does in Excel. They're both incredibly useful for executing more complicated actions or for automating repetitive tasks. In this article, I'll give you a brief overview of Google Apps Script by]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is the Second Argument in JSON.stringify() usually null?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-is-the-second-argument-in-json-stringify-usually-undefined/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-is-the-second-argument-in-json-stringify-usually-undefined/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T17:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Usually, when developers use the JSON.stringify() method, the second argument is usually skipped, or with a value null. But this argument has its relevance. Here's a common example usage of JSON.stringify(): const obj = {   name: "Dillion",   language: "JavaScript",   age: 100,   isEngineer:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software Engineering Job Interview – Full Mock Interview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/real-world-coding-interview-for-software-engineering/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/real-world-coding-interview-for-software-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T14:28:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you preparing for a technical programming interview for a software engineering role? If so, you might want to check out this new informative video, which features a mock full-length, real-world coding technical interview. This is a full-length interview between Keith Gali and Kylie Ying. Keith, who is an experienced]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slicing and Indexing in Python – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/slicing-and-indexing-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/slicing-and-indexing-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T14:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slicing and indexing are two fundamental concepts in Python. They help you access specific elements in a sequence, such as a list, tuple or string.  By using these techniques, you can extract substrings from strings, filter lists, and extract columns from 2D lists, among other things.  Understanding how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-Grained Access Handling And Data Management With Row-Level Security]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/access-handling-data-management-row-level-security/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/access-handling-data-management-row-level-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with sensitive data is an important topic for any app. In this article, you will find out how to handle sensitive or confidential information in your apps and what Row-Level Security means.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter App Development – Create a Twitter Clone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flutter-app-development-create-a-twitter-clone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flutter-app-development-create-a-twitter-clone/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T20:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking to improve your Flutter skills and build a fully-functional Twitter clone? We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Flutter, Appwrite, and Riverpod to create a Twitter clone. Rivaan Ranawat created this course. He is an expereinced course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a 3D Element in Your React Site]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/3d-react-webgi-threejs-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/3d-react-webgi-threejs-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T20:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you interested in learning how to build a 3D animation using React? We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to add 3D elements into your React websites. Slobodan Gajic created this course. He is a senior fullstack developer and popular]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix Merge Conflicts in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fix-merge-conflicts-in-git/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fix-merge-conflicts-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T20:25:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever worked on a team that's working on a large codebase, you’ve likely experienced merge conflicts while creating a pull request or merging two branches. Even if you’ve never worked with a team or on a large codebase, it is still possible to have merge conflicts as long]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Iterate Over Rows with Pandas – Loop Through a Dataframe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-iterate-over-rows-with-pandas-loop-through-a-dataframe/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-iterate-over-rows-with-pandas-loop-through-a-dataframe/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T18:35:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article provides a comprehensive guide on how to loop through a Pandas DataFrame in Python.  I'll start by introducing the Pandas library and DataFrame data structure. I'll explain the essential characteristics of Pandas, how to loop through rows in a dataframe, and finally how to loop through columns]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Website Encryption Works]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-website-encryption/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-website-encryption/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T17:35:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's one thing to protect your data when it's sitting quietly on your own local machine and not bothering anyone. But moving data between locations – as you do whenever you open a website on a remote server or send an email attachment across the internet – introduces a whole]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Get Current Directory – Print Working Directory PWD Equivalent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-get-current-directory/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-get-current-directory/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T16:27:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to get the current working directory (another name for folder) in Python, which is the equivalent of using the pwd  command. There are a couple of ways to get the current working directory in Python:  * By using the os module]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use GitHub Actions to  Automate Open-Source Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-open-source-projects-with-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-open-source-projects-with-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T15:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, developers use automation tools all the time to manage tasks effectively and streamline their daily activities. And one of these popular tools is GitHub Actions. When talking about software, including the open-source variety, you'll likely agree with me that efficiency is in high demand. And with the help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hillary Nyakundi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is R Squared? R2 Value Meaning and Definition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-r-squared-r2-value-meaning-and-definition/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-r-squared-r2-value-meaning-and-definition/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T14:51:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regression analysis is a statistical method used to study the relationship between a dependent variable and one or more independent variables.  One of the most commonly used methods for linear regression analysis is R-Squared.  In this article, you'll get to know what R-Squared is and the meaning of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to replace links in a text with Anchor Tags using JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-replace-links-in-a-text-with-anchor-tags-using-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-replace-links-in-a-text-with-anchor-tags-using-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T10:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you make a post on social media, and that post contains links, you would see the links styled differently from other text. How can you achieve this? For example, here's a tweet I made on Twitter The text for my tweet is: > hi good morning my website is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn React by Building a Mortgage Calculator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-mortgage-calculator-tutorial-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-mortgage-calculator-tutorial-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T22:56:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we will learn and practice ReactJs by building a mortgage calculator step by step. This is the project that we will build today 👇  * Heres a live demo of the project    [https://mortgage-calculator-tutorial.vercel.app/]  * And here's the Github Repo Link    [https://github.com/JoyShaheb/mortgage-calculator-tutorial]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joy Shaheb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Setup a CI/CD Pipeline for a Next.js App using AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ci-cd-pipeline-for-nextjs-app-with-aws/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ci-cd-pipeline-for-nextjs-app-with-aws/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T21:53:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Everyone! Deploying a web application is a challenging task (at least for me), especially when it comes to keeping it updated. It can take up a lot of time and energy if it has to be deployed manually every time you make a change.  But I recently discovered]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Array Tutorial – Array Methods in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-array-tutorial-array-methods-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-array-tutorial-array-methods-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T19:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arrays are data structures that are extremely useful and versatile. They're present in many programming languages, and they allow you to store multiple values in a single variable. In this tutorial, we will explore how arrays work in JavaScript, their characteristics, and how to manipulate them using the most common]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dario Di Cillo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dataframe Drop Column in Pandas – How to Remove Columns from Dataframes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dataframe-drop-column-in-pandas-how-to-remove-columns-from-dataframes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dataframe-drop-column-in-pandas-how-to-remove-columns-from-dataframes/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T18:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Pandas, sometimes you'll need to remove columns from a DataFrame for various reasons, such as cleaning data, reducing memory usage, or simplifying analysis. And in this article, I'll show you how to do it. I'll start by introducing the .drop() method, which is the primary method for removing columns]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create and Sync Git and GitHub Repositories]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-and-sync-git-and-github-repositories/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-and-sync-git-and-github-repositories/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T17:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working with Git and GitHub is often an essential part of your daily programming tasks. In many cases, you'll want both a local Git repository and a remote GitHub repository for a project.  * With the local repository, you work on your own copy of the project. You make]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Kurata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Instal ChatGPT in VSCode]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/install-chatgpt-in-vscode/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/install-chatgpt-in-vscode/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T17:50:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT – or Chat Generative Pre-Training Transformer – has been making waves in the tech industry recently.  It was first launched in November 2022 and upgraded to ChatGPT-4 in March 2023. In this tutorial, I will explain how you can use ChatGPT to become more productive. Then I'll walk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Measure and Improve the Performance of a React App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/measure-and-improve-performance-of-react-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/measure-and-improve-performance-of-react-apps/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T17:18:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! React is a popular JavaScript library for building user interfaces. As applications built with React become more complex, their performance can start to degrade.  Poor performance can lead to a frustrating user experience and a negative impact on user engagement. So in this article, we will discuss]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up AWS Simple Email Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-aws-simple-email-service/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-aws-simple-email-service/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T15:44:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're looking for a reliable and cost-effective way to send emails, AWS Simple Email Service (SES) is a great option. It's a cloud-based email platform that helps you send and receive emails quickly and easily.  With SES, you don't have to worry about managing your mail server, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Iroegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Handoff Is No Handoff]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/best-handoff-is-no-handoff/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/best-handoff-is-no-handoff/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design handoffs are inefficient and painful. They cause frustration, friction and a lot of back and forth. Can we avoid them altogether? Of course we can! Let’s see how to do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn Different Tech Stacks IRL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-learn-different-tech-stacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-learn-different-tech-stacks/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-25T17:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last couple years, I've learned that being a consultant means you have to be able to learn new things quickly. At first, this was really scary to me. Now, as someone who has had to learn several new tech stacks over the last year, it’s still a little]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dataframe to CSV – How to Save Pandas Dataframes by Exporting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dataframe-to-csv-how-to-save-pandas-dataframes-by-exporting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dataframe-to-csv-how-to-save-pandas-dataframes-by-exporting/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T18:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pandas is a widely used open-source library in Python for data manipulation and analysis. It provides a range of data structures and functions for working with data, one of which is the DataFrame.  DataFrames are a powerful tool for storing and analyzing large sets of data, but they can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Scroll Animations to a Page with JavaScript's Intersection Observer API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/scroll-animations-with-javascript-intersection-observer-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/scroll-animations-with-javascript-intersection-observer-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T17:42:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, when you visit a website, you'll notice that certain elements or a particular section gets revealed dynamically as you scroll.  It's like the contents of that particular section weren't available to view until you scrolled into the section – but now, because you're there, the website decides to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mwendwa Bundi Emma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Where Contains String – Substring Query Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-where-contains-string-substring-query-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-where-contains-string-substring-query-example/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T22:36:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re working with a database, whether large or small, there might be occasions when you need to search for some entries containing strings. In this article, I’ll show you how to locate strings and substrings in MySQL and SQL Server. I‘ll be using a table I call products_data in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Reveal on Scroll in React using the Intersection Observer API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/reveal-on-scroll-in-react-using-the-intersection-observer-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/reveal-on-scroll-in-react-using-the-intersection-observer-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T22:20:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking for an elegant way to reveal content on your React website as users scroll down the page? Look no further than the Intersection Observer API. In this article, you’ll learn how to implement the reveal on scroll effect in React using Intersection Observer. This will allow you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Remove from List – How to Remove an Item from a List in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-remove-from-list-how-to-remove-an-item-from-a-list-in-python-2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-remove-from-list-how-to-remove-an-item-from-a-list-in-python-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T18:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A list in Python is a collection of items that are ordered and changeable. It is one of the most versatile and frequently used data structures in Python.  A list can contain any type of data, such as integers, strings, floats, and even other lists. In Python, lists are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Undo Git Add – How to Remove Added Files in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/undo-git-add-how-to-remove-added-files-in-git/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/undo-git-add-how-to-remove-added-files-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T18:27:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a powerful version control and collaboration tool. It allows developers to work together seamlessly on projects. But even the most experienced developers can make mistakes while using Git, such as accidentally adding files that were not meant to be committed. This can be a problem, especially if the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overcoming The Challenges Of Content Creation For Informational Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/overcoming-challenges-content-creation-informational-websites/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/overcoming-challenges-content-creation-informational-websites/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content matters! Unfortunately, when it comes to informational websites, content quality is often poor. There is no magic answer to fix that. However, there are practical techniques you can use to improve the copy on your websites and ensure your users find the content they are looking for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a Directory in Python – How to Create a Folder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/creating-a-directory-in-python-how-to-create-a-folder/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/creating-a-directory-in-python-how-to-create-a-folder/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T13:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to create new directories (which is another name for folders) in Python. You will also learn how to create a nested directory structure. To work with directories in Python, you first need to include the os module in your project, which allows you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Vite to Speed Up Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-vite-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-vite-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T13:20:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vite is a powerful build tool and development server designed to speed up modern web development. We just published a full Vite course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Vite effectively and efficiently to streamline your web development workflow. Arsalan Khattak developed this course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started in Data Analytics – A Roadmap for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-analytics-roadmap/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-analytics-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T00:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello and welcome to the world of data analysis! If you're considering a career in this field, you're in good company. Data analysis is a growing and exciting field that's becoming increasingly important in today's data-driven world. Let's face it, we're all drowning in data these days. From social media]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Squash Commits – Squashing the Last N Commits into One Commit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-squash-commits/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-squash-commits/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T23:16:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are working on a project and trying to implement a new feature, you might commit your code a few times to test things out. This lets you see how the code works or looks. While doing this, things might get messy because you now have several commits, even]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Cross-Browser DevTools Features You Might Not Know]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377264</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-cross-browser-devtools-features-you-might-not-know/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T20:22:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I spend a lot of time in DevTools, and I’m sure you do too. Sometimes I even bounce between them, especially when I’m debugging cross-browser issues. DevTools is a lot like browsers themselves — not all of the features in …
Some Cross-Browser DevTools Features You Might Not Know originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pankaj Parashar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CRM App Development with Django, Python, and MySQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crm-app-development-with-django-python-and-mysql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crm-app-development-with-django-python-and-mysql/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T19:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you interested in learning how to build a customer relationship management (CRM) app with Django, Python, and MySQL? We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will guide you step-by-step on how to build a fully-functional CRM application using Django, Python, and MySQL. John Elder developed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Print Newline in Python – Printing a New Line]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/print-newline-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/print-newline-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T19:17:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working with strings or text data in programming frequently involves printing a newline. The end of a line is indicated by a newline character, which also advances the cursor to the start of the following line. Using the escape character "\n," we can print a newline in Python. Other programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Variables – The Complete Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-variables/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-variables/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T18:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Variables are an essential part of Python. They allow us to easily store, manipulate, and reference data throughout our projects. This article will give you all the understanding of Python variables you need to use them effectively in your projects. If you want the most convenient way to review all]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Prevent Account Loss When using Two-Factor Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-prevent-account-loss-when-using-two-factor-authentication/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-prevent-account-loss-when-using-two-factor-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T16:28:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If someone gains unauthorized access to your passwords, two-factor authentication (2FA) can prevent them from accessing your account.  But if you ever lose access to all your 2FA methods, you have lost your account. How do you prevent such loss? In this article, we will look at two-factor authentication]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Obumuneme Nwabude</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Incorporate Cybersecurity Audits into Your Workflow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/incorporate-cybersecurity-audits-into-your-workflow/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/incorporate-cybersecurity-audits-into-your-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T16:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The word "audit" describes any process designed to review and assess a system's current state, capacity, and integrity.  An internal audit is a review process initiated and carried out by an organization itself. External audits are often performed by or on behalf of banking entities or government regulatory bodies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>