<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-08-31T02:02:26.980Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From WordPress to Hugo – How I Migrated a 250+ Page Site and the Scripts I Used]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/wordpress-to-hugo-scripts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/wordpress-to-hugo-scripts/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T23:25:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently decided to switch Boot.dev's [https://boot.dev] blog from WordPress to a static site generator. I decided on Hugo [https://gohugo.io/], partly because I’m a huge fan of the Go programming language, but also because it just seemed like the best option from a dev-experience perspective.  Here’s why I decided]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Wagner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use JavaScript's Map() Method to Solve Breadth-First and Depth-First Search Problems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-javascript-map-method-to-make-a-breath-first-and-depth-first-search/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-javascript-map-method-to-make-a-breath-first-and-depth-first-search/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T17:17:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript map() method [/news/array-map-tutorial/] is an object [https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/JavaScript/Reference/Global_Objects/Object]  with a key and value pair. An object's key and value are connected using a colon (:) while the key and value of a map are connected using an arrow (=>). Here's an example of an object in JavaScript: {]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Njoku Samson Ebere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Personal Digital Security – How to Protect Yourself Online for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/personal-digital-security-an-intro/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/personal-digital-security-an-intro/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T16:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you protect yourself online without having to remember a million impossible passwords?  This is an (actually) easy to implement guide, which is the digital equivalent of locking your house when you leave.  Taking these steps won’t make you hack-proof (just as locking your house won’t make]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Kaczanowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[String to Number in JavaScript – Convert a String to an Int in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/string-to-number-in-javascript-convert-a-string-to-an-int-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/string-to-number-in-javascript-convert-a-string-to-an-int-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T16:38:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're programming, you'll often need to switch between data types. For example, you may need to convert a string into a number. The ability to convert one data type to another gives you great flexibility when working with information. JavaScript has different built-in methods to convert or cast a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL HAVING – How to Group and Count with a Having Statement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-having-how-to-group-and-count-with-a-having-statement/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-having-how-to-group-and-count-with-a-having-statement/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T15:59:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In SQL, you use the HAVING keyword right after GROUP BY to query the database based on a specified condition. Like other keywords, it returns the data that meet the condition and filters out the rest. The HAVING keyword was introduced because the WHERE clause fails when used with aggregate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SSH Keygen Tutorial – How to Generate an SSH Public Key for RSA Login]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ssh-keygen-how-to-generate-an-ssh-public-key-for-rsa-login/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ssh-keygen-how-to-generate-an-ssh-public-key-for-rsa-login/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T15:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptography uses encryption and decryption to conceal messages. This introduces secrecy in information security.  The purpose of cryptography is to ensure secure communication between two people or devices who are connecting through insecure channels. The sender often employs an encryption key to lock the message, while the recipient uses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bolaji Ayodeji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use GitHub Super Linter in Your Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/github-super-linter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/github-super-linter/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T15:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're starting a new project, you might have to add multiple linting tools to beautify your code and prevent simple errors.  You will often use multiple linters – one of them might support an npm installation and other one might have a PyPI installation and so on. You]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rishit Dagli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS in 11 Hours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-in-11-hours/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-in-11-hours/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T13:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is essential for frontend web developers to understand how to use CSS. This is what is used to style a website. We just published a comprehensive CSS course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. In this in-depth course, you will learn about all the key features of CSS. This is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interpolating Numeric CSS Variables]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372839</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/interpolating-numeric-css-variables/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T13:17:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can make variables in CSS pretty easily:
:root {
  --scale: 1;
}
And we can declare them on any element:
.thing {
  transform: scale(--scale);
}
Even better for an example like this is applying the variable on a user …
Interpolating Numeric CSS Variables originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Improve And Measure Your Progress Learning Web Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/improve-measure-progress-learning-web-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/improve-measure-progress-learning-web-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever felt overwhelmed by the number of things you need to learn? Today, we look at how [Uxcel](https://uxcel.com/) eases this transition and approaches actively learning new skills to take our careers to the next level.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shane Hudson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Common Attacks on SSL/TLS – and How to Protect Your System]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/attacks-on-ssl-tls-and-how-to-protect-your-system/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/attacks-on-ssl-tls-and-how-to-protect-your-system/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T21:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SSL and TLS protocols are frequently attacked. And understanding past attacks can inform your knowledge as a defender and help you secure current systems. It can also help you predict the direction of future attacks. So here's a summary of some of the most famous attacks targeting these protocols:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Kaczanowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Makes A Great Toggle Button? (Case Study, Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/toggle-button-case-study-part-2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/toggle-button-case-study-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The problem of how to design an effective toggle button that shows the selected option clearly is a long-term open question among UI/UX designers. In this second part, Eduard Kuric explains a complex list of visual cues used by toggle buttons to communicate which of their options is active.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eduard Kuric)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Linear Models and Decision Trees in Julia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linear-models-vs-decision-trees-in-julia/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linear-models-vs-decision-trees-in-julia/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T13:46:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a machine learning engineer or data scientist, one of the most critical decisions you can make is what type of model to use to solve a specific problem. Do you really need to use Deep Learning to model this specific problem? Will something like a Random Forest model or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Logan Kilpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code 20 Beginner Python Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/20-beginner-python-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/20-beginner-python-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T12:44:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking to improve your Python skills? Try coding these 20 Python projects! We just posted a video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create 20 fun Python projects. Tomi Tokko created this course. Tomi has created a bunch of really popular tutorials]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java scanner.nextLine() Method Call Gets Skipped Error [SOLVED]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-scanner-nextline-call-gets-skipped-solved/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-scanner-nextline-call-gets-skipped-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T21:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a common error that tends to stump new Java programmers. It happens when you group together a bunch of input prompts and one of the scanner.nextLine()  method calls gets skipped – without any signs of failure or error. Take a look at the following code snippet, for example:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farhan Hasin Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python to Lowercase a String – str.lower() Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-to-lowercase-a-string-str-lower-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-to-lowercase-a-string-str-lower-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T20:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strings can be in different formats such as lowercase, capitalized, and uppercase. In this article, I'll show you how to convert a string to lowercase in Python. A lowercase string has all its characters in small letters. An example is python . A capitalized string has the first letter of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML TextArea – How to Add a Text Box Input Type Tag to Your Website]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-textarea-how-to-add-text-box-to-your-website/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-textarea-how-to-add-text-box-to-your-website/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T16:21:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A text box is a section of your website where users can enter text. A blinking cursor appears when you click or tap on or inside the text box, indicating that you are ready to begin typing. And an on-screen keyboard will appear if you're using a tablet or smartphone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perform Integration Testing using JUnit 5 and TestContainers with SpringBoot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/integration-testing-using-junit-5-testcontainers-with-springboot-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/integration-testing-using-junit-5-testcontainers-with-springboot-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T15:46:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TestContainers is a library that helps you run module-specific Docker containers to simplify Integration Testing.  These Docker containers are lightweight, and once the tests are finished the containers get destroyed. In the article we are going to understand what the TestContainers is and how it helps you write more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sameer Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[File Handling in Python – How to Create, Read, and Write to a File]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/file-handling-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/file-handling-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T15:42:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn how to open a file, write to the file, and close it. You will also learn how to read from the file using Python.  By the end of this tutorial, you should know the basics of how to use files in Python. File]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Fagbuyiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn Serverless AWS by Building 7 Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-serverless-aws-by-building-7-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-serverless-aws-by-building-7-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T15:34:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following tutorials when you start learning serverless is a good first step. But to really get better, you need to build your own projects.  The problem is that coming up with ideas that are realistic but help you grow is hard. To help you out, I’ve come up with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Grid Named Areas to Visualize (and Reference) Your Layout]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372634</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-grid-named-areas-to-visualize-and-reference-your-layout/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T13:44:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whenever we build simple or complex layouts using CSS Grid, we’re usually positioning items with line numbers. Grid layouts contain grid lines that are automatically indexed with positive and negative line numbers (that is unless we explicitly name them). …
Using Grid Named Areas to Visualize (and Reference) Your Layout originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi Selvam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Relational Database? RDBMS Definition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-relational-database-rdbms-definition/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-relational-database-rdbms-definition/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T22:51:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A relational database is a type of database that stores data in tables made up of rows and columns. Each table represents a specific object in the database like users, products, orders, and so on.  The term "relational" is the main characteristic feature that makes relational databases unique. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Better Error Messages UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/error-messages-ux-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/error-messages-ux-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Error messages need to be easy to spot, but they also need to be helpful. Let’s explore when error messages should live above input fields and why toast error messages are usually not a very good idea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Sure How to WordPress Anymore?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372616</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/not-sure-how-to-wordpress-anymore/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T14:34:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neither do I! And that’s probably because there’s a lot happening in WordPress-land. The evolution towards full-site editing (FSE) introduces frequent changes to the way we build themes and plugins, and at such break-neck speed that the documentation itself is …
Not Sure How to WordPress Anymore? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Games with LÖVE 2D and Lua]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-games-with-love-2d-and-lua/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-games-with-love-2d-and-lua/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T13:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Lua programming language is becoming increasingly popular for game development. And the LÖVE 2D game engine makes it simpler to create games using Lua.  We just published a full 11-hour game development course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create games using LÖVE]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Video Streaming With imgix]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/better-video-streaming-with-imgix/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/better-video-streaming-with-imgix/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you need to deliver a large number of images and videos, a solution like [imgix](https://imgix.com/?utm_medium=banner&utm_source=smashingmag&utm_campaign=video-api-smashingmag-article-2022-08) can optimize and process both types of assets without you having to build it from the ground up or cobble together different solutions. Let’s take a closer look at how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Doug Sillars)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Dual Boot Windows 10 and Ubuntu – Linux Dual Booting Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-dual-boot-windows-10-and-ubuntu-linux-dual-booting-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-dual-boot-windows-10-and-ubuntu-linux-dual-booting-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T20:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You don’t have to have two different computers to use Linux and Windows 10. It's possible to have a Linux distro installed on a computer with Windows 10 preinstalled. In this article, I will show you how to dual boot Windows 10 and the popular Ubuntu Linux distro. But before]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Python Concepts to Know Before Learning Data Science]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/top-python-concepts-for-data-science/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/top-python-concepts-for-data-science/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T17:53:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're interested in learning data science, you've likely heard the buzzword  "Python,". It's a popular programming language often used in data science.  But Python is a general-purpose programming language. This means that it's not limited to data science alone. You can use it to develop web and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ibrahim Abayomi Ogunbiyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend Web Developer 21-Hour Bootcamp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/frontend-web-developer-bootcamp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/frontend-web-developer-bootcamp/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T17:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a lot of jobs available for frontend web developers. And you can learn all the skills you need to know without paying anything. You probably already know about freeCodeCamp's free interactive curriculum [https://freecodecamp.org] that will teach you the skills you need to become a fullstack web developer. But]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Date Format – How to Format a Date in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-date-format-how-to-format-a-date-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-date-format-how-to-format-a-date-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T15:25:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is one of the three fundamental web technologies you'll use when developing websites or web applications. When creating these web pages, you will, at some point, likely need to use dates for some reason – such as displaying when something was uploaded, stored, and so on. In this article,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an OTP Input in Vue 3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-otp-input-vue-3/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-otp-input-vue-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T15:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OTP inputs are one of the most fun components you can use in your app. They make the dry process of filling in yet another form a little more engaging. In this article, you’ll learn how to build an OTP input from scratch in Vue 3. By the end of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Akinyemi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using CSS Cascade Layers to Manage Custom Styles in a Tailwind Project]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372576</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-css-cascade-layers-to-manage-custom-styles-in-a-tailwind-project/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T13:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If a utility class only does one thing, chances are you don’t want it to be overridden by any styles coming from elsewhere. One approach is to use !important to be 100% certain the style will be applied, regardless of …
Using CSS Cascade Layers to Manage Custom Styles in a Tailwind Project originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Linux Utilities to Improve Your Programming Workflow in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/5-linux-utilities-for-better-programming-workflow/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/5-linux-utilities-for-better-programming-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T11:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working as a Software Developer, there are always new tools and frameworks coming out that can completely change your workflows – for the better (or worse?).  Either way, there is always the possibility to optimize how you do things day-to-day. This article contains some Linux utilities that have recently]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rishabh Rawat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.gitignore File – How to Ignore Files and Folders in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gitignore-file-how-to-ignore-files-and-folders-in-git/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gitignore-file-how-to-ignore-files-and-folders-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T16:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a popular version control system. It is how developers can collaborate and work together on projects. Git allows you to track the changes you make to your project over time. On top of that, it lets you revert to a previous version if you want to undo a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Python in Power BI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-in-powerbi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-in-powerbi/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T16:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Power BI is a business analytics tool which allows users to gain insight from their data.  You can easily create an interactive dashboard by just dragging and dropping data columns into the visualization plane. In this article, I'll show you how to use Python to help you leverage]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yannawut Kimnaruk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chart.js Tutorial – How to Make Bar and Line Charts in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-bar-and-line-charts-using-chartjs-in-angular/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-bar-and-line-charts-using-chartjs-in-angular/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T15:35:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial we will learn how to create simple bar and line charts using the Chart.js library in an Angular application. But first of all, what is Chart.js and what does it do? What is Chart.js? Chart.js is a JavaScript library for building charts. It's designed to be intuitive]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Swatej Patil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Arrays.binarySearch() in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-arrays-binarysearch-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-arrays-binarysearch-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T15:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'm going to show you how to use the Arrays.binarySearch()  method in Java. What is Arrays.binarySearch() in Java?  According to the official docs [https://docs.oracle.com/javase/7/docs/api/java/util/Arrays.html#binarySearch(byte[],%20byte)]  on the Arrays.binarySearch() method: > (It) Searches the specified array of bytes for the specified value using the binary search]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farhan Hasin Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Override Root Font Size to Create a Better User Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/override-root-font-size-for-a-better-user-experience/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/override-root-font-size-for-a-better-user-experience/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T15:14:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in the day, web developers, front-end engineers, and UI designers had a bit of an easier job. This is because they weren't expected to rearrange their code and designs to fit so many different screen sizes.  But in today's world, if you make a decision that doesn't take]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damla Erkiner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Removing jQuery from GOV.UK]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372485</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/removing-jquery-from-gov-uk/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T13:04:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GOV.UK team recently published “How and why we removed jQuery from GOV.UK“. This was an insightful look at how an organization can assess its tooling and whether something is still the best tool for the job. This …
Removing jQuery from GOV.UK originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Kouchi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 51 With Ben Callahan: What’s The Value Of A Design System?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/smashing-podcast-episode-51/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/smashing-podcast-episode-51/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we ask how you can prove the value of a Design System and how you can pitch it effectively to stakeholders. Vitaly talks to Ben Callahan to find out more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Markdown Cheat Sheet – How to Write Articles in Markdown Language]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/markdown-cheatsheet/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/markdown-cheatsheet/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T22:16:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a developer, you have likely heard of HTML [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTML], which stands for HyperText Markup L anguage. And you may know that HTML is a language used to create websites – but what does  markup mean? Markup languages [https://techterms.com/definition/markup_language] are languages that use tags to define different elements within]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kealan Parr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Generate WordPress Posts Automatically with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-generate-wordpress-posts-automatically/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-generate-wordpress-posts-automatically/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T20:55:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you run a website, you are aware of the importance of content. It's important for your web presence, to help you be recognized as a leader in your field, to improve your SEO ranking, to increase your audience, and more. WordPress is one of the most popular and widely-used]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Venturi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Round to 2 Decimal Places in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-round-to-2-decimal-places-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-round-to-2-decimal-places-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T17:17:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python provides many math methods for mathematical operations such as square roots, exponents, and so on. In this article, I will show you how to round up a number to a specified decimal place. What is a Decimal Place? Look at this number: 324.89. Each number here has a position]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize Your Node.js API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-optimize-nodejs-apis/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-optimize-nodejs-apis/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T17:16:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will walk you through some of the best methods to optimize APIs written in Node.js. Prerequisites To get the most out of this article, you will need an understanding of the following concepts:  * Node.js setup and installation  * How to build APIs with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kayode Adeniyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming Naming Conventions – Camel, Snake, Kebab, and Pascal Case Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/programming-naming-conventions-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/programming-naming-conventions-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T15:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've been programming for a while, you may have heard the words "camel case" or "pascal case". And maybe you're wondering what those terms mean. Well, let me explain. What are Naming Conventions in Programming? Apart from the hard and fast rules that we get with every programming language,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farhan Hasin Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Developer Certification (AZ-204) – Pass the Exam With This Free 13.5-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/azure-developer-certification-az-204-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-13-5-hour-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/azure-developer-certification-az-204-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-13-5-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T14:51:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can learn everything you need to know to earn the Azure Developer Certification by completing this free 13-hour course. What is Microsoft Azure Developer Associate? The Microsoft Azure Developer Associate (commonly known as the AZ-204) is a Microsoft Azure certification focused on building web-applications on-top of Azure cloud services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Brown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Grid and Custom Shapes, Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372396</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-grid-and-custom-shapes-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T14:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alright, so the last time we checked in, we were using CSS Grid and combining them with CSS clip-path and mask techniques to create grids with fancy shapes.
Here’s just one of the fantastic grids we made together:
CodePen…
CSS Grid and Custom Shapes, Part 2 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Makes A Great Toggle Button? (Case Study, Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/toggle-button-case-study-part-1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/toggle-button-case-study-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this first part of a two-part article, Eduard Kuric analyzes the characteristics of effective toggle buttons that make it error-proof and prevent confusion and frustration of users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eduard Kuric)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement a GameKit Leaderboard in SwiftUI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-a-leaderboard-in-swiftui/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-a-leaderboard-in-swiftui/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T21:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article we will talk about why and how to implement the GameCenter's Leaderboard [https://developer.apple.com/design/human-interface-guidelines/technologies/game-center/leaderboards/]  within your app.  Why GameCenter is Making a Huge Revival You can make iPhone games without a scoreboard, but leaderboards can help make the game feel more competitive, like people are competing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saamer Mansoor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Graph Theory to Build a More Sustainable World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-value-of-graph-theory-within-sustainability/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-value-of-graph-theory-within-sustainability/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T20:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discrete mathematics is an area of mathematical knowledge based on the study of formal structures whose nature is fundamentally separate and distinct.  This means it focuses on integers and natural sets of numbers, shapes, and other objects that can be counted finitely or distinguished from one another. It models]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel García Solla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Refactor to Configurable Dependency in 5 Steps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/refactoring-to-configurable-dependency-in-5-steps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/refactoring-to-configurable-dependency-in-5-steps/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T20:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Configurable Dependency, also known as Dependency Injection, is a pattern that enables you to switch dependencies of your application. The term [https://web.archive.org/web/20170624023207/http://alistair.cockburn.us/Configurable+Dependency]  was coined by Alistair Cockburn. Say your application has a GUI. But your administrator wants to use certain functions via the console. Or your production code calls]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bertil Muth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Timestamp – How to Use getTime() to Generate Timestamps in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-timestamp-how-to-use-gettime-to-generate-timestamps-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-timestamp-how-to-use-gettime-to-generate-timestamps-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T17:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, timestamps are usually associated with Unix time [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Unix_time]. And there are different methods for generating such timestamps. When we make use of the different JavaScript methods for generating timestamps, they return the number of milliseconds that has passed since 1 January 1970 UTC (the Unix time).  In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing A Reset Password Feature With Next.js Dynamic Routes]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/implementing-reset-password-feature-nextjs-dynamic-routes/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/implementing-reset-password-feature-nextjs-dynamic-routes/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most users tend to forget their passwords, so create experiences that will always be valuable for people when they use your products. In this article, we’ll discuss how to implement a password-reset feature with Next.js dynamic routes while prioritizing the UX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Caleb Olojo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I Learned Speaking at VueConf US 2022 – Tech Conference Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-i-learned-speaking-at-vueconf-us/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-i-learned-speaking-at-vueconf-us/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T19:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year I had the honor of speaking at VueConf US 2022 [https://us.vuejs.org/]  and I thought I would share my experience.  Part of this article will cover my personal process, part will look at VueConf specifically, and the rest will be about the conference at large. I hope]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Austin Gil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Calculate Percentage in Excel – Formula for Percentages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-calculate-percentage-in-excel-formula-for-percentages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-calculate-percentage-in-excel-formula-for-percentages/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T17:44:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A percentage is a kind of fraction saying how many parts over 100 something is. In this article you will see in detail what a percentage is, and how to calculate a percentage in Excel. First, before diving into how it works in Excel, let's take a look at the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilenia Magoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Revert File – Reverting a File to a Previous Commit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-revert-file-reverting-a-file-to-a-previous-commit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-revert-file-reverting-a-file-to-a-previous-commit/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T15:39:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a version control system that helps teams and individuals track and record changes made to a file or an entire project. When working with Git, you often commit your changes and then push them to a remote repository. Suppose you have made a lot of commits and later]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discord Update Failed – How to Fix the Error on a Windows 10 PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/discord-update-failed-how-to-fix-the-error-on-a-windows-10-pc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/discord-update-failed-how-to-fix-the-error-on-a-windows-10-pc/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T15:31:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discord is a popular chat app for gamers and anyone else who wants to create an online community. Despite its popularity, one major problem users report about Discord is the update failed loop. Discord has to update often because the Discord team implements new features and bug fixes regularly. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Structural Directive Patterns – What They Are and How to Use Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/angular-structural-directive-patterns-what-they-are-and-how-to-use-them/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/angular-structural-directive-patterns-what-they-are-and-how-to-use-them/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T15:21:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two types of  directives in Angular. Attribute directives modify the appearance or behavior of DOM elements. Structural directives add or remove elements from the DOM. Structural directives are one of the most powerful features of Angular, and yet they’re frequently misunderstood.  If you’re interested in learning more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code Refactoring Best Practices – with Python Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-practices-for-refactoring-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-practices-for-refactoring-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T15:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will discuss what code refactoring is. We'll go over why you need to refactor your code, the advantages of code refactoring, and some best practices for code refactoring. What is Code Refactoring? Refactoring means organizing your code without modifying its original functionality. Refactoring is the process]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Fagbuyiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Flatten an Array in JavaScript Using Recursion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flatten-array-recursion/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flatten-array-recursion/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T15:11:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we'll go through a common coding problem that interviewers love to ask candidates. Hopefully this will help you understand how to think through it and solve it. Let's begin by understanding the problem. You are given an array which contains numbers and nested arrays of numbers. Your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adwaith KS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn C Programming Using the Classic Book by Kernighan and Ritchie]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-c-programming-classic-book-dr-chuck/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-c-programming-classic-book-dr-chuck/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T14:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dennis Ritchie created the C programming language. He also co-authored the authoritative reference book on C programming with Brian Kernighan. If you want to truly understand C programming, it is a good idea to go straight to the source. We just published a C programming course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Do You Use CSS Columns?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372539</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/when-do-you-use-css-columns/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T13:24:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That ain’t rhetorical: I’m really interested in finding great use cases for CSS multi-column layouts.
The answer seems straightforward. Use columns when you want to split any content into columns, right? Here is generally the sort of example you’ll find …
When Do You Use CSS Columns? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To Context Propagation In JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/react-context-propagation-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/react-context-propagation-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React popularized context-propagation within applications with the context API. Evyatar Alush brings a brief intro to context propagation in JavaScript and how you can build React Context yourself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Evyatar Alush)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freelance Project Management – 10 Tips to Help You Work with Clients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-trello-to-manage-freelance-web-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-trello-to-manage-freelance-web-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T20:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've recently wrapped up a freelance client website using Trello [https://trello.com/] for project management.  I've wasted hours on projects in the past due to a lack of organization, processes, and general good practices. So this time I wanted to sharpen my project management skills in a way that would]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Computer Scientist? What Exactly Do CS Majors Do?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-computer-scientist-what-exactly-do-cs-majors-do/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-computer-scientist-what-exactly-do-cs-majors-do/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T16:49:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computer Science is one of the most popular STEM majors. STEM stands for Science Technology Engineering and Mathematics. Computer Science is popular because it offers promising and diverse job prospects in several industries, along with job security and a generally comfortable starting salary. Now, you may be wondering what Computer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run Android Games on Linux with Android-x86]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/run-android-games-on-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/run-android-games-on-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T16:09:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll learn how you can use virtual machines on Linux while having fun with vintage games. If you have an Android phone, one of your guilty pleasures might be playing some very entertaining games. Or it could be that there is an application that only runs on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why (and How) I Write Code With Pencil and Paper]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=367045</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/why-and-how-i-write-code-with-pencil-and-paper/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T13:21:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If the thought of handwriting code seems silly, it might surprise you to know that it’s inevitable. If you’re unsure, think about the last job interview you did, and remember how there was no computer around in the interview room …
Why (and How) I Write Code With Pencil and Paper originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Open Source? How to Contribute to OSS Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-open-source-software/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-open-source-software/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T20:23:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll talk about open source software. Open source software is often considered free software.  In this article, I'll give a high-level explanation of what open source software (OSS) really is, its advantages in the modern technological world, how to use it, and some best practices to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Destiny Erhabor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Image Centering – How to Center an Image in a Div]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-center-an-image-in-a-div-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-center-an-image-in-a-div-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T19:32:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working on the front-end of a web page, you sometimes need to center an image within a div (container). This can become tricky at times. And based on certain conditions, a particular method may not work at some point, leaving you searching for alternatives. In this article, you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Regular Expressions in JavaScript – Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/regular-expressions-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/regular-expressions-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T17:51:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regular expressions (regex) are a useful programming tool. They are key to efficient text processing. Knowing how to solve problems using regex is helpful to you as a developer and improves your productivity.  In this article, you will learn about the fundamentals of regular expressions, regular expression pattern notation,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chinwendu Enyinna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP vs HTTPS – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/http-vs-https/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/http-vs-https/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T17:47:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We interact with HTTP and HTTPS a lot in our day-to-day lives, but many people don't know the difference. Most computer users just see that the browser is telling them their application is not safe and that a hacker might want to steal their important information. This leads to users]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Annoh Karlgusta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Delete Remote Branch – How to Remove a Remote Branch in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-delete-remote-branch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-delete-remote-branch/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T17:20:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with Git, you might want to delete remote branches pushed to a platform like GitHub for various reasons. In this article, I will show you how to delete a remote branch in Git. But firstly, let’s look at how to delete a local branch. I’ll use Git]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing A Better Back Button UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/back-button-ux-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/back-button-ux-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the “Back” button, users often get confused and frustrated. How to design a better back button UX and where to put those “Back” buttons in our interfaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve AWS Performance Without Spending More Money]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-aws-performance-without-spending-more-money/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-aws-performance-without-spending-more-money/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T21:50:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Identifying performance issues has always been the holy grail of engineering. You want to be known as the software engineer who's able to diagnose and rectify the performance issue that came up in production. It really adds credibility to your engineering chops. We had an issue at work recently that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaid Humayun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Upgrade Postgres Major Versions with Near-Zero Downtime – a Practical Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-upgrade-postgres-major-versions-with-near-zero-downtime/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-upgrade-postgres-major-versions-with-near-zero-downtime/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T21:42:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's impossible to create zero-downtime Postgres upgrades across major versions – right? Please, correct me if I’m wrong :)  But at least we’ve found a way to get close to zero downtime.  * PostgreSQL Upgrades are hard!    [https://andreas.scherbaum.la/blog/archives/1116-PostgreSQL-Upgrades-are-hard!.html]  * How Retool upgraded our 4]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wenbin Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn JavaScript Basics by Building a Counter Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-by-building-a-project/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-by-building-a-project/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T20:31:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript allows you to make dynamic web sites. It's the final part of the web development trinity with HTML and CSS, and you use it to make your static pages dynamic. You'll likely start learning JavaScript as soon as you've covered the basics of HTML and CSS. Then, after some]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spruce Emmanuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My First Year as a Professional Developer – Tips for Getting into Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/my-first-year-as-a-professional-developer-tips-for-getting-into-tech/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/my-first-year-as-a-professional-developer-tips-for-getting-into-tech/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T20:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article I'll share my thoughts on my first year of professional experience as a software developer. It's almost been two years since I got into coding and a year since I became a full-time dev.  I started writing this article merely as a self-reflection exercise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Stardew Valley Using Python and Pygame]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-stardew-valley-using-python-and-pygame/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-stardew-valley-using-python-and-pygame/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T18:09:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stardew Valley is a popular open-ended country-life RPG video game. But instead of just playing the game, why not code your own version of the game? We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create a Stardew Valley game clone using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does a Software Developer Do? Software Engineer Career Overview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-a-software-developer-do-software-engineer-career-overview/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-a-software-developer-do-software-engineer-career-overview/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T14:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're studying to become a professional software developer, you might be wondering what a software developer does everyday on the job. In this article, I will talk about the typical day of a software developer and what to expect on the job.  Main Responsibilities of a Software Developer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Grid and Custom Shapes, Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=367324</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-grid-and-custom-shapes-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T13:13:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous article, I looked at CSS Grid’s ability to create complex layouts using its auto-placement powers. I took that one step further in another article that added a zooming hover effect to images in a grid layout…
CSS Grid and Custom Shapes, Part 1 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything Developers Must Know About Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/everything-developers-must-know-about-figma/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/everything-developers-must-know-about-figma/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Christine highlights some of Figma’s features and possibilities to help you build a design that aligns with code as much as needed and improve your team work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Christine Vallaure)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Java Hashmap?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-java-hashmap/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-java-hashmap/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-12T20:53:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Java, you use a HashMap to store items in key/value pairs. You can access items stored in a HashMap using the item's key, which is unique for each item.  In this article, we'll talk about the features of a HashMap, how to create a  HashMap, and the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Sieve Of Eratosthenes Algorithm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sieve-of-eratosthenes-algorithm/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sieve-of-eratosthenes-algorithm/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-12T18:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One day, while learning algorithms in JavaScript, I found this challenge: > Using a for loop, iterate from 0 to 100, and return an array of all prime numbers within that range. It seemed easy initially, but I couldn't quite figure it out. So I did a google search and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Divine Orji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Google like a Pro – 10 Tips for More Effective Googling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-google-like-a-pro-10-tips-for-effective-googling/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-google-like-a-pro-10-tips-for-effective-googling/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-12T18:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pretty much everything is available on the internet, and Google is one of the main ways people search for information. And while you might think it's obvious, many internet users don't know how to use Google search efficiently and effectively. In truth, Googling is an art. To get the right]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soham De Roy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML New Line – How to Add a Line Break with the BR Tag]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-new-line-how-to-add-a-line-break-with-the-br-tag/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-new-line-how-to-add-a-line-break-with-the-br-tag/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-12T18:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll explain what line breaks are and show you how to create them in HTML. What is a Line Break? A line break, as the name implies, is a break in line 😅. A line break in HTML is a point where a line ends horizontally, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sense Walkthrough – HackTheBox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sense-walkthrough-hackthebox/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sense-walkthrough-hackthebox/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-12T16:09:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HackTheBox is an online hacking platform that allows you to test and practice your penetration testing skills.  It contains several vulnerable labs that are constantly updated. Some of them simulate real-world scenarios and some of them lean more towards a Capture The Flag (CTF) style of challenge. Note: Only]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shuaib Oseni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Skeleton: Svelte + Tailwind For Reactive UIs]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/skeleton-svelte-tailwind-reactive-uis/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/skeleton-svelte-tailwind-reactive-uis/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The power of framework-specific UI libraries, such as Skeleton, can lead to more productivity using the combined ability of Svelte and Tailwind to build modern web-based apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Chris Simmons)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVM for Windows – How to Download and Install Node Version Manager in Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nvm-for-windows-how-to-download-and-install-node-version-manager-in-windows-10/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nvm-for-windows-how-to-download-and-install-node-version-manager-in-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T16:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Different software development tools might require specific versions of Node.js and NPM (Node Package Manager). NPM is a tool for managing packages installed from the NPM registry. In addition, if you are making an NPM package, you might need to test it with different versions of Node.js. This is why]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implement Event-Driven Architecture with React and FastAPI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/implement-event-driven-architecture-with-react-and-fastapi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/implement-event-driven-architecture-with-react-and-fastapi/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T14:38:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An event driven system is a common way to setup software. In event-driven architecture, event-handlers are registered for specific events. When an event occurs, the handlers are invoked. A great way to understand this concept is to build a project. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Tip: Clear VS Code Cache for Open Files]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=367403</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/quick-tip-clear-vs-code-cache-for-open-files/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T13:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you use VS Code, you might have enabled the setting for re-opening a previously open file next time the app launches. I do. I like that.
Hey, thanks for remembering, buddy! 🤗
But sometimes you really, really don’t want …
Quick Tip: Clear VS Code Cache for Open Files originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Databases For Front-End Developers: The Rise Of Serverless Databases (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/databases-frontend-developers-rise-serverless-databases/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/databases-frontend-developers-rise-serverless-databases/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, the first part of “Databases for Front-end Developers” series, Atila Fassina helps you understand the concepts behind database architecture in order to use them reliably and sheds some light on serverless databases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[... in JavaScript – the Three Dots Operator in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/three-dots-operator-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/three-dots-operator-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T23:38:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The three dots operator in JavaScript is one of the significant updates that was shipped with ES6. This operator (...) helps you achieve many things that previously required many lines of code, unfamiliar syntax, and more. In this short article, you will learn what the three dots operator means and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2D Array in Java – Two-Dimensional and Nested Arrays]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/2d-array-in-java-two-dimensional-and-nested-arrays/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/2d-array-in-java-two-dimensional-and-nested-arrays/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T20:49:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A multidimensional array is simply an array [/news/java-array-how-to-declare-and-initialize-an-array-in-java-example/] of arrays. You can look it as a single container that stores multiple containers.  In this article, we'll talk two dimensional arrays in Java. You'll see the syntax for creating one, and how to add and access items in a two]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Real-time Chat Application with Nuxt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-real-time-chat-application-with-nuxt/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-real-time-chat-application-with-nuxt/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T19:39:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a real-time chat application, the recipient can view the sender’s message almost immediately. This can either be in a one-on-one conversation between two parties or a group conversation.  And that's what we're going to build in this tutorial. For this application, we will be using Nuxt [https://nuxtjs.org/], the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Idorenyin Udoh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn HTML and CSS by Building an Order Summary Component]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-html-and-css-order-summary-component/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-html-and-css-order-summary-component/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T17:26:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML and CSS are the most important technologies when it comes to creating websites. And building projects is one of the best ways to learn them. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you learn HTML and CSS through building an order summary component.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Docker Engine-like Custom Container without Any Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-your-on-custom-container-without-docker/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-your-on-custom-container-without-docker/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T16:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article will discuss every aspect of containers, including how they operate in the background and their various component elements. We will also discover why Docker is so lightning-fast. By the end, you'll be able to create your own custom container. We'll also examine why Kubernetes deprecated Docker and embraced]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gursimar Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Multiline String – How to Create Multi Line Strings in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-multiline-string-how-to-create-multi-line-strings-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-multiline-string-how-to-create-multi-line-strings-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T15:54:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn three different ways to create multi-line strings in JavaScript. I will first explain the basics of strings in JavaScript and go over how to use template literals. Then, you will learn how to create a string that spans multiple lines with the help of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create and Validate Modern Web Forms with HTML5]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-and-validate-modern-web-forms-html5/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-and-validate-modern-web-forms-html5/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T15:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML forms consist of a body of text boxes, buttons, dropdowns and other selection widgets. Web developers use these elements to receive users' information on a website.  If you've ever searched on Google, signed up or logged into a website, made a payment, or responded to a questionnaire, you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ophy Boamah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Array Methods – How to Use every() and some() in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-every-and-some-array-methods-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-every-and-some-array-methods-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T15:23:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, every and some help you test if something is true for every element or some elements of an array. In this article, I'll show you how to use these helpful array methods. Table of Contents  * 1How every() and some() Work – an Overview  * 2Parameters]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Biswas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing for Long-Form Articles]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=367370</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/designing-for-long-form-articles/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T14:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Designing a beautiful “article” is wrought with tons of considerations. Unlike, say, a homepage, a long-form article is less about designing an interface than it is designing text in a way that creates a relaxed and comfortable reading experience.
That’s …
Designing for Long-Form Articles originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Share Links that Anchor to Any Text on a Webpage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-you-can-share-links-that-anchor-to-any-text-on-a-webpage/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-you-can-share-links-that-anchor-to-any-text-on-a-webpage/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T19:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that there's an unofficial draft [https://wicg.github.io/scroll-to-text-fragment/] specification for a feature that would allow arbitrary text to be passed to the fragment (#) of a URL?  This would allow users to share links that point to any particular text on a webpage! What's a URI fragment? The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Falco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Scraping in Python – How to Scrape Sci-Fi Movies from IMDB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-scraping-sci-fi-movies-from-imdb-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-scraping-sci-fi-movies-from-imdb-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T19:50:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever struggled to find a dataset for your data science project? If you're like I am, the answer is yes.  Luckily, there are many free datasets available – but sometimes you want something more specific or bespoke. For that, web scraping is a good skill to have]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Riley Predum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Recursion in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-recursion-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-recursion-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T18:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you'll need to print records from an array, but the array is too big and nested.  Let's say we have a family tree, or a folder structure. We have multiple arrays nested inside arrays, and it goes on and on. It's so big and deep that it's not]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nishant Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Command Line Commands – CLI Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/command-line-commands-cli-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/command-line-commands-cli-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T15:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Windows command line is one of the most powerful utilities on a Windows PC. With it, you can interact with the OS directly and do a lot of things not available in the graphical user interface (GUI). In this article, I’ll show you 40 commands you can use on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Core Web Vitals Tools To Boost Your Web Performance Scores]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/core-web-vitals-tools-boost-performance/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/core-web-vitals-tools-boost-performance/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Identify, compare, analyze and fix your Core Web Vitals scores to boost web performance of your sites. These tools will help you to do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Committing CSS Crimes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=367369</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/committing-css-crimes/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T13:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The time for CSS-Tricks is over. Now is the time for CSS Crimes!
In this current landscape of content service providers, users are often limited to expressing themselves in text, links, and images. Sanitization rules tend to strip out HTML, …
Committing CSS Crimes originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Kouchi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Python Programming Course [2022]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-programming-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-programming-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T12:54:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python is considered one of the most popular programming languages in the world and it is only growing in popularity. It's a great first language to learn. We just released an all-new Python programming course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. My name is Beau Carnes and I created this course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 50 With Marko Dugonjic: Can You Change A UX Dinosaur?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/smashing-podcast-episode-50/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/smashing-podcast-episode-50/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we ask how you can affect change to UX design in large organizations stuck in their ways. Vitaly talks to Marko Dugonjić to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Callback Function in JavaScript? JS Callbacks Example Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-callback-function-in-javascript-js-callbacks-example-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-callback-function-in-javascript-js-callbacks-example-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T00:32:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript there are higher order methods and functions that accept a function as an argument. These functions used as arguments for other functions are called callback functions. What is a callback in JavaScript? A callback is a function passed as an argument of another function. This means that the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilenia Magoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux `Vimdiff` Command – How to Compare Two Files in the Command Line]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/compare-two-files-in-linux-using-vim/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/compare-two-files-in-linux-using-vim/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T20:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software development and maintenance can get complicated sometimes. And you might find yourself comparing code or configuration changes.  When you compare them manually, you might make a mistake, and it's easy to miss minute changes. Apart from that, finding changes in large files can be exhausting.  There are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Git for the First Time on macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/setup-git-on-mac/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/setup-git-on-mac/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T20:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're setting up Git for the first time on a MacBook, you don't have to struggle to get it done. Maybe you just got a new laptop, or you're getting into tech for the first time with a MacBook. Either way, I've got you covered. This short article will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Style Guide in Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-style-guide-in-figma/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-style-guide-in-figma/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T14:35:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Style guides are important to help you deliver a consistent brand experience.  As a UI/UX designer, creating style guides is indispensable if you hope to create great user experiences and interfaces.  In this article, you will learn what a style guide is, the importance of a style guide,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typeerror: str object is not callable – How to Fix in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typeerror-str-object-is-not-callable-how-to-fix-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typeerror-str-object-is-not-callable-how-to-fix-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T14:21:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every programming language has certain keywords with specific, prebuilt functionalities and meanings.  Naming your variables or functions after these keywords is most likely going to raise an error. We'll discuss one of these cases in this article — the  TypeError: 'str' object is not callable error in Python.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zooming Images in a Grid Layout]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=367204</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/zooming-images-in-a-grid-layout/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T12:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a grid of images is easy, thanks to CSS Grid. But making the grid do fancy things after the images have been placed can be tricky to pull off.
Say you want to add some fancy hover effect to …
Zooming Images in a Grid Layout originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Our Organization Improved Web Accessibility (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/organization-improved-web-accessibility-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/organization-improved-web-accessibility-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Catherine Houle and Ilknur Eren share how their organization “Understood” removes barriers for people who learn and think differently by combining accessibility and usability in their processes. They also cover basic steps on how to fix common accessibility issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Catherine Houle &amp; Ilknur Eren)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Node.js and Express in Spanish – Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-node-js-and-express-in-spanish-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-node-js-and-express-in-spanish-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T04:35:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi! If you speak Spanish and you want to learn Node.js, and Express, you are in the right place.  In this article, you will find a brief introduction to back-end web development, Node.js, and Express. You will learn why they are very powerful tools for developing web servers and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Best Practices – How to Write Meaningful Commits, Effective Pull Requests, and Code Reviews]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-best-practices-commits-and-code-reviews/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-best-practices-commits-and-code-reviews/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-05T15:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As developers we push regular code commits – and after a while, it's almost second nature to us.  But does this mean we're doing things right? Familiarity often leads to sloppiness and overlooking the basics. In this article, we will explore  * How to write meaningful Git commit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Weatherston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Switch Statement – Switch Case Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-switch-statement-switch-case-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-switch-statement-switch-case-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-05T15:27:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Until version 3.10, Python never had a feature that implemented what the switch statement does in other programming languages. So, if you wanted to execute multiple conditional statements, you would've had to use the elif keyword like this: age = 120 if age > 90:     print("You]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Added Scroll Snapping To My Twitter Timeline]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=367283</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-i-added-scroll-snapping-to-my-twitter-timeline/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-05T13:10:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Scroll Snap allows websites to snap the web page or any other scroll container to a specific scroll position when the user performs a scrolling operation. This feature has been supported in all modern browsers for over two years, …
How I Added Scroll Snapping To My Twitter Timeline originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Šime Vidas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Actually, the San Francisco Typeface Does Ship as a Variable Font]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=367361</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/actually-the-san-francisco-typeface-does-ship-as-a-variable-font/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T20:20:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple unveiled an expanded version of its San Francisco system font at WWDC 2022. Then, last month, Jim Nielsen zeroed in on the font’s variations, explaining how the font provides a spectrum of variations based on the width and weight…
Actually, the San Francisco Typeface Does Ship as a Variable Font originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Props Work in React – A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/beginners-guide-to-props-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/beginners-guide-to-props-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T17:31:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Props are used to store data that can be accessed by the children of a React component.  They are part of the concept of reusability. Props take the place of class attributes and allow you to create consistent interfaces across the component hierarchy. In this article, we'll learn about]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oyedele Temitope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Blazor App with Syncfusion UI Components]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-blazor-app-with-syncfusion-ui-components/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-blazor-app-with-syncfusion-ui-components/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T17:04:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Syncfusion provides a UI component suite for building powerful web, desktop, and mobile apps. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to harness the power of the Syncfusion UI components from within a Blazor server application. You'll also learn to integrate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Real-time Chat App with React, Node, Socket.io, and HarperDB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-realtime-chat-app-with-react-express-socketio-and-harperdb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-realtime-chat-app-with-react-express-socketio-and-harperdb/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T15:53:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will be using Socket.io and HarperDB to build a fullstack, real-time chat application with chat rooms.  This will be a great project to learn how to put together fullstack apps, and how to create an app where the backend can communicate with the frontend in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Font Size – How to Change Text Size with an HTML Tag]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-change-text-size-in-html/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-change-text-size-in-html/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T14:52:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you add text to your HTML file with an HTML tag, you won't always want the text to remain the default size. You'll want to be able to adjust how the text displays in the browser. In this article, you will learn how to change the text size with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rethinking Authentication UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/authentication-ux-design-guidelines/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/authentication-ux-design-guidelines/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to improve authentication UX, with magic links, 2FA, better password recovery and relaxed rules for secure, accessible and usable passwords.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Converting Speech to PDF with NextJS and ExpressJS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=367238</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/converting-speech-to-pdf-with-nextjs-and-expressjs/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T12:55:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With speech interfaces becoming more of a thing, it’s worth exploring some of the things we can do with speech interactions. Like, what if we could say something and have that transcribed and pumped out as a downloadable PDF?
Well, …
Converting Speech to PDF with NextJS and ExpressJS originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Onuorah Bonaventure Chukwudi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[List Index Out of Range – Python Error [Solved]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/list-index-out-of-range-python-error-solved/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/list-index-out-of-range-python-error-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T22:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll talk about the IndexError: list index out of range error in Python.  In each section of the article, I'll highlight a possible cause for the error and how to fix it. You may get the IndexError: list index out of range error for the following]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Redux-Powered React App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-redux-powered-react-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-redux-powered-react-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T21:51:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Problem We're Solving In many cases when we want to create a small application, we might have some components that declare and use their own state. And in a few cases, a component might want to share the state with its immediate children. We can handle these situations just]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soham De Roy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Random Number – How to Generate a Random Number in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-random-number-how-to-generate-a-random-number-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-random-number-how-to-generate-a-random-number-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T19:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with a JavaScript program, there may be times when you will need to generate a random number. For example, you may want to generate a random number when developing a JavaScript game, such as a number guessing game. JavaScript has many built-in methods for working with numbers and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Sheets Tutorial – How to Use Regex and VLOOKUP to Display Images from Google Drive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-sheets-use-regex-and-vlookup-to-display-images-from-google-drive/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-sheets-use-regex-and-vlookup-to-display-images-from-google-drive/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T17:03:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images make many things better. And Google Sheets is one of those things.  The easiest way to add an image to Google Sheets is to simply insert one into your sheet.  But if you have added many images this way, you'll quickly tire of the multiple clicks it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Coding Bootcamp – Learn to Code with Class Central + freeCodeCamp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-coding-bootcamp-learn-to-code-with-class-central-and-freecodecamp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-coding-bootcamp-learn-to-code-with-class-central-and-freecodecamp/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T16:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2021, the Class Central team helped my friend and me teach three cohorts of free programming bootcamps based on freeCodeCamp curricula.  We’ve been joined by over 20,000 learners from around the globe and it’s just been an honor and a delight to get to learn along with so]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Rose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Factorial? How to Calculate Factorials with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-factorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-factorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T16:32:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A factorial is a mathematical operation that you write like this: n!. It represents the multiplication of all numbers between 1 and n. So if you were to have 3!, for example, you'd compute 3 x 2 x 1 (which = 6). Let's see how it works with some more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilenia Magoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Page fault in nonpaged area – How to Fix the Error on a Windows 10 PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/page-fault-in-nonpaged-area-how-to-fix-the-error-on-a-windows-10-pc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/page-fault-in-nonpaged-area-how-to-fix-the-error-on-a-windows-10-pc/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T16:20:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Windows, the nonpaged area is the part of the memory that contains critical files your computer needs to function properly. Those critical files are stored in the nonpaged area so the RAM won’t switch them back and forth between itself and the paged area. Once there’s an issue with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Keep your Angular Data-Flow Tidy and Efficient]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-keep-your-angular-data-flow-tidy-and-efficient/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-keep-your-angular-data-flow-tidy-and-efficient/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T15:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developing large-scale Angular applications can feel like trying to ride a bicycle with your eyes closed and both hands tied behind your back.  The data flow in an Angular application can be extremely complex, especially when dealing with bidirectional data binding, asynchronous updates, forms, and routing.  The key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migration From jQuery to Next.js: A Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/migration-jquery-next-js-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/migration-jquery-next-js-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re going to walk through how to migrate your site from jQuery to [React](/category/React) with [Next.js](/category/next.js). This will help with performance and the maintainability of your code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sam Robbins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is PHP? How to Write Your First PHP Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-php-write-your-first-php-program/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-php-write-your-first-php-program/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn what the PHP programming language is and how to write your first program with it.  History of PHP PHP is the most used and popular scripting language generated for web development. You can embed it in HTML documents. PHP is written in the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Read a JSON File in JavaScript – Reading JSON in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-read-json-file-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-read-json-file-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T21:35:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When fetching data from external sources or servers, you need to make sure that the data returned is in JSON format. Then you can consume the data within your application. In some situations, when you're working locally or when you upload the data file to a server, we might want]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Rough Notation Library to Animate Your Website]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-animation-to-your-site-with-rough-notation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-animation-to-your-site-with-rough-notation/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T16:52:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love animating websites. It's so fun when you just look at a site, and there are cool animations that make everything look pretty.  Getting started with an animation library does not have to be hard. Anyone can add a bit of animation to their site regardless of whether]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Njong Emy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implicit Grids, Repeatable Layout Patterns, and Danglers]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=367158</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/implicit-grids-repeatable-layout-patterns-and-danglers/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T13:10:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dave Rupert with some modern CSS magic that tackles one of those classic conundrums: what happens when the CSS for component is unable to handle the content we throw at it?
The specific situation is when a layout grid expects …
Implicit Grids, Repeatable Layout Patterns, and Danglers originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Evaluation Metrics for Regression Problems in Machine Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/evaluation-metrics-for-regression-problems-machine-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/evaluation-metrics-for-regression-problems-machine-learning/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T14:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A regression problem is a common type of supervised learning problem in Machine Learning. The end goal is to predict quantitative values – for example, continuous values such as the price of a car, the weight of a dog, and so on.  But to be sure that your model]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ibrahim Abayomi Ogunbiyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create an Industry Level REST API Using .NET 6]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-an-industry-level-rest-api-using-net-6/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-an-industry-level-rest-api-using-net-6/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T14:21:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a lot of REST API tutorials out there but many of them do not teach you how to create production-ready code using industry best practices. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create a REST API using industry-level .NET]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>