<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-09-14T01:17:34.788Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lessons from freelancing for dozens of startups with Eddie Jaoude [Podcast #141]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/lessons-from-freelancing-for-dozens-of-startups-eddie-jaoude/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/lessons-from-freelancing-for-dozens-of-startups-eddie-jaoude/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T18:32:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews Eddie Jaoude who is a software engineer and open source creator. He's worked more than 15 years as a developer everywhere from Germany banking sector to London's tec...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two CSS Properties for Trimming Text Box Whitespace]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=380589</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/two-css-properties-for-trimming-text-box-whitespace/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T14:11:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The text-box-trim and text-box-edge properties in CSS enable developers to trim specifiable amounts of the whitespace that appear above the first formatted line of text and below the last formatted line of text in a text box, making the text …
Two CSS Properties for Trimming Text Box Whitespace originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Be a Productive Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-be-a-productive-developer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-be-a-productive-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T13:13:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are having trouble accomplishing as much as you want to accomplish, we have a course for you. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is designed to equip software developers with essential soft skills for boost...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Old is New]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=380692</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/whats-old-is-new-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T14:05:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I collect a bunch of links in a bookmarks folder. These are things I fully intend to read, and I do — eventually. It’s a good thing bookmarks are digital, otherwise, I’d need a bigger coffee table to separate them …
What’s Old is New originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Chart js for Interactive Data Visualization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-chart-js-for-interactive-data-visualization/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-chart-js-for-interactive-data-visualization/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T12:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data surrounds us, but its raw form can be overwhelming and difficult to interpret. That's where data visualization comes in. It can help you take your data and turn it into charts and graphs that make sense at a glance. Among the many data visualiza...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwadamisi Samuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Custom Data Visualizations Using Luzmo Flex]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/09/how-build-custom-data-visualizations-luzmo-flex/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/09/how-build-custom-data-visualizations-luzmo-flex/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing data to life in your application can be done without the usual headaches. Paul Scanlon shows you how you can build beautiful data visualizations using the Google Analytics API, and you won’t have to spend any time “massaging” the data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Music Production for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-music-production-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-music-production-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T20:08:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you interested in exploring the world of music production but don't know where to start? We just posted comprehensive course designed for beginners that will guide you through the process of creating music tracks in various styles using FL Studio...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Expense Tracker with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-expense-tracker-with-html-css-and-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-expense-tracker-with-html-css-and-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T17:25:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building projects is a great way to practice and improve your web development skills. And that's what we'll do in this in-depth tutorial: build a practical project using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. If you often find yourself wondering where all your m...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API Testing with Postman: A Step-by-Step Guide Using the Spotify API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/api-testing-with-postman-a-step-by-step-guide-using-the-spotify-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/api-testing-with-postman-a-step-by-step-guide-using-the-spotify-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T17:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🎯 The Objective In this guide, I’ll introduce you to Postman, a popular API development and testing tool. If you are a beginner mainly focused on frontend development, you may not have had much experience fetching data from an API. And in that case ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthes B.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Event Handling Works in Vue 3: A Guide for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-event-handling-works-in-vue-3-guide-for-devs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-event-handling-works-in-vue-3-guide-for-devs/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T17:21:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Event handling in Vue 3 allows developers to respond to user interactions like clicks, key presses, form submissions, and more. Vue provides simple and flexible ways to manage these interactions, enabling you to build dynamic and engaging application...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asfak Ahmed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Ways to Create Custom Translated Messaging for HTML Forms]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=380325</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/two-ways-to-create-custom-translated-messaging-for-html-forms/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T14:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML forms come with built-in ways to validate form inputs and other controls against predefined rules such as making an input required, setting min and max constraints on range sliders, or establishing a pattern on an email input to check …
Two Ways to Create Custom Translated Messaging for HTML Forms originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fatuma Abdullaho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pass the Azure AI Engineer Associate Certification (AI-102)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pass-the-azure-ai-engineer-associate-certification-ai-102/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pass-the-azure-ai-engineer-associate-certification-ai-102/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T18:45:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to take your AI skills to the next level and earn the Azure AI Engineer Associate Certification (AI-102)? We just posted a comprehensive course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is designed to help you prepare for and pass th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Hit #18]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=380660</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/quick-hit-18/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T18:40:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PSA: Today’s the day that Google’s performance tools officially stops supporting the First Input Delay (FID) metric that was replaced by Interaction to Next Paint (INP).…
Quick Hit #18 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anchor Positioning Quirks]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=380521</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/anchor-positioning-quirks/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T18:33:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am thrilled to say, that from this week onwards, the CSS-tricks Almanac has an entry for each property, function, and at-rule related to the new Anchor Positioning API! For the last month, I have tried to fully understand this …
Anchor Positioning Quirks originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Diego Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shodan – What to Know About the Internet’s Most Dangerous Search Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/shodan-what-to-know-about-the-internets-most-dangerous-search-engine/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/shodan-what-to-know-about-the-internets-most-dangerous-search-engine/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T17:43:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shodan is a search engine that discovers devices connected to the internet. In this article, we’ll look at why it’s both a valuable tool and a potential threat. When you hear the term “search engine,” your mind likely jumps to Google, Bing, or Yahoo....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AI Agents Can Help Supercharge Language Models – A Handbook for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-ai-agents-can-supercharge-language-models-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-ai-agents-can-supercharge-language-models-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T17:01:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rapid evolution of artificial intelligence (AI) has resulted in a powerful synergy between large language models (LLMs) and AI agents. This dynamic interplay is sort of like the tale of David and Goliath (without the fighting), where nimble AI ag...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sanding UI]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=380662</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/sanding-ui/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim hit a snag while working on a form. Placing labels next to inputs is trivial with flexbox, sure, but what happened in Jim’s case was a bit of dead-clicking between the labels and radio buttons.
The issue? Not the …
Sanding UI originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Anticipatory Design Isn’t Working For Businesses]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/09/why-anticipatory-design-not-working-businesses/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/09/why-anticipatory-design-not-working-businesses/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anticipatory design, powered by Artificial Intelligence (AI), Machine learning (ML), and Big Data (BD), promises to transform user experiences by predicting and fulfilling needs before users even express them. While this proactive approach seems revolutionary, many businesses struggle to meet the high expectations it sets. Joana Cerejo delves into the challenges of anticipatory design, highlights key failures, and offers a framework to help designers and businesses succeed in this complex landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joana Cerejo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time Travelling CSS With :target]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=380334</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/time-travelling-css-with-target/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T15:16:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Checkbox and radio button hacks are the (in)famous trick for creating games using just CSS. But it turns out that other elements based on user input can be hacked and gamified. There are very cool examples of developers getting creative with CSS games based on…
Time Travelling CSS With :target originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Meyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sticky Headers And Full-Height Elements: A Tricky Combination]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=380517</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/sticky-headers-and-full-height-elements-a-tricky-combination/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T14:09:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quite a fun article I worked on with Philip Braunen. Do you know that little bit of elasticity you get when scrolling beyond the viewport when browsing the web on a mobile device? iPhone calls it a “rubber-banding” effect. …
Sticky Headers And Full-Height Elements: A Tricky Combination originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Hit #17]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=380584</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/quick-hit-17/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T13:53:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Wrapping the <labelaround the <inputis fine, and is sufficient for conformance on its own, however adding explicit association with for and id is still necessary in practice.” —James Edwards…
Quick Hit #17 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Diego Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create A Weekly Google Analytics Report That Posts To Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/09/how-create-weekly-google-analytics-report-posts-slack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/09/how-create-weekly-google-analytics-report-posts-slack/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Analytics is often on a “need to know” basis, but why not flip the script? Paul Scanlon shares how he wrote a GitHub Action that queries Google Analytics to automatically generate and post a top ten page views report to Slack, making it incredibly easy to track page performance and share insights with your team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Hit #16]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=380340</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/quick-hit-16/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T16:04:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Never, ever hire for JavaScript framework skills. Instead, interview and hire only for fundamentals like web standards, accessibility, modern CSS, semantic HTML, and Web Components.” — Alex Russell…
Quick Hit #16 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Hit #15]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=380298</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/quick-hit-15/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T16:02:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost missed that the WP Twenty Twenty-Five theme was approved a couple weeks ago.…
Quick Hit #15 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sticky Headers And Full-Height Elements: A Tricky Combination]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/09/sticky-headers-full-height-elements-tricky-combination/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/09/sticky-headers-full-height-elements-tricky-combination/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sticky positioning is one of those CSS features that’s pretty delicate and can be negated by a lot of things, so here’s another one to add to your mental catalog: Sticky elements don’t play nicely if they have to coordinate with other elements to make up a combined height, like `100vh`. Philip Braunen explores why this happens and presents a solution to fix it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Philip Braunen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Hit #14]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=380296</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/quick-hit-14/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T19:08:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inclusive Design 24 is in 8 short days — and it’s FREE, no sign-up required!…
Quick Hit #14 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Stab at Truncated Text]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=380214</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/another-stab-at-truncated-text/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T15:57:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seems like we’re always talking about clipping text around here. All it takes is a little browsing to spot a bunch of things we’ve already explored.
    
        Article

    on
    Sep 19, 2012  
    

      accessibility content truncation    
    

    
…
Another Stab at Truncated Text originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Big Difference Between Digital Product And Web Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/09/big-difference-between-digital-product-and-web-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/09/big-difference-between-digital-product-and-web-design/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Designing for digital products requires a different mindset than traditional websites. It’s all about continuous adaptation, refining, and iterating as user behavior and needs evolve. Paul Boag reflects on the key differences, including how the frequency of usage impacts your design approach and what you can do about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goodbye Summer, Hello September (2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/08/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-september-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/08/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-september-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s get ready for September with a fresh collection of desktop wallpapers! Created with love by the community for the community, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSSWG Minutes Telecon (2024-08-21)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=380227</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/csswg-minutes-telecon-2024-08-21/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T19:06:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View Transitions are one of the most awesome features CSS has shipped in recent times. Its title is self-explanatory: transitions between views are possible with just CSS, even across pages of the same origin! What’s more interesting is its …
CSSWG Minutes Telecon (2024-08-21) originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Diego Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paragraphs]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=380206</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/paragraphs/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T14:23:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I sure do love little reminders about HTML semantics, particularly semantics that are tougher to commit to memory. Scott has a great one, beginning with this markup:
<pI am a paragraph.</p<spanI am also a paragraph.</span<div
…
Paragraphs originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating Image-To-Text And Text-To-Speech Models (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/08/integrating-image-to-text-and-text-to-speech-models-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/08/integrating-image-to-text-and-text-to-speech-models-part2/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the second part of this series, Joas Pambou aims to build a more advanced version of the previous application that performs conversational analyses on images or videos, much like a chatbot assistant. This means you can ask and learn more about your input content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generating Unique Random Numbers In JavaScript Using Sets]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/08/generating-unique-random-numbers-javascript-using-sets/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/08/generating-unique-random-numbers-javascript-using-sets/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to create more randomized effects in your JavaScript code? The `Math.random()` method alone, with its limitations, won’t cut it for generating unique random numbers. Amejimaobari Ollornwi explains how to generate a series of unique random numbers using the `Set` object, how to use these random numbers as indexes for arrays, and explores some practical applications of randomization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Amejimaobari Ollornwi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering Typography In Logo Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/08/mastering-typography-in-logo-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/08/mastering-typography-in-logo-design/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finding the right typeface for a logo is a challenge and can be a very time-consuming process that requires both creativity and a practical approach. Levi Honing provides the essential background and tools to enhance your typography journey and apply this knowledge to your logo design. Let’s dive deep to learn how to create a logo that is not only expressive but also purposeful and well-thought-out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Levi Honing)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regexes Got Good: The History And Future Of Regular Expressions In JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/08/history-future-regular-expressions-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/08/history-future-regular-expressions-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although JavaScript regexes used to be underpowered compared to other modern flavors, numerous improvements in recent years mean that’s no longer true. Steven Levithan evaluates the history and present state of regular expressions in JavaScript with tips to make your regexes more readable, maintainable, and resilient.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Steven Levithan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pricing Projects As A Freelancer Or Agency Owner]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/08/pricing-projects-freelancer-agency-owner/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/08/pricing-projects-freelancer-agency-owner/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover effective pricing strategies for digital projects. Learn how to balance fixed pricing, time and materials, and value-based approaches while managing client expectations and scope creep.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>