<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-07-16T01:05:06.546Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://osmoscraft.github.io/osmosfeed-demo/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use LINQ in C# – With Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-linq/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-linq/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T20:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.Net (pronounced as "dot net") has many internal libraries and tools, but one that wields great power is LINQ (Language Integrated Query). It can be used in two ways: the language-level query syntax, or the LINQ API. In this article, we'll explore:  * What LINQ is.  * How]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Riordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's the Difference Between the useMemo and useCallback Hooks?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/difference-between-usememo-and-usecallback-hooks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/difference-between-usememo-and-usecallback-hooks/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T19:14:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React provides various hooks that make it easier to manage application state and other React features in functional components. Hooks provide class component features to functional components, and they don't need a lot of code compared to class components. Hooks also make your life easier by providing some convenient features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up a CI/CD Pipeline with Husky and GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-a-ci-cd-pipeline-with-husky-and-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-a-ci-cd-pipeline-with-husky-and-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T17:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CI/CD is a core practice in the modern software development ecosystem. It helps agile teams deliver high-quality software in short release cycles. In this tutorial, you'll learn what CI/CD is, and I'll help you set up a CI/CD pipeline using Husky and GitHub Actions in a Next.js application.  This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Viviana Yanez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Selectors]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=378745</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-selectors/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T16:13:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A complete guide covering all of the various methods we have to select elements in CSS and how to use them for applying styles.
CSS Selectors originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Design Effective Conversational AI Experiences: A Comprehensive Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/07/how-design-effective-conversational-ai-experiences-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/07/how-design-effective-conversational-ai-experiences-guide/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This in-depth guide takes you through the three crucial phases of conversational search, revealing how users express their needs, explore results, and refine their queries. Learn how AI agents can overcome communication barriers, personalize the search experience, and adapt to evolving user intent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yinjian Huang)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Generics in Java – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/generics-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/generics-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T18:57:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In your Java program, you might have encountered the dreaded ClassCastException  at runtime while working with different types of objects such as Integer, String, and so on. This error is mostly caused by casting an object to the wrong data type. In this article, you'll learn about generics and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anjan Baradwaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From doing data entry to becoming a developer with Jessica Chan AKA Coder Coder [Podcast #132]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-doing-data-entry-to-becoming-a-developer-with-jessica-chan-aka-coder-coder-podcast-132/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-doing-data-entry-to-becoming-a-developer-with-jessica-chan-aka-coder-coder-podcast-132/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T16:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Jessica Chan AKA Coder Coder. She's a software engineer has worked in the field for more than a decade. Interestingly, she studied photography in school and never took a programming class. We talk ab...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Linux for Beginners: From Basics to Advanced Techniques [Full Book]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-linux-for-beginners-book-basic-to-advanced/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-linux-for-beginners-book-basic-to-advanced/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T13:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Linux is one of the most valuable skills in the tech industry. It can help you get things done faster and more efficiently. Many of the world's powerful servers and supercomputers run on Linux. While empowering you in your current role, lear...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the tRPC Library? Explained with a Demo Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-trpc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-trpc/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T19:09:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a while now, I've been noticing a technology named tRPC [https://trpc.io/]  that's cited in many modern tech stacks, including T3 [https://create.t3.gg/]. But I didn't know what it was or why it had become so popular. So I began researching and learning about it. I didn't know what it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Afan Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Asynchronous JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-asynchronous-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-asynchronous-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T15:16:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asynchronous programming is a critical skill in modern JavaScript development, enabling developers to create more efficient and responsive applications. Whether you're a seasoned developer looking to brush up on your skills or a beginner eager to lea...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy a Web App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-a-web-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-a-web-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T13:54:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying a web application can seem daunting, but with the right tools and guidance, it becomes a manageable task. We are excited to share a comprehensive course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will explain this process. This course wil...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Secure Authentication: From Passwords to Passkeys]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/more-secure-authentication-from-passwords-to-passkeys/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/more-secure-authentication-from-passwords-to-passkeys/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T13:38:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving world of cybersecurity, authentication remains a cornerstone. Traditional methods, like passwords and social logins, are increasingly vulnerable to attacks. Enter passkeys—a revolutionary approach promising enhanced security and user convenience.  This guide will explore the current state of authentication, delve into what passkeys are, how they work,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Cruz Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Upgrade from Node 16 and Jest 26 While Staying on React Scripts 4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-upgrade-node-and-jest-while-on-react-scripts-v4/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-upgrade-node-and-jest-while-on-react-scripts-v4/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T19:35:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I was trying to upgrade some of my open source projects [https://github.com/classtranscribe/FrontEnd/]. They were made using  create-react-app [https://github.com/facebook/create-react-app] around 2019, and I wanted to upgrade to a newer version of NodeJS and Jest. This would let me take advantage of the security updates, bug fixes, speed improvements, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harsh Deep</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does a CPU Work Internally? From Transistors to Instruction Set Architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-does-cpu-work-internally/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-does-cpu-work-internally/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T19:14:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CPU (Central Process Unit) is the brain of a computer, and the main connection between software and hardware. It makes it possible to operate software on hardware. However, how does it work in deep detail? And how can it connect programs to certain computer hardware? This article aims to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Python Generators – Explained With Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-python-generators/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-python-generators/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T19:05:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python generators are a powerful feature that allow lazy iteration through a sequence of values. They produce items one at a time and only when needed, which makes them the best choice for working with large datasets or streams of data where it would be inefficient and impractical to load]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rochdi Khalid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Send HTTP Requests Using JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-send-http-requests-using-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-send-http-requests-using-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T17:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nowadays, the interaction between web applications relies on HTTP [/news/what-is-http/]. For instance, let's say you have an online shop application and you want to create a new product. You have to fill in all the necessary information and probably click on a button that says "Create". This action will send]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Hu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Stack Development with Next.js, Clerk, and Neon Postgres]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nextjs-clerk-neon-fullstack-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nextjs-clerk-neon-fullstack-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T15:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Full stack development is constantly evolving, with new developer tools and products being introduced that allow us to build secure and reliable applications more efficiently. In this tutorial, I’ll walk you through how to build highly performant web applications with Neon – a serverless PostgreSQL [https://neon.tech] database designed for the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankur Tyagi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Counter Button with React, TailwindCSS, and TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-counter-button-with-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-counter-button-with-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T14:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can you keep track of the number of times a user clicks a button? How are the hearts on Instagram or the likes on Facebook counted?  In this tutorial, we will build a button that tracks the number of times a button has been clicked. Along the way,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Devin Lane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Python SDK to Build Your Own Web Scraper]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-python-sdk-to-build-a-web-scraper/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-python-sdk-to-build-a-web-scraper/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T13:11:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Web scraping? Web scraping is a technique used to collect large amounts of data automatically using a programming script. This makes it useful for many professionals such as data analysts, market researchers, SEO specialists, business analysts, and academic researchers. What You'll Learn Here Python provides two libraries, Requests]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jess Wilk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Friction Is A Good Thing: Designing Sustainable E-Commerce Experiences]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/07/designing-sustainable-e-commerce-experiences/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/07/designing-sustainable-e-commerce-experiences/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, UX design contributes to the problem of excessive consumption through persuasive e-commerce practices and designing for companies with linear and exploitative business models. Anna Rátkai explores practical steps we can take to reduce material consumption and the massive environmental impact that comes along with it by designing mindful shopping experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Anna Rátkai)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve User Experience with Optimistic UI and SWR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-user-experience-with-optimistic-ui-swr/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-user-experience-with-optimistic-ui-swr/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T22:33:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever noticed how some apps feel like they can read your mind? You click a button, and before you can even blink, it's done – no loading screens, no waiting around. It's like magic, right? Well, let me tell you a little secret: that's the power of Optimistic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prepare to pass the AWS SysOps Administrator Associate (SOA-C02) Certification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-to-pass-the-aws-sysops-administrator-associate-soa-c02-certification/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-to-pass-the-aws-sysops-administrator-associate-soa-c02-certification/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T17:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you trying to earn the AWS SysOps Administrator Associate certification? We just released a MASSIVE course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is is designed to help you pass the certification exam and showcase your expertise in AWS tech...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn TypeScript with Interactive Lessons]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-typescript-with-interactive-lessons/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-typescript-with-interactive-lessons/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T16:26:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript can make your life easier as a programmer and make your code less error-prone. We just posted a TypeScript course for beginners on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Bob Ziroll from Scrimba teaches this course. Interactive code is avail...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Pandoc – An Open Source Tool for Technical Writers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-pandoc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-pandoc/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T15:33:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technical writers frequently navigate the complexities of various document formats and revisions. Pandoc [https://pandoc.org/], a free and open-source tool, offers a powerful solution to streamline these processes. In this tutorial, I'll explain the Pandoc's functionalities, specifically focusing on two key areas that can significantly enhance the workflow for technical writers:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikram Aruchamy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“If” CSS Gets Inline Conditionals]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=379002</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/if-css-gets-inline-conditionals/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T15:18:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few sirens went off a couple of weeks ago when the CSS Working Group (CSSWG) resolved to add an if() conditional to the CSS Values Module Level 5 specification. It was Lea Verou’s X post that same day that …
“If” CSS Gets Inline Conditionals originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does Knowledge Distillation Work in Deep Learning Models?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/knowledge-distillation-in-deep-learning-models/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/knowledge-distillation-in-deep-learning-models/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T13:35:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deep learning models have transformed several industries, including computer vision and natural language processing. However, the rising complexity and resource requirements of these models have motivated academics to look into ways to condense their knowledge into more compact and efficient forms. Knowledge distillation, a strategy for transferring knowledge from a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oyedele Tioluwani Taiwo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perform Load Testing in Spring Boot with Gatling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-integrate-spring-boot-with-gatling/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-integrate-spring-boot-with-gatling/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T19:46:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To evaluate the performance of a system, you need a tool that can simulate its behavior in production.  For this purpose, you can use a software tool based on Scala [https://www.scala-lang.org/] called Gatling [https://gatling.io/]. This article will teach you how to integrate it into a Spring Boot [https://spring.io/projects/spring-boot] application]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mario Casari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Vue E-commerce App Using MSW]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-vue-ecommerce-app-using-msw/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-vue-ecommerce-app-using-msw/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T18:49:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building an e-commerce app can be a time-consuming task, but with the right tools, it becomes much more manageable. In this guide, we'll explore how to create a robust Vue.js e-commerce application using Mock Service Worker (MSW) to simulate backend interactions.  Whether you're a seasoned developer or just starting]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhijeet Dave</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Markov Chains? Explained With Python Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-markov-chain/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-markov-chain/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T12:53:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are various mathematical tools that can be used to predict the near future based on a current state. One of the most widely used are Markov chains. Markov chains allow you to predict the uncertainty of future events under certain conditions. For this reason, it is widely used in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[​​How to Upload Large Files Efficiently with AWS S3 Multipart Upload]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/upload-large-files-with-aws/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/upload-large-files-with-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T12:02:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine running a media streaming platform where users upload large high-definition videos. Uploading such large files can be slow and may fail if the network is unreliable.  Using traditional single-part uploads can be cumbersome and inefficient for large files, often leading to timeout errors or the need to restart]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Destiny Erhabor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Customer Journey Maps (+ Figma & Miro Templates)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/07/customer-journey-maps-figma-miro-templates/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/07/customer-journey-maps-figma-miro-templates/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visualize the user experience with user journey maps. Here are some helpful templates, real-world applications, and insights on the importance of mapping both successful and unsuccessful touchpoints. Part of [Smart Interface Design Patterns](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com) by yours truly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Scott Hanselman learned from 900 podcast interviews with devs [Podcast #131]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-scott-hanselman-learned-from-900-podcast-interviews-with-devs-podcast-131/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-scott-hanselman-learned-from-900-podcast-interviews-with-devs-podcast-131/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T14:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Scott Hanselman. Scott's a developer at Microsoft, a prolific teacher, and has hosted the Hanselminutes podcast for nearly two decades. We talk about: How he leads a fully-remote team from his home ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Callback Functions in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-callback-functions-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-callback-functions-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T21:24:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building dynamic applications with JavaScript that display real-time data – like a weather app or live sports dashboard – you'll need a way to automatically fetch new data from an external source without disrupting the user experience.  You can do this using JavaScript's callback functions, which showcase]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwadamisi Samuel Praise</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Meditation App with React Native & Expo Router]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-meditation-app-with-react-native-expo-router/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-meditation-app-with-react-native-expo-router/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T16:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking to enhance your React Native skills while creating a practical and soothing application? This new course from freeCodeCamp.org is perfect for you! You'll learn how to build a meditation app using Expo, an open-source platform for maki...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Flow in Redux Explained – A State Management Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-data-flows-in-redux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-data-flows-in-redux/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T13:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In complex React applications, managing application state effectively can become a challenge. This is where Redux, a predictable state management library, steps in. By introducing a unidirectional data flow, Redux brings order and clarity to how data updates and interacts within your React components. This article discusses the inner workings]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React 19 Actions – How to Simplify Form Submission and Loading States]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-19-actions-simpliy-form-submission-and-loading-states/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-19-actions-simpliy-form-submission-and-loading-states/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T21:29:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React 19 introduces Actions, which are asynchronous functions. Actions are helpful in making form submissions easier. This tutorial dives into what Actions are and how to use them. You'll learn about:  1. The new React 19 feature, Actions  2. The new React 19 hooks, useActionState and useFormStatus]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shruti Kapoor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work with Tables in Excel vs Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/excel-vs-google-sheets-tables/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/excel-vs-google-sheets-tables/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T17:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Sheets recently released an all new feature: tables. Well, new is a bit of an overstatement. Excel has had proper tables for many, many years, and it's been a point of contention in the spreadsheet community. In this article, I'll break down what exactly tables are, why they're important,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve Your JavaScript Code with Powerful Build Tool Configs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-your-javascript-projects-with-build-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-your-javascript-projects-with-build-tools/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T15:56:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have been a frontend developer for over 6 years now, mostly working with Javascript, TypeScript, and React. When stepping into the world of the front end, the number of libraries and build tools available can be overwhelming – especially since each has its own configuration options. At first these]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keyur Paralkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go for Absolute Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/go-for-absolute-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/go-for-absolute-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T16:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking to dive into a new programming language that is both powerful and efficient? Go, also known as Golang, is a modern language that has quickly become a favorite among developers for its simplicity and performance. Whether you're a seaso...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use JAWS on Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/howto-use-jaws-on-windows/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/howto-use-jaws-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T16:07:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JAWS (Job Access With Speech) is a screen reader for the Windows operating system. JAWS assists individuals with visual impairments in interacting with computers by helping them navigate applications, read documents, and browse the web. According to WebAIM [https://webaim.org/projects/screenreadersurvey9/#primary], JAWS is the most popular screen reader on the market as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilknur Eren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Infinite Scrolling in React Using the Intersection Observer API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/infinite-scrolling-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/infinite-scrolling-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T09:24:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi fellow developers! Have you ever wondered how social media apps like Facebook and Instagram keep you scrolling endlessly through your feed?  This user experience, designed to load new content on demand, uses a technique called infinite scrolling. This helps keep you hooked to these apps for hours. Traditionally,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tales Of An Eternal Summer (July 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-july-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-july-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s welcome the new month with some fresh desktop wallpapers! Created by artists and designers from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for July 2024. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Media Queries vs Container Queries – Which Should You Use and When?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/media-queries-vs-container-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/media-queries-vs-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T20:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the web evolves, new tools and ideas are released with the goal of making our lives as web developers easier. This means we have to choose whether to stick with the old ways or discard them entirely for the shiny new stuff. But does this always demand an either-or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ophy Boamah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript GameDev with Kaboom.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-gamedev-with-kaboomjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-gamedev-with-kaboomjs/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T16:29:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a game can be one of the most rewarding experiences in programming, and building a Metroidvania-style game takes that excitement to another level. These games are known for their intricate maps, challenging enemies, and complex mechanics tha...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering Shadcn UI Components]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-shadcn-ui-components/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-shadcn-ui-components/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T16:25:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you master Shadcn. This comprehensive course dives deep into the versatile world of Shadcn, a powerful toolset for building modern web applications with customizable an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change Background Color with JavaScript – BG Color in JS and HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-change-background-color-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-change-background-color-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T16:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can style elements with JavaScript using the element's style property. In this article, you'll learn how to change background color using JavaScript. Here's what the mini project you'll build looks like: In the image above, each button changes t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Fashion to Software Engineer with Alison Yoon [Podcast #130]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-fashion-to-software-engineer-with-alison-yoon-podcast-130/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-fashion-to-software-engineer-with-alison-yoon-podcast-130/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T15:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews Alison Yoon. She's a Software Engineer who started off in fashion design and taught herself to code using freeCodeCamp. We talk about: What it's like to work in fas...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transitioning to Auto Height]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=378862</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/transitioning-to-auto-height/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T13:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know this is something Chris has wanted forever, so it’s no surprise he’s already got a fantastic write-up just a day after the news broke. In fact, I first learned about it from his post and was unable …
Transitioning to Auto Height originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Improve Your Microcopy: UX Writing Tips For Non-UX Writers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/how-improve-microcopy-ux-writing-tips-non-ux-writers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/how-improve-microcopy-ux-writing-tips-non-ux-writers/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interface copy plays a crucial role in the overall user experience, helping guide users smoothly, allowing them to navigate easily through the app, discover and start using product features, and more. In this article, you’ll find simple, practical tips and a checklist to help you create a clear and concise microcopy, ensuring a seamless user experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Irina Silyanova)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Migrate from Play Core Library]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/migrate-from-play-core-library/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/migrate-from-play-core-library/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T17:53:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have recently received an email from Google Play Store stating the following: > Update your Play Core Maven dependency to an Android 14 compatible version! Your current Play Core library is incompatible with targetSdkVersion 34 (Android 14), which introduces a backwards-incompatible change to broadcast receivers to improve user]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Ben Rachel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poppin’ In]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=378637</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/poppin-in/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T16:37:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, hey there! It’s been a hot minute, hasn’t it? Thought I’d pop in and say hello while we get to know the Popover API a bit.
Poppin’ In originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a RAG Chatbot with Agent Cloud and Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-rag-chatbot-agent-cloud-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-rag-chatbot-agent-cloud-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T14:43:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's companies are data factories. Every interaction, transaction, and internal process generates a constant stream of information. This data holds immense value, promising to improve decision-making, streamline operations, and unlock deep customer insights.  But data often remains siloed and inaccessible. It may be spread across different departments and systems,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankur Tyagi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Make A Strong Case For Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/how-make-strong-case-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/how-make-strong-case-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaining buy-in for accessibility can be challenging due to common myths and misunderstandings. For many, accessibility remains a big mystery. Here are some practical techniques for winning stakeholder support. Part of [Smart Interface Design Patterns](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com) by yours truly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Database Migrations in Go Using Docker and Postgres]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-database-migrations-in-go/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-database-migrations-in-go/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T11:40:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Go is a fast programming language with a relatively simple syntax. While learning Go, it is important to learn how to build APIs and how to use them to communicate with databases. In the process of learning, I decided to take on a project that helped me in that regard:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okure U. Edet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PySpark for Beginners – How to  Process Data with Apache Spark & Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pyspark-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pyspark-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T08:25:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re diving into the world of big data, you’ve probably come across the term PySpark. PySpark is a tool that makes managing and analyzing large datasets easier. In this article, we will see the basics of PySpark, its benefits, and how you can get started with it. What is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scope, Closures, and Hoisting in JavaScript – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/scope-closures-and-hoisting-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/scope-closures-and-hoisting-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T08:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the dynamic world of JavaScript, understanding the intricacies of scope, closures, and hoisting is fundamental for mastering the language and building robust applications. These concepts, though often misunderstood, play a crucial role in determining how variables and functions behave within the code. Scope dictates the accessibility of variables, closures]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidera Humphrey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's New in React 19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/whats-new-in-react-19/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/whats-new-in-react-19/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T15:54:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React 19 has just been released, bringing a wealth of new features and enhancements to this popular JavaScript library. For developers looking to stay ahead of the curve, understanding these updates is crucial. This course is designed to help you nav...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a ML Model with Azure Machine Learning Designer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-an-ml-model-with-azure-machine-learning-designer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-an-ml-model-with-azure-machine-learning-designer/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T14:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that you can create machine learning models without writing any code? If you’re here, you’re probably curious about how to achieve this. In this article, I will guide you through building a regression model that predicts automobile prices using Azure Machine Learning’s Low-Code/No-Code tools.  Regression is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eniola Ajala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Validate Forms in React and React Native Using Yup and Formik]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-how-to-validate-user-input/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-how-to-validate-user-input/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T19:51:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Validation is a key part of development, regardless of what programming language you’re writing. Developers should always be validating user input, API parameters, and retrieved values. One of the most common elements where you’ll need to apply user input validation is via a form. This could be a user sign]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Riordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=378960</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/378960-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T18:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Meditation #8: .work + .life { border: 10px solid #000; }…
 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=378958</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/378958-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T18:27:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Meditation #7: Nobody is perf-ect.…
 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=378956</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/378956-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T18:27:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Meditation #6: The color space is always calc(rgb(0 255 0)+er) on the other side of the fence.…
 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=378954</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/378954-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T18:26:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Meditation #5: :where(:is(.my-mind))…
 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=378952</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/378952-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T18:26:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Meditation #4: Select, style, adjust. Select, style, adjust. Select, sty……
 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=378950</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/378950-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T18:25:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Meditation #3: A pseudo is as a pseudo does.…
 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=378948</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/378948-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T18:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Meditation #2: Who gives a flying frick what constitutes a “programming” language.…
 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=378946</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/378946-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T18:22:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Meditation #1: If the code works as expected and it fits your mental model, then it’s perfect.…
 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Breakpoints for Responsive Web Design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/breakpoints-for-responsive-web-design/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/breakpoints-for-responsive-web-design/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T18:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Breakpoints are fundamental to the concept of responsive web design. They enable websites to adapt seamlessly across different devices and screen sizes.  Breakpoints mark the points at which a website's layout and content should change to ensure optimal user experience on devices ranging from smartphones and tablets to desktop]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So Your Website Or App Is Live… Now What?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/website-improvement-after-launch/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/website-improvement-after-launch/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The biggest mistake you can make in UX design is to launch a website or app and then walk away. Monitoring and improving after launch will benefit users and your metrics. Nothing will bring bigger gains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When to Use NPM Packages – A Guide for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/when-to-use-npm-packages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/when-to-use-npm-packages/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T15:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know when you hit a roadblock while coding and think, "Hey, someone has probably done this before"? That's where npm (Node Package Manager) comes in handy. This huge collection of ready-made code modules created by other developers allows you to plug them into your projects and take advantage of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering VIM: Your Guide to Efficient Text Editing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-vim-your-guide-to-efficient-text-editing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-vim-your-guide-to-efficient-text-editing/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T15:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VIM is a highly configurable text editor that enables efficient text editing, and it's favored by many developers and system administrators for its powerful capabilities and extensive customization options. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are the SOLID Principles in Java? Explained With Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-solid-principles/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-solid-principles/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T15:45:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll learn about the SOLID principles. You'll gain an understanding of each principle along with Java code examples. SOLID principles are a set of five design principles used in object-oriented programming. Adhering to these principles will help you develop robust software. They will make your code more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anjan Baradwaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Controlled and Uncontrolled Components in React.js?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-controlled-and-uncontrolled-components-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-controlled-and-uncontrolled-components-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T20:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In React.js, managing form inputs and user interactions is a crucial part of building dynamic web applications.  Two key concepts that developers need to understand are controlled and uncontrolled components. These concepts define how form data is handled within a React component.  Controlled components rely on React state]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MDX Or: How I Learned To Stop Worrying And Love Multimedia Writing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/mdx-or-how-i-learned-love-multimedia-writing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/mdx-or-how-i-learned-love-multimedia-writing/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Balancing the age-old simplicity of words on paper with the myriad creative possibilities of the web is a tension as old as the web itself. Leaning into that overlap can bring new dimensions not just to the things we write but also to how we write them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why are senior developers learning low-code and AI tools? [Adrian Twarog Interview #129]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-are-senior-developers-learning-low-code-and-ai-tools-adrian-twarog-interview-129/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-are-senior-developers-learning-low-code-and-ai-tools-adrian-twarog-interview-129/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T15:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Adrian Twarog. He's a Software Engineer who started his career by working as the office IT guy for 10 years. He's since published YouTube courses that millions of people have watched. We talk about: ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Generative AI Handbook – How GenAI is Impacting Business and Innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/generative-ai-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/generative-ai-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T17:43:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The emergence of Generative Artificial Intelligence (GenAI) is both shaping the future of innovation management and revolutionizing it. This handbook delves into the groundbreaking research presented in "Generative Artificial Intelligence in Innovation Management: A Preview of Future Research Developments" by Marcello Mariani and Yogesh K. Dwivedi (2024) [https://ideas.repec.org/a/eee/jbrese/v175y2024ics0148296324000468.html]. It's a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Technical Writer – A Guide for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-technical-writer-guide-for-devs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-technical-writer-guide-for-devs/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:54:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being a top-notch developer was my dream – until I realized I could combine my passion for writing with my technical knowledge to earn a living. That's right: I'm talking about becoming a technical writer. And if you're a developer, you may be in a good position to get into]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tooba Jamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn to Create a 3D RPG Game with Godot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-create-a-3d-rpg-game-with-godot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-create-a-3d-rpg-game-with-godot/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:20:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Godot is an open-source game engine that is perfect for creating both 2D and 3D games. It is known for its user-friendly interface, robust features, and active community support. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Accessibility in Web Development? Best Practices for Web Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-practices-for-accessibility-in-web-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-practices-for-accessibility-in-web-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T11:33:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone should be able to use technology, regardless of their abilities or disabilities. An accessible website or platform attracts a broader audience and has a high chance of achieving user retention. This article will discuss the importance of accessibility, best practices for accessibility in frontend web development, and their implementations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria (Burah) Poromon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniting Web And Native Apps With 4 Unknown JavaScript APIs]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/uniting-web-native-apps-unknown-javascript-apis/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/uniting-web-native-apps-unknown-javascript-apis/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you heard of the Screen Orientation API? What about the Device Orientation API, Vibration API, or the Contact Picker API? Juan Diego Rodriguez is interested in these under-the-radar web features and discusses how they can be used to create more usable and robust progressive web apps if and when they gain broader support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Time To Live in Event-Driven Architecture in AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-time-to-live-in-event-driven-architecture/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-time-to-live-in-event-driven-architecture/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T18:08:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Distributed systems generally involve the storage and exchange of huge amounts of data. Not all data is created the same, and some of it can even expire – by design.  As the Buddha said, "All conditioned things are impermanent." In this article, we'll look at how the concept of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anant Chowdhary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does Python's For-Else Loop Construct Work?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/for-else-loop-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/for-else-loop-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T13:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python supports the for-else loop construct that is lesser known but super helpful. If you’ve programmed in Python, you may have used the for loop to iterate over items in iterables such as lists. But for some use cases, using the for loop in conjunction with the else clause can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bala Priya C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[T-Shaped vs. V-Shaped Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/t-shaped-vs-v-shaped-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/t-shaped-vs-v-shaped-designers/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Job openings typically cast a very restrictive frame for candidates, with long lists of expectations and requirements. But what if this narrow focus can overlook the value of “V”-shaped designers who excel by crossing boundaries, connecting dots, and innovating beyond rigid boxes?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Arrays in Practice: How to Rebuild the Football Team Cards Project with PHP and MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/php-arrays-how-to-rebuild-the-football-team-cards-with-php-and-mongodb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/php-arrays-how-to-rebuild-the-football-team-cards-with-php-and-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T20:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the second part of my PHP array handbook. You can find the first part here [/news/php-array-handbook/], where I cover array basics. In the first part, you learned about arrays, how to create arrays, array functions, and how to loop through arrays. This second part will teach you how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Decorators in Python? Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/decorators-in-python-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/decorators-in-python-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T18:53:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn about Python decorators: what they are, how they work, and when to use them.  But before diving into decorators, it's helpful to understand two foundational concepts in Python: first-class functions and closures. First-Class Functions in Python First-class functions mean that functions in Python]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samyak Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Non-Technical Introduction to Generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-non-technical-introduction-to-generative-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-non-technical-introduction-to-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T15:39:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to learn about the concepts around generative AI without getting bogged down with the technical details, we have a great course for you. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is a non-technical intro to g...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Intelligent Apps with Mistral AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/building-intelligent-apps-with-mistral-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/building-intelligent-apps-with-mistral-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T15:11:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open source LLMs can help you create intelligent apps without having to pay for each API call. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use the open source models from Mistral AI to create intellig...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Trunk Based Development? A Different Approach to the Software Development Lifecycle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-trunk-based-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-trunk-based-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T12:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC) is different at every company. The version control system used, peer review process, code review process, design review process, how you do CI, automated testing, and manual testing – all vary greatly depending on where you work. How a company plans, writes, builds, reviews, deploys,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kealan Parr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Masonry Layout Using HTML and CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-mansory-layout-using-html-and-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-mansory-layout-using-html-and-css/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T12:22:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A masonry layout is a grid-based design where items are arranged in a way that minimizes vertical gaps between them.  an example of a masonry layoutUnlike traditional grids with fixed row heights, masonry layouts adjust the positioning of items dynamically based on their content height, creating a visually appealing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fanny Nyayic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve Your Digital Security and Privacy – Best Practices for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-your-digital-security-and-privacy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-your-digital-security-and-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T12:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, there are many different types of attacks that can jeopardize your digital security and privacy. So it’s a good idea to stay up-to-date with best practices to keep you safe online.  But it can be hard to understand exactly how to do this. So I built this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Privacy Tipster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Host Static Sites on Azure Static Web Apps for Free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-host-static-sites-on-azure-static-web-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-host-static-sites-on-azure-static-web-apps/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T10:59:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will show you how you can host your React/Next.js app or any static web app on Azure Static Web Apps.  I will be showing you both ways of doing it – through the GUI and with the CLI. I assume you already have built a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shrijal Acharya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide to Object-Oriented Programming Principles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-guide-to-object-oriented-programming-principles/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-guide-to-object-oriented-programming-principles/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T09:13:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A programming language is generally classified based on its support for one or more paradigms. Object-oriented programming is one such paradigm, where the code is organized as objects. It is used to develop desktop and mobile applications or more complex web or enterprise applications. Using object-oriented programming, you can build]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anjan Baradwaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enhance Embedded Links in React with Microlink]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-enhance-embedded-links-in-react-with-microlinks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-enhance-embedded-links-in-react-with-microlinks/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T02:56:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The web has evolved from rigid color coding and 2D rendering to an era of complex, aesthetically pleasing animations and 3D rendering options. Additionally, there have been integrations with new technologies, such as virtual reality tools and frameworks, to make the user experience worthwhile. In this article, we'll optimize]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oluwatobi Joshua</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Auto Scaling and Load Balancing Work in Software Architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/auto-scaling-and-load-balancing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/auto-scaling-and-load-balancing/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T18:52:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While auto scaling and load balancing are two separate techniques in software architecture management, they are often implemented simultaneously. In the software architecture wild, one rarely exists without the other, as they complement each other to handle unpredictable changes in demand. This article will explain how auto scaling and load]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write QA Documentation That Will Actually Work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-qa-documentation-that-will-actually-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-qa-documentation-that-will-actually-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T18:29:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine developing a complex software product without taking any action to protect against errors. Human error and unexpected code combinations can cause a wide range of defects. This is where quality assurance (QA) documentation comes in.  Usually, a QA tester creates a report after discovering a bug. The next]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oleg Romanyuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Handle KeyErrors in Python – with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-keyerror-exceptions-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-keyerror-exceptions-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T18:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with dictionaries in Python, you’d often run into KeyError  exceptions. Dictionaries are built-in data structures of key value pairs. So you can look up a value—in constant time—using the corresponding key like so: dict[key] returns  value. But what if the key doesn't exist in the dictionary?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bala Priya C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Email Newsletters For Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/useful-email-newsletters-for-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/06/useful-email-newsletters-for-designers/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you want to take your user research skills to the next level, get better at UX writing, or stay up-to-date on the latest design trends, a newsletter is the perfect opportunity to get the best of the best resources delivered straight to your inbox on a regular basis. In this post, we highlight some design newsletters that you might want to consider subscribing to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Black-Scholes Equation Works – Explained with Python Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-the-black-scholes-equation-works-python-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-the-black-scholes-equation-works-python-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T16:42:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[$$\frac{\partial V}{\partial t} + \frac{1}{2}\sigma^2 S^2 \frac{\partial^2 V}{\partial S^2} = rV - r S \frac{\partial V}{\partial S}$$  Black-Scholes Equation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Frameworks vs Laravel – Which Should You Choose for Web Development?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-frameworks-vs-laravel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-frameworks-vs-laravel/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T14:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a long time, developers in the JavaScript ecosystem have tried to launch Laravel-like frameworks for JavaScript. We've seen Blitz for NextJS, Adonis for NodeJS, RedwoodJS, and more. All these frameworks tried to build a Laravel for JavaScript. But none of them were really successful. Why? We'll figure it out]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Afan Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Multi-Page Animations Using Framer Motion & React-Router-Dom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-multi-page-animations-using-framer-motion-and-react-router-dom/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-multi-page-animations-using-framer-motion-and-react-router-dom/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T05:57:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animations are what make plain websites turn into exciting and unforgettable experiences. They give your website a bit of personality and uniqueness and leave the visitor admiring the overall aesthetic. It's a no-brainer that humans love beautiful things. We all love products that look easy on the eyes.  In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okosa Leonard Onyekachukwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Attention Mechanisms in Deep Learning?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-attention-mechanisms-in-deep-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-attention-mechanisms-in-deep-learning/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T05:46:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attention mechanism is a fundamental invention in artificial intelligence and machine learning, redefining the capabilities of deep learning models. This mechanism, inspired by the human mental process of selective focus, has emerged as a pillar in a variety of applications, accelerating developments in natural language processing, computer vision, and beyond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oyedele Tioluwani Taiwo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>